<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Angie,Gnarly,Jacob Kurtz,Tracy Lawless,Mallory,Ricky Lawless</Characters>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-109826</GTIN>
  <Locations>Baghdad,Iraq,The Undertow Bar,Center City</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:32:37 [Issue ID 4000-109826] urn:comicvine:4000-109826
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-21 05:14:53. [Issue ID 109826]</Notes>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Criminal</Series>
  <Summary>A New Storyline! A New Anti-Hero! And a Perfect Place for New Readers to Jump On!

That’s right, if you’ve been missing out on Criminal up until now, this is your chance to see why the critics have hailed it as Brubaker and Phillips best work! Pick up the first trade collection, for the story of Leo, and then join us in issue #6 for a new beginning as we meet Tracy Lawless, the last surviving son of a once-famous family of crooks (who have been lurking in the background of Criminal since the first issue).

Twenty years ago, Tracy Lawless traded the crime-ridden streets of the city for a life in the military, and it’s a decision he’s rarely regretted. But now he’s walking out of the deserts of Afghanistan and Iraq and back into the world he grew up in, to find out who killed his brother Rick, and why. But truth is one of the few things uglier than family history, and the only thing Tracy has in his favor as he unravels the twisted strands of the criminal life his brother led, is that no one knows who the hell he is. And what they don’t know, just might kill them. Don’t miss the hard-hitting debut of the next Criminal lead character, in “Lawless” Part 1! And remember, every issue of Criminal is crammed cover to cover with content, including text pieces, back-up stories and noir articles by Brubaker and many other crime writers!</Summary>
  <Tags>Angie,Gnarly,Jacob Kurtz,Ricky Lawless,Tracy Lawless,Mallory,United States Army</Tags>
  <Teams>United States Army</Teams>
  <Title>Lawless, Part One</Title>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/criminal-6-lawless-part-one/4000-109826/</Web>
  <Year>2007</Year>
  <Count>10</Count>
</ComicInfo>