<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Ed,Dr. Beane</Characters>
  <Colorist>Glynis Oliver Wein,Glynis Oliver,Glynis Oliver</Colorist>
  <Count>62</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Editor>Carl Potts,Jim Shooter,Rosemary McCormick-Lowy</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comixology:446956</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Bob McLeod,Bob McLeod</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Joe Rosen,Joe Rosen</Letterer>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:08:22 urn:comixology:446956 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/41218
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 13:13:16. [Issue ID 41218]</Notes>
  <Number>20</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Bob McLeod,Bob McLeod</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Power Pack</Series>
  <Summary>On Christmas Eve, the Power kids' mother, Margaret, is still hospitalized for the injuries she sustained during Secret Wars II (issue #18). Doctors tell the family that an infection has set in and the prognosis is not good. They also mention that if her fever breaks by morning, she might have a chance to survive.

As the kids leave the hospital, they apprehend demons who are trying to steal babies from the maternity ward. They overhear the demons say that they are planning to take the entire island of Manhattan to Limbo. Katie also investigates a pouch left behind by the demons and discovers Kitty Pryde's library card. The team decides to call Xavier's School to make sure that Kitty is okay and to report what they've heard; Shadowcat is away, but they reach Mirage. Upon hearing the demons' plans, Mirage, Cannonball and Wolfsbane head to Manhattan.

 

Katie is kidnapped by the demons, who intend to use her as both an energy source and a human sacrifice to move Manhattan to Limbo. While the rest of the team, along with Cannonball and Wolfsbane, fight the demons, Mirage fights an Angel of Death who has come to claim Margaret Power's soul.

 

Both Katie and Margaret are saved, the demons are vanquished and Manhattan stays firmly in place. The doctors tell James Power, who has been sitting with his wife, that the crisis has passed and Margaret will survive.

Guest stars: New Mutants (Mirage, Cannonball, Wolfsbane)</Summary>
  <Tags>Ed,Dr. Beane</Tags>
  <Title>Turning Point</Title>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/power-pack-20-turning-point/4000-26604/</Web>
  <Writer>Louise Jones Simonson,Louise Simonson,Louise Simonson</Writer>
  <Year>1986</Year>
  <Teams>Limbo Demons,New Mutants,Power Pack</Teams>
  <Locations>New York City,Xavier Institute</Locations>
  <CoverArtist>Mike Mignola,Terry Austin</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>