<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Tanner,Tim (Tanner's Dad),Grandpa,Superhero G [George],Ellen,Cassie (Tanner's Mom),Wren;,Harvey</Characters>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-194208</GTIN>
  <Locations>Imagined Nation</Locations>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:56:11 [Issue ID 4000-194208] urn:comicvine:4000-194208
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 03:01:45. [Issue ID 381780]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>The Imaginaries</Series>
  <Summary>A child's faith is a powerful thing. It fuels the fires of his imagination, and that imagination can take on a life of its own. But what happens to the imaginary friends, the childhood superheroes, the playmates and stuffed animals when the children who gave them life no longer believe in them? They go to the Imagined Nation. Join Superhero G as he explores this strange new world populated by imaginary figments of billions of children around the world. Follow him as he meets strange and wonderful characters, the kind only a child could believe in, discovers a new purpose for his existence unbound by the imagination of his creator and feels free to become more than he could ever imagine. Tanner finds a new imaginary friend in his dad's old closet. As their relationship grows, Tanner's parents' relationship ends, and when that happens, Tanner believes it's time to grow up and stop believing in childish things. This includes his imaginary friend, Superhero G. But having been brought to life through Tanner's love and faith, Superhero G lives on in the Imagined Nation. The adventure begins here!</Summary>
  <Title>Lost and Found, Part 1 (of 4)</Title>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-imaginaries-1-lost-and-found-part-1-of-4/4000-194208/</Web>
  <Writer>Ben Avery</Writer>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Penciller>Gregory Titus,Mike Miller</Penciller>
  <CoverArtist>Gregory Titus,Mike Miller</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Superhero,Children</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>