<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Artie,Benjamin Franklin,Bobby Tisdell,Casey,Corrado Coloruno,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Horatio,Mephisto,Michael Hawthorne,Vetis</Characters>
	<Colorist>Val Staples</Colorist>
	<Count>45</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Jordan D. White</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-413656</GTIN>
	<Inker>Jason Gorder,John Lucas,Mike Hawthorne</Inker>
	<Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
	<Locations>Baxter Building,New York City</Locations>
	<Month>8</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:05:04 [Issue ID 4000-413656] urn:comicvine:4000-413656</Notes>
	<Number>12</Number>
	<PageCount>22</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2095167" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1435844" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1380896" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="2127994" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1878990" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1488809" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1488171" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1589098" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1546242" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1809106" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="2008083" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1903866" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1954576" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="4010257" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1976632" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="2042788" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1781829" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1838472" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="3087303" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1286395" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1619225" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="805240" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Mike Hawthorne</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Deadpool</Series>
	<Summary>Concluding the 2nd arc of MARVEL NOW! Deadpool!

Can Wade trust hell to keep their side of his contract?

Will all of Deadpool's new friends end up dead because of him?

Are turkey sandwiches better than ham?

2 of these 3 questions will be answered!

SynopsisThe battle between Deadpool and Vetis begins very poorly. Deadpool is hurled through the air and lands on a car. Instead of countering any attack, Deadpool saves a mom and her son by tossing them into a shoe store. Vetis arrives in the form of Hulk and smashes Deadpool. (Vetis now has all the powers of the people whose souls he has consumed.)

Elsewhere, two bums camp out in the ice cream truck. A being rises from one of the freezers and the bums flee the truck. The truck drives away.

Vetis continues his brutal beating of Deadpool. Deadpool lands at the foot of the Baxter Building and places a charge on the wall. Robots climb out to attack Vetis while Deadpool tries to get Dr. Strange on the phone to come help him out.

Vetis easily defeats the Baxter Building security robots and turns into Cyclops, blasting Deadpool into a neighboring street. Deadpool gives up the fight and just starts shooting Vetis until Vetis hurls a manhole cover at Deadpool. Agent Preston uses her influence on Deadpool's brain to get him to move, saving both their lives. Deadpool looks to the side and sees a dumb kid recording the fight on his mobile phone. Deadpool clears the kid out of the way and then gets wrapped by Vetis. Just before Vetis can throw Deadpool to Hell, however, Vetis gets tied up by a necromancer. Everyone assumes it is Dr. Strange; it is Michael, brought back to life.

Vetis tosses Deadpool to the side and approaches Michael, confident that he will be able to kill the necromancer and suck down his soul. Michael explains, however, that he has already died and come back. Vetis realizes that Michael must have made a deal with Mephisto, who conveniently appears. In pure insolence, Vetis chops off Mephisto's head and tries to attack Michael. Michael has mystic powers and slits Vetis open from crotch to neck. Deadpool pulls out Vetis's heart. The entrapped souls escape Vetis and Deadpool hands the heart to Mephisto, who has reattached his head. Mephisto eats the heart.

Deadpool and Michael's reunion is brief, as Mephisto senses Agent Preston's presence in Deadpool's head. He puts everyone in Deadpool's head and tells Preston that he knows how to get her out. The group decides that they won't ask for the devil's help. He leaves. 

Feeling brazen, Deadpool kicks down one of the barricades in his brain and the group proceeds into a room that should house his darkest secrets. They find the room empty. Deadpool begins to realize that his memories have been hijacked. In fact, the attack/abduction from a week earlier begins to make more sense. Michael storms off to be alone (he did just spend a long amount of time in Hell, after all) and Benjamin Franklin follows him. Preston leaves Deadpool alone to deal with emotions long buried.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-10 10:21:01.  [CVDB413656]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-12-damned-if-you-win-damned-if-you-lose/4000-413656/</Summary>
	<Tags>Artie,Baxter Building,Benjamin Franklin,Bobby Tisdell,Casey,Corrado Coloruno,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Horatio,Mephisto,Michael Hawthorne,New York City,Vetis</Tags>
	<Title>Damned If You Win, Damned If You Lose</Title>
	<Volume>2012</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-12-damned-if-you-win-damned-if-you-lose/4000-413656/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Posehn,Gerry Duggan</Writer>
	<Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>