<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Invisible Sunrise</Title>
  <Series>Overtaken</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2013</Volume>
  <Summary>The sci-fi thriller OVERTAKEN takes center stage as Aspen's 10 year anniversary celebration marches on! Some questions, you may not want to know the answers to. Journalist Will Harden is well equipped for most situations, but nothing can prepare him for what's about to come. Relocating from the big city to a small mountain town with his wife, everything is turned upside-down the moment she goes missing. Are the rumors of alien abductions true or did something far worse happen to his wife? No matter the cause, Harden will not stop until he uncovers the truth, or dies trying. Written and created by Frank Mastromauro, featuring artwork by the talented newcomer Marco Lorenzana, OVERTAKEN is going to take your breath away and leave you gasping for more!

Notes: This issue has 7 (A01-A02 &amp; B-F) covers and 19 Retailer Exclusive covers.

List of covers and their creators:

Direct Edition - Marco Lorenzana &amp; Peter SteigerwaldWade's Comics MadnessDirect Edition - Marco Lorenzana &amp; Peter SteigerwaldSpecial Reserved Edition - Marco Lorenzana &amp; Peter SteigerwaldOriginal Sketch EditionRetailer Exclusive Edition - Marco Lorenzana &amp; Peter Steigerwald10th Anniversary EditionDragon Con Exclusive Limited Edition of 200 - Siya OumList of Retailer Exclusive Editions and their creators:

Rupp's ComicsLone Star ComicsCapt. Chuck's ComicsCaptain ComicsGhost Ship ComicsWV Pop Con - Pencils/inks by Chris Ehnot, colors by David DelantyThe Source Comics &amp; GamesGotham Central Comics &amp; Collectibles - Pencils/inks by Vince Sunico, colors by Gen IshiharalHeroes &amp; FantasiesWarp 9 ComicsCreative ComicsStadium Comics - Daniel WongReader CopiesRockin' Rooster Comics &amp; GamesCleveland ComicsPlanet ComicsMile High Comics - Pencils/inks by Brent Peeples, colors by Pezi of UrbanMYTHCincinnati Comic Expo - Pencils/inks by Chris Ehnot, colors by David Delanty</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-14 20:25:20.  [CVDB423724]</Notes>
  <Year>2013</Year>
  <Month>08</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Frank Mastromauro</Writer>
  <Penciller>Marco Lorenzana</Penciller>
  <Colorist>David Delanty, Gen Ishiharal, Pezi, Wes Hartman</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Joshua Reed</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Brent Peeples, Chris B Ehnot, Daniel Wong, David Delanty, Gen Ishiharal, Marco Lorenzana, Peter Steigerwald, Pezi, Siya Oum, Vince Sunico</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Vince Hernandez</Editor>
  <Publisher>Aspen MLT</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/overtaken-1-invisible-sunrise/4000-423724/</Web>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Locations>Minnesota</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1418050" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1819704" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1457041" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1996565" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="3359822" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1817853" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1861217" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2191639" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2114599" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1686058" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1558624" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1549725" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1561531" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1791079" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1521654" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1451238" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1103807" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1565081" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1404178" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1479153" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1235157" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1951536" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1703113" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="4405075" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1268232" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1014123" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
