<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd,Judge Maitland</Characters>
	<Colorist>Eva de la Cruz,Matthew Soffe</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Luke Horsman</CoverArtist>
	<Day>14</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1045002</GTIN>
	<Inker>Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Laura Helsby,Luke Horsman,Simon Davis</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>2</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:26 [Issue ID 4000-1045002] urn:comicvine:4000-1045002</Notes>
	<Number>2369</Number>
	<PageCount>31</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1484539" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1468611"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1614142"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1721733"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1483677"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1427487"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1778749"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1517370"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1103779"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1059213"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1098791"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1031775"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="997307"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="896586"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1388864"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1490064"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1173585"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="2799539"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1324386"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1148421"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1149983"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1042215"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="968248"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="794458"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1523547"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1446578"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1482048"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1793627"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1552644"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="516557"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1622275"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Laura Helsby,Luke Horsman,Simon Davis</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(february 2024)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Another circuit-scorching collection of sci-fi stories for your optical entertainment, Terrans, and this prog sees the ghafflebette climax to the Enemy Earth saga as well as the brain-twisting conclusion to The English Astronaut, alongside the latest instalments of Dredd, Full Tilt Boogie and Thistlebone. 

Steel your Thrill-receptors for the return next week of The Fall of Deadworld and the start of a new Indigo Prime transdimensional adventure, courtesy of Kek-W and Lee Carter!

I’m sending this issue off to the print-bots the same week that the news broke about Duncan Jones’ Rogue Trooper movie beaming into this reality in 2025. By the time you read this, the details will have spread across the Internet like bio-wire, but just in case you missed it, here’s the skinny: principal photography on this animated feature has wrapped at Rebellion Film Studios, and it stars Aneurin Barnard as the titular G.I., with the likes of Hayley Atwell, Reece Shearsmith, Matt Berry, Diane Morgan, Jemaine Clement and Sean Bean filling out the cast.

*Judge Dredd » A better world (Part 6)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law! Now, Accounts Judge Maitland has been conducting an experiment in Sector 304 in a bid to reduce crime...

*Tharg's 3rillers Present » The English Astronaut (Part 3)*
Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story — a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre! Earth, November 1963, and Major Thomas Anderson is about to become the subject of a British Experimental Space Programme project. Locked into the Injection Seat, he’ll take a cocktail of drugs that will dislocate him from the current year and plunge him into 2024...

*Full Tilt Boogie » Full Tilt Boogie: Book two(Part 3)*
Out in the deep reaches of the cosmos, teenager Tee — together with her grandmother and cat — is a bounty hunter/hired help, operating from her spaceship the FULL TILT BOOGIE. Capable and resourceful, Tee was paid to rescue the Luxine Prince Ifan from his debtors’ prison. In the process, she encountered a resurrected Anubite warrior, a member of the enemy race with whom the Luxine Empire was at war...

*Enemy Earth » Enemy Earth: Book Three (Part 10)*
The near future. Mother Nature has turned against the people that live upon the Earth’s surface. Now, the planet’s flora and fauna have mutated and are viciously attacking humanity. As society crumbles, and survivors seek safety, young Zoe, who has lost her own family, has rescued Jules, who’s the prime minister’s son. Now, the pair have been reunited with the PM, and they’re journeying to India...

*Thistlebone » The Dule Tree (Part 6)*
Britain, 2020. It’s been over a year since journalist Seema Chaudry accompanied cult survivor Avril Easton back to the village of Harrowvale, where she suffered at the hands of THISTLEBONE worshippers, a crazed occult group that believed in an ancient woodland deity. One man in the village, Malcolm Kinniburgh, was keeping the Thistlebone legend alive — but now he’s dead, and his house is being cleared...

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-24 12:22:43.  [CVDB1045002]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2369-prog-2369/4000-1045002/</Summary>
	<Tags>Judge Dredd,Judge Maitland</Tags>
	<Title>ad</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2369-prog-2369/4000-1045002/</Web>
	<Writer>Alex de Campi,Arthur Wyatt,Cavan Scott,Paul Cornell,Rob Williams,T.C. Eglington</Writer>
	<Year>2001</Year>
</ComicInfo>