<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Luna</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Web>https://www.comixology.com/Luna-1/digital-comic/909854 https://comicvine.gamespot.com/luna-1/4000-160014/</Web>
  <Notes>Scraped metadata from Comixology [CMXDB909854]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 23:51:31. [Issue ID 906877]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Adult</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Year>2003</Year>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
  <AgeRating>Suggested for Mature Readers</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Fotis Georgeles</Writer>
  <Penciller>Fotis Pehlivanides</Penciller>
  <Inker>Fotis Pehlivanides</Inker>
  <Colorist>Fotis Pehlivanides</Colorist>
  <Editor>Michael Dowers</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>A journalist working as a police reporter goes undercover as a fashion photographer. It seems that rich elderly gentlemen are hiring supermodels at premium prices to perform sex acts privately for them. Anything goes in these clandestine meetings. Enter Luna.... the most beautiful supermodel of them all. The journalist has a session with Luna and he becomes obsessed with her natural beauty. In the end the reporter gets his story, but will he get Luna? Beautifully painted full-color artwork from Greece. 80 pages.

*Back Blurb*
Models, naked bodies and mature gentlemen willing to pay and watch. The fashion world, the glamorous pages of magazines and the shocking revelations of pop tabloids. Aris Sartas is once again on the streets. The reporter of The Journal in search of front page news. He knows love for money but confuses police reporting with fashion editorials. Fashion, media, models. Night and day. The trafficking of love. Known names of the Athenian society and beautiful girls with exotic names. Luna, Lu to her friends. She stirs the city's nightlife. She smiles on the cover of magazines. At nights she strips for art lovers. And for Sartas.</Summary>
  <Characters>Aris Sartas,Luna</Characters>
  <CoverArtist>Fotis Pehlivanides</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>