<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Smothered Hope</Title>
  <Series>Savage Henry</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Count>13</Count>
  <Volume>1987</Volume>
  <Summary>A remote Max unit (extension of Professor Ed's computer Max) breaks in on David Borden at the city Harmony disturbed that Bugtown is no longer under Professor Ed's control and the fact that Savage Henry apparently no longer exists on any reality level. The Residents burst in at the same time wondering the exact same things, but they discover that in their ignorance they accidentally improved Henry's Caroline clone so that, unknown still to her, she can now shift between realities.  Professor Ed is not happy with this improvement as apparently is has made Caroline somewhat unstable.   Meanwhile Henry's Caroline clone, Nash the Slash and their friends are stranded in Hiroshima's new interpretation of Bugtown as the only living inhabitants as Monsieur Boche has abandoned them out of fear of Hiroshima and none of them can shift -- or so Caroline thinks. The Max unit and the Residents pool their power and manage to break into Bugtown only to have Hiroshima instantly discover them and subsequently annihilate the Max unit right away -- another feat thought to be impossible. The Residents confront Hiroshima and discover the source to her new unheard of level of power to be Savage Henry himself -- a being so pure and naively innocent that she simply resurrects him and kills him over and over in order to boost her power as she feeds on his pure essence. Unfortunately Hiroshima cause The Residents to forget who they are so their newfound information is all for naught.   Hiroshima's evil Caroline clone catches up with Henry's Caroline clone and attempts to kill her as the final and most important Caroline clone. Purely on instinct Henry's Caroline clone shifts out of Hiroshima's Bugtown reality, an act which so surprises and enrages her that she causes another titanic nuclear explosion to occur killing the remaining survivors.   Can anybody stop Hiroshima?</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-15 21:22:41.  [CVDB272488]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 12:38:08. [Issue ID 272297]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Penciller>Matt Howarth</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Howarth</Inker>
  <Editor>Patricia Jeres</Editor>
  <Publisher>Vortex</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/savage-henry-5-smothered-hope/4000-272488/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Savage Henry,Hiroshima,Caroline Clone,Nash the Slash</Characters>
  <Teams>The Residents</Teams>
  <Locations>Bugtown,Australia</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="2346392" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="340622" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1214320" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1193624" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1336174" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1011016" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="733494" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="726514" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1045560" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="773372" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="970056" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="518826" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="569690" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="612854" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="312558" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="597200" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="333870" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="632098" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="888304" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="604236" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="658048" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="789188" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="965360" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="863736" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1045392" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="404584" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="229864" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="428976" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>