<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Gravel,Simon Shiranian</Characters>
	<Colorist>Greg Waller</Colorist>
	<Count>22</Count>
	<Country>US</Country>
	<Editor>William Christensen</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-407069</GTIN>
	<Genre>Fantasy,Horror-suspense</Genre>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Locations>Afghanistan,England,London</Locations>
	<Month>12</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:35:29 [Issue ID 4000-407069] urn:comicvine:4000-407069 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/407069</Notes>
	<Number>0</Number>
	<PageCount>14</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1746945" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1687971"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1899658"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="2257563"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="2018881"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1625619"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1666318"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1331970"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="2370318"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1995726"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1825858"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="2185078"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1717436"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1838790"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
	<Series>Gravel</Series>
	<Summary>It’s never a dull day, being a Magician. The mad mind of Warren Ellis is once again unleashed on combat magician William Gravel, this time on a full-color, on-going monthly series! This special #0 issue is ad-free and the all-new story leads directly into the new series! Magic. The kind of magic that can strip the skin from a screaming man’s skull, or direct the path of a shrieking bullet through a maze of city streets, striking its target between the eyes with pin-point accuracy. This is not just magic… This is Combat Magic, wielded by Sergeant Major William Gravel, Warren Ellis’ cult-hit sensation from the pages of STRANGE KISS and STRANGE KILLINGS, now in his own, ongoing, full-color monthly series! From war-torn Afghanistan to the deceptively mundane streets of London, this special introductory chapter sets the stage for a tale so dark, twisted and disturbing that it could only have sprung from the mind of Ellis. SAS soldier Gravel has returned home, only to find that another has taken his place in the mysterious enclave of Britain’s seven Occult Detectives. Worse, the seven are now in possession of the legendary Sigsand Manuscript, a supernatural device that could bestow its keepers with a most vile and terrifying power. Gravel has a new mission, one that will be filled with his own unflinching brand of horrific and bloody violence. Ellis is joined by co-writer Mike Wolfer and rising start artist Raulo (Crecy) Caceres for the launch of this messy, magical epic! This issue is available with a regular cover by Mike Wolfer, a wraparound by Raulo Caceres, and also a rare 1-in-15 Black Magic Edition featuring a new cover by Wolfer.</Summary>
	<Title>Issue One Preview Artwork; Between the Wars</Title>
	<Volume>2007</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-407069/</Web>
	<Writer>Warren Ellis</Writer>
	<Year>2007</Year>
</ComicInfo>