<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Julie the Dancing Bear,The Wild Hunt,Joh,Rosehip,Brother Hugh,Tim Hunter,Bahrbaetous,Accasbel</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Jamison</Colorist>
  <Editor>Cliff Chiang,Stuart Moore</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-46642</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:34 [Issue ID 4000-46642] urn:comicvine:4000-46642
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:16:26. [Issue ID 63619]</Notes>
  <Number>65</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1534" ImageSize="650409" ImageWidth="995" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1560" ImageSize="524755" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1558" ImageSize="478312" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1556" ImageSize="483232" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1554" ImageSize="584062" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1562" ImageSize="603456" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1547" ImageSize="625009" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1556" ImageSize="596798" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1549" ImageSize="632555" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1557" ImageSize="566024" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1560" ImageSize="579775" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1559" ImageSize="527705" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1574" ImageSize="486179" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1574" ImageSize="484743" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1557" ImageSize="609252" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1552" ImageSize="504292" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1569" ImageSize="628741" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1548" ImageSize="611137" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1552" ImageSize="549507" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1571" ImageSize="560903" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1558" ImageSize="537992" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1548" ImageSize="723791" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="601561" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Tim Hunter's new life continues as the young mage, now disguised as a girl named Mary, encounters an old woman whose children are nearly as disturbing as her collection of coffins. And elsewhere in the realms, the mythic menace of the Wild Hunt prepares to strike. 

The Wild Hunt, newly freed from their extradimensional prison, finds Hephaestos, one of their jailors, who is living in the modern world as a gas station attendant. However, instead of killing him, they want him to make them new weapons. He agrees, since his skills have not been needed in many years.

Tim, now traveling in the guise of his mother and going under the name of "Mary," is still with the friends he met last issue, who are all refugees of the great magic storm that has thrown all the realms into disarray.

They find a woman's corpse in a coffin in the woods. A young black girl comes up, named Jeannie Day. She says her mother needs help. As they walk to her home, we see many other coffins in the woods.

Her mother is trying to put an adult man's body back in a coffin as they arrive. She says his name is Jimmy, which is also the name of a young boy nearby. The people are clearly spirits of the dead in the coffins.

They're invited to eat, but decide to leave. However, they find themselves back at the cabin anyway. Inside, they find the whole family. Mam Day explains that she has hidden the cabin and her children from Death herself. The kids say that no one can leave or find them until they say they love her--but even the children's ghosts want to leave. They are all the age they were when they stopped loving her.

The travelers decide they need to persuade the kids to find some love for her. Tim talks with the boy, Jimmy, and even takes off his glamour stone to reveal that he is really a boy too, but Jimmy says he can't love her when everything is always about her for her.

The monk, Hugh, talks with Jeannie. He says he can find his way out, and wants to help her do the same. Hugh smashes her coffin, and says she can now go to heaven--and he can use her as a ride. The flitling, Rosehip, flies along after her and into her mouth, transforming her into her pure self. With all the gates smashed by the strom, she can now go wherever she wants, not just heaven. She leaves in happiness.

Hugh freaks out, and Julie the bear claws him, revealing that he was just maggots in a skin shell. They all turn on Mama Day again for keeping them there, and she explains that she wasn't waiting for the kids to love her, but for her to love them. Now she knows she does, and they all leave.

Julie and Rosehip decide to stay with Mama Day, so Joh and "Mary" take the gate to the Inn Between Worlds. Joh gets Mary a job at the Inn, working with her boss Accasbel.

Back at the site of Hugh's death, Barbatos enjoys eating and collecting the Christian maggot souls that had accumulated in Hugh's robes. He is aided by Hauptmann. He hopes to use the souls to gain power within Hell.  We haven't seen Barbatos since issue 20 when he was trapped by a giant statue.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:21:55.  [CVDB46642]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-65-the-arrangement/4000-46642/</Summary>
  <Title>The Arrangement</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-65-the-arrangement/4000-46642/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>