<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Interlude in Palmettoville; The Deathsnake, Part Two; Lure of the Deathsnake; Isle of the Dead</Title>
  <Series>The Deathsnake</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-03 22:37:28.  [CVDB160293]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 23:51:25. [Issue ID 351873]</Notes>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Writer>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Writer>
  <Penciller>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Penciller>
  <Inker>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Inker>
  <Letterer>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>John Blackburn</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Tom Verre,Jeremy Pinkham,Carol Gnojewski</Editor>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Adult</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deathsnake-2/4000-160293/</Web>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Curtis Banning (Private Investigator, Atlanta),Harry "Lance" Larue</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="57270" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="394094" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="474552" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="404310" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="347602" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="628192" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="489752" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="405572" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="402360" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="437656" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="420752" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="359330" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="395330" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="471258" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="502452" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="481006" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="388110" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="507694" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="433414" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="451036" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="477356" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="438212" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="416792" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="404084" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="360432" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="336994" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Interlude in Palmettoville: Harry and Banning discuss Judge O'Hara's corruption and involvement in dumping toxic waste in the swamp.

The Deathsnake, Part Two: Delila has her way with Coley, during which he also "takes care" of Daniel. She accuses Coley of making her father gay, then shows him a lampshade made of human skin.

Lure of the Deathsnake: Valdosta &amp; Ashley discuss Coley. Jack shows Coley the bridge "he" built thru the swamp, which he's proud of, but Coley calls it an "abomination" against the natural surroundings, that was built on the lives of the prisoners. Coley reveals he knows about Judge O'Hara's involvement with dumping toxic waste in the swamp, and had taken and hidden evidence from Jack's office, intending to turn it over to Chief Beasley! Jack says this leave him no choice but to kill Coley, but Coley says he can't do it because Jack's in love with him. Instead, he puts Coley in "the oven", a sweatbox. One of the guards, Steve, lets Coley out and the two make love in the swamp. Steve feels for sure there's no malice whatsoever in Coley, and offers to help him escape. But back with the other prisoners, while Coley is servicing a black inmate, Ed, Smiley and a group of others attack savagely, apparently killing both Coley and Valdosta.

Isle of the Dead: Jack has Coley and Valdosta buried on the "Isle Of The Dead", after dropping Coley's "voodoo junk" into the coffin. He then has Ed and Smiley, who he suspects of the murders, sent to clean up the weeds on the island. While there, they stumble upon a dead raven that has been ritually sacrificed-- and Coley, alive and well!

</Summary>
  <AgeRating>Adults Only</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>