<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Samhain,Maggie Reilly,Cassie Hack,Chris Krank,Cat Curio,Vlad,Lisa Elsten,Pooch</Characters>
  <Count>25</Count>
  <Day>9</Day>
  <Editor>James Lowder</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-261369</GTIN>
  <Inker>Daniel Leister,JM Ringuet,Daniel Leister,JM Ringuet</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!</Letterer>
  <Locations>Nevada,Alabama,Russia,Louisiana,Indiana</Locations>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:10:02 [Issue ID 4000-261369] urn:comicvine:4000-261369
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-19 07:54:25. [Issue ID 261369]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Daniel Leister,JM Ringuet,Daniel Leister,JM Ringuet</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Hack/Slash</Series>
  <Summary>HACK/SLASH returns in all-new ongoing series by the creative team behind the hit HACK/SLASH: MY FIRST MANIAC mini! Cassie Hack, killer of killers, and her partner Vlad hunt a slasher who haunts a small town's Make Out Point. Meanwhile, Cat Curio, Former Teen Detective, searches for the man who put her in a coma and the murderous cult that employed him. What she finds will set up the biggest HACK/SLASH story yet. A great jumping on point for new readers!

In Louisiana young lovers are in a car overlooking an oil strewn beach are interrupted by a decaying Zombie.

In Alabama Vlad is talking to Chris at Hack/Slash Inc about his concerns about Cassie who has been on edge of late. Cassie joins Vlad and they set off right away for another target. they arrive at the teens car and setup a trap to lure in the slasher. Vlad confronts her over the Georgia situation but Cassie just laughs it off ironically. Cassie gets int he car and makes noises of lovemaking while Vlad hides in the trees. When a figure appears Vlad texts her of the danger and he is attacked by a disfigured female zombie. The Zombies flee and they find an acid etched hand print on the car where the male zombie touched it and fear the Acid Angel is behind this.

On the beach Cassie wipes the face off the male zombie with her bat and the female escapes again. They follow her lead and find the teens: the girl half melted in a spa pol, and the boy with seemingly only a half melted face. The swimming pool ripples and a beautiful blonde rises from the depths, dripping acid, to tell them they are all going to die.

On a bus Cat Curio is on a mission to bring down the Black Lamp society. She leaves the bus and while walking down a country road she witnesses a cop car run over a dog only for the dog to get up and run into the woods. Back at home the cop is a woman and arranges a night out on the phone with a friend. She strips and dresses in silks and then sitting in a circle of candles before a laptop with cam and communes with the other members of the Black Lamp.

In the woods Cat uses her night-vision binoculars and sees a man stood among the trees as he dons a Pumpkin faced hood and she flees. She trips over a dead animal and turns to find her self surrounded by undead woodland creatures with red glowing eyes.</Summary>
  <Teams>Hack/Slash Inc,Slashers,Zombies</Teams>
  <Title>Crossroads, Part 1</Title>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/hackslash-1-crossroads-part-1/4000-261369/</Web>
  <Year>2011</Year>
  <Writer>Tim Seeley</Writer>
  <Colorist>Mark Englert</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Carlos Badilla,Erik Larsen,Mark Englert,Tim Seeley</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>