<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Wig Wam Bam, Part 7; Wig Wam Bam, Part 6; Poison River - Part Ten; Love and Rockets X - Part Eight</Title>
  <Series>Love and Rockets</Series>
  <Number>38</Number>
  <Count>53</Count>
  <Volume>1982</Volume>
  <Summary>Wig Wam Bam, Part 7: Back on the East Coast, Izzy visits Terry and then her old friend Barb, whose hairstyle now resembles Maggie's. But her Maggie and Hopey obsession is triggered each time when the subject of Hopey's face being on milk cartons comes up. Finally caving in to her obsession, she meets Hopey at a bar but then gets into an argument with her over Maggie. Hopey spies on Nan playing out her mommy caring for baby daughter fetish with Crystal. Doyle leaves town for good now that his romantic attachments have evaporated and Bumper's night club, his home away from home has closed.

Wig Wam Bam, Part 6: Nan Tucker has arrived as she and Hopey chat and get to know each other. Izzy visits the newly pregnant Penny as well as Marco, but her seemingly dormant obsession with Maggie and Hopey is triggered after each visit. Hopey finds out Nan has a fetish for women cosplaying as little girls.

Poison River - Part Ten: With Peter incapacitated due to his stroke, a power vacuum has opened as people jostle for power including Cilingis and Flaco. Armando Jose, Luba's newborn baby who was taken in a deal Peter had, has died of heart failure. Fermin continues his killing spree in defense of any threat to his son as he strangles Javier for taking that baby. But after insulting Peter's-ex Isobel for being trans, Peter temporarily comes to and kills him. Blas becomes more dominant as he takes Peter to safety. Gorgo ensures that Luba safely makes it to her cousin Ofelia's place.

Love and Rockets X - Part Eight: Kristen takes Maricela to her place ostensibly so her dad can help with her immigration papers. However, when she sees her dad in the pool talking intimately with Igor she gets highly upset. Carl stands in front of Malvina's house, the elderly black woman he assaulted. Junior Brooks and Erf'Quake see him, but Ben and Charlie whisk him away. The trio kidnap E. T., taking him to a secluded location, intending to kill him. Carl orders Ben to kill him in order to prove he's not a rat, but he refuses. Charlie volunteers to do it and takes the gun. But when Carl exhorts him he kills him instead.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-31 10:13:20.  [CVDB95765]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 21:57:30. [Issue ID 212424]</Notes>
  <Year>1992</Year>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Writer>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Drama</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/love-and-rockets-38/4000-95765/</Web>
  <PageCount>37</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Crystal,Barb</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="167088" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="525252" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="585152" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="666228" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="529494" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="499254" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="542490" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="548006" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="586362" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="611446" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="603330" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="540836" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="532148" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="625260" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="506252" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="694690" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="661824" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="484166" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="523270" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="252662" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="437970" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="469292" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="454306" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="477878" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="486112" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="335742" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="489432" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="548598" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="520568" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="446504" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="498844" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="433048" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="399240" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="462424" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="384950" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="208494" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="35672" />
  </Pages>
  <AgeRating>Recommended for Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>