<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294563</GTIN>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:17 [Issue ID 4000-294563] urn:comicvine:4000-294563
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:43. [Issue ID 136599]</Notes>
  <Number>10</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Title>The Spectre of Fate; The Brain That Wouldn't Die; The Cavern of the Damned; Death's Highway</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-10-spectre-of-fate/4000-294563/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>The Spectre of Fate: Eric Marston unwillingly is a stowaway on the cruise liner “Queen Ann” and witnesses the ship’s sinking after a collision with an iceberg. He survives, however, because he was not meant to die. An emissary of fate appears to him and declares him to be his successor. Marston is doomed to act as a “spectre of death” for the rest of his days.

The Brain That Wouldn't Die: Criminal mastermind Benny “the Brain” Bronson goes to the electric chair, but Dr. Andre Renard steals his head from out of the grave and manages to revive the brain. The brain then commands the doctor to execute his revenge. So Renard starts killing Bronson’s treacherous colleagues and the judge who convicted him.

The Cavern of the Damned: World traveler and explorer Lloyd Ramsey is exploring some underwater caverns and encounters a race of human looking aliens with three eyes. These beings plan on infiltrating society and overthrowing humanity. They can walk among us using a special spray to hide their third eye. Lloyd escapes and tries to warn everyone about the invasion, but finds that not only does no-one believe him, but they have already began integrating into society.

Death's Highway: Torpo and Randy, two hitmen for the mob, crash their car on the way to the next job. They stay miraculously unharmed and encounter their former victims. It dawns upon them that they have died and have to face a court of justice beyond the grave.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>