<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Werewolf by Night [Jack Russell],Buck Cowan,Topaz,Lissa Russell (cured of werewolfism),Taboo (villain, death),Dr. Glitternight (villain)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Don Warfield,Don Warfield</Colorist>
  <Editor>Len Wein</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-15297</GTIN>
  <Inker>Don Perlin,Don Perlin</Inker>
  <Letterer>Dave Hunt,Dave Hunt</Letterer>
  <Locations>Monterey,California</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:01:45 [Issue ID 4000-15297] urn:comicvine:4000-15297
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:45:54. [Issue ID 28693]</Notes>
  <Number>30</Number>
  <PageCount>19</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="6008770" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="5160407" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="4466958" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="4430295" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="4311107" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="3878548" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="3821454" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="4710476" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="4226438" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="4118024" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="4982727" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="4292676" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="4122231" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="4237316" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="4877992" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="4475592" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="4588116" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="4432023" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="4079301" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Don Perlin,Gil Kane,Don Perlin</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
  <Summary>An unlikely sacrifice frees Lissa from her lycanthropic curse!

In Russoff Castle on an island off the coast of California, Lissa Russell recuperates from her transformation into a Weredemon, a transformation she believes was merely a nightmare. Her brother Jack and their friends Buck Cowan and Topaz have subdued and bound Dr. Glitternight, the sorcerer responsible for Lissa's demonic corruption. They now confront him, demanding he use his magic to undo the curse. He refuses and Jack strikes him. Buck restrains Jack, and they decide to see if the revived spirit of Taboo (Topaz's adoptive father) can be of any aid. Left alone, Glitternight breaks free, leaving a simulacrum of himself for the others to see, as he seeks out Lissa.

With Taboo unable to help, Jack once again threatens Glitternight, only to see the image dissipate into nothingness. The sorcerer, meanwhile, has taken Lissa to a terrace where he pours his mystic black light into her body, corrupting her further. The moon rises, and she and Jack transform. The Werewolf finds the terrace where Glitternight has magically enslaved the Weredemon and they resume their battle while the magician floats above, observing.

Taboo has renewed his abilities enough that with Topaz augmenting his powers, he sacrifices his soul to cleanse Lissa of both the lycanthropic curse, and the demonic corruption. Turning from Lissa's unconscious form, the Werewolf accosts Glitternight who soars out over the ocean, trying to shake the man-beast loose. With a savage effort, the Werewolf slashes Glitternight's chest, the core of his mystic light. The released magical energies cause an explosion and the pair plummet toward the sea.

While Topaz and Buck tend to the now-cured Lissa, the Werewolf finds his way to the shore.</Summary>
  <Tags>Werewolf By Night,Dr. Glitternight,Buck Cowan,Topaz,Monterey,Lissa Russell,California,Werewolves,Taboo</Tags>
  <Teams>Werewolves</Teams>
  <Title>Red Slash Across Midnight</Title>
  <Volume>1972</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-30-red-slash-across-midnight/4000-15297/</Web>
  <Writer>Doug Moench,Doug Moench</Writer>
  <Year>1975</Year>
  <Count>43</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Gil Kane</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Adventure</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>