<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Crossroads</Title>
  <Series>Star Wars: Rebellion</Series>
  <Number>0</Number>
  <Count>17</Count>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Summary>With the destruction of its Death Star battle station, the Galactic Empire has been shaken to the core by the ever-growing Rebel Alliance. Its iron-fisted order challenged, the Empire quickly finds an increasing number of systems slipping through its fingers.

In one of those systems, the remote desert planet of Jabiim held promise for Luke Skywalker and the Rebellion. But a well-intentioned diplomatic mission turned tragic when the Rebels' presence alerted Darth Vader and led to the complete subjugation of Jabiim's immense slave population.

Seeking to rescue one of their own left behind on Jabiim&#8212;an Alliance mathematician called Jorin Sol&#8212;the rebels mounted a daring and covert mission against an Imperial stronghold on Kalist VI. An operation that brought Luke Skywalker into direct and heartbreaking conflict with his childhood friend "Tank", now known to the Empire as Lieutenant Janek Sunber ...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-01 07:45:13.  [CVDB174148]</Notes>
  <Year>2006</Year>
  <Month>03</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Jeremy Barlow</Writer>
  <Penciller>Michel Lacombe, Michel Lacombe</Penciller>
  <Inker>Michel Lacombe, Michel Lacombe</Inker>
  <Colorist>Wil Glass</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Michael Heisler</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Brandon Badeaux</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Dave Marshall, Jeremy Barlow</Editor>
  <Publisher>Dark Horse Comics</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/star-wars-rebellion-0-crossroads/4000-174148/</Web>
  <PageCount>13</PageCount>
  <Characters>2-1B, Able, Basso, Commander Demmings, Darth Vader, Janek Sunber, Jorin Sol, Luke Skywalker, Nolan Gillmunn, Orliss Gillmunn, Princess Leia, R2-D2, Raze, Tal Hesz</Characters>
  <Teams>Astromech Droids, Barabels, Biths, Clone Troopers, Galactic Empire, Gamorreans, Jedi Order, Nikto, Ortolans, Quarrens, Rebel Alliance, Rodians, Stormtroopers, The Sith, Togrutas, Toydarians, Twi'leks, Weequays, Wookiees</Teams>
  <Locations>Jabiim, Kalist VI</Locations>
  <ScanInformation>(DarthScanner-DCP)</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="764758" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="698434" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="668409" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="805435" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="681982" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="646934" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="717003" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="673304" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="755747" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="708942" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="857277" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="683777" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="332387" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
