<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-103589</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:40:07 [Issue ID 4000-103589] urn:comicvine:4000-103589
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 01:38:12. [Issue ID 229937]</Notes>
  <Number>12</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Pines</Publisher>
  <Series>Adventures into Darkness</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-darkness-12/4000-103589/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>10</Count>
  <Title>Nightmare Island; The Gypsy Curse; The Last Dance; Conspiracy with Death; The Living-Dead of Kulatum!; Horror's Scrapbook; The Spectral Sergeant; Serpent of Doom</Title>
  <Genre>War,Horror-suspense,Fantasy,Western-frontier</Genre>
  <Summary>Nightmare Island: An island off the Australian coast proves indeed to be haunted, as a dockworker finds out who volunteered to spend the night there.

The Gypsy Curse: Nogoodnik Lou disposes of his difigured wife and is therefore faced with a gypsy curse. He won't find happiness as fate strikes pushing him into poverty and madness.

The Last Dance: A cavalry soldier killed by Apaches returns from the dead to prevent his girl from marrying someone else.

Conspiracy with Death: A sailor pays a witch doctor to put a jinx on his rival. The sailer gets the girl, but refuses to pay his debt. It's his turn to be jinxed now.

The Living-Dead of Kulatum!: In Brazil an explorer discovers the pyramids of Manoa and the cult of the living-dead. His escape is only temporary, for he is lost in the jungle.

Horror's Scrapbook: Accounts of weird occurrences and incidents.

The Spectral Sergeant: A sergeant's phantom warns his soldier buddies about an imminent German attack in WW I.

Serpent of Doom: Lydia longs for riches and enters into a pact with snake god Seth. Covering her murderous tracks, Seth grants her fame and fortune. When Lydia herself begins to turn into a snake, she plunges into despair.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>