<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-92035</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Stan Lee</Letterer>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:45:35 [Issue ID 4000-92035] urn:comicvine:4000-92035
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 16:18:41. [Issue ID 204895]</Notes>
  <Number>10</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Crypt of Shadows</Series>
  <Title>The Man in the Tank!; You Can't Touch Bottom; A Scream in the Dark!; Devil's Island</Title>
  <Volume>1973</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crypt-of-shadows-10-the-man-in-the-tank/4000-92035/</Web>
  <Year>1974</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Horror-suspense,Crime</Genre>
  <Summary>The Man in the Tank!: A killer hides in a water tank and when the train takes on engine water and drains the tank to halfway, the man can no longer latch on to the lid, eventually tires treading water and drowns.

You Can't Touch Bottom: A mysterious jacket has a spell on it that compels any who wear to stuff objects into the bottomless right pocket. A scientist figures he can get rich if he can figure out the secret of the other dimension and tries inserting various objects, even a note attempting to communicate, but he cannot figure out what object the other dimensional beings are looking for. Finally, he sticks his head in attempting to see, and falls all the way in. When the jacket is found the next day, the pocket now has a bottom sewn in.

A Scream in the Dark!: When a couple arrive at the end of the tunnel of love, they find that they have aged rapidly and the fairground deserted. They attempt to return the way they came, and they succeed in getting out the front entrance where the fair is still going on, but they remain of advanced age.

Devil's Island: A man takes his unfaithful lover in the dark to the largest pearl she has ever seen. It's still inside the giant clam which closes on her.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Carl Wessler,Carl Wessler</Writer>
  <Penciller>Everett Raymond Kinstler,Ross Andru,Sam Citron,Paul Reinman,Everett Raymond Kinstler,Ross Andru,Sam Citron,Paul Reinman</Penciller>
  <Inker>Everett Raymond Kinstler,Mike Esposito,Sam Citron,Paul Reinman,Everett Raymond Kinstler,Mike Esposito,Sam Citron,Paul Reinman</Inker>
  <Editor>Roy Thomas,Stan Lee,Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>