<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Francine,Katchoo,Marie Peters,R2-D2,David Qin</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digital Chameleon</Colorist>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-45294</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:46:28 [Issue ID 4000-45294] urn:comicvine:4000-45294
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:09:03. [Issue ID 45294]</Notes>
  <Number>17</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>Flash Forward Its been 10 whole years since they last saw each other and Francine's emotions are high. Brad phones Francine to tell her he wont be home till late but gets Marie instead. She reminds him Francie is out to meet him for lunch but he's forgotten that too. Today Marie is looking after Francine's little girl.  Francine wanders from the restaurant absentmindedly missing her friend terribly even now... She sees someone who looks like her on the gazebo where they once sat.. she is distracted when a waitress runs over with her handbag and when she turns back the woman is gone. She goes and gets drunk at a bar....   *The Past *
Francine comes to and she is in an art Gallery with David and a short haired Katchoo **
 Flash Forward  Fran arrives home drunk and melancholy and tells her mother she feels like 10 years of marriage has gone nowhere when she thinks of her friend. As Fran sobs her mother tries to comfort her and then hardens and goes to a phone and opens a  folded piece of paper with a phone number on it.                                                                                                 In Sante Fe Katchoo arrives home at a lavish house with a maid who tells her about business phone calls for her artwork and that a woman called about someone called Francine. Katchoo leaps for the phone and listens to the message. Marie Peters has had her number for some time and for two changes of address. She stays no matter what she's said of their relationship in the past she cant see her daughter this way.  Katchoo is booking tickets before the phone message even ends.  *The Past *
The three are at the park and Francine's allusions to Katchoo saving her if she fell in the pond make the slightly sullen Katchoo think all the more.</Summary>
  <Title>My Old Addiction</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-17-my-old-addiction/4000-45294/</Web>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>