<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Everything but the Girl</Title>
  <Series>Static</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>45</Count>
  <Volume>1993</Volume>
  <Summary>Virgil has a lot of explaining to do as Frieda demands to know the shocking origin of Static. And Hotstreak and Static are ready for a brutal rematch. Written by Dwayne McDuffie and Robert Washington,

Virgil tells Frieda how he became Static and why he couldn't fight Biz Money B (Hot-Streak). He describes how Biz Money B had bullied him when he first met Frieda which caused him to get a gun from Larry and head to the big bang. Virgil had intended to kill Biz Money, but then he realized he wasn't a killer and threw the gun away and had intended to leave, but then they unleashed the gas (Quantum Juice) and Virgil fell unconscious. When he awoke Virgil saw the changes that had begun in the people around him and fled the scene while discovering his own newfound powers. He then trained using these powers and emerged as Static. Static then faces Hot-Streak again and defeats him with ease and later he tries to bring his relation ship with Frieda to a new level, but she turns him down. Tarmack and Holocaust are shown discussing Hot-Streak's defeat and wonder if they should employ Static.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-21 06:45:54.  [CVDB37537]</Notes>
  <Year>1993</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Dwayne McDuffie, Robert L. Washington III</Writer>
  <Penciller>John Paul Leon, John Paul Leon</Penciller>
  <Inker>Steve Mitchell</Inker>
  <Colorist>Noelle C. Giddings, Hanne Kjellgaard, Noelle Giddings</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Steve Haynie</Letterer>
  <Editor>Dwayne McDuffie</Editor>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/static-2-everything-but-the-girl/4000-37537/</Web>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Frieda Goren, Holocaust, Hot-Streak, Jean Hawkins, Larry Wade, Rick Stone, Sharon Hawkins, Static, Tarmack</Characters>
  <Teams>5-Alarm Crew, Bang Babies, System</Teams>
  <Locations>Dakota, Ernest Hemingway High School, Paris Island</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="583440" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="386736" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="544668" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="504498" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="520252" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="527710" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="454884" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="527132" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="446918" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="456582" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="433848" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="392822" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="453912" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="383450" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="491918" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="476942" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="430152" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="402242" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="394442" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="447608" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="416122" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="426442" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="417320" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="339052" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
