<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Haseena,GoGirl!</Characters>
  <Colorist>Christopher Butcher</Colorist>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-51848</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Sean Glumace</Letterer>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:46:26 [Issue ID 4000-51848] urn:comicvine:4000-51848
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-19 23:23:09. [Issue ID 51848]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Go Girl!</Series>
  <Summary>THIS IS THE BOOK THE FANS DEMANDED! Before its publication date, GoGirl! generated enormous buzz on the internet in the form of interviews and rave advance reviews. Excited fans couldn't wait to buy it and read it. But evidently direct-sales retailers don't surf the net. Low advance orders made our original plans for a full-color book an impossibility. What happened next surprised and encouraged us. Fans sent us e-mails, wrote articles on the net, expressing their disapointment, offering help, even pledging a word-of-mouth and internet campaign to help GoGirl! See print. And we've taken them up on it! Starting in August, and every four months after that, you can now follow the adventures of teen superheroine GoGirl! in crisp black and white with full-color covers. Here's what Maggie Thompson had to say about GoGirl! in the Comics Buyer's Guide: " It's clearly aimed at an audience for which not much has been available...: pre-teen girls. And it should entertain that audience well....ALL the female characters (including the villain) are strong and resourceful; ...it's a comic book that could attract readers that comics have largely lost. Try it on them." GOGIRL! YOU'LL BELIEVE A GIRL CAN FLY!</Summary>
  <Title>Go Girl!</Title>
  <Volume>2000</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/go-girl-1-go-girl/4000-51848/</Web>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Writer>Trina Robbins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Anne Timmons,Anne Timmons</Penciller>
  <Inker>Anne Timmons</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Anne Timmons</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Trina Robbins</Editor>
</ComicInfo>