<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-387937</GTIN>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:29 [Issue ID 4000-387937] urn:comicvine:4000-387937
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:48:46. [Issue ID 9420]</Notes>
  <Number>9</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Crime SuspenStories</Series>
  <Summary>Understudy to a Corpse!: Brad and Alice discover an old trunk in the attic of their new home....a trunk containing the bones of a corpse. And the story concerning those bones involves several murders over money.

Medicine!: When Luther arrives home late from surgery, his wife Nora rushes away in the car, even though her husband tries to tell her something. She recounts how she met Luther, and the quick wedding (only for his money, not love). Later, she discovers Luther had to have his meds every day at 4pm and counted on Miss Doyle reminding him of that. But Nora is jealous of Miss Doyle, who went with Luther everywhere. So Nora decides to poison Luther's meds. Unfortunately, Nora gets into an accident because of bad brakes on the car and only her husband can operate....after he takes his meds, that is!

Cut!: Vain movie stand-in Russell Slade, realizing that his make-up man makes the actor look exactly like John Hammond, devises a plan to get rid of the actor and take his place. But the plan backfires in an unexpected way.

A Tree Grows in Borneo!: George and Amos are exploring dense Borneo jungles in search of a proper location for company mine development when they discover ancient temples built by the Kenyahs, a people who buried their dead inside hollowed out trees. George is interested in the solid gold roofs of the temples, but Amos explains a curse on anyone desecrating the temples. They bring gold back, sharing it, but Amos gets greedy and decides to kill George and not share the rest of the gold. When he returns to the Kenyah temples to get more gold, the curse strikes him down.

</Summary>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-9/4000-387937/ https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-9-understudy-to-a-corpse/4000-109756/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>27</Count>
  <Title>Understudy to a Corpse!; Medicine!; Cut!; A Tree Grows in Borneo!</Title>
  <Characters>Brad,Cyrus Klitch (miserly hypocrite, death, in flashback),Alice (Brad's wife),Jeremy (villain, Klitch's nephew, death, in flashback),Myra (villain, Klitch's nurse, in flashback)</Characters>
  <Penciller>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Jack Davis,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Inker>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Jack Davis,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Johnny Craig</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein</Editor>
  <Genre>Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Al Feldstein,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Al Feldstein</Writer>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>