<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Casey Femur,David Qin,Francine,Katchoo,Tambi Baker</Characters>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-179590</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:46:58 [Issue ID 4000-179590] urn:comicvine:4000-179590
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:18:50. [Issue ID 179590]</Notes>
  <Number>23</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>Francine goes fishing like she did as a child in the river but ends up sitting on the bank thinking about how much simpler life is when you are a child.  Katchoo starts softly enough with Casey but when she has enough she bodily dumps her on the floor. Casey complains so what is he likes David to which Katchoo points out she is Mrs Femur. She then asks of Katchoo can turn her gay as she did it for Francine. Katchoo is stunned for once in her life. Casey says if she can do it for Francine when with Casey and her body it should be easy. She frightens Casey with her predicable rage but takes pity on the fragile creature.  They notice David has been on the phone and is now quiet and is suddenly shaking.  Elsewhere Tambi is with a lawyer who has just told David he has a half share in his sisters wealth. Tambi says he will refuse to take on the partnership aspect of it and he is not like his sister.  David sits stunned and tells the girl in a daze he inherited 1.4.. Casey jumps in  Million?!  David mutters.. 1.4 Billion. Casey in all seriousness says "Take Me!".  David gets a drink and laments his sister did nothing with her money and he will use it to do good and will leave an empty account when he dies. Katchoo kisses him.  Casey gets up when they don't come back in to the room. She hears them in a darkened bedroom and tears roll down her face. She strips and joins them on the bed much to their surprise. She meekly asks if she can join them but Katchoo orders he off and to get dressed.  Seconds later the front door opens and Francine shouts "Hello" they scramble and Katchoo pretends to be asleep in bed as Casey and David hide in the en-suit. Francie comes in and hopes to say her piece to the sleeping Katchoo first. Casey knock something and Fran heads to the bathroom. Katchoo jumps up and heads her off. She says her piece about Katchoo knowing her better than she does herself and Casey adn David tumble out of the bathroom much to Francine's Confusing. Casey sees shes the only one with no clothes on.</Summary>
  <Title>Fear of Swimming</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-23-fear-of-swimming/4000-179590/</Web>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>