<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-805664</GTIN>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Locations>Virginia</Locations>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:53:51 [Issue ID 4000-805664] urn:comicvine:4000-805664 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/805664
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 18:23:10. [Issue ID 805664]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>14</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1325459" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1858839" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1501092" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1532082" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1735217" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1570822" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1610525" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1636148" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1338999" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1353848" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1466633" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1528578" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1370223" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="243938" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Plague of the Living Dead</Series>
  <Summary>Picking up where the Plague of the Living Dead Special left off, the survivors in the Price household try to get a grip on what is happening. They try to phone the police to no avail and Jessica sees the zombies eating Kelly. Zombie Greg busts through the door and Mr. Price is taken. As he is, he yells for Larry to get the women to the basement where his guns are. They watch Mr. Price get eaten. The women head for the basement, but Larry doesn't want to be stuck down there and wishes to stay above ground. Jessica and Darlene go down and leave him upstairs.

On the Stone Mountain military base, Major Henry is having Corporal Todd Clark and Privates Terry Ellis and Steve Green transferred to Fort Sill. Todd hears gunfire in the distance, but Major Henry shrugs it off, telling their guards to use lethal force if necessary. Back at the Price residence, Darlene is trying to open the gun cabinet, but Jessica says her father must have the key. In shock, Jessica goes to open the door to the basement, thinking it is her father. The startling fact is that when she opens it, it is him, only now a zombie...</Summary>
  <Teams>Zombies</Teams>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-805664/</Web>
  <Writer>John Russo</Writer>
  <Year>2007</Year>
</ComicInfo>