<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Escape of the Living Dead</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Summary>They thought it was over, but the Dead still walk the Earth! The co-writer of the classic film NIGHT OF THE LIVING DEAD brings his all-new, never-before-seen zombie masterpiece to comics! 1971: It's been three years since the blood-soaked night that the dead rose from their graves, attacking and devouring the living. Now, the legacy of that horrific and unexplained event is about to be unleashed once again upon an unsuspecting world... What was initially a sanctuary from the rotting grasp of the undead, Henry Brinkman's roadside bar might now become a deathtrap for he and his daughter, Sally. With an army of ravenous zombies prowling outside, Henry opened the door to save the lives of three outlaw bikers, but that decision may have been his biggest mistake. In a desperate attempt to escape from the living dead, someone will have to serve as human bait- and Henry's not holding the gun- in the most vicious and sensual installment of ESCAPE OF THE LIVING DEAD yet! As well as this regular cover by series artist Dheeraj Verma, it's also available with a Wraparound, Gore, and Terror by Verma, and a special Die Cut cover with art by Mike Wolfer.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-10-06 22:25:27.  [CVDB115712]</Notes>
  <Year>2006</Year>
  <Month>01</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>John Russo</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dheeraj Verma</Penciller>
  <Inker>Lalit</Inker>
  <Colorist>Andrew Dalhouse</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Dheeraj Verma, Lalit, Mike Wolfer</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>William Christensen</Editor>
  <Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/escape-of-the-living-dead-3/4000-115712/</Web>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Teams>Zombies</Teams>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="7332258" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="7965562" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="6681208" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="7074438" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="7392433" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="6876641" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="7288819" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="7928950" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="8170643" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="8563031" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="7381144" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="7981338" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="8423828" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="7193118" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="7521719" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="7177551" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="7427108" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="7125250" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="8277440" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="7137528" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="7483174" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="6616600" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="8712803" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="7629351" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
