<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Father Vincent Adobe,Roxanna,Werewolf By Night</Characters>
	<Colorist>Marie Javins</Colorist>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Ralph Macchio</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-108956</GTIN>
	<Inker>Leonardo Manco</Inker>
	<Letterer>Janice Chiang</Letterer>
	<Locations>New York City</Locations>
	<Month>2</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:18:37 [Issue ID 4000-108956] urn:comicvine:4000-108956</Notes>
	<Number>1</Number>
	<PageCount>23</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="337605" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="318646" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="332958" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="325811" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="334633" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="366300" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="373738" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="335501" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="321974" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="290433" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="341792" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="265047" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="312005" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="332139" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="322152" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="364538" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="365478" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="340896" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="336026" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="303645" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="363102" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="365824" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="285593" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Leonardo Manco</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
	<Summary>Jack Russell, somewhat drunk, is kicked out of a movie theater, and soon makes his way to prepare for the coming full moon. On the way, he passes his friend, Father Adobe, who senses something wrong in Jack. Adobe offers to help, but Jack declines, and proceeds to enter the sewers where, during the day he works, but on nights of the full moon, he locks himself away as he uncontrollably transforms into the Werewolf. Adding to Jack's distress, his recent transformations are accompanied by hellish visions of a nether realm dominated by some kind of demon that addresses him directly.

While the Werewolf pounds in vain at the walls of his cell, he is watched over from a grate above by a misshapen, crippled denizen of the docks.

The next morning, Jack sits in his untidy apartment, making notes regarding something from his subconscious about an oddly-shaped knife. He is soon visited by his girlfriend Roxanna, who tries to discuss his disappearance of the past three days. Jack won't explain to her, but tells her he loves her, and she lets him keep his secrets for now.

Late that night, Jack surfs the internet, searching for information about lycanthropy and possible cures. He finds a site about a group called the Cult of the Third Moon that also displays an image of the knife he had drawn earlier. Eager for more data, Jack calls Father Adobe, who had studied the occult in the past. Roused out of his sleep, Adobe tells Jack what he knows: the group, thought to be over 2000 years old, is associated with werewolves, and in particular, a wolf-demon; in the Middle Ages, the Cult came across a mystic blade with which they hoped to control the demon, but as a fragment of a greater talisman, it merely indebted them to the being; in the 1930s, the knife came into the possession of Walter Clark, a Hollywood actor, and is now presumably part of his estate.

Adobe asks Jack why it is so urgent to know this, but at this point, Jack is unsure.

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-1-somewhere-south-of-heaven/4000-108956/</Summary>
	<Tags>Father Vincent Adobe,New York City,Roxanna,Werewolf By Night,Werewolves</Tags>
	<Teams>Werewolves</Teams>
	<Title>Somewhere South of Heaven</Title>
	<Volume>1998</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-1-somewhere-south-of-heaven/4000-108956/</Web>
	<Writer>Paul Jenkins</Writer>
	<Year>1998</Year>
</ComicInfo>