<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Spawn (Simmons),Mark,Terry Fitzgerald,Wanda Fitzgerald</Characters>
  <Colorist>Brian Haberlin,Dan Kemp</Colorist>
  <Count>352</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-83172</GTIN>
  <Inker>Danny Miki</Inker>
  <Letterer>Tom Orzechowski</Letterer>
  <Locations>Santa Monica,Hell,California</Locations>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:51:16 [Issue ID 4000-83172] urn:comicvine:4000-83172
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-20 01:44:10. [Issue ID 83172]</Notes>
  <Number>92</Number>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="280154" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="178609" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="223300" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="242145" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="228992" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="231474" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="189931" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="234976" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="241290" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="253349" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="236651" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="229037" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="239157" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="225273" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="231262" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="235435" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="209202" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="290807" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="220898" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="199871" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="263278" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="174839" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="239244" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="155297" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Spawn</Series>
  <Summary>Mark continues his attempts to persuade Spawn to exchange lives with him, claiming he is dying and knows he'll go to Hell and therefore, if he were a Spawn he could be a ruler there instead of a bottom-feeder. Spawn takes Mark on a tour of Hell, puts him through a ritualistic test that rids him of his terminal illness and begs him not to pursue Hell. When Mark still insists that he wants to be a ruler in Hell, he "accidentally" falls to his death with no arrangement as a HellSpawn.

As Mark tells him of the plan Spawn thinks of the possibility of becoming human again and growing old with his wife Wanda Fitzgerald, Spawn snaps out of the thought and asks Mark not to do it. When Mark refuses Spawn uses his powers to send he and Mark to his own Hell. As they walk through Mark's Hell Spawn tells him about each persons own hell and they see the terrors of his Hell. Mark however actually enjoys it and then tells Spawn that he has a tumor and is going to die and that no matter what he does he's going to Hell either way. When Mark tells him this Spawn directs to a tower. As they head to the tower Mark sees people in cages including Reneé, Spawn points out that they're his sins then lets out Reneé and tells her to leave and never return. As they reach the tower they are stopped by a real gatekeeper demon who asks to see the stamp. Without hesitation mark shows the demon his pentagram tattoo on his chest and enters the tower. Spawn taunts Mark with an initiation like the one Mark gave Reneé telling him to climb the steps of the tower and get to the top without screaming or the darkness would consume him. As Mark climbs the steps he starts to burn from his feet up and the flames crawl higher the farther he goes. On his way up demons taunt him telling him to go back and then Mark is completely engulfed by the flames when suddenly he reaches the top and Spawn tells him the fire cured him and instructs him to look at the view and Mark sees the true face of Hell. A black cat appears and offers him crown of thorns, when Spawn asks him to leave ark refuses and then the tower starts to fall apart sending Mark falling down to the demons below. When Mark awakens his back has been pierced by the pitchfork of a statue and realizes the whole thing was an illusion and that he had fallen off the top of his house. As he watches Spawn staring down on him the paramedics try to save him but he is reported dead at the scene. The paramedics then go to help Reneé and she tells them to take her home as she stares up at spawn who disappears into the night.</Summary>
  <Teams>Hellspawn</Teams>
  <Title>Black Cat Bones II</Title>
  <Volume>1992</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/spawn-92-black-cat-bones-ii/4000-83172/</Web>
  <Writer>Brian Holguin,Todd McFarlane</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Penciller>Greg Capullo</Penciller>
  <CoverArtist>Greg Capullo,Todd McFarlane</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>