<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<Colorist>Jim Boswell</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Paul J Holden,Simon Parr (PYE)</CoverArtist>
	<Day>5</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1058733</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Nick Brokenshire,Nick Percival,Simon Parr (PYE)</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>6</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:37 [Issue ID 4000-1058733] urn:comicvine:4000-1058733</Notes>
	<Number>2385</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1249954" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1618103"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="847970"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="861922"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="788236"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1007580"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="858898"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="805116"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1927334"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1368220"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1459719"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1665727"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1189431"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1367877"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1362865"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="926719"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1112494"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1265977"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1141621"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1061307"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1007453"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="997146"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="944475"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="786244"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="933498"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1262580"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1482386"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1643914"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1503074"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1608239"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1999986"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="796363"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Nick Brokenshire,Nick Percival,Simon Parr (PYE)</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Weep with joy and buckle your diodes - I am The Mighty Tharg and I bring you Thrill-power! 

We surge into summer like a squad of Intestinauts falling upon a bacterial cluster in your upper colon - June is upon us and the Thrills are hot, hot, hot! Dredd edges closer to a confrontation with the Undercity entity known as Iron Teeth; Kurtis and Lind wrestle sigils in Brink; the net is closing in on Proteus Vex; the microbial cover stars come face to cerebellum with the mysterious Dr Globulon; and 3riller Blue Skies Over Deadwick reaches its explosive finale. All in all, another packed prog of searing sci-fi to fry your imaginations!

I expect many of you Squaxx picture the Command Module to be a dark and gritty environment, in which stories of anti-heroes battling hostile worlds are conjured into being - and, to be fair, it is ninety per cent of the time like that - but here at Thrill-Central we’re not averse to a little romance, which is why my droids have been working hard on a new Kickstarter project that sees the return of classic title Roxy as an eighty-page special.

The crowd-funding launches this month - check it out, Terrans!

*Judge Dredd » Iron Teeth (Part 4)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, where poverty and overcrowding is rife and tensions run a constant knife-edge. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*INTESTINAUTS » Busted Flush (Part 4)*
For stomach upsets, future technology has developed nano-robots called INTESTINAUTS, who fight parasites in the gut. These micro-droids are ingested orally, then once their brave battle against the various horrors that can be found in the stomach is over, they take the Big Flush, ready to be uploaded back to headquarters, where their accrued knowledge of the enemy will help them in future missions...

*Tharg's 3rillers Present » Blue Skies Over deadwick (Part 3)*
Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story - a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre! Earth, the far future. Three climbers have been tasked with an important mission, one that cannot afford to fail. They have heard the rumble, and so must make the arduous, dangerous ascent if they are to save their settlement of Deadwick...

*Brink » Consumed (Part 8)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 11)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 2385</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2385-prog-2385/4000-1058733/</Web>
	<Writer>Arthur Wyatt,Dan Abnett,David Baillie,Kenneth Niemand,Michael Carroll</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>