<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Day>10</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-190818</GTIN>
  <Inker>Don Heck,Don Perlin,A. C. Hollingsworth</Inker>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T01:09:40 [Issue ID 4000-190818] urn:comicvine:4000-190818
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-14 06:49:32. [Issue ID 10341]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="391678" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="361395" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="357899" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="403333" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="416237" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="385578" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="404694" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="413593" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="412007" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="348319" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="393382" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="394570" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="419408" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="401241" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="399635" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="412439" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="509884" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="457874" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="327152" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="394028" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="402437" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="407133" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="362067" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="433141" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="404485" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="441059" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="362159" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="435852" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="477076" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="411768" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="412118" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="494998" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="389732" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="308531" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="420601" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="328757" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Don Heck,Don Perlin,A. C. Hollingsworth</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Comic Media</Publisher>
  <Series>Horrific</Series>
  <Summary>Last Ride!: Death narrates the fate of race-car driver Hugh Lanson. Hugh's face was deformed in a burning car crash. Hugh confronts his rival, Johnnie Rivers. Vickie tells Johnnie to let the confrontation go. Later at a bar, Hugh is approached by a fortune teller named Maggie. He hires her, but she says she sees death for him. Maggie helps Hugh possess Johnnie's body through a magical ritual. He does so, but demons begin to follow him. After the switch, instead of paying her a promised $10,000, Hugh kills Maggie and takes Johnnie's identity. In a race, Hugh finds himself racing in the land of the dead.

Ring of Death: During WWII, Nazi submariners Max and Hans buy an antique jar in Algiers. Max dreams about Princess Narnia, whose betrothed Kasir betrayed her to Genghis Khan in exchange for a ruby he made into a ring. Kasir was cursed for the rest of his life and now Narnia warns Max to give up the ring as well. The submarine sinks to the bottom of the ocean. Before they die, Max and Hans discover the ring was hidden in the jar.

The Coffin: Jud coerces his great-uncle Andrew Marlin--who has a heart attack and dies--into handing over a manuscript indicating their ancestor obtained a fortune in gold during the War of 1812 and hid it in the family house in Salem. While Jud is searching for the gold, his cousin Chris arrives and Jud murders him as well. While burying the corpse, Jud becomes trapped. The police arrive as Jud is dying. They see tracks of a man with a peg-leg (like Captain Marlin had) going into the sea.

Hating Corpse: Nathan loans Charlie money that Charlie can't repay, but offers to forgive the debt if Charlie divorces his wife Thyra and urges her to marry Nathan. Charlie prepares to fight Nathan but is shot to death. Nathan arranges the scene to look like suicide, then leaves to establish an alibi. However, Charlie's hate keeps him alive until Nathan returns to his office: Charlie writes a letter to his wife, kills Nathan, then collapses. The police are puzzled because Charlie died hours before Nathan, yet still appears to have shot him.

</Summary>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/horrific-4/4000-190818/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>13</Count>
  <Title>Last Ride!; Ring of Death; The Coffin; Hating Corpse</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Vickie,Hugh Lanson,Death,Johnnie Rivers,Maggie</Characters>
  <Letterer>John Duffy</Letterer>
  <Editor>Allen Hardy</Editor>
</ComicInfo>