<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Home to Stay! The Complete EC Ray Bradbury Stories</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Volume>2022</Volume>
  <Summary>Earthlings land on a barren abandoned war-torn Mars and find an aging scientist living there with his young family. When the old man dies of a heart attack, they find a nearby cemetery and find the graves of his family. They realized he had built android versions of his deceased family to keep him company and from going insane with loneliness.

The blind victims of an unscrupulous and cruel director lock him and his dog up for several days without food and then release them into a maze with razor blades embedded into the walls. And then turn out the lights.

Charles and Howard Norton, of Norton's Pharmaceutical Company, are having an argument. It seems the company has received an order for one million hypodermic inserts for insulin, but can only make 500,000. Not wanting to lose the order, Charles muses that they could dilute each insert by half, and thereby still provide the one million inserts. Howard refuses, calling it criminal, and Charles calls him a spineless jellyfish! Charles dilutes them anyway and many patients die, with Howard going to jail. When he is released, Howard visits his brother, exacting his revenge in an unusual way.

When Margaret's parents send her for ice cream, she walked through a lot and heard a woman's voice coming from underground, begging for someone to dig her up. When she tells her parents about it, they don't believe her, but they do discuss the Nesbitts. Once, long ago, Mr. Leary was engaged to Helen Nesbitt, who wrote a song for him....but they broke off the engagement. When Margaret's Dad goes to check on the story, no sounds can be heard. Later, Margaret returns to the lot and hears a sad song being sung by the woman...the song Helen once wrote for her father.

Deeply hurt that his wife was in love with another man, George decides to do something that was considered illegal: he paid $10,000 to re-enact his life with a stringless marionette version of Katherine, then murder her as an act of revenge. A cathatic murder....the violent unviolence.....the death without death.....the murdering without murder. Or so he thought.....

A rocket full of Earthlings land on a planet occupied by a mysterious "Soul Well": a place where waiting things.....things that once had flesh.....reside and wait......and wait.

Martha was very suspicious of Leonard. Although she planned to kill him, she had this eerie feeling that something was different about him and she wondered if there were two of him. Soon she discovers that she was partially right; there were six of him!

Two boys witness a ferris wheel at a creepy carnival that can make time go forwards or backwards for the rider depending on which way the wheel spins. A man tries to take advantage of this by riding the wheel backwards 24 times until he is a 10 year boy and then posing as an orphan in order to find and steal a kindly old woman's money who has taken him in. He plans to then ride the wheel forwards 24 times so no one will ever find the culprit. The boys tell the woman, but are not believed, so they wait until the man is on the ferris wheel and sends it into the future....with amazing results.

A madman who hates his wife dismembers his daughter and passes around her body parts to children in a darkened cellar on Halloween.

A very expensive new rocketship, once built for war and now rusting away, relates the story of her glory with Captain Lamb in charge, but also of treachery aboard ship, which the rocket secretly dealt with.

A group of boys watch the launching of a rocket ship, and two of them wish that they were older and could make the trip themselves. They apply for the Interplanetary Patrol and await their decision once they turn 21, but soon Chris gets a surprise that will change his life forever.

Mr. Eckles and his guide visit Safari, Incorporated, an agency that uses a time machine to transport people to the past to hunt dinosaurs. He pays the $10,000 stipend and signs a release......then back 60 million years into the past both he and his guide travel with several other hunters. Their goal: to bag a T-Rex! They are warned to stay on a certain path....otherwise they could change the course of history.....and they do: in a weird way.

When Emperor Yuan discovers that a villager has learned how to create a flying machine, he has him killed so the secret won't fall into the wrong hands.

Acton had killed Arthur Huxley and now tried to remove any clue that he had been at Huxley's home and had committed the crime. But his fixation with eliminating evidence of his presence had its consequences.

In the year 2963 Jerome Kraft lands on a planet to catalog various life forms with four years of provisions. The rocket that dropped him off expects to return in four years but will later be destroyed and all records of Jerome's mission lost. Jerome encounters a primitive society and, using advanced technology, heals the sick and feeds the hungry. The people proclaim him their Savior sent by God, but he tells them that he is simply a man from a far distant star who possesses greater scientific advancement. The high priest orders Jerome brought before him and denounces the idea of other worlds as heresy. He tells Jerome that he must cease working his miracles for the poor and benefit only the wealthy. Jerome refuses. Thousands of years pass before another rocket lands on the planet and they find an advanced civilization. Many people wear curious designs around their neck and the space explorers ask what they represent. They are told it is a religious symbol representing a stretch rack, upon which their Savior was put to death.

Mrs. Morris, at first, thinks nothing of her daughter and a friend playing their game of "invasion". But when Mink starts telling of a Martian named Drill, who is the fore-runner of a Martian invasion of Earth, and Mary discovers that kids of her friends in other parts of the country are playing the same game, she wonders if this is for real.

One of Rodney Simon's lab workers at his company has discovered a way of refining high octane gasoline that produces certain gases, whose molecular structure is unknown.....but, when liquified, creates a new gas that, when mixed with oxygen, provides the force necessary to propel a rocket outside Earth's gravitational field. Although the Moon is the planned landing area, Simon decides Venus to be a better choice.....with dire consequences!

A mother and father take their kids on a million year trip in their boat, past dead cities whose Martian population had been wiped out in a war with the Earth. Finally arriving at one of the cities, the family stops and decides to make their new home there, with Dad promising the kids that they would soon see Martians. After traveling a bit into one of the canals, they peered into the water therein and saw themselves: Martians.

This story basically serves as a allegory for human's ethical progress failing to keep pace with his technological progress. It describes an automatic house that continues to function long after the people that once lived there have been reduced to dust stains on the wall by nuclear holocaust.

Earthlings land on a barren abandoned war-torn Mars and find an aging scientist living there with his young family. When the old man dies of a heart attack, they find a nearby cemetery and find the graves of his family. They realized he had built android versions of his deceased family to keep him company and from going insane with loneliness.

Walter surveys a little white silent town on the edge of a dead Martian sea, wondering what happened to all of its inhabitants. He suddenly hears a phone ringing, but he is too late to answer it.  After this happens twice, he succeeds in answering a phone and finds a Miss Selsor on the other end, and he meets her, only to find that she is fat and ugly. Knowing that she is the only woman alive and he is the only man, he does the only thing he can: he goes back to the bachelor life!

Sneaky Martians disguise themselves as the dead loved ones of astronauts in order to slay them in their sleep.

Chased away from his father's lab while he dissects a body, Stevey finds a stranger in the forest. Wanting to brag, Stevey tells the man all sorts of falsehoods, which he believes. But Stevey soon learns a secret about the stranger he doesn't expect to discover.

A man is so unsatisfied with the commercial attitudes of his fellow morticians, including that of the son-in-law he fruitlessly tried to impart a sense of art, that he builds his own robot mortician to euthanize him and do a job he himself would be proud of.

A nephew murders his uncle for his money and winds up a prisoner in one of his ship-in-a-bottles.

Ezra Deepley is an undertaker who feels he has suffered injustice at the hands of influential town citizens so when they die during an epidemic of disease, Ezra takes advantage of the situation to revenge himself upon their corpses. But soon, the five corpses rise and get their revenge on Ezra.

Blind Betty's dog Jerry is hit by a car but cared for by wealthy Roger Cartwright, who returned her dog to her. Betty was happy to have company and invited him back, which he did and they soon grew quite close. One day, as Roger left her house in his car, he didn't see the truck coming from the other direction. Betty sent Jerry after him and day after day Jerry returned without Roger. Until one day Jerry came in with Roger.

A madman holds a dinner party for five people who have done dirt to him in the past and decapitates them.

The employees of a mortuary are haunted by the spirit of an old woman who refuses to leave until they return her body to her.

Mr. Howard returned to his classroom in time to see some of his students corner a young boy, who then fell out of a window to his death. Stunned, Howard resigned his position because he secretly now hated all children because of what happened. Seven years later, he resumed teaching after a fellow teacher friend of his died. He called his charges less than human....and they resented it. One day he came across some the kids "playing poison".....on sidewalks with names on them that they took for gravestones. From then on, Howard screamed at any kid even playing hopscotch on the sidewalk. One night, as he sat in his home, he saw a skull appear outside his window.....and he continued seeing it, night after night. One evening, he ran outside after the kids responsible, and fell into an excavation ditch. The kids covered him with dirt. In the days that followed, no adult paid much attention to the sidewalk square with the name "M. Howard R.I.P." on it......as the kids continued to play their game of poison!

A man builds an automatic coffin to lower the cost of funerals. The coffin plays music, reads a service, and unfortunately for his sponging kid brother who lies down in it, drains the corpse's blood, injects formaldehyde, and buries itself with shovel attachments on its side.

A mortician avenges himself against perceived slights upon the closed-casket victims of his parlor by violating their bodies until a corpse who isn't quite dead yet overhears his gruesome doings and begs the dead to rise from their graves and stop this horrid man. This they do, and bury parts of Mr. Benedict under a dozen gravestones.

Years ago, a little boy and his young girl friend, Tally played at the beach and built sandcastles together. One day, Tally swam out into the water and drowned, leaving the sandcastle undone, and no closure for the boy. Years later, the little boy, now grown, got married and returned to the beach with his wife, and met with the old lifeguard, who showed him Tally's body in a sack. Once more, the young man returned to the beach, built an entire sandcastle and walked back to his wife, Margaret, leaving the past behind.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-26 17:26:48.  [CVDB1001489]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 22:02:46. [Issue ID 2446395]</Notes>
  <Year>2023</Year>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Writer>Ray Bradbury,Ray Bradbury,Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,William M. Gaines,Carl Wessler</Writer>
  <Penciller>Al Williamson,Angelo Torres,Bernard Krigstein,Frank Frazetta,George Evans,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Joe Orlando,John Severin,Johnny Craig,Reed Crandall,Roy Krenkel,Wally Wood,Will Elder,Joe Orlando,George Evans,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Al Williamson,Frank Frazetta,Roy Krenkel,John Severin,Bernie Krigstein,Johnny Craig,Wally Wood,Wallace Wood,Reed Crandall,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Inker>Al Williamson,Angelo Torres,Bernard Krigstein,Frank Frazetta,George Evans,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Joe Orlando,John Severin,Johnny Craig,Reed Crandall,Roy Krenkel,Wally Wood,Will Elder,Joe Orlando,George Evans,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Al Williamson,Frank Frazetta,Roy Krenkel,Bill Elder,Angelo Torres,Bernie Krigstein,Johnny Craig,Wally Wood,Wallace Wood,Reed Crandall,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Al Feldstein,Al Williamson,Frank Frazetta</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>J. Michael Catron</Editor>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/home-to-stay-the-complete-ray-bradbury-ec-stories-/4000-1001489/</Web>
  <PageCount>330</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>Razor and the Ladies of London Night, 1997 -- London Night -- d514fa9cc8aa50513d452fd39f5a365e -- Anna’s Archive</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="20399328" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2073904" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="3500562" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="3430534" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="3533672" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="3381494" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="3417840" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="3433502" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="3449236" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="4390498" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2753982" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="26273722" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="31069472" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="18876806" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="47946674" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="360274" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="21487178" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="21163626" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="32763972" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="26953800" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="30059518" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="31404518" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="473590" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="32092546" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="30647216" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="31871352" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="33450254" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="33066504" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="32539536" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="32534260" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="652874" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="6550190" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="3410752" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="2933840" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="3641518" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="3654364" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="3852652" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="2120966" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="3711794" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="3187862" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="3030826" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="2162186" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="2781278" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="3007456" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="2153170" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="27171212" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="2562138" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="3781432" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="2097986" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="5516494" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="4387080" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="4899536" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="4899742" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="4600032" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="4621074" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="4513866" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="4209384" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="4985124" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="4489774" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="4429436" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="4496136" />
    <Page Image="61" ImageSize="4425558" />
    <Page Image="62" ImageSize="4872496" />
    <Page Image="63" ImageSize="4213360" />
    <Page Image="64" ImageSize="2735634" />
    <Page Image="65" ImageSize="4847228" />
    <Page Image="66" ImageSize="5091820" />
    <Page Image="67" ImageSize="5130268" />
    <Page Image="68" ImageSize="5084448" />
    <Page Image="69" ImageSize="5080966" />
    <Page Image="70" ImageSize="5079482" />
    <Page Image="71" ImageSize="5044178" />
    <Page Image="72" ImageSize="5478534" />
    <Page Image="73" ImageSize="5295794" />
    <Page Image="74" ImageSize="5590106" />
    <Page Image="75" ImageSize="5640906" />
    <Page Image="76" ImageSize="5460424" />
    <Page Image="77" ImageSize="5482398" />
    <Page Image="78" ImageSize="5092562" />
    <Page Image="79" ImageSize="5646898" />
    <Page Image="80" ImageSize="4937318" />
    <Page Image="81" ImageSize="5000586" />
    <Page Image="82" ImageSize="4406010" />
    <Page Image="83" ImageSize="4508610" />
    <Page Image="84" ImageSize="4488680" />
    <Page Image="85" ImageSize="4343218" />
    <Page Image="86" ImageSize="5377810" />
    <Page Image="87" ImageSize="5659404" />
    <Page Image="88" ImageSize="5348638" />
    <Page Image="89" ImageSize="5206448" />
    <Page Image="90" ImageSize="5340240" />
    <Page Image="91" ImageSize="5202442" />
    <Page Image="92" ImageSize="4253246" />
    <Page Image="93" ImageSize="5323916" />
    <Page Image="94" ImageSize="5430688" />
    <Page Image="95" ImageSize="5277204" />
    <Page Image="96" ImageSize="5254126" />
    <Page Image="97" ImageSize="5284414" />
    <Page Image="98" ImageSize="5542998" />
    <Page Image="99" ImageSize="4310162" />
    <Page Image="100" ImageSize="5449806" />
    <Page Image="101" ImageSize="5626482" />
    <Page Image="102" ImageSize="5307564" />
    <Page Image="103" ImageSize="5121168" />
    <Page Image="104" ImageSize="5401244" />
    <Page Image="105" ImageSize="5416930" />
    <Page Image="106" ImageSize="5501636" />
    <Page Image="107" ImageSize="4569392" />
    <Page Image="108" ImageSize="4826208" />
    <Page Image="109" ImageSize="4934330" />
    <Page Image="110" ImageSize="5398148" />
    <Page Image="111" ImageSize="5258182" />
    <Page Image="112" ImageSize="5289150" />
    <Page Image="113" ImageSize="4716348" />
    <Page Image="114" ImageSize="4302106" />
    <Page Image="115" ImageSize="4958614" />
    <Page Image="116" ImageSize="4662956" />
    <Page Image="117" ImageSize="4574328" />
    <Page Image="118" ImageSize="4752532" />
    <Page Image="119" ImageSize="4839350" />
    <Page Image="120" ImageSize="4710708" />
    <Page Image="121" ImageSize="4835616" />
    <Page Image="122" ImageSize="4179746" />
    <Page Image="123" ImageSize="1217834" />
    <Page Image="124" ImageSize="4920990" />
    <Page Image="125" ImageSize="5237018" />
    <Page Image="126" ImageSize="4945638" />
    <Page Image="127" ImageSize="5117694" />
    <Page Image="128" ImageSize="5002374" />
    <Page Image="129" ImageSize="5068426" />
    <Page Image="130" ImageSize="4624978" />
    <Page Image="131" ImageSize="5127038" />
    <Page Image="132" ImageSize="5171438" />
    <Page Image="133" ImageSize="4628394" />
    <Page Image="134" ImageSize="5167544" />
    <Page Image="135" ImageSize="4667472" />
    <Page Image="136" ImageSize="4902222" />
    <Page Image="137" ImageSize="5098724" />
    <Page Image="138" ImageSize="4492556" />
    <Page Image="139" ImageSize="4289754" />
    <Page Image="140" ImageSize="4394764" />
    <Page Image="141" ImageSize="4289594" />
    <Page Image="142" ImageSize="4570630" />
    <Page Image="143" ImageSize="4479198" />
    <Page Image="144" ImageSize="3212190" />
    <Page Image="145" ImageSize="1474954" />
    <Page Image="146" ImageSize="5110990" />
    <Page Image="147" ImageSize="5342298" />
    <Page Image="148" ImageSize="5491162" />
    <Page Image="149" ImageSize="5309588" />
    <Page Image="150" ImageSize="5411500" />
    <Page Image="151" ImageSize="4657792" />
    <Page Image="152" ImageSize="1935636" />
    <Page Image="153" ImageSize="4840636" />
    <Page Image="154" ImageSize="4631716" />
    <Page Image="155" ImageSize="4833574" />
    <Page Image="156" ImageSize="4947058" />
    <Page Image="157" ImageSize="4761424" />
    <Page Image="158" ImageSize="4596676" />
    <Page Image="159" ImageSize="4516496" />
    <Page Image="160" ImageSize="4993070" />
    <Page Image="161" ImageSize="4678448" />
    <Page Image="162" ImageSize="5030312" />
    <Page Image="163" ImageSize="4966264" />
    <Page Image="164" ImageSize="5087394" />
    <Page Image="165" ImageSize="4799568" />
    <Page Image="166" ImageSize="4260076" />
    <Page Image="167" ImageSize="5002554" />
    <Page Image="168" ImageSize="4746664" />
    <Page Image="169" ImageSize="4847566" />
    <Page Image="170" ImageSize="4782864" />
    <Page Image="171" ImageSize="4753886" />
    <Page Image="172" ImageSize="4886512" />
    <Page Image="173" ImageSize="1349214" />
    <Page Image="174" ImageSize="5388762" />
    <Page Image="175" ImageSize="5069910" />
    <Page Image="176" ImageSize="5402298" />
    <Page Image="177" ImageSize="5636030" />
    <Page Image="178" ImageSize="5794670" />
    <Page Image="179" ImageSize="5076642" />
    <Page Image="180" ImageSize="5202082" />
    <Page Image="181" ImageSize="1908250" />
    <Page Image="182" ImageSize="5208238" />
    <Page Image="183" ImageSize="5169012" />
    <Page Image="184" ImageSize="4841226" />
    <Page Image="185" ImageSize="4823732" />
    <Page Image="186" ImageSize="4915006" />
    <Page Image="187" ImageSize="4791422" />
    <Page Image="188" ImageSize="4288876" />
    <Page Image="189" ImageSize="4800764" />
    <Page Image="190" ImageSize="4353262" />
    <Page Image="191" ImageSize="4538350" />
    <Page Image="192" ImageSize="4332628" />
    <Page Image="193" ImageSize="4666850" />
    <Page Image="194" ImageSize="4310254" />
    <Page Image="195" ImageSize="3685160" />
    <Page Image="196" ImageSize="5516352" />
    <Page Image="197" ImageSize="5296102" />
    <Page Image="198" ImageSize="5423134" />
    <Page Image="199" ImageSize="5311944" />
    <Page Image="200" ImageSize="5575420" />
    <Page Image="201" ImageSize="5443564" />
    <Page Image="202" ImageSize="5154958" />
    <Page Image="203" ImageSize="4017292" />
    <Page Image="204" ImageSize="4446322" />
    <Page Image="205" ImageSize="4084362" />
    <Page Image="206" ImageSize="4391804" />
    <Page Image="207" ImageSize="4601894" />
    <Page Image="208" ImageSize="4273770" />
    <Page Image="209" ImageSize="4100444" />
    <Page Image="210" ImageSize="4056496" />
    <Page Image="211" ImageSize="5331168" />
    <Page Image="212" ImageSize="13895716" />
    <Page Image="213" ImageSize="5380394" />
    <Page Image="214" ImageSize="5725168" />
    <Page Image="215" ImageSize="5287694" />
    <Page Image="216" ImageSize="5263886" />
    <Page Image="217" ImageSize="5971256" />
    <Page Image="218" ImageSize="5638628" />
    <Page Image="219" ImageSize="1933074" />
    <Page Image="220" ImageSize="5986474" />
    <Page Image="221" ImageSize="5567270" />
    <Page Image="222" ImageSize="5515072" />
    <Page Image="223" ImageSize="5630512" />
    <Page Image="224" ImageSize="5652004" />
    <Page Image="225" ImageSize="5374606" />
    <Page Image="226" ImageSize="5018046" />
    <Page Image="227" ImageSize="5530208" />
    <Page Image="228" ImageSize="5245220" />
    <Page Image="229" ImageSize="5322056" />
    <Page Image="230" ImageSize="5160186" />
    <Page Image="231" ImageSize="5188116" />
    <Page Image="232" ImageSize="5575590" />
    <Page Image="233" ImageSize="5544260" />
    <Page Image="234" ImageSize="4741348" />
    <Page Image="235" ImageSize="5264992" />
    <Page Image="236" ImageSize="5528084" />
    <Page Image="237" ImageSize="5693960" />
    <Page Image="238" ImageSize="5381046" />
    <Page Image="239" ImageSize="5381888" />
    <Page Image="240" ImageSize="5297504" />
    <Page Image="241" ImageSize="4423912" />
    <Page Image="242" ImageSize="4681010" />
    <Page Image="243" ImageSize="4698226" />
    <Page Image="244" ImageSize="4740220" />
    <Page Image="245" ImageSize="4866742" />
    <Page Image="246" ImageSize="4651236" />
    <Page Image="247" ImageSize="5226168" />
    <Page Image="248" ImageSize="4922232" />
    <Page Image="249" ImageSize="4527550" />
    <Page Image="250" ImageSize="4631062" />
    <Page Image="251" ImageSize="4779986" />
    <Page Image="252" ImageSize="4759372" />
    <Page Image="253" ImageSize="4550156" />
    <Page Image="254" ImageSize="4811010" />
    <Page Image="255" ImageSize="5046358" />
    <Page Image="256" ImageSize="4284284" />
    <Page Image="257" ImageSize="4881126" />
    <Page Image="258" ImageSize="5320560" />
    <Page Image="259" ImageSize="5312090" />
    <Page Image="260" ImageSize="5498890" />
    <Page Image="261" ImageSize="5424018" />
    <Page Image="262" ImageSize="5311418" />
    <Page Image="263" ImageSize="5308968" />
    <Page Image="264" ImageSize="3815304" />
    <Page Image="265" ImageSize="1482902" />
    <Page Image="266" ImageSize="5348246" />
    <Page Image="267" ImageSize="5005212" />
    <Page Image="268" ImageSize="5380384" />
    <Page Image="269" ImageSize="5355774" />
    <Page Image="270" ImageSize="5079572" />
    <Page Image="271" ImageSize="5191536" />
    <Page Image="272" ImageSize="4198706" />
    <Page Image="273" ImageSize="5243540" />
    <Page Image="274" ImageSize="5173902" />
    <Page Image="275" ImageSize="5165248" />
    <Page Image="276" ImageSize="5526910" />
    <Page Image="277" ImageSize="5605092" />
    <Page Image="278" ImageSize="5181018" />
    <Page Image="279" ImageSize="4646784" />
    <Page Image="280" ImageSize="5275876" />
    <Page Image="281" ImageSize="5480440" />
    <Page Image="282" ImageSize="5212256" />
    <Page Image="283" ImageSize="5610942" />
    <Page Image="284" ImageSize="5517228" />
    <Page Image="285" ImageSize="5612242" />
    <Page Image="286" ImageSize="4664930" />
    <Page Image="287" ImageSize="4881558" />
    <Page Image="288" ImageSize="4909550" />
    <Page Image="289" ImageSize="5169554" />
    <Page Image="290" ImageSize="4691298" />
    <Page Image="291" ImageSize="4729196" />
    <Page Image="292" ImageSize="4639614" />
    <Page Image="293" ImageSize="4387098" />
    <Page Image="294" ImageSize="4514334" />
    <Page Image="295" ImageSize="4858114" />
    <Page Image="296" ImageSize="4395664" />
    <Page Image="297" ImageSize="4503030" />
    <Page Image="298" ImageSize="4427872" />
    <Page Image="299" ImageSize="4395934" />
    <Page Image="300" ImageSize="4564922" />
    <Page Image="301" ImageSize="4649384" />
    <Page Image="302" ImageSize="5153462" />
    <Page Image="303" ImageSize="5666548" />
    <Page Image="304" ImageSize="4375928" />
    <Page Image="305" ImageSize="4762550" />
    <Page Image="306" ImageSize="4618772" />
    <Page Image="307" ImageSize="1407824" />
    <Page Image="308" ImageSize="3138132" />
    <Page Image="309" ImageSize="1925464" />
    <Page Image="310" ImageSize="2754604" />
    <Page Image="311" ImageSize="3307838" />
    <Page Image="312" ImageSize="2931258" />
    <Page Image="313" ImageSize="3756016" />
    <Page Image="314" ImageSize="2881136" />
    <Page Image="315" ImageSize="3639670" />
    <Page Image="316" ImageSize="2844202" />
    <Page Image="317" ImageSize="2145540" />
    <Page Image="318" ImageSize="2961028" />
    <Page Image="319" ImageSize="2825338" />
    <Page Image="320" ImageSize="21277688" />
    <Page Image="321" ImageSize="2085696" />
    <Page Image="322" ImageSize="2004852" />
    <Page Image="323" ImageSize="2075068" />
    <Page Image="324" ImageSize="7432286" />
    <Page Image="325" ImageSize="1865882" />
    <Page Image="326" ImageSize="2168444" />
    <Page Image="327" ImageSize="512598" />
    <Page Image="328" ImageSize="17788554" />
    <Page Image="329" ImageSize="7516018" />
  </Pages>
  <Title>The Long Years!; Blind Alleys; The Jellyfish!; The Screaming Woman!; Punishment Without Crime; The One Who Waits; Surprise Package; The Black Ferris!; The October Game; I, Rocket; King of the Grey Spaces!; A Sound of Thunder; The Flying Machine; Touch and Go!; He Walked Among Us; Outcast of the Stars; Zero Hour; Home To Stay!; Mad Journey!; The Million Year Picnic; There Will Come Soft Rains...; The Long Years!; The Silent Towns; Mars Is Heaven!; A Lesson In Anatomy!!; A Work of Art!; Model Nephew; A Strange Undertaking...; What the Dog Dragged In!; Just Desserts!; There Was an Old Woman!; Let's Play Poison!; The Coffin!; The Handler; The Small Assassin!; The Lake</Title>
  <Genre>Historical,Horror-suspense,Crime,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Format>Collection</Format>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>