<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Life's Great Rewards; My Reality; Sushi Lesson; Bunnygrunt High; Flip Flop; The Adventures of Pezgal; M.R.E. Blues: A True ROTC Story; Pivotal Scenes From My Life As A Stage Actress</Title>
  <Series>Action Girl Comics</Series>
  <Number>10</Number>
  <Count>19</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-12 08:39:30.  [CVDB142016]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 11:59:49. [Issue ID 304899]</Notes>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <Writer>Anastasia Moreno,Sarah Dyer,Stephanie Gladden</Writer>
  <Penciller>Anastasia Moreno,Sarah Dyer,Stephanie Gladden</Penciller>
  <Inker>Anastasia Moreno,Sarah Dyer,Stephanie Gladden</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Sarah Dyer,Stephanie Gladden</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Sarah Dyer</Editor>
  <Publisher>Slave Labor</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/action-girl-comics-10/4000-142016/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="643546" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="546182" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="412230" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="548696" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="666422" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="531542" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="498278" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="470738" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="554382" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="612672" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="350404" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="597584" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="439158" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="549266" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="568754" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="604388" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="548978" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="586028" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="493264" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="806606" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="473616" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="584010" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="647832" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="751940" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="632308" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="625342" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="440544" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="939150" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Life's Great Rewards: Author recounts many of her favorite things ever - like soda, her first stuffed animal, leopard prints, kitties, old 1910s-1920s girls' adventure series books, Sanrio, video games, valentines, cooking, tiny fake food, and more.

My Reality: Author tells how she plans to spend the rest of her life secretly illustrating every aspect of her ordinary life, telling the pure truth in an illustrated diary that she thinks will be found after her death, then published and hailed as a masterpiece.

Sushi Lesson: Alky, Melba and Terry stop for some BBQ, but leave when they realize the fresh meat is probably from the pony that the BBQ joint no longer has (they used to give free pony rides on Saturdays).  Instead they go for sushi.  Terry is obnoxious to May and Kayobo who run the sushi restaurant, so because "the customer is always right" they allow Terry to eat a mouthful of hot wasabi that he at first thought was guacamole, and he then explodes in pain, literally breathing fire.

Bunnygrunt High: Three high school students are in Saturday detention.  At 8:00 a.m. Jen is writing in her diary about how she hopes the other two - the geek, Matt, and the snob, Karen - won't try to talk to her.  By 2:00 p.m. they've decided to form a band, and by 10:00 p.m. they're playing in a band.

Flip Flop: Author recounts her various dreams of wanting to be a writer, a radical lawyer, a celebrity, a great chef, or a saint, but most of all wanted to be a cartoonist.

The Adventures of Pezgal: PJ and Ant are working in their candy store - Fun Stuff - when Monstroso attacks.  PJ transforms into Pezgal to defend the city.  She shoots peppermint Pez candy at him, and discovers he wasn't attacking, he just wanted something for his bad breath.  Instead of sending him away, they turn Monstroso into an interactive roller coaster ride that costs 50 Pez candy pieces to ride.

M.R.E. Blues: A True ROTC Story: Author recounts an experience in ROTC when she and several other ROTC members were eating a MRE (Meal Ready-to-Eat), which have a notoriously long shelf life.  The year was 1996, and the M&amp;M candy in the meal had an Olympic logo on the bag, so they thought perhaps they had gotten lucky and gotten new MRE's since the 1996 Atlanta Olympics were going on at the time.  A closer look, however, revealed the M&amp;M package was commemorating the 1988 Seoul Olympics.

Pivotal Scenes From My Life As A Stage Actress: Author recounts her childhood experience as a minion of the evil Morgan Le Fay in a stage production of Camelot.  Before the show she peeked out through the curtain.  people notice and applauded, so she came out on stage and took a bow.  The orchestra director shooed her off stage, and the director yelled at her.

</Summary>
</ComicInfo>