<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<Colorist>Dylan Teague,Jim Boswell</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Nick Percival</CoverArtist>
	<Day>15</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1055617</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Nick Percival,Patrick Goddard,Simon Parr (PYE)</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>5</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:35 [Issue ID 4000-1055617] urn:comicvine:4000-1055617</Notes>
	<Number>2382</Number>
	<PageCount>31</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1470112" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1580824"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="893063"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="941549"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="807578"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1007867"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="975793"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="799888"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1237922"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1673436"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1671978"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1342955"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1453671"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1462954"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="747566"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1703494"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1066531"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1012577"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1230543"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1223109"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1060638"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1003760"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="929109"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1010976"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="937968"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1288353"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="983982"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1193952"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1101804"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1096360"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="841682"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Nick Percival,Patrick Goddard,Simon Parr (PYE)</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>I am Tharg The Mighty, enemy of mundanity and scourge of Thrill-suckers everywhere! 

Welcome, my Squaxx, to the latest blast of zarjazosity courtesy of the Galaxy’s Greatest Comic - pure, undiluted graphic excitement beamed directly into your eyeballs. This prog we’ve got two new stories starting - future lawman Judge Dredd investigates a mythical monster in Iron Teeth by Ken Niemand and Nick Percival, and those microscopic gut-champions Intestinauts are back for another adventure in Busted Flush by the regular creative team of Arthur Wyatt and Pye Parr. Plus there’s more Brink and Proteus Vex, and Aquila reaches the climax to its current arc!

Joining this awe-inspiring issue on the shelves this week is Judge Dredd Megazine 468, which is another ghafflebette delight - Mike Carroll and John Higgins reunite for a new Dreadnoughts mini-series, plus there’s a complete Dredd story from the Edginton and D’Israeli droids alongside Armitage, Harrower Squad and DeMarco, P.I. Add to that chats with creators such as RM Guera, Giulia Brusco and Laura Helsby, as well as former droids like Wayne Reynolds and Jaspre Bark, the start of a new IDW Dredd, and much, much more!

*Judge Dredd » Iron Teeth (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, where poverty and overcrowding is rife and tensions run a constant knife-edge. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*Aquila » The Rivers of Hades, Book Two: PART 1 (Part 6)*
Following Spartacus’s failed revolt against his Roman masters, his rebel army was crucified. Amongst these was the slave-turned-gladiator AQUILA, who cried out to the gods for vengeance - and was answered by Ammit the Devourer, a deity that gifted him with immortality in return for keeping her fed with evil men’s souls. Now, Aquila has travelled into Hades and retrieved the spirit of Nero, who knows Ammit’s location...

*INTESTINAUTS » Busted Flush (Part 1)*
For stomach upsets, future technology has developed nano-robots called INTESTINAUTS, who fight parasites in the gut. These micro-droids are ingested orally, then once their brave battle against the various horrors that can be found in the stomach is over, they take the Big Flush, ready to be uploaded back to headquarters, where their accrued knowledge of the enemy will help them in future missions...

*Brink » Consumed (Part 5)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 8)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 2382</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2382-prog-2382/4000-1055617/</Web>
	<Writer>Arthur Wyatt,Dan Abnett,Gordon Rennie,Kenneth Niemand,Michael Carroll</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>