<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Xenozoic Tales</Series>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <Count>14</Count>
  <Title>In the Dreamtime...; Foul Weather</Title>
  <Volume>1987</Volume>
  <Genre>Adventure,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>*Publication information*
Originally published by Kitchen Sink, "In the Dreamtime..." was reprinted in 2003 as part of the two-volume Xenozoic Tales set from Dark Horse, collecting all of the Mark Schultz stories, and again in 2010, by Flesk, in a single volume simply titled Xenozoic. It was not part of the IDW Artists Edition, which picked up with number 9. "Foul Weather" was not reprinted in the Flesk volume, nor were any of Steve Stiles' contributions to the series.

*Content*
"In the Dreamtime..." opens with Cadillac Jack teaching Hannah Dundee how to drive as he delivers directives to a road gang in the Lake Machtando region as a favor to Mustapha Cairo. However, the duo arrives to find the road crew and surrounding wildlife mysteriously dead. Jack and Hannah set up camp nearby, but both experience mysterious dreams that alert them to the immediate physical danger of poisonous gas. The pair manage to escape.

The second story, "Foul Weather," Jack follows thief Vice Terhune after an successful raid on the city's treasure vaults. Terhune returns to his hideout, an old lighthouse, where his lover, Mikla van Ermine, awaits. As the weather worsens, she attempts to persuade Terhune to remain, while he insists on leaving before Jack catches him. A confrontation ensues between Jack, Terhune, and Mikla, who Terjune erroneously thinks is in league with Jack. However, the weather develops into a hurricane which penetrates the walls of the lighthouse. In the end, Vice Terhune is apparently swept away, and his loot from the treasure vaults is revealed to be a case full of cash, useless in the Xenozoic world.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:02:27. [Issue ID 45738]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Kitchen Sink Press</Publisher>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Year>1989</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(january 1989)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Jack Tenrec,Hannah Dundee,Lorraine Dahlgren,Mustapha Cairo</Characters>
  <Penciller>Mark Schultz,Steve Stiles,Mark Schultz,Steve Stiles</Penciller>
  <Inker>Mark Schultz,Steve Stiles,Mark Schultz,Steve Stiles</Inker>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>Jack Tenrec,Hannah Dundee,Lorraine Dahlgren,Mustapha Cairo</Tags>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/xenozoic-tales-8-in-the-dreamtime-foul-weather/4000-30771/</Web>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Colorist>Ray Fehrenbach</Colorist>
  <Writer>Mark Schultz,Mark Schultz</Writer>
  <Letterer>Denise Prowell,Denise Prowell</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>