<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>various citizens of Mouse-Town,crime school students,police chief of Mouse-Town,Mugger Mouse,various thuggish cats,Mighty Mouse,Mitzi Mouse,crime school teacher,mayor of Mouse-Town,Professor Ohm,The Claw,juvenile delinquent mice</Characters>
  <Editor>Tom Morrison</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-227299</GTIN>
  <Inker>Art Bartsch,Jim Tyer,Connie Rasinski,Jim Tyer,Art Bartsch</Inker>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T01:08:35 [Issue ID 4000-227299] urn:comicvine:4000-227299
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 21:36:59. [Issue ID 241842]</Notes>
  <Number>40</Number>
  <PageCount>100</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="933304" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="929820" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1081964" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="982856" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="952732" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="977781" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="924557" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1014052" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="910754" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="938129" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="943790" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="995800" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="932010" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="996168" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="924289" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1009562" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="939678" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1019774" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="943546" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="998918" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="944646" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="971335" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="923796" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1029039" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="913172" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="982588" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="915426" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="930641" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="942564" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="996037" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="897865" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1010358" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="925182" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="987681" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="965788" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="940826" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="855197" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="961247" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="980825" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="916442" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="855259" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="1034102" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="1006566" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="982660" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="906317" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="1047312" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="1010452" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="1008747" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="909938" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="1053954" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="981233" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="969276" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="935104" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="1082582" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="1026507" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="1009214" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="963942" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="1037967" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="1004233" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="1011770" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="904756" />
    <Page Image="61" ImageSize="1076412" />
    <Page Image="62" ImageSize="1018178" />
    <Page Image="63" ImageSize="846471" />
    <Page Image="64" ImageSize="880131" />
    <Page Image="65" ImageSize="910831" />
    <Page Image="66" ImageSize="876573" />
    <Page Image="67" ImageSize="981008" />
    <Page Image="68" ImageSize="894014" />
    <Page Image="69" ImageSize="910702" />
    <Page Image="70" ImageSize="896558" />
    <Page Image="71" ImageSize="949716" />
    <Page Image="72" ImageSize="889709" />
    <Page Image="73" ImageSize="874688" />
    <Page Image="74" ImageSize="823439" />
    <Page Image="75" ImageSize="977460" />
    <Page Image="76" ImageSize="913251" />
    <Page Image="77" ImageSize="972061" />
    <Page Image="78" ImageSize="868193" />
    <Page Image="79" ImageSize="884591" />
    <Page Image="80" ImageSize="922205" />
    <Page Image="81" ImageSize="932092" />
    <Page Image="82" ImageSize="871960" />
    <Page Image="83" ImageSize="1036946" />
    <Page Image="84" ImageSize="963583" />
    <Page Image="85" ImageSize="974401" />
    <Page Image="86" ImageSize="926961" />
    <Page Image="87" ImageSize="962525" />
    <Page Image="88" ImageSize="931622" />
    <Page Image="89" ImageSize="965622" />
    <Page Image="90" ImageSize="953660" />
    <Page Image="91" ImageSize="984703" />
    <Page Image="92" ImageSize="961981" />
    <Page Image="93" ImageSize="939574" />
    <Page Image="94" ImageSize="987034" />
    <Page Image="95" ImageSize="977255" />
    <Page Image="96" ImageSize="977157" />
    <Page Image="97" ImageSize="984331" />
    <Page Image="98" ImageSize="926621" />
    <Page Image="99" ImageSize="934474" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Art Bartsch,Jim Tyer,Connie Rasinski,Jim Tyer,Art Bartsch</Penciller>
  <Publisher>St. John</Publisher>
  <Series>Paul Terry's Mighty Mouse Comics</Series>
  <Summary>The Hoodlum Gang: A baby mouse in a stroller accidently rolls downhill from Mouse-Town to Cat-Town, falls into the clutches of The Claw and Professor Ohm, and is raised as a tough juvenile delinquent. Taking the name “Mugger Mouse”, he is sent back by the cats to corrupt the youth of Mouse-Town. As crime rises under the influence of Mugger Mouse, Mighty Mouse is left to wonder how even he can combat rampant juvenile delinquency - especially when the young punks dismiss his efforts with a resounding "Drop dead!"

At Grips with the Lava Men: Lava Men, flaming bipedal creatures from "another world beneath the crust of the Earth", emerge from suddenly-created volcanoes and proceed to overrun and destroy the territories of both mice and cats. Mighty Mouse finds these magma-made monsters too hot to handle.

Wonderful Papa: Papa shows the boys how salmon can swim up a waterfall.

Soft-Touch Gandy: Gandy gives - a bit more than he intended.

Let's Be Kind: Papa tells the boys that it's "Be Kind to Animals Week" and, as expected, the boys overdo it to Papa's great dismay.

Choo Choo: While on a train trip, Dimwit follows the instructions of every railroad employee he encounters - but still gets thrown off the train.

The Serenade: Sourpuss hopes to woo a senorita.

Lights, Action, Camera: Sourpuss decides to make a movie to showcase his acting and directing talents, but his efforts are overshadowed by Gandy's dumb luck in errantly aiming the camera at a robbery, leading to the capture of the crooks.

Pulling Stumps: Farmer Gray's efforts to uproot a tree stump by the strength of his horse are thwarted when the chain used for pulling the stump snaps. Enter Dimwit with a substitute for the chain.

The Flirt: As a practical joke, Heckle and Jeckle frame Chesty as a masher.

Squirrel Rescue: Sourpuss' prank on Gandy backfires, but succeeds in rescuing Gloria's pet squirrel.

Peeping Rudy: Rudy hides in the bushes to eavesdrop on Dinky and Dotty, and is embarrassingly found out.

Terror In the Tropics: On a tropical island populated by peaceful mice – and where cats are unknown – shipwrecked cats Black Mike and his unnamed henchman begin the hoax of “Kuloo The Powerful”, a mountaintop-god who demands a daily sacrificial mouse. This frightful ruse has worked for “many moons”, until the chance arrival of Mighty Mouse.

Shamus the Leprechaun: Shamus the Leprechaun watches over all the animal citizens of an Irish woodland village, planting lucky shamrocks, making shoes, and doing good deeds. No Good Bear, a practitioner of evil magic, transforms himself into a giant bear, and terrorizes the village.

The Wolf's Pardon: Released from prison after ten years, the Big Bad Wolf finds that "life on the outside" ain't what it used to be.

Duel or Snow Duel: Mighty Mouse and Oil Can Harry take their perpetual duel to the arctic, where Harry has frozen Pearl Pureheart in a block of ice, and Mighty Mouse is trapped by an extraordinary bolt of lightning.

Underground Tyrants: Posing as a stage magician, Professor Ohm puts a theatre-full of mice into a chemically-induced sleep, and kidnaps them for The Claw. Once inside Claw Territory, the mice are forced into hard labor mining an explosive mineral ore. Mighty Mouse’s search and rescue efforts are stymied by a peace treaty with the cats, who are more than pleased to show him everything in Clawville… except the remote mine. Can one brave little mouse get word of their captivity out to their hero?

Loosened Log: As Little Roquefort walks across a log bridge, Percy tries to dump him in the river.

</Summary>
  <Tags>Jeckle,Professor Ohm,Terry Bears,Rudy the Rooster,Farmer Al Falfa,Chesty,Oil Can Harry,Dimwit,Dinky Duck,Mighty Mouse,Heckle,Pearl Pureheart,Sourpuss,Big Bad Wolf,Mitzi Mouse,Little Roquefort,Percy Puss,Three Little Pigs,Red Riding Hood,Gandy Goose</Tags>
  <Teams>Terry Bears,Three Little Pigs</Teams>
  <Volume>1951</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/mighty-mouse-40/4000-227299/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>50</Count>
  <Title>The Hoodlum Gang; At Grips with the Lava Men; Wonderful Papa; Soft-Touch Gandy; Let's Be Kind; Choo Choo; The Serenade; Lights, Action, Camera; Pulling Stumps; The Flirt; Squirrel Rescue; Peeping Rudy; Terror In the Tropics; Shamus the Leprechaun; The Wolf's Pardon; Duel or Snow Duel; Underground Tyrants; Loosened Log</Title>
  <Genre>Superhero,Anthropomorphic-funny animals,Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>