<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Shop Till You Drop Dead Part 2</Title>
  <Series>Army of Darkness: Shop Till You Drop Dead</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Summary>It's an "End of the World Sale" at S-Mart! All living creatures must go to make room for the new Deadite models. The Evil Spirit from the woods now inhabits the aisles of S- Mart and Ash finds himself caught between possessed bargain shoppers and demonic store mascots. Join intrepid Houswares clerk Ash and his inept trio of minimum wage co-workers as they try to stop the Deadite infestation, save the girls, and destroy the Necronomicon before Armageddon is unleashed at a bargain price!

Ash, Buck and Iggy are fighty back a wave of Deadites at S-mart. As they are fleeing for the basement Ash spys the Sapmaster 3000, the ultimate chainsaw. While he is boasting about his new weapon Iggy hits him in the face. Ash and Buck learn that Iggy now has a possessed hand and shoot it off, making Iggy pass out.

When Iggy comes to he discovers that Ash and buck have attached a pruner to his arm. The three are then jumped by Mini Ashes and Mini Mindis. They are then tied up and the Mini Ashes force themselve into Iggy and Buck. Iggy grows a second evil head which Ash quickly cuts off. Buck how ever drinks too heavly for his would be possessers and has to pass them out the other end.

Next the Three co workers find the basement but discover possessed Shelia and Mindi. The basement attacks the men and reveals Mr. Smart and the Necronomicon.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-01 13:28:20.  [CVDB111529]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 09:50:09. [Issue ID 304464]</Notes>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Writer>James Kuhoric</Writer>
  <Penciller>Nick Bradshaw</Penciller>
  <Colorist>Jim Charalampidis</Colorist>
  <Publisher>Devil's Due Publishing</Publisher>
  <Genre>Horror,Action,Comedy</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/army-of-darkness-shop-till-you-drop-dead-2/4000-111529/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Ash</Characters>
  <Teams>Deadites,Mini-Ashes</Teams>
  <Locations>Detroit</Locations>
  <ScanInformation>(2 covers) (Digital-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="638066" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="614756" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="433646" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="506464" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="422794" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="497358" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="461448" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="410116" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="426100" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="438500" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="481548" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="498352" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="581952" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="513176" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="515018" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="435066" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="433332" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="520992" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="451192" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="515466" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="609202" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="492118" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="495420" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="649696" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="587280" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>