<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Palestine</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Title>A Boy in the Rain; Jenin; Roadblock; Nablus; Sugar; Lucky Reunion; Tel Aviv; Through Other Eyes; Pilgrimage; Rewind; Handicapped; The Boys, part four; The Boys, part three; The Boys, part two; The Boys, part one; Jabalia; Edward Said; One Shekel to Gaza Town; Tomatoes; Sons of the Curfew; Black Coffee; Law; Rooms; Refugeeland; Still One of the Boys; Hijab; Women; Getting the Story; Chicago; Ramallah; Moderate Pressure Part 2; The Tough and the Dead; A Palestinian Joke; Moderate Pressure Part 1; Ansar III; Where is Saburo?; Brother for a Day; The Bucket; A Thousand Words; Remind Me; Hebron; Carry On, Doctor; Public &amp; Private Wounds (Nablus); Taxi; Valley of Kidron; Eye of the Beholder; Return; Blind Dates; Cairo</Title>
  <Volume>2001</Volume>
  <Genre>Humor,Biography,Drama</Genre>
  <Summary>A Boy in the Rain: Sacco recalls his acquaintance with a religious Oxford student in Jerusalem as well as some conversations he had with others concerning the peace process. The last sequence describes the time he saw some Israeli soldiers make a boy stand out in the pouring rain while they questioned him. This for him sums up the possible future outcomes for peace in the area.

Jenin: In Jenin, Sacco talks to a Shakespeare-quoting man who not only is extremely cynical about peace coming from any side in the conflict, but is extremely cynical about the peace process itself.

Roadblock: Sacco is stuck in a taxi during a roadblock with a screaming baby nearby and fighter-bombers circling overhead.

Nablus: Sacco witnesses Israeli soldiers accost several vendors and apprehend one of them in Nablus.

Sugar: Sacco talks to a woman who has an Australian lover she feels she could never marry.

Lucky Reunion: In Nablus, Sacco encounters Jabril, one of his friends from the Balata refugee camp.

Tel Aviv: The two women enjoy the sunny day in Tel Aviv. They give their opinions on the viability of the peace process and express fatigue at Israel having to apologize all the time.

Through Other Eyes: Sacco acts as a guide for two Israeli women in the Old City. He manages to convince one of them to walk with him through the Arab market.

Pilgrimage: Sameh and Joe visit the grave of the first person killed in the intifada. They then interview a refugee from 1948 who experienced firsthand the Jewish atrocities. Later, they spend the evening with Sameh's family. The following day, they talk to a woman who had two sons shot dead by Israeli soldiers. Finally, in Rafah, a family details how they were displaced after Egypt and Israel signed the peace agreement and redrew the border.

Rewind: Sameh and Joe get hold of a forbidden video that shows amateur footage of the intifada. They wind up going home past curfew on foot.

Handicapped: Sameh details the serious obstacles in developing programs for the handicapped in Gaza.

The Boys, part four: Sacco interviews a seventeen-year-old who was shot by men in Arabic dress. A YMCA program head wonders how the large number of injured youth in Gaza can be integrated into society.

The Boys, part three: Firas, a fifteen year old, details how he got involved with the "Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine" resistance group, and what he experienced after that.

The Boys, part two: Mohamed and Husein relate what changed for them in the first few days of the intifada.

The Boys, part one: Mohamed and Husein retrace for Joe the route the mourners took that marked the beginning of the first intifada in 1987.

Jabalia: Sameh is the perfect host for Sacco as he gives him an intensive tour of the Jabalia refugee camp.

Edward Said: Sacco spends the night at Larry's place in Gaza Town.

One Shekel to Gaza Town: Sacco, who is leaving the camp, gets his taxi fare paid by Ammar.

Tomatoes: Sacco visits a desk factory and meets with some tomato farmers.

Sons of the Curfew: Ibrahim talks about his son and is offended by the illustration of a Palestinian in  Sacco's guide book.

Black Coffee: Sacco talks to Ammar's uncle, who was a Palestinian refugee from 1948.

Law: Sacco talks to an Islamic lawyer who is defending an honor killing. One man sitting nearby asks Sacco several tough questions, including what good will his writings about Palestine do.

Rooms: In Gaza's Nuseirat Camp, Sacco visits a roofless house and talks to several people.

Refugeeland: Sacco tours a refugee camp in the Gaza Strip and sees some shocking poverty.

Still One of the Boys: In the Jabalia camp, a blind man tells a joke.

Hijab: Sacco talks about how the hijab ties in with the intifada, Islam and women.

Women: A few feminists talk to Sacco about the treatment of women vis-a-vis the Arabic culture of Palestine.

Getting the Story: Sacco tries to find out more details about an Israeli settler attack in Hebron.

Chicago: A Palestinian woman who lived eleven years in the U.S. talks to Sacco.

Ramallah: In Ramallah, Sacco witnesses a demonstration that turns violent.

Moderate Pressure Part 2: Sacco interviews a man who experienced days of being bound with sleep deprivation.

The Tough and the Dead: A Palestinian woman talks about the torture she experienced while being held by the Shin Bet. In addition, Sacco attends the funeral procession of Mustafa Akkawi, who died after two weeks of Israeli interrogation.

A Palestinian Joke: What happens when a CIA agent, a KGB agent and a Shin Bet agent walk along a forest and see a rabbit?

Moderate Pressure Part 1: Sacco talks to a few people who experienced torture under custody of the Shin Bet.

Ansar III: Sacco relates the representative stories of three alumni of the Ansar III prison.

Where is Saburo?: Saburo finally comes back from an outing at Camp One.

Brother for a Day: Joe meets Khaled, who has soldiers looking for him. Both go to Kalandia and meet the family of Khaled's friend. Sacco attempts to convince them that many Israelis don't agree with the occupation.

The Bucket: Sami takes Sacco to a village east of the Green Line. He hears several stories from the villagers about injustices committed by settlers and soldiers alike.

A Thousand Words: Sacco and Saburo come across a Palestinian demonstration on Nablus Road.

Remind Me: A text piece accompanied by several illustrations. In the Balata refugee camp, Sacco gives a little background history on how the camp came into existence. Sacco stays overnight in the house of one family and with some difficulty visits a school.

Hebron: Sacco visits the Cave of Machpelah, accompanied by a Palestinian tour guide. The guide is taunted by a small group of settlers.

Carry On, Doctor: A medical technician details some of the tactics Israeli soldiers used when inside their hospital.

Public &amp; Private Wounds (Nablus): In Nablus, Sacco attracts a small crowd. He is taken to a hospital to see several Palestinian gunfire casualties.

Taxi: Sacco details what his taxi rides are like to various Palestinian locations.

Valley of Kidron: Sacco meets a kid who claims that settlers kicked out his family from their home in Silwan.

Eye of the Beholder: In Silwan, Sacco comes across a demonstration against the settlements and a demonstration in favor of them.

Return: Sacco talks to a young Jewish man in Jerusalem and gives a brief rundown on the origins of Zionism. He meets a Palestinian refugee from 1948.

Blind Dates: Sacco meets a man in the West Bank who welcomes him with open arms. He goes on to contrast the widespread exposure the Leon Klinghoffer/ Achille Lauro affair received with the lack of U.S. media coverage of the oppression of Palestinians.

Cairo: Sacco talks to a couple of hotel receptionists in Cairo. While one is apolitical, the other has strong feelings against Israel.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-04-25 08:35:41. [Issue ID 627970]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Year>2001</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Collection</Format>
  <ScanInformation>(february 1993)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Jewish Lady,Israeli,Irishman,Joe Sacco,Palestinian Boy</Characters>
  <Writer>J. Sacco,Joe Sacco</Writer>
  <Penciller>J. Sacco,Joe Sacco</Penciller>
  <Inker>J. Sacco,Joe Sacco</Inker>
  <Letterer>J. Sacco,Joe Sacco</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>