<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Satan</Characters>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-204117</GTIN>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:13 [Issue ID 4000-204117] urn:comicvine:4000-204117
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:31. [Issue ID 136593]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>Monster of the Mist: Marine biologist Dr. Mornay discovers a giant sea serpent and keeps it close to study the creature. Mornay feeds the beast with sheep, but only teaches it a lust for blood. Mornay’s son and his fiancée arrive and help him prepare a deadly bait.

Crime Circus: An ensemble of circus artistes decides to make some big money and operates as a gang of criminals. Masterminded by the “midget” Lilliput they rob and steal. But ghost-like Fate steps in and sabotages their heists. In the end the last remaining members kill off each other.

Satan's Spectacles: The devil sets a trap for optometrist Harry Lenz. In disguise he lets him have magic glasses which reveal the thoughts of others. At a moment’s notice, Lenz goes for a life of crime and high finance. Years later Satan comes to collects his dues. Surprisingly not Lenz’s soul, but just his eyesight.

Dance of Death: John Drune runs the "Devil's Den" night club. Because he's too cheap to buy a fireproof dress, his dancer Helen perishes in a dangerous flame dance. She returns from the grave to teach him a dancing lesson.

</Summary>
  <Tags>Satan</Tags>
  <Title>Monster of the Mist; Crime Circus; Satan's Spectacles; Dance of Death</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-4-monster-of-the-mist/4000-204117/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Writer>Jack Cole,Jack Cole</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jack Cole,Sam Citron,Jack Cole,Sam Citron</Penciller>
  <Letterer>Sam Rosen,Sam Rosen</Letterer>
  <Editor>Alfred Grenet</Editor>
</ComicInfo>