<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Glory</Characters>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-139179</GTIN>
  <Inker>Daniel HDR,Danny Miki,Emir Ribeiro,Jaime Mendoza,Jon Sibal,Marlo Alquiza,Mike Deodato Jr.</Inker>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T19:17:01 [Issue ID 4000-139179] urn:comicvine:4000-139179
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-08 14:55:19. [Issue ID 139179]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Ed Benes,Mike Deodato Jr.,Roger Cruz,Stephen Platt</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Glory &amp; Friends Bikini Fest</Series>
  <Summary>This issue consists of pin-ups of Glory and other Extreme Studios characters wearing swimsuits:

Glory by Sam Liu, Danny Miki, and Drew Posada;
Glory by Mike Deodato, Jr. and Brenda Donnelly;
Glory by Cedric Nocon and Danny Miki;
Glory by Daniel Horn, Jaime Mendoza, and Bill Simpson;
Vogue from Youngblood by Roger Cruz, Danny Miki, and Aron Lusen;
Glory by Pat Lee, Danny Miki, and Alex Posada;
Glory by Emir Ribeiro and Andy Troy;
The Experts from Bloodstrike by Karl Altstaetter, Danny Miki, and Brett Evans;
Darlene and Troll from Brigade by Ed Benes, Jonathan Sibal, and Bill Simpson;
Glory by John Stinsman, Marlo Alquiza, and Dan Kemp;
Judas from Prophet by Stephen Platt and Jonathan Sibal;
Centerfold swimsuit photo of model Denise Franzen as Glory;
Athena from Bloodstrike by John Fang, Danny Miki, and Tanya Horie;
Glory by Andy Park, Jonathan Sibal, and Jeff Voeltner;
the New Men by Todd Nauck and Marlo Alquiza;
Glory by Fabio Laguna, Danny Miki, and Dan Kemp;
Psilence from Bloodpool by Andy Park and Marlo Alquiza;
Glory by Mark Pajarillo, Danny Miki, and Alex Posada;
Glory by Marat Mychaels and Danny Miki;
Masada from Youngblood by Andy Park, Jonathan Sibal, and Jeff Voeltner;
Dash and Byrd from New Men by Brian Denham.
Both photo covers of this issue feature model Denise Franzen role playing as Glory posing in a bikini.</Summary>
  <Title>Bikini Fest</Title>
  <Volume>1995</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/glory-friends-bikini-fest-1-bikini-fest/4000-139179/</Web>
  <Year>1995</Year>
</ComicInfo>