<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Challenge of the Unknown</Series>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Title>Villa of the Vampire</Title>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>High Priestess of the Snake People (7 pages) - In the Swiss Alps, a young American stumbles across a cult of snake-worshipers. He is bewitched by the beautiful snake queen Gilda. An old villager comes to his help and blows the whole bunch to kingdom come with a pack of dynamite.

True Tales of the Supernatural #1 (1 page) - "Among a certain noble family of Scotland, there was a legend..." If a family member hears the beating of drums, another member is stricken by tragic death. It so happens.

The Ghost in the Portrait (7 pages) - A young couple free the ghost of an evil ancestor. He takes revenge on the bones of the people who sentenced him to death. Then he commands the man to murder his wife, as he did with his wife. The woman manages to destroy the evil spirit in the last moment. The couple lives happily ever after.

True Tales of the Supernatural #2 (1 page) - "There is a legend about a ghost-infested cell in a jail in New Orleans..." The inhabitants of this cell become suicidal because of the ghost of an old woman who hanged herself in it.

Villa of the Vampire (7 pages) - A vampire haunts an Italian villa. The inhabitants are decimated. With the help of a doctor and a blood transfusion, the husband can save his wife and kill the creature of darkness.

Text Story: Unburied Dead (2 pages) - Man hypnotizes wife, but summons demon in the process. They fight over possession of the woman's body. Her body explodes. Man is arrested and sentenced to death.

No Grave to Hold Him (7 pages) - To live on after his demise, the brain of a dying professor is planted into the body of an executed criminal. His gangster pals kidnap him to find the hidden money from their last robbery. Dramatic showdown on an airfield landing strip. The bad guys are killed, the professor's assistant regains control over the Frankenstein-like creature. Hidden from the public, it lives on scribbling formulas.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-16 19:45:58. [Issue ID 333867]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Ace Magazines</Publisher>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Year>1950</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Penciller>Mike Sekowsky,Art Peddy,Lin Streeter,Ken Rice,Frank Giusto,Ken Rice,Lin Streeter,Mike Sekowsky,Warren Kremer</Penciller>
  <Inker>Lin Streeter,Ken Rice,Frank Giusto,Al Avison</Inker>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/challenge-of-the-unknown-6-villa-of-the-vampire/4000-333867/</Web>
  <Teams>Vampires</Teams>
  <Locations>New Orleans,Scotland,Italy,The Alps,Switzerland</Locations>
  <CoverArtist>Al Avison,Warren Kremer</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>