<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-91071</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:05:40 [Issue ID 4000-91071] urn:comicvine:4000-91071
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 13:00:36. [Issue ID 203217]</Notes>
  <Number>37</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>War Comics</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/war-comics-37/4000-91071/</Web>
  <Year>1955</Year>
  <Count>49</Count>
  <Title>Behind the Lines!; Enemy Territory!; Patrol Mission!; Nothing Can Stop the Infantry!</Title>
  <Genre>War</Genre>
  <Summary>Behind the Lines!: Battling the Nazis in France, quartermaster Captain Leonard Hill helps the regular army by flanking around the Nazis, confusing them and, with just Private Harvey Green assisting him, tricks an entire platoon of Nazis into surrendering, winning him the Silver Star from General Patton.

Enemy Territory!: During the invasion of Mexico, Private Bill Lawrence wonders why the US should want to take territory from Mexico but eventually resolves if his country wants something it's his duty to help them get it.

Patrol Mission!: Private Herbert Persley was drafted into the US Army during World War I and has no love for the service, preferring cards to heroism. When the squad is caught in the open, they draw straws to see who will stay behind to cover the others' retreat, and Ernest Farraday wins, but Persley knocks Farraday out and takes his place, saying Farraday is needed as a soldier. However, some time later, Persley returns to his own lines, having been captured by the Germans, only to play them at cards, win their weapons and depart.

Nothing Can Stop the Infantry!: Able Company leader Captain Kettridge has a keen mind for details. When the Chinese pin down Able Company and seem to have an unlimited supply of ammunition, Kettridge realizes they've hidden it nearby.  Using a metal detector, they find the ammo underground and destroy it forcing the Chinese to surrender.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>General George S. Patton</Characters>
  <Penciller>Joe Sinnott,Bob Forgione,Bill Benulis,Mort Drucker,Joe Sinnott,Bob Forgione,Bill Benulis,Mort Drucker</Penciller>
  <Inker>Joe Sinnott,Jack Abel,Bill Benulis,Mort Drucker,Joe Sinnott,Jack Abel,Bill Benulis,Mort Drucker</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>