<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>That Hellbound Train</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Summary>Take a trip back in time on Robert Bloch&#8217;s That Hellbound Train! Join Martin, an out-of-luck orphan, as he struggles to fulfill the American dream. As Martin comes of age, fate conspires against him at every turn. On the verge of giving up hope, our young protagonist is visited by a monstrous train, one whose conductor might just have a ticket to fame and riches... if Martin is willing to pay the price! Scribes Joe and John Lansdale ( 30 Days of Night: Night, Again) and artist Dave Wachter bring this unique tale of American folklore to life! 

In this first episode of this American Gothic tale we meet Martin, a great depression era boy who lives alone with his father, an alcoholic railroad man. His father teaches Martin everything there is to know about trains - including the legend of the Hellbound Train. When Martins father gets killed in a strange train accident at midnight, the boy is put in orphanage from where he escapes and try&#180;s a life of hobo and small time criminal. Eventually he joins the Salvation Army, but seduces the commanders daughter and is cast away. But then the Hellbound Train comes for him and he makes a deal with it&#180;s "conductor"; he will have the ability to stop once the time for eternity for a seat in the train.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-11-26 21:29:55.  [CVDB274960]</Notes>
  <Year>2011</Year>
  <Month>06</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Joe R. Lansdale, John L. Lansdale, Robert Bloch</Writer>
  <Colorist>Alfredo Rodriguez</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Neil Uyetake</Letterer>
  <Editor>Bobby Curnow</Editor>
  <Publisher>IDW Publishing</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/that-hellbound-train-1/4000-274960/</Web>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1068813" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="905333" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="772704" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="788675" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="635929" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="612878" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="602403" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="703959" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="689455" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="594039" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="827750" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="622863" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="805553" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="845877" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="865631" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="837663" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="783231" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="823056" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="846116" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="842459" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="796912" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="763121" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="837794" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="716593" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="591590" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="972190" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
