<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Polyphemus</Characters>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-143668</GTIN>
  <Locations>Mediterranean Sea,Italy,Greece,London</Locations>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:42:58 [Issue ID 4000-143668] urn:comicvine:4000-143668
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 22:03:54. [Issue ID 258842]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Mythstalkers</Series>
  <Summary>The myths are coming back. Trolls and faeries, giants and dragons, monsters and gods are no longer merely the stuff of legend. It's 1894, and in the dark corners and shadows of the world the myths are alive once more. The only hope to discover the truth is the Society for Cryptozoological Research, an explorers club dedicated to investigating and understanding the reappearance of creatures that " Should Not Be". Three things stand in their way: ancient gods with a sinister agenda, the mysterious disappearance of the last Society... and the British Empire. The Mythstalkers' journey to the Labyrinth at Crete takes an unfortunate turn as they encounter the ghost pirates known as The Cheated. Of course, that's not nearly as bad as being shipwrecked on the island of the legendary Cyclops. Back in England things aren't much better. The time traveler, Coble, tightens his grip on London, and British mobsters, Batson and Quill, meet their new boss... the faerie witch, Valende. Confused? You won't be... if you read this issue of Mythstalkers!</Summary>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/mythstalkers-2/4000-143668/</Web>
  <Year>2003</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>