<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Metal Man],Joe Lombard,Atomics [Horn,Madman,Haley Foufoo,Black Crystal,Slug,Mr. Gum,It Girl,Crimson King</Characters>
  <Colorist>Laura Allred,Laura Allred</Colorist>
  <Count>17</Count>
  <Editor>Jamie S. Rich</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-122076</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Nate Piekos,Nate Piekos</Letterer>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:03:40 [Issue ID 4000-122076] urn:comicvine:4000-122076
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 07:47:26. [Issue ID 393871]</Notes>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Madman Atomic Comics</Series>
  <Summary>Frank "Madman" Einstein and the Atomics have ganged up in an all out effort to save the Universe. But it will come at a tragic personal cost. Lives will be lost. And there will be no turning back, no reprieves, no sneaky tricks. Death comes calling for keeps! But for who? Who?!!

Horn sits with Haley as she watches Madman and the Atomics on their mission. He tells her not to kid herself since he has a girlfriend. She insists that she is only concerned about the mission and saving the Universe.

The team stands in front of the Crimson King. He congratulates and absorbs his son. They try standing up him. Tired of their complaining, the Crimson King starts blasting them away into nothingness with Frank the first to go. The Crimson King is ready to remake the Universe.

Madman and the Atomics now find themselves far outside of the Crimson King's lair. Confused, Madman tells them that he got into his head and made him think he destroyed all of them. Madman tells them they have to stop him because he basically wants to do the Big Bang in reverse.

As if things weren't bad enough, they get attacked by brain eaters. In a courageous move, Metalman becomes a victim. Hale tells them his brain is gone but his body could be preserved. It Girl is shocked by this. Frank tries telling her they have to carry on. He pulls her to him and asks to feel her pain and he'll show her all that he knows. As they merge, she becomes enlightened.

They join together, willing to die as heroes in order to save the Universe. They succeed and return to Haley. As thanks, she says she sent engineers from her planet to Earth to build a base with some of their technology to help them in fighting the good fight. Frank's rocket has also been fixed and modified so that it is easier to navigate. Frank is given a new spacesuit and It Girl is given a re-animated Metalman. Haley is confused at her distress. She figured they'd want to use him as a Zom-bot. Next is the arrival of Joe. Haley figured Frank would want to celebrate with her there and she is being brought in a sphere. As she approaches, Frank realizes that he's having deja vu. This is when she dies. It Girl stretches out her arms to save her. Haley stops her saying she'll be killed too. With an explosion, Joe is gone.

Haley tries apologizing. Frank just takes the spacesuit and leaves in the rocket. The rest of the Atomics are left not knowing what they'll do next.</Summary>
  <Teams>The Atomics</Teams>
  <Title>Crushed in the Court of the Crimson King!</Title>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/madman-atomic-comics-6-crushed-in-the-court-of-the/4000-122076/</Web>
  <Year>2008</Year>
  <Writer>Mike Allred,Michael Allred,Michael Allred</Writer>
  <Penciller>Mike Allred,Ralph Niese,Michael Allred,Michael Allred</Penciller>
  <Inker>Mike Allred,Ralph Niese,Michael Allred,Michael Allred</Inker>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>