<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-56996</GTIN>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:38:12 [Issue ID 4000-56996] urn:comicvine:4000-56996
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 19:00:22. [Issue ID 75643]</Notes>
  <Number>26</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Atlas.1954)  (Pmack)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Adventures into Weird Worlds</Series>
  <Title>The Dead; Menace from Mars!; The Edge of Madness; The Robot that Hated; Good-Bye Earth</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-weird-worlds-26-good-bye-earth/4000-56996/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>30</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>The Dead: Passive zombies return to find that they are not wanted by their relatives and so they sadly leave.

Menace from Mars!: A draft dodger heads for Mars to avoid being inducted into Earth's army, but the Martians are preparing for war as well, and since the Martians are not choosy the dodger and his pals get inducted into their army.

The Edge of Madness: A man and the werecreature half of his nature both are in love with the same woman and consider each other rivals, so when the evening transition between the two of them occurs, they fight each other to the death using knives to lacerate the body they both share.

The Robot that Hated: A scientist builds a robot attuned to his emotional impulses so that it kills a woman who rejected his proposal. When he demonstrates love towards the robot later that evening, it crushes him in a hug.

Good-Bye Earth: A man is confronted by an alien disguised as a human who reveals to him that he is actually one of them, deep undercover as a spy. He gives the man an injection that will bring his true nature to the surface in a matter of hours. The man writes the whole story down as a warning to his wife and children and to all of Earth to "watch the skies".

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Dick Ayers,Chuck Winter,Tony DiPreta,Al Eadeh,Paul Reinman</Penciller>
  <Inker>Dick Ayers,Chuck Winter,Tony DiPreta,Al Eadeh,Paul Reinman</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>