<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Ms. Victory,Nightveil,Queen Drusilla,She-Cat,Stardust,Synn,Tara,Valkyra</Characters>
	<CoverArtist>Ed Coutts</CoverArtist>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Bill Black</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-123914</GTIN>
	<Genre>Superhero</Genre>
	<Inker>Antonio Conversano,Ed Coutts,Jeff Austin,Ken Hunt,Mark Heike</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Steph Heike</Letterer>
	<Month>1</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.2.0 on 2024-11-30T20:44:39 [Issue ID 4000-123914] urn:comicvine:4000-123914</Notes>
	<Number>139</Number>
	<PageCount>42</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="171580" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="152850"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="262572"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="212948"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="200966"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="192694"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="217942"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="204652"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="256092"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="250006"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="254728"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="197660"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="195060"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="227720"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="189196"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="175322"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="176208"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="131486"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="274464"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="238296"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="244990"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="228368"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="272208"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="232106"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="248654"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="220354"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="131490"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="132128"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="246572"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="266684"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="252116"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="242542"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="317052"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="258040"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="239164"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="229384"/>
		<Page Image="36" ImageSize="167208"/>
		<Page Image="37" ImageSize="160450"/>
		<Page Image="38" ImageSize="181692"/>
		<Page Image="39" ImageSize="212030"/>
		<Page Image="40" ImageSize="255294"/>
		<Page Image="41" ImageSize="243586"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Antonio Conversano,Chad Halcom,Ed Coutts,Ken Hunt,Larry Guidry</Penciller>
	<Publisher>AC</Publisher>
	<Series>FemForce</Series>
	<Summary>When Ms. Victory responds to strange happenings at a local junkyard, she finds herself battered by a hidden foe, make that 3 foes as the villains Valkyra, Alexandria the Greatest, and Prom Queen, take their turns with the Femforce powerhouse! Story by Paul Monsky, art by Ed Coutts. Then Nightveil tracks a serial killer in a short story by Enrico Teodorani with art by Ken Hunt, followed by another Ms. Victory solo tale as the heroine is "One Against Evil," in a tale again written by Enrico Teodorani but with art this time by Antonio Conversano. The flip-side of this issue is the third installment of Gargantarama, the Comic Book!

A new giantess comes onto the scene in "Carry A Big Torch", a giant-woman heroine with a new twist. Created, written and drawn by Chad Halcom, with ink finishes by Jeff Austin, we're sure she's going to be a big hit- SO sure that a sequel story is already being prepared for next issue!! Then, another GTS premiere, as the team of Enrico Teodorani and Antonio Conversano introduce an urban giantess crimefighter, La Vedoya. Finally, Femforce star "Too Tall TARA" takes center stage in "Natural Habitat", as corporate hitmen leave her for dead in an overgrown wilderness, but the big, bold and bombastic jungle brunette tracks down her assailants and brings them to justice in a BIG way in the end!! Written by Steve Orlando, with art by Larry Guidry and Mark Heike. All this plus pinups by Heike- one, an Old West gunfightin' giantess- and the other, Big 'Uns star Queen Drusilla!! As always, Gargantarama - The Comic Book is produced in flip-book format, sharing an issue of Femforce- this one being FF #139. So, flip the book upside down, turn to the opposite cover and start flipping!! Femforce #139 opens with an all-out action tale starring MS. VICTORY, who must take on not one, not two, but three supervillainesses (Valkyra, Alexandria the Greatest &amp; Prom Queen) in "What You Can't See Can Kill You"!! Written by Paul Monsky, with art by Ed Coutts. Then, NIGHTVEIL must stop a homicidal psychotic killer in an untitled story written by Enrico Teodorani, with art by new sensation Ken Hunt. Next, MS. VICTORY is back for a return engagement when she must face off against a sorceress who is evil incarnate in "One Against Evil", written by Teodorani, with art by Antonio Conversano.</Summary>
	<Teams>FemForce</Teams>
	<Title>One Against Evil; What You Can't See, Can Kill You!; Natural Habitat; La Vedova; Carry a Big Torch</Title>
	<Volume>1985</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/femforce-139-trashed/4000-123914/</Web>
	<Writer>Chad Halcom,Enrico Teodorani,Paul Monsky,Steph Heike,Steve Orlando</Writer>
	<Year>2007</Year>
</ComicInfo>