<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294539</GTIN>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:06 [Issue ID 4000-294539] urn:comicvine:4000-294539
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:13. [Issue ID 136605]</Notes>
  <Number>16</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>Death's Vengeance: Curator Arthur Dunster collects Aztec relics of horror. When museum visitors laugh at his stories, the ancient artifacts come to life and prove their truth by killing the explorers who desecrated their tombs.

The Hamlet of Horror: John Ames and his wife Doris have a car accident in the wilderness and are taken by a gang of misshapen creatures. They plan on operating on John and Doris to transform them into members of their tribe. The couple manages to outwit them and returns to civilization.

The Fiend of Terror Mountain: The brutish Roco escapes from a mental institution and finds shelter at the house of the criminal Mr. Leache. He uses Roco’s strength for a series of holdup murders and thefts. When Leache learns of a terminal illness he’s carrying, he orders Roco to kill him in an unobserved moment. The doctor, however, made a mistake and confused medical reports…

The Medium of Murder: Zakor, master medium, offers his services to underworld czar Keller. Zakor conjures ghosts from beyond to dispose of Keller’s rival mobsters. The gangster obeys his every wish, although Zakor employs a trusty assistant named Maja to commit the murders in costume. Then Zakor takes over the crime business himself and pushes Keller out of the picture. But now a real ghost appears and murders the evil Zakor.

</Summary>
  <Title>Death's Vengeance; The Hamlet of Horror; The Fiend of Terror Mountain; The Medium of Murder</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-16-the-medium-of-murder/4000-294539/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime,Adventure</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>