<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Love and Rockets</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Title>Final; 1980; You're Right, it's not About you; 1980; Is This How You See Me? (part 1); Is This How You See Me? (part 2)</Title>
  <Volume>2016</Volume>
  <Genre>Drama</Genre>
  <Summary>This is volume four in the series. Uses the same oversize magazine format as volume one.

Vol. 1- 1982-1996 (50 issues in magazine format)
Vol. 2- 2001-2007 (20 issues in standard US comic book periodical format)
Vol. 3- 2008-2016 (8 issues as Love and Rockets: New Stories in trade paperback format)

Comes with at least one cover variant per issue available exclusively from the publisher. Each variant has its own individual front &amp; back cover.Final: Vignette of 50+ Daffy with her unnamed companion in the supermarket.

1980: Vignette about teen Maggie as she chats with and kisses the bashful Speedy. The not-long-for-this-world Del who doesn't get visitors anymore invites Maggie in but she's going to a Siouxsie Sioux concert.

You're Right, it's not About you: Rosario is left alone in Fritz mansion after Fritz and Baby leave for a week. The story is interspersed with scenes from an unnamed decade-old Fritz sci-fi movie that Rosy is watching.

1980: A sequence featuring Hoppers punkers hanging out a Del's place. Licha tries to get Del to talk to his cousin Malo who is threatening his life. Hopey's friends talk about her newfound inheritance money. Maggie chats with Tony Chase and Speedy, then heads out with Hopey where the two fortify their relationship.

Is This How You See Me? (part 1): It's three a.m. and Eugene is still following Hopey and Maggie with no one around to help.

Is This How You See Me? (part 2): Hopey and Maggie, still being followed, seek help from a couple that they come across, but the bigoted couple refuse to help. Maggie runs to a cleaning lady that she sees in the distance but her ankle gives out. The duo are treated at Huerta Medical, then Sadaf arrives to take Hopey home.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev36 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-03-22 15:07:24. [Issue ID 1810560]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>23</Day>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Year>2018</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Web>https://www.comics.org/issue/1810560</Web>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (Salem-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Daffy's Unnamed Companion</Characters>
  <Writer>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>Daffy's Unnamed Companion</Tags>
</ComicInfo>