<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Looking for a Snark</Title>
  <Series>Snarked!</Series>
  <Number>0</Number>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Summary>Special $1 introduction to the eagerly awaited new hit series starting this October! You were amazed by his Harvey Award-winning run on THE MUPPET SHOW. You thrilled to his run on THOR: THE MIGHTY AVENGER. Now the next great Roger Langridge comic begins as he brings Lewis Carroll's imaginative world to new heights in a side-splitting adventure that can only be explained as... SNARKED! Presenting a fresh and incredibly modern "Langridge" spin on an already-warped classic, the SNARKED epic adventure starts here with a self-contained 8 page story featuring The Walrus and The Carpenter from Through the Looking Glass -- that's right, the same Walrus that inspired the Beatles song "I Am the Walrus" is now in Roger Langridge's merry, mad hands for new All-Ages adventures at KABOOM! This $1 special includes a full issue's worth of back matter that dives deep into the world of SNARKED with an exclusive behind-the-scenes look at the new series. Don't miss this comic book industry event! Buy the $1 issue now, pick up the series in October!</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-11-25 22:21:28.  [CVDB285173]</Notes>
  <Year>2011</Year>
  <Month>08</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Lewis Carroll, Roger Langridge</Writer>
  <Penciller>Roger Langridge</Penciller>
  <Inker>Roger Langridge</Inker>
  <Colorist>Matthew Wilson, Rachelle Rosenberg</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Matthew Wilson, Roger Langridge</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Bryce Carlson</Editor>
  <Publisher>Boom! Studios</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/snarked-0-looking-for-a-snark/4000-285173/</Web>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Characters>Alice, Baker, Banker, Barrister, Beaver, Bellman, Billiard Marker, Bonnet Maker, Broker of Goods, Butcher, Cheshire Cat, Clyde McDunk, Jabberwocky, Prince Rusty, Queen Scarlet, Red King, Wilburforce J. Walrus</Characters>
  <Teams>Bellman's Crew</Teams>
  <Locations>Wonderland</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="449048" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="549938" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="648174" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="599800" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="503479" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="528216" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="607718" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="576261" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="574652" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="613379" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="450233" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="531794" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="496849" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="678498" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="804098" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="779193" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="776420" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="600058" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="639763" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="682809" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="435549" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="334450" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="547863" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
