<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Abby Holland,Alec Holland,Sethe,Swamp Thing</Characters>
	<Colorist>Nathan Fairbairn</Colorist>
	<Count>42</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Chris Conroy,Matt Idelson</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-319038</GTIN>
	<Inker>Yanick Paquette</Inker>
	<Letterer>Travis Lanham</Letterer>
	<Locations>Bone Kingdom</Locations>
	<Month>5</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:13:23 [Issue ID 4000-319038] urn:comicvine:4000-319038</Notes>
	<Number>7</Number>
	<PageCount>22</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2128305" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="2784893"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="2222502"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="2593660"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="3273883"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="3051193"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="2806569"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="3280812"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="6096538"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="3480351"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="3268662"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="3185675"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="3529301"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="3991959"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="2986871"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="2870374"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="3569279"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="2276686"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="2574530"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="2066179"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="2559943"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="2104141"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Yanick Paquette</Penciller>
	<Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Swamp Thing</Series>
	<Summary>Moss fills lungs. Leaves scrape across skin and wood against bone. A Swamp Thing is rising in The Green's hour of darkest need…but is Alec Holland a part of it? Or is he just bleeding out in a ditch? And as Alec falls, a horrible champion is taking the throne of the Bone Kingdom at Sethe's right hand!

 

We find Alec Holland in a swamp of blood. After being ambushed by Sethe's puppets and on the brink of death Alec's consciousness is taken into the Green. We see the Parliament ablaze, and all of them denouncing him. They tell him the took his consciousness from his body so that he could suffer with them. They tell him that Abby is on her way to be seated next to Sethe to take over the Rot in a Bone Kingdom and that when she emerges from the cocoon she will be forever changed.

The Parliament has put a Alec's body in a protective cocoon that the emissaries of the Rot are slowly breaking through. Alec tells them that in his bag is the last batch of the bio-restorative formula and that they need to use it to turn him into Swamp Thing. They realize that it could be possible to change him but they would not be able to fight alongside him. They break the vial and the transformation begins. The vines all spread throughout him and foliage forms off his human body.

Swamp Thing now rises from his cocoon and strikes down every single one of the attackers with a stroke of his hand. He grows wings and flies off to fight the Rot on their land.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-11-19 06:55:40.  [Issue ID 319038]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-7-swamp-thing/4000-319038/</Summary>
	<Tags>Abby Holland,Alec Holland,Bone Kingdom,Parliament of Trees,Sethe,Swamp Thing</Tags>
	<Teams>Parliament of Trees</Teams>
	<Title>Swamp Thing</Title>
	<Volume>2011</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-7-swamp-thing/4000-319038/</Web>
	<Writer>Scott Snyder</Writer>
	<Year>2012</Year>
</ComicInfo>