<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Trials &amp; Tribulations, Part 1: Once Were Ghost Riders</Title>
  <Series>Ghost Rider</Series>
  <Number>33</Number>
  <Count>35</Count>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Summary>After the shocking events of last issue, the all-new Caretaker struggles to pick up the pieces of her life, but the mad dog man-mountain called The Deacon has other plans. Also, Caretaker gives us a special guided tour of the long sordid history of the Spirit of Vengeance in America, including glimpses of some previously unseen Ghost Riders of the past.

Sara is at the morgue getting ready for her Grand father Caretaker's funeral. Moments later she rides back to the nun convent she was raised one only to find all of the nuns bloody and dead. She finds the Mother Superior mortally wounded. She tells Sara that the Deacon was the one who killed all the nuns. As she dies she says something is wrong with the angels. As she dies Sara thirsts for revenge to kill the Deacon.

As Sara buries Caretaker, she is all of a sudden visited by two Ghost Riders of the future that were sent by her. They warn her to not give up. They say that Zadikiel has conquered the golden city of heaven but is not a God unless he remains there for a very long time. They say this is the time for Sara to attack and bring back both Johnny Blaze and Danny Ketch to fight with her. Sara accepts the mission and rides off to find Blaze and Ketch.

Elsewhere the Deacon is revealed to be working Zadikeil and that Blackout is working with him as well. At this time Blackout is surrounded by photos of many villains and is deciding which one he wants to Ghost Rider with.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-22 12:12:25.  [CVDB153442]</Notes>
  <Year>2009</Year>
  <Month>05</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Jason Aaron</Writer>
  <Penciller>Tony Moore, Tony Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Tony Moore, Tony Moore</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dave McCaig</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Joe Caramagna</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Arthur Suydam</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso, Joe Quesada, Sebastian Girner</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Genre>Superhero,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ghost-rider-33-trials-tribulations-part-1-once-wer/4000-153442/</Web>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Big Wheel, Black Talon, Blackheart, Blackout, Caleb, Caretaker, Chief Hellhawk, Deacon, Death Ninja, Devil Rig, Doghead, Dracula, Ghost Flyer, Ghost Rider (Blaze), Ghost Rider (Ketch), Goom, Grogg, Hell-Driver, Hellbilly, Highwayman, Iron Mike, Knuckles O'Shaughnessy, Madcap, Man-Thing, Manphibian, Noble Kale, Orb, Razorback, Reverend Styge, Ringmaster, Sara, Satana, Scarecrow, Trull The Unhuman, Undead G-Man, Zadkiel, Zzutak</Characters>
  <Teams>Black Host, Circus of Crime, Tank 666</Teams>
  <Locations>Africa, Germany, Kansas</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="503755" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="489119" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="756333" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="732876" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="510751" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="655897" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="820103" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="849017" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="710439" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="797039" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="532940" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="606760" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="732763" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="890437" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="666350" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="744155" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="833453" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="721328" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="781011" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="679583" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="787893" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="761436" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="703241" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="773984" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>