<ComicInfo>
  <Title>The Troll, the Serpent, and the Princess; Grumble vs. the Goon</Title>
  <Series>Grumble vs the Goon</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Volume>2019</Volume>
  <Summary>From the pages of Grumble, Tala and Eddie think it might be a good idea to go dimension hopping when they find death incarnate hot on their heels. Unfortunately, things go from bad to worse when they land in the world of The Goon. And Franky, the newly appointed dog catcher, don't like talkin' mutts that give him the sass!

ContentsGrumble vs. The GoonHillbilly: The Troll, The Serpent and the PrincessGrumble vs. The Goon Somewhere out West, Eddie and Tala are on the run from the Lacerta Biker Gang and take a portal in a gift shop to another dimension.   In that other dimension, in Norton's Pub, Goon's a poker game is interrupted by a rat being thrown on the table, which leads to Goon bludgeoning the Dogcatcher, which leads to Franky being the dogcatcher.

Meanwhile, Eddie and Girl, exit the portal into Goon's dimension, and wander into Norton's Pub.  Eddie soon starts playing poker and cheating while Girl goes to look around.  The cheating leads to dogcatcher Franky to take notice and though Eddie is not a dog, Franky doesn't believe hes not a stray.  After a brief fight Franky drags a beaten Eddie away down the street where some starving hobos take notice.

Meanwhile inside Norton's Pub, Tala asks Goon for help finding Eddie.

Later at the dog pound, Franky tries to kill Eddie but is interrupted by the starving hobos.  When things look dim for Franky Goon and Tala show up.  Goon uses his fists to kill Hobos while Tala uses her magic powers and when the head Hobo is taken down the rest retreat to the woods once again.  Goon and Tala strike up a deal while Eddie and Franky argue over magic vs shivs.

And so... back in Eddie and Tala dimension, Goon uses his fists against the Lacertas while the rest look on from safety. 

Hillbilly: The Troll, The Serpent and the PrincessReprint of the very first Hillbilly story from 2016

Hillbilly  and Lucille rescue Princess from a pair of troll planning on eating.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-17 14:58:52.  [CVDB707784]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/grumble-vs-the-goon-1/4000-707784/</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-17 14:58:52.  [CVDB707784]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 08:50:18. [Issue ID 1959940]</Notes>
  <Year>2019</Year>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Day>4</Day>
  <Writer>Eric Powell,Rafer Roberts,Eric Powell,Rafer Roberts</Writer>
  <Penciller>Eric Powell,Mike Norton,Eric Powell,Mike Norton</Penciller>
  <Inker>Eric Powell,Mike Norton,Eric Powell,Mike Norton</Inker>
  <Colorist>Eric Powell,Marissa Louise,Eric Powell,Marissa Louise</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Eric Powell,Crank!,Eric Powell,Crank!</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Eric Powell</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Tracy Marsh</Editor>
  <Publisher>Albatross</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/grumble-vs-the-goon-1/4000-707784/</Web>
  <PageCount>33</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>FCBD</Format>
  <Characters>The Goon,Eddie Endino,Franky,Norton,Tala Palacio,Lucille,Rondel</Characters>
  <Locations>Norton's Pub</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="960080" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="949530" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1089695" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1020314" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1025382" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1123658" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1015195" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="886738" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="845996" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="909909" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="953003" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="913416" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1081465" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="904239" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="860096" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="899278" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1010094" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="873110" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="933143" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="923643" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="857951" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="887497" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="900271" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1114588" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="942493" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="974478" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="932101" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="909391" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="961313" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="902597" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="934483" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="669712" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="102079" />
  </Pages>
<Genre>Comedy,Zombie</Genre></ComicInfo>