<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Digging In</Title>
  <Series>Savage Henry</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Count>13</Count>
  <Volume>1987</Volume>
  <Summary>Nash the Slash has finally regrown (thanks to Bugtown's regenerative properties) after having his head blown off by one of Monsieur Boche's door bombs. Things get confusing when Nash claims he has only just risen from the dead which means The Bulldaggers have been hanging around with what now seems to be a false Nash for a couple of days. Henry's Caroline clone assumes something bad is going on and everyone decides to head to Narcosis Labs to find out what that is.   Meanwhile at Narcosis Labs as Cthulu regails Conrad with a very brief history of how he came to join The Bulldaggers band, the false Nash the Slash opens the door for Hiroshima who promptly squares of with Cthulu resulting in a nuclear blast so large that it destroys every square inch of Bugtown in one blast -- a feat thought impossible given Bugtown's nigh infinite dimensional intersecting borders. Cthulu rises from the ashes of the destruction ready for battle, but so does Hiroshima whose current incarnation is suddenly so large, immense and powerful that it seemingly dwarfs that of Cthulu's. She blasts Cthulu into oblivion leaving his friend Conrad to tumble and fall into infinity.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-23 22:41:55.  [CVDB272486]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 12:37:51. [Issue ID 272296]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Penciller>Matt Howarth</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Howarth</Inker>
  <Editor>Patricia Jeres</Editor>
  <Publisher>Vortex</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/savage-henry-4-digging-in/4000-272486/</Web>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Cthulhu,Nash the Slash,Ron Post,Monsieur Boche,Savage Henry,Caroline Clone,Hiroshima,Conrad Schnitzler</Characters>
  <Locations>Bugtown</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="604752" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="352902" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="506934" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="439946" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="460834" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1523038" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="490612" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1064250" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="644846" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="725316" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="605026" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="436632" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="432272" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="386436" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="595550" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="893980" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1301980" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="850628" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="964184" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="774504" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="478056" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="488650" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="384828" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>