<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-389904</GTIN>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:40 [Issue ID 4000-389904] urn:comicvine:4000-389904
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:49:00. [Issue ID 9691]</Notes>
  <Number>11</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Crime SuspenStories</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-11/4000-110185/ https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-11/4000-389904/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>27</Count>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Al Feldstein</Writer>
  <Penciller>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Jack Davis,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Inker>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Jack Davis,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Johnny Craig</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein</Editor>
  <Title>Stiff Punishment!; One Man's Poison!; Two for One!; Four for One!; A Fool and His Honey Are Soon Parted!</Title>
  <Genre>Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>Stiff Punishment!: Jo Ann, fifteen years the junior of her husband, is sickened by his profession: a college professor in anatomy, and cannot stand his fascination with dissecting bodies and the like. After an argument, the two split up, but Fred decides on a fool-proof plan to kill his wife... or so he thinks!

One Man's Poison!: John and Mary fought tooth and nail all the time, until one evening, Mary decided to kill her husband. However, she had to make it look like an accident. Partially opening a can of beans, then letting it sit out for a week or so, she was sure the contents would provide the food poisoning to do the job. Every day, she would ingest a bean or two and get sick, then recover, figuring that if her husband ate a large portion of the contents one night, he would die. He did, but Mary celebrated the fact by having a glass of wine, not knowing it had been poisoned by her husband.

Two for One!: Carleton Ashley must raise $20,000 quickly or be forced to declare bankruptcy, meaning that he would lose everything he had worked for. The same day a Mr. Simms informed Ashley that he had a fool-proof way to double any investment almost immediately. So Ashley scrapes together $10,000, sees Simms and exchanges the $10,000 for $20,000 in what he believes to be fool-proof counterfeit currency. But Ashley soon becomes a victim of a scam perpetrated on him by his bookkeeper.

Four for One!: Donald Irwin tells a bank President that he has exaggerated his wealth to a prospective client, and if that client accepts Irwin's offer, then Irwin must pay that client $10,000. What he needs the bank to do, to impress the client with Irwin's supposed wealthy status, is to open a checking account for Irwin, deposit the $10,000 that Irwin gives them, then gladly cash that check later for the client when he presents it. What the bank President doesn't realize is that five different people will appear to different tellers at the same time to cash a check.

A Fool and His Honey Are Soon Parted!: Armand and Bovant get together to discuss the soon to be unsettling visit of a man from the home office to inspect all plantations, and is well known as a gigolo (or love pirate). Armand warns Bovant that this man well go after Nanette as his next prize. He does and nearly succeeds when Armand informs Rudy of being invited to a native Chief's daughter's forthcoming marriage. When they arrive, Rudy falls for the Chief's daughter, the last woman he would try to win over.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Fred (villain, medical college Professor),Gibbs (a student),Dean Martin (Fred's friend, cameo),Jo Ann (Fred's wife, death)</Characters>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>