<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Star Wars: X-Wing Rogue Squadron</Series>
  <Number>½</Number>
  <Volume>1995</Volume>
  <Summary>Wedge, Biggs, Porkins and Doc have come to Commenor on a secret mission to pick up R2 units necessary to fly X-Wings most efficiently. The Alliance has taken a pounding in recent days, and are starved enough of astromech droids that it has become a mission of critical importance.

Unfortunately, their movements have not been so covert as they would have liked. They got into a fight with some local thugs, and now one of them has run to the planet's stormtrooper garrison to get some revenge by tattling on the quartet.

While the four negotiate the final deal for the R2 units, a hidden stormtrooper watches the transaction go down. He quietly leaves before they do so that he can alert a TIE-fighter squadron in orbit of Commenor's moon.

When they attempt to jump back to the Rebel base on Yavin 4 with the R2 units, they are therefore surprised to find Imperials blocking their progress. A battle ensues, during which Doc must sacrifice herself and her X-wing so the others can safely jump back home.

Safely back on Yavin 4, they mourn the loss of their fallen comrade just as her replacement--a kid from Tatooine named "Skywalker"--arrives.

(Ironically, this issue never features Rogue Squadron, but serves instead as a kind of introduction to its pre-cursor, Red Squadron.)

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-28 21:24:03.  [CVDB127974]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/star-wars-x-wing-rogue-squadron-12/4000-127974/</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-28 21:24:03.  [CVDB127974]</Notes>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <Month>02</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Michael A. Stackpole, Mike W. Barr</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gary Erskine, Gary Erskine</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gary Erskine, Gary Erskine</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dave Nestelle</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Christopher Moeller</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Bob Cooper, Dave Land</Editor>
  <Publisher>Dark Horse Comics</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/star-wars-x-wing-rogue-squadron-12/4000-127974/</Web>
  <PageCount>17</PageCount>
  <Characters>Biggs Darklighter, Cesi Eirriss, Garven Dreis, Jek Porkins, Luke Skywalker, Nera Dantels, R2-D2, Wedge Antilles</Characters>
  <Teams>Arcona, Astromech Droids, Galactic Empire, Jawas, Kitonaks, Kubaz, Pa'lowick, Quarrens, Rebel Alliance, Rogue Squadron, Stormtroopers, Sullustans, Twi'leks</Teams>
  <Locations>Yavin 4</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="726836" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="734246" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="675155" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="625750" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="609450" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1122524" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="671537" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="721635" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="566910" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="594560" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="681754" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="746708" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="674031" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="742532" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="876533" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="291773" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="653035" />
  </Pages>
<Genre>Science Fiction</Genre></ComicInfo>