<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Vault-Keeper (host),Santa Claus</Characters>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Editor>Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-100720</GTIN>
  <Inker>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:43:08 [Issue ID 4000-100720] urn:comicvine:4000-100720
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:51:38. [Issue ID 223250]</Notes>
  <Number>35</Number>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="2070" ImageSize="260022" ImageWidth="1433" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="2023" ImageSize="362357" ImageWidth="1394" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="2038" ImageSize="272332" ImageWidth="1426" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="2051" ImageSize="364420" ImageWidth="1408" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="2021" ImageSize="303619" ImageWidth="1382" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="331762" ImageWidth="1396" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="2035" ImageSize="307173" ImageWidth="1369" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="2051" ImageSize="323491" ImageWidth="1396" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="2035" ImageSize="343448" ImageWidth="1361" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="342600" ImageWidth="1400" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="2038" ImageSize="289932" ImageWidth="1395" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="2032" ImageSize="383780" ImageWidth="1387" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="2027" ImageSize="343299" ImageWidth="1399" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="2047" ImageSize="382651" ImageWidth="1399" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="2033" ImageSize="365835" ImageWidth="1386" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="2040" ImageSize="338626" ImageWidth="1396" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="2039" ImageSize="371709" ImageWidth="1387" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="2055" ImageSize="314290" ImageWidth="1399" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="2034" ImageSize="363063" ImageWidth="1396" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="313305" ImageWidth="1416" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="2042" ImageSize="330426" ImageWidth="1384" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="2044" ImageSize="388791" ImageWidth="1408" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="2040" ImageSize="384886" ImageWidth="1388" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="2047" ImageSize="321239" ImageWidth="1400" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="369179" ImageWidth="1401" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="365955" ImageWidth="1416" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="251785" ImageWidth="1408" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="2047" ImageSize="367165" ImageWidth="1420" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageHeight="2047" ImageSize="308936" ImageWidth="1392" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageHeight="2035" ImageSize="372122" ImageWidth="1404" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageHeight="2035" ImageSize="335262" ImageWidth="1412" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageHeight="2038" ImageSize="351152" ImageWidth="1424" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageHeight="2035" ImageSize="339864" ImageWidth="1420" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageHeight="1988" ImageSize="251451" ImageWidth="1444" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageHeight="2043" ImageSize="268482" ImageWidth="1400" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="218941" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Vault of Horror</Series>
  <Summary>...And All Through the House...: A terrific thud w/the fireplace poker and her husband Joseph lay dead on the floor. But then she heard her little girl upstairs, who asked her mommy if Santa Claus had come yet, and was told no and to go back to sleep. The wife then returned downstairs, cleaned off the poker, turned on the radio and heard an announcement of a maniac woman-killer dressed as Santa on the loose in the area. She wondered how she would be able to get rid of Joseph's body, when there was a knock at the door. She looked outside and saw a Santa at her door, the woman-killer, and paniced knowing she couldn't call the Police w/her husband's body there on the floor. Quickly she ran to every door and window, locking them, putting Joseph into a closet and then trying to board up windows from the inside. Going upstairs to check on Carol, her daughter, the woman was terrified when she found the little girl gone.....but more terrified when she went downstairs to see Carol having let in "Santa Claus"!

Tombs-Day!: The expedition, led by Professor Burton, neared the Pyramid of Khafra, the scene of the disappearance of a previous expedition. As they passed by the Sphinx, in legend called the "Father of Terrors", he told the accompanying journalist, Miss Allen facts about the previous expedition. Reaching the entrance to the pyramid, all entered to make a preliminary investigation when suddenly the massive stone panel they had entered through closed behind them, and a booby-trap killed of one the explorers. The group headed down some passages to find a possible exit, and as they proceeded, one by one members of the group were killed, leaving only Burton and Allen alive. As they made their way deeper into the pyramid, Burton told her that legend said the sphinx actally lived at one time, but Allen pooh-poohed the idea. Suddenly they came upon King Khafra's tomb, crawled through a passage and reached the interior to find all of Khafra's wealth and some hieroglyphics stating the legend of the sphinx was true.....just before the living sphinx sprang out and killed them!

Beauty Rest: Helen gazed out the window of the room she shared w/Joyce as the latter bid goodnight to a Mr. Boxer, the man she told Helen would help her to win a beauty contest the next day: "Miss Corpse of 1954"! Helen decided to play a trick on her roomie: she'd drug Joyce's drink w/sleeping pills, take a note Boxer had given to Joyce and appear in her place the next day. Helen gave the note to the man in charge, got into her suit and won the contest, being told to report that evening to an address for the award presentation. Arriving home, Helen found Joyce dead in bed [from an overdose of those pills], she called the Police and reported it as a suicide. Later Helen reported to the address she was given, but told the people there she had taken Joyce's spot.....a bad move, since she discovered that the wonner had to ACTUALLY be a corpse to win. That's the last she knew as the men came at her with scapels, rubber tubes and embalming fluid!

Shoe-Button Eyes!: The little boy celebrated the best Christmas he ever had because he could now see! Born blind, all he ever knew was the love of his mother, and the companionship of his teddy bear. His father died, so Mom remarried a cruel and vicious man who mistreated her. He always said that the little boy had "shoe-button" eyes, just like his teddy. One day, the little boy's mother became deathly ill, and he asked his step-dad to help her. He abused her, took the boy's bear and ripped the eyes off of it. Mom sewed on new button eyes before she died. Jed killed the boy, who regained his sight in heaven.

</Summary>
  <Tags>The Vault-Keeper,Santa Claus,The Crypt-Keeper,The Old Witch</Tags>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/vault-of-horror-35/4000-100720/</Web>
  <Writer>Jack Oleck,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Oleck</Writer>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>29</Count>
  <Title>...And All Through the House...; Tombs-Day!; Beauty Rest; Shoe-Button Eyes!</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>