<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Casey Femur,Francine,Tambi Baker,David Qin,Katchoo,Freddie Femur</Characters>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-179591</GTIN>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:46:56 [Issue ID 4000-179591] urn:comicvine:4000-179591
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:18:07. [Issue ID 179591]</Notes>
  <Number>24</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>Freddie is livid when he discovers Francine is having a hot and steamy love affair with a married man. Why couldn't it be him? Little does he know his own wife, Casey, is pursuing another man, David, who only has eyes for Katchoo! Make sense? Of course not! Don't miss this decidedly torrid issue of SIP, guaranteed to raise your blood pressure!

In a police station as soaking Casey accuses Freddie of telling her he paid for the painting of Francine. He claims he paid for it by spending a year with Francine. Francine shouts at him accusing him of being a borderline stalker while Katchoo casually chats with the desk officer.

Francine demands her Polaroids back and Casey wails that he hosed her down. Through the chaos a cop fires a gun and with the sudden quiet Katchoo starts to explain the story to the desk officer

*Flashback*
Francine, Katchoo, David and Casey are around the able eating and filling Francine in on what was going on. They tease but forgive Casey who suddenly remembers the painting of Francine was her reason for coming in the first place. Katchoo and Francine are stunned but Katchoo not for long and grabs her keys.

Freddie gets home and admires his acquisition until he hears Katchoo's voice. She throws him across the room and collects up all her paintings as Casey sees if he is alright and Francie demands her bikini back. Casey has enough and takes Freddie's Porsche driving it in reverse over neighbors gardens.

*Present*
Casey and Freddie get held but the rest leave as David and Katchoo discuss flying to New York to sort out the inheritance Francine feels left behind.

In a room Tambi is weight lifting before her on t e wall are three photograph,s two dark haired girls have their faces X'd out with Katchoo's photo in the middle.</Summary>
  <Title>I, Me, Mine</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-24-i-me-mine/4000-179591/</Web>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>