<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-361852</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:40:04 [Issue ID 4000-361852] urn:comicvine:4000-361852
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 01:38:06. [Issue ID 244828]</Notes>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Pines</Publisher>
  <Series>Out of the Shadows</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/out-of-the-shadows-6/4000-361852/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>10</Count>
  <Title>Salesman of Death; Requiem; Witch's Wish; Trapped from the Grave; The Secret One; Facts on the Fantastic; The Phantom Ship</Title>
  <Genre>Non-fiction,Detective-mystery,Horror-suspense,Fantasy</Genre>
  <Summary>Salesman of Death: An employee's ghost haunts his cruel boss. The dead salesman tries to sell his former employer on death. He kills the man's wife, destroys his factory, makes him a cripple and succeeds in the end.

Requiem: Summary of Mozart's being commissioned by a mystery man to compose his famous "Requiem" and dying in the process.

Witch's Wish: Young Madlyn discovers that her wishes become true. It is the spirit of Tess, a 300-year-old witch, who wants to take over the woman's body, though. A duel ensues, in which both women lose their lives.

Trapped from the Grave: Ghost of a murdered man leads his friends to his unknown grave.

The Secret One: Old man Harvey summons a demon, the "Secret One". After fulfilling Harvey's fantasies of revenge, the demon demands food - and goes after his new master.

Facts on the Fantastic: Allegedly true facts of how the people of the world deal with ghosts.

The Phantom Ship: The vicious sorceress Circe lures treasure hunters aboard her gold-filled phantom ship - and transforms them into giant rats.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>