<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Throttle,Vinnie,Greasepit,Lawrence Limburger,Dr. Karbunkle,Fred the Mutant,Modo,Charley Davidson</Characters>
  <Colorist>David Boller,Poncho Bemko</Colorist>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Editor>Mort Todd,Tom DeFalco</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-94414</GTIN>
  <Inker>Rick Ungar,Rick Ungar</Inker>
  <Letterer>Gary Fields</Letterer>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:34:34 [Issue ID 4000-94414] urn:comicvine:4000-94414
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-21 05:48:10. [Issue ID 94414]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="476698" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="458660" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="456539" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="539020" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="553976" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="490394" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="523784" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="488947" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="570676" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="492817" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="988980" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="539828" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="468483" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="607958" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="535979" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="540120" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="509810" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="525624" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="439012" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="597345" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="474390" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="528392" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="490533" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Rick Ungar,Rick Ungar</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Biker Mice from Mars</Series>
  <Summary>The three issues is an adaption of the first episode, "Rock 'n' Ride".

(Note:  Sometimes, the comic book will differ from the cartoon.  I will point these part out as I go along.)

The Biker Mice are back in the garage, talking with Charley.  You can see Modo's bionic hand in the foreground.  Vinnie is on the left, leaning against a filing cabnet, while Throttle is on the right, leaning against a desk.  Charley can't believe that she's been saved by a a "bunch of giant gerbils?!?", to which Throttle politely corrects her ("Mice, ma'am.  We're Mice.  Modo:  You were expecting maybe turtles?)  That's just as unbelieveable to Charley, especially "six-foot Mice...with motorcycles...and biker clothes.."

Vinnie:  Yo, sweetheart -- You forgot to mention studly bods!

Charley:  I've seen better!

Vinnie:  Maybe!  But not with this much charm!

(Note:  You'd have to hear him say that in the episode.)

The Mice explain to Charley where they come from.  Throttle then shows Charley by using what fans have come to call, "Touch-Telepathy":  His antennae glows as he touches her forehead with them.  Charley now sees Throttle's memories in her mind, as his voice accompanies the images she sees.

She first sees an ugly, brown planet.  This is the planet, Plutark.  An armada of ships stream from Plutark, on their way to stripmine other planets.

Then, she sees the Plutarkians on Mars, stripping it of its resources.  But an army of Mice --Throttle identifies them as the Freedom Fighters (on the show, he simply says "the Cavemouse population".)-- are fighting the Plutarkians.

(Note:  It's not clear in the comic, but in the show, you can see the leaders of the Mice.  They were Throttle, Modo, and Vinnie.)

Throttle breaks contact, but continues:

Throttle:  Modo gave an arm to the cause!  Vinnie had half his face taken off!

Vinnie:  Still cute, though!

(Note:  On the show, Vinnie's line was, "Yeah, but that's okay, because what's left is still grade-A Mouse material!"  To which Charley retorted:  "In your dreams!")

Charley then shows the Mice the scene outside of the garage.  Large, crab-like machines are digging holes in the ground.  These same machines were also on Mars.  In the words of Charley:  "They're Heeeeeeere!"

Meanwhile, a tire-covered Greasepit is confronted by his angry boss as to why the Last Chance Garage is still standing.  When Greasepit tells Limburger about the mice on motorcycles, the Plutarkian has a frightening notion.  He calls up his resident scientist, Dr. Karbunkle.  Karbunkle is, at the time, working on his ever-eager assistant, Fred, the Mutant.

(Fred looks different in the comic, than he does on the show.  His head is more skull-like, and his brain i exposed (Karbunkle seems to be driving a large nail into Fred's brain), and his human arm looks like its covered with fur.  The tentacle-arm is skeletal at the wrist.)

When Limburger tells Karbunkle about the Mice that was imprisoned on Mars, and that the Mice are here, on Earth, Karbunkle suddenly appears --crashing through the floor-- with a huge, metal trap.  There is a spring-loaded sitting area, and around it are several arms with huge, metal "teeth".

Back at the Last Chance, Charley is finishing her work on Throttle's bike.  She tells them that she also upgraded their weapons.  "This is Chicago, after all."  Vinnie touches a button on his bike (in the show, it was Modo), and two missles fire from the back and smash a hole though the metal bay door.  Charley leaves the garage through the hole to retrieve the missles, only to be captured by Greasepit.

Greasepit calls for the Mice, and when they look out, they see Charley sitting atop the mousetrap, bound and gagged, with Greasepit holding the trigger rope.  He tells the Mice that if they did not surrender, he'll pull the rope, and the trap would go "SNAP!" on Charley.  The Mice crash through the door on their motorcycles, causing Greasepit to drop the rope.  The thug reaches for it, but Modo fires at it and it breaks.  Throttle blasts the trap, sending the bound-but-no-longer-gagged Charley into the air.  She lands in Vinnie's arms.  The two rejoin Throttle and Modo as Greasepit tries to get away.  Modo shoots a grappling hook and rope at Greasepit, and the thug is once again bound.  Modo swings the thug around to Throttle, where a pair of missles appear from a hidden compartment in the seat.  Greasepit lands on the missles, and Throttle shoots him into the sky.

(Note:  In the show, Modo ties Greasepit up, and then pitches him to Throttle, who punches Greasepit in the direction of Limburger Tower.)

After a little light banter, the Mice go off to attack Limburger Tower.

Meanwhile, Greasepit sails through the sky, finally crashing through Limburger's office window.  Next momment, Limburger (half his mask is gone, showing part of his Plutarkian face) is storming into Karbunkle's lab, Greasepit right behind him.  The scientist then activates a transporter unit.  Inside, shown in silhouette, was a menacing figure that Karbunkle introduces as "The X-Terminator!"</Summary>
  <Tags>Throttle,Vinnie,Greasepit,Lawrence Limburger,Biker Mice from Mars,Dr. Karbunkle,Fred the Mutant,Modo,Charley Davidson</Tags>
  <Teams>Biker Mice from Mars</Teams>
  <Title>The Secret Origin</Title>
  <Volume>1993</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/biker-mice-from-mars-2-the-secret-origin/4000-94414/</Web>
  <Writer>Bob Forward,Rick Ungar</Writer>
  <Year>1993</Year>
  <Count>3</Count>
</ComicInfo>