<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Jumpstreet Siren,Jerry Smith,Jockbully,Rick Sanchez,Summer Smith,Robert,Morty Smith,Beth Smith,Pete</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ryan Hill,Ryan Hill</Colorist>
  <Day>24</Day>
  <Editor>Ari Yarwood,Robin Herrera</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-517067</GTIN>
  <Inker>Marc Ellerby,Marc Ellerby</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!,Crank!</Letterer>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:01:39 [Issue ID 4000-517067] urn:comicvine:4000-517067
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 14:48:08. [Issue ID 1538956]</Notes>
  <Number>11</Number>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="958386" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1256192" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1035424" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1078929" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1399014" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1364259" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1304596" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1133816" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1325482" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1581837" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1508591" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1347570" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1830999" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1555618" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1337367" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1097175" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1458354" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1680704" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1856278" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1121356" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1568029" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1399164" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1329836" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1090969" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="819376" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1456925" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Marc Ellerby,Marc Ellerby</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Oni Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Rick and Morty</Series>
  <Summary>READY PLAYER MORTY-Rick takes Morty to a High School Simulation planet that allows the player to accelerate his experience straight to a diploma in just one day*. Rick repeatedly kills Morty's character, forcing him to restart in more and more vicious (and sometimes illegal) HS experiences - until Morty does things the way Rick wants and finds himself on the brink of intergalactic war. But ultimately Morty will be Morty, no matter what universe or scenario. (*Not Accredited)

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                                                                  | Creator(s)            | Sidebar Location |
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover                                                         | CJ Cannon &amp; Ryan Hill | 1                |
 RI    | Retailer Incentive Cover                                              | Ben Sears             | 2                |
 RE    | Exceed Comic: A Divison of Jesse James Comics Exclusive Variant Cover | Mady G                | 3                |
 RE    | Convention Exclusive Cover                                            | Erica Hayes           | Missing          |
SynopsisTired of Morty being a dumb kid, Rick kidnaps Morty (who puts up quite the sleep fight) and takes him to a world that has a high school experiences simulator. The hope is that Morty will become a man sooner, yet continue to have the few time constraints of an adult in order to continue going on adventures. The two are surprised to find that Summer and her boyfriend Robert fell asleep in the ship. Robert is sent out into space while Summer is given the ship while Morty does his simulation.

During the simulation, Morty is pitted against a bully, a sexual encounter, and even a battle royale in order to graduate. Rick tries to sway Morty's decisions - even making him start over in some instances - but Morty wins out by doing things his own way. The ultimate test for graduation, however, proves a bit much when Morty must fight several hulking aliens. Rick gets the idea to put Morty into a deep sleep, which causes him to annihilate the competition in the simulation and thereby graduate.

During Morty's simulation, Summer learns that her father also fell asleep in the ship and is excited to join her on an adventure. Jerry flubs up, of course, by pushing a button in the ship that transfers his head onto Summer's body and vice versa. Jerry experiences a surge of confidence while Summer feels the futility of existence. 

Jerry gets a call (which Summer-as-Jerry answers) and hears Beth on the other end. Beth asks Jerry to come home to help her with something. The two head back home and Summer-as-Jerry meets up with Beth who is ready for a sexual rendezvous. Summer-as-Jerry naturally declines. During this awkward exchange, Jerry-as-Summer meets up with Summer's friends and invites them to a girlfriends' weekend. The four have a wonderful time.

Rick and Morty head back home, but Morty is less enthusiastic about the day's events. Rick promises not to put Morty through something like that again and then collects Robert from space. Rick then gathers and changes Jerry and Summer back and the five head home.

At home, Beth tells Jerry that his treatment of her sexual advances has only made her more intrigued by Jerry (who has no idea was Summer-as-Jerry said to Beth). Jerry is shocked when Beth hugs him. Summer walks past and tells her dad that he owes her.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-02 14:03:41.  [Issue ID 517067]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-11-ready-player-morty/4000-517067/</Summary>
  <Tags>Jumpstreet Siren,Jerry Smith,Jockbully,Rick Sanchez,Summer Smith,Robert,Morty Smith,Beth Smith,Pete</Tags>
  <Title>Ready Player Morty</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-11-ready-player-morty/4000-517067/</Web>
  <Writer>Pamela Ribon,Pamela Ribon</Writer>
  <Year>2016</Year>
  <Count>61</Count>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>