<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-4130</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:00:05 [Issue ID 4000-4130] urn:comicvine:4000-4130
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:41:24. [Issue ID 14778]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Atlas.1958)  (Pmack-Novus)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Strange Worlds</Series>
  <Summary>I Discovered the Secret of the Flying Saucers!: A man discovers that flying saucers are real, but are not actually ships, but alien beings able to travel through space on their own. They are often forced to crashland on Earth because of local radiation, and leave as quickly as possible.

I Captured the Abominable Snowman!: A man lies, cheats and steals to find the abominable snowman, and eventually discovers a lama who knows the secret of the snowman and is forced to summon it. He discovers that the snowman was a greedy man like him, cursed to wear a bestial form until another took his place. He is horrified as the snowman becomes human and he is transformed into a monster.

I Am Robot: A man creates a robot so advanced that it has the capacity to think and feel as a human. He entrusts his son to it, but when the robot is damaged while defending the child from alien abductors, the scientist's suspicious wife is convinced that it malfunctioned, and he abandons the project.

I Am the Last Man on Earth!: When the humans of a peaceful future discover a planet where they could live five times as long they all leave Earth, except for one couple who are too attached to Earth's heritage and are left on the abandoned world to refound civilization: Adam and Eve.

</Summary>
  <Teams>Marvel Monsters</Teams>
  <Title>I Discovered the Secret of the Flying Saucers!; I Captured the Abominable Snowman!; I Am Robot; I Am the Last Man on Earth!</Title>
  <Volume>1958</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strange-worlds-1-i-discovered-the-secret-of-the-fl/4000-4130/</Web>
  <Year>1958</Year>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Stan Lee,Larry Lieber,Stan Lee,Larry Lieber</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jack Kirby,Steve Ditko,Don Heck,Jack Kirby,Steve Ditko,Don Heck</Penciller>
  <Inker>Christopher Rule,Steve Ditko,Don Heck,Christopher Rule,Steve Ditko,Don Heck</Inker>
  <Colorist>Stan Goldberg,Stan Goldberg</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Artie Simek,John Duffy,Artie Simek,John Duffy</Letterer>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>