<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Werewolf By Night,Roxanna,Father Vincent Adobe</Characters>
  <Colorist>Mariana Manco</Colorist>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Editor>Joe Andreani</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-108997</GTIN>
  <Inker>Leonardo Manco</Inker>
  <Letterer>Janice Chiang</Letterer>
  <Locations>New York City,New York State</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:18:40 [Issue ID 4000-108997] urn:comicvine:4000-108997
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 17:17:42. [Issue ID 108997]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Leonardo Manco</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
  <Summary>In a rural part of New York state, Jack Russell visits his friend and former co-worker Fred. Fred was crippled while working in the sewers of the city when a large metal grate fell on him. Jack had transformed to the Werewolf, lifted the grate off of him and carried him to safety. Although Jack suspects his friend knows his secret, Fred's never talked about it.

Some time later, Jack wanders the docks above his underground cell and he comes across the misshapen cripple who watches over him when he's locked up as the Werewolf. Jack tries to befriend him, but the man scoots away until Jack transforms and his watcher recognizes him. Jack asks him what his story is and the man, who calls himself Lump explains.

He was born to circus acrobats, but his father rejected him because of his birth defects and because his mother died during his birth. At first, he was raised by the bearded lady, but eventually, she too neglected Lump. He found an affinity with the beasts kept by the circus, but as he became older, he was forced to be a clown to earn his food and board. In the middle of a gig in Central Park, the circus went bankrupt and Lump joined the legions of New York's homeless. Finally one night, Lump heard the howls of the Werewolf from his cell, and has watched him ever since.

Jack promises Lump he'll return to see him, then pays a visit to his priest friend, Father Vince Adobe. Lastly, he goes to see his girlfriend Roxanna, carrying a bouquet of roses.</Summary>
  <Tags>Werewolves,Werewolf By Night,Roxanna,Father Vincent Adobe</Tags>
  <Teams>Werewolves</Teams>
  <Title>New Face Revealed</Title>
  <Volume>1998</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-5-new-face-revealed/4000-108997/</Web>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Leonardo Manco</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>