<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Catherine,Donald,Egon Spengler,Jason,Peter Venkman,Ray Stantz,Slimer,Winston Zeddemore</Characters>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Katherine Llewellyn,Tony Caputo</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-161175</GTIN>
	<Inker>David Mowry,Gary Fields</Inker>
	<Letterer>Jorge Pacheco</Letterer>
	<Month>6</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:59:50 [Issue ID 4000-161175] urn:comicvine:4000-161175</Notes>
	<Number>2</Number>
	<PageCount>36</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="206143" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="202156"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="186370"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="197354"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="204956"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="209501"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="199819"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="216505"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="211136"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="190253"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="217560"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="185412"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="209552"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="216339"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="96086"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="129760"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="174581"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="173059"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="192262"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="177996"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="199860"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="174913"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="193948"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="189260"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="197022"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="176462"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="127537"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="157662"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="128822"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="249427"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="142328"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="209061"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="26691"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="20786"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="245841"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="34722"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>David Schwartz,Gary Fields</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Now Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Slimer!</Series>
	<Summary>Slime Floods!

Slimer is out of money and hungry. Slimer asks his friend Manx the cat if he will share is food. Manx refuses to share and sends Slimer on his way. Slimer runs into his friend Rudy. Rudy offers to pay him to clear the snow out of Clinton Street. Slimer starts his job, but finds it hard to shovel the snow. Luckily, his slime melts snow. Slimer dances his way all over Clinton Street melting all the snow. Unfortunately Slimer melts all the snow and creates a flood. The water comes rushing down the street. Thinking quickly Slimer puts on his mittens and creates a dam of snow. The water rushes towards a construction site. At the construction site Slimer sees Manx eating in a dumpster. He tries to warn Manx, but he doesn't listen and gets caught in the flood.

Slimer gets his money from Rudy and sees the Junior Ghostbusters running off to a new ice skating rink. It turns out that the flood water froze at the construction site and made a ice rink. And the kids get up to the ice rink by climbing up an ice block which has Manx frozen in it..

Improving Business

Slimer visits his favorite restaurant only to have the owner Rafael to kick him out for hurting business. However the owner invites Manx the cat in to have some dinner. The cook, Luigi, kicks the cat away for playing in the spaghetti. Luigi makes a special meal for Slimer. Rafael and the cat hear Slimer eating his dinner and the Manx gets an idea. If he can scare Slimer away the owner will let him eat anything he wants. So Manx dresses up as a ghost and scares Luigi and Rafael. Slimer thinks he can stop this new ghost but Manx sneaks up behind him and scares him. Manx jumps at Slimer, but goes right through him. Slimer realizes that the ghost is Manx and so does the owner. Manx wrecks the restaurant throwing plates everywhere trying to hit Slimer. Luigi gives Slimer a big bag of catnip. Slimer pours the catnip over Manx who goes crazy and bounces all over the restaurant. Rafeal kicks Manx out into the alley.

Rafael is distraught, his restaurant is ruined, but Slimer can help. They tape a table and some plates together and serve a new special "Chicken-Catch-A-Cat-Tory."

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/slimer-2-slime-floods/4000-161175/</Summary>
	<Tags>Catherine,Donald,Egon Spengler,Ghostbusters,Jason,Junior Ghostbusters,Peter Venkman,Ray Stantz,Slimer,Winston Zeddemore</Tags>
	<Teams>Ghostbusters,Junior Ghostbusters</Teams>
	<Title>Slime Floods!</Title>
	<Volume>1989</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/slimer-2-slime-floods/4000-161175/</Web>
	<Writer>Hilarie Staton</Writer>
	<Year>1989</Year>
</ComicInfo>