<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Staired... in Horror!; Dead Wait!; 99 44/100% Pure Horror!; A Stitch in Time!; What the Dog Dragged In!; Gone...Fishing!; The Monster in the Ice!; Fountains of Youth!; Trapped!; Child's Play; That's a 'Croc'!; One Last Fling!; Revenge is the Nuts!; Grandma's Ghost!!; The Reluctant Vampire!; About Face!; Reunion!; Daddy Lost His Head!; The Jellyfish!; Southern Hospitality!; Dying to Lose Weight!; The Mask of Horror; Lend Me a Hand!; Sink-Hole!</Title>
  <Series>The EC Archives: The Vault of Horror</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Volume>2021</Volume>
  <Summary>Staired... in Horror!: Irma stared down at the grave of her late husband and smiled....just as a gentleman came near to pay respects to his late wife. As the two conversed, Irma gleaned that this old boy must have money, so she struck up an on-going affair with this Mr. Hornsby, and plotted to have him murdered for his insurance.....just the way she murdered her first husband, Herman, for his! Soon, Robert popped the question and Irma accepted, and after their marriage, they went to his palatial country estate. But suddenly, as she looked up the carpeted winding staircase, the scene came back to her of the lighthouse steps she went up with Herman....and where she pushed him over the railing to his death! Soon the bickering started....Robert wanted to still visit his former wife's grave and Irma forbid it, eventually leading to his very ill health. Then one night, Robert bolted from his bed for the cemetery to visit his beloved Ethyl one more time, where he died from a fatal heart attack on her grave. Back at the estate, Iram was contemplating tearing out the spiral staircase when she looked up to see the the rotting corpses of Herman and Ethyl coming at her. She raced up the spiral steps to escape into the balcony bedroom when she remembered that she had had them sealed shut! In the morning, all that was found were the remains of two rotting corpses, and the body of Irma.....smashed into tiny little pieces!

Dead Wait!: In an isolated plantation home on a tropic isle, 'Red' Buckley's former plantation boss lies dead at his feet. In the shadows, a native, Kulu, watches Buckley get into the home's safe and remove a black pearl, then they enter a boat for a three day trip to Banggai. As Kulu paddles down the river, Buckley tells Kulu he will be paid off at Banggai.....then 'Red' discovers that they are heading for a village instead. When Buckley turns around to question the native, Kulu kills him with a machette....and proudly walks into the village with his prize: a human head with red hair!

99 44/100% Pure Horror!: Life had been good to Ernie ever since he had become manager of the Hudson Soap Company, and his predecessor, Benny Anderson, had disappeared. Benny had been his boss, really giving him a hard time in the soap plant, until one day he knifed Benny and threw his body in the rending vat, and made bars of soap out of him. The best thing is that no one could prove what had really happened to Benny. Then came the night that Ernie had a date with a showgirl and decided to take a shower, using one of those bars of soap. Benny ended up getting revenge on Ernie.

A Stitch in Time!: An old-fashioned sweatshop, run by Mr. Lasch, makes the women work 14 hours a day, 6 days a week, for a salary of $6, using dangerous, outdated machinery, and being treated like slaves. Complainers were forced to go the "scrap box”: a place where scraps of cloth and thread were thrown together and they would have to untangle it all and respool the thread, a job that usually drove the woman insane. But they had a plan to get even, much to Mr. Lasch's regret!

What the Dog Dragged In!: Blind Betty's dog Jerry is hit by a car but cared for by wealthy Roger Cartwright, who returned her dog to her. Betty was happy to have company and invited him back, which he did and they soon grew quite close. One day, as Roger left her house in his car, he didn't see the truck coming from the other direction. Betty sent Jerry after him and day after day Jerry returned without Roger. Until one day Jerry came in with Roger.

Gone...Fishing!: Max was a noted sport fisherman, but Steven hated the sport, which he considered cruelty to animals. Max outfitted his reel with the latest gadgets and cast into the water. Soon he got a strike and reeled in his beauty. Steven, sick to his stomach, went back to the car and drove off, taking Max's lunch with it. Spotting a candy bar on the beach, he shoved it in his mouth, never noticing the thin, silky, nearly invisible thread attached to it. When Steven returned, he saw the horrible sight of Max bobbing up out of the water and being drawn farther and farther out to sea!

The Monster in the Ice!: As Gerald Dawson sits as his desk in a shack in the Arctic, Herbert Campbell enters, telling him that their Eskimo guide refuses to take them any further. Dawson goes to see Lomo in his igloo, and the Eskimo tells him of the monster in the ice, and that no one who sees it comes back in their right mind. Dawson &amp; Campbell rig up a dog-sled and go to the site, spot the monster and dig its ice-encased body out and take it back to their shack. They show the body in ice to Lomo and he freezes in fear, especially when he is ordered to chip the body out of the ice! While that is happening, Dawson and Campbell kick back, telling themselves that this whole thing reminds them of Mary Shelly's book about Frankenstein. Suddenly, they hear a scream and a crash, and enter the adjoining room and see the window broken out and Lomo shaking in fear. Now they know the creature must be put back into the ice, so they go out and dig through the ice to water, and they hope to lure the monster into the trap. The monster shows up....jumps into the hole and drags both men down with him. One year later, the U.S. Air Force decides to build a base near that very spot and two airmen happen to spot the bodies trapped in the ice. So......they start digging out the bodies to see what they can determine what happened to them.....

Fountains of Youth!: Eileen responds to a newspaper ad asking for a traveling companion for a heavily veiled Madam DuBois, who is traveling abroad, even though her brother Ken is not too happy with the idea. Then she and Madam DuBois board a cruise ship. Unfortunately, Eileen mysteriously passes away, and Ken investigates. A shipboard doctor informs him that Madam DuBois is similar to a human vampire, who prolongs its life by sapping the youth of their victims. By the time the pair get to DuBois' cabin, her next victim is already withering and dying before their eyes!

Trapped!: Inside a moving railroad boxcar, Marty encounters an old hobo, who informs Marty that the Smoky Mountain area is haunted. Soon a railroad policeman forces them to jump off the train, and the hobo dies. Marty makes his way to a farmhouse inhabited by an old man, whom Marty kills and buries. A mysterious, screaming fly follows Marty back to the house, so he decides the place is cursed, grabs his bag of swag, and runs out, getting caught in the sticky earth of the grave.....just like a fly gets stuck on flypaper!

Child's Play: As a group of boys were playing football in front of Mr. Collin's house, they were rudely told by him to get away from the front of his home or he'd call the Police. So they moved down the street, but when the football accidently fell into his yard, he wouldn't give it back. Later. Collin's wife, Emma, gave it back to the boys when Milton was asleep.....but he found out and slapped his wife around. The next day, as the boys were passing by the Collin's home, they yearned for some apples off his tree, but when they attempted to get a few, he came out, took his belt off and was going to hit them when his wife came out to put a stop to it.....and Collin's struck her instead. The next day, feeling sorry for Emma Collins, the boys waited until Milton left and then went to the door to surprise her with some candy.....but they were told she was dead. The next day, they watched the funeral and interment from a distance....and then plotted to scare the pants off Mr. Collins. That night, as Collins was resting on his backporch, he glimpsed movement in the darkness and an eerie voice, purporting to be that of his wife, began calling to him. As he walked out into the yard, a ghostly apparition suddenly appeared, asking him why he had killed her. He apologized for doing it, then pitched forward....stone dead!

That's a 'Croc'!: At the local zoo, people crowd around the newest attraction: a pit with four crocodiles in it, and along comes Mr. Coogan, the zoo keeper and lover of these ferocious animals, to feed them their daily ration of meat. But when a young boy reminds him that these animals are MAN eaters and maybe they don't like being fed other types of meat, it makes him stop and think. That evening, he heads to town and kills someone and feeds them to his charges. Meanwhile, at the home of Norman Simms, family members discover him to be missing and they begin to backtrack his steps to locate him, without success. Back at the zoo, "Crazy" Coogan is over-seeing the cleaning of the crocodile pit when one of the men, Lou, discovers a ring on the floor and pockets it secretly. Later, in town, Lou stops in for a drink and sits down next to Norman Simm's relative, who has just learned others have disappeared in town mysteriously....then he sees Simm's ring on the finger of Lou, who tells him where he got it. Two and two are added together, and the angry men in the bar head for the zoo to confront Coogan. When Coogan sees them coming, he jumps into the crocodile pit, thinking these creatures will protect him.....instead, they devour him!

One Last Fling!: A knife-throwing act in Hungary was extremely popular. Harry woke up the next day and couldn't rouse Olga, whom he thought was dead. He made burial arrangements, then discovered that Olga was a vampire. Harry decided the act would change and go to the U.S. where Harry became her victim. She continued to feed on him, until one night, at the end of the knife-throwing act, he announced he was going to commit a murder, then threw a wooden stake at his wife's heart before collapsing in death on the stage!

Revenge is the Nuts!: At the eerie Croydon Insane Asylum, horrible screams are heard as patients are being whipped, and as Mr. Aldershot, a relative of a patient, is in Blackpool's office in response to a letter from his patient-relative. Blackpool tells him that these people are filled with evil spirits and his "treatments" are the only way to deal with the patients...and he kicks the man out. Blackpool then retreats to the dungeon-basement area and has the patient taken back to the ward, where the other patients are shocked by what has happened. As days drag by, Blackpool continues to tease and mistreat the patients, unknowing that the patients have decided to strike back. That evening, as Blackpool sat in his office, the door bursts in and the patients drag him to the dungeon, and to the cell of an insane patient named Olaf [many times maltreated himself], and gleefully watch as Olaf tears him apart!

Grandma's Ghost!!: Little Peggy is awoken from her sleep by her Grandmother, who is having a heat attack. She asks for her pills, but they are not to be found on the nightstand, and by the time Peggy finds them in another room, her Grandmother has passed away. After the funeral, Peggy's Aunt Helen and Uncle Lawrence were celebrating with each other, thinking they have inherited all of the old woman's money. But at the reading of the will, they learn the money goes to Peggy....at the age of 22....so they plot to kill her. Meanwhile, Peggy is seeking out the friendship of the gardner, who pays more attention to her that her aunt and uncle. That evening, Peggy tells her "new folks" that Grandma came to see her and told her that the gardner was a fine man to associate with....but her aunt and uncle say NO! The next day, all three go on a picnic and Uncle Lawrence sees an opportunity to push Peggy off a cliff. Unfortunately, he goes over the cliff instead when Peggy "sees" her Grandma and moves out of the way. Later that day, Aunt Helen is already counting the fortune as hers, and grabs Peggy by the arm to the basement, opens the furnace door to push her in when Peggy sees her Grandma again.....as does Helen....and Helen falls back into the flames! Peggy then becomes the responsibility of the gardner.

The Reluctant Vampire!: Mr. Drink, a vampire, has a job as night watchman at the local Blood Donor Center, and he has used this job to secure his daily supply of blood, then doctors the books to make everything appear legitimate. But one evening, the record book is missing, forcing him to kill someone to replace the blood he has supped on. When Drink discovers that the blood center is to be closed unless the facility takes in twice the amount of blood it does now, Drink decides to kill more victims to restock the shelves. The center's director reports this to the Police, bringing the case to an unusual end.

About Face!: Lydia was a circus lion tamer and considered the best, until one evening she was attacked and severely injured by a black panther. After her recovery, she took to wearing a veil and literally retired from the world. She began to pore over books on witchcraft, hoping to find a solution when her chauffeur, Steve, began to act as if he was in love with her. When he took her money and ran off with another woman, Lydia swore revenge and cast a spell restoring her face but, in Florida, Steve's face had become rotting flesh!

Reunion!: Lillian was much too young when she married Waldo, and, soon, he began to age. One night at a party, she met Roger, fell in love and agreed to get a divorce from Waldo. Unfortunately, Waldo fell ill with polio and needed constant attention and Lillian told Roger she just couldn't go through with the divorce. They vowed to meet by the lake every five years to see if they can finally be together, but Roger is killed in a train wreck. Still, three years later, she visited the lake again, this time to be greeted by Roger's rotting corpse!

Daddy Lost His Head!: Martin Blackson hates his stepdaughter Kathy because she reminds him of his wife's first husband. When Kathy meets neighbor Mrs. Thaumaturge, Martin intervenes and tells Kathy to leave that "witch" alone or she'll bake her in her oven! After Kathy's mother dies, Mrs. Thaumaturge gives Kathy a man-shaped candy doll. Although Kathy swears she'll never eat it, later while Martin cuts wood, Kathy bites the doll's left hand, then hears a scream as Martin has cut off his left hand. When he hears about the doll, Martin demands Kathy hand it over, but she proves it isn't evil by biting off its head!

The Jellyfish!: Charles and Howard Norton, of Norton's Pharmaceutical Company, are having an argument. It seems the company has received an order for one million hypodermic inserts for insulin, but can only make 500,000. Not wanting to lose the order, Charles muses that they could dilute each insert by half, and thereby still provide the one million inserts. Howard refuses, calling it criminal, and Charles calls him a spineless jellyfish! Charles dilutes them anyway and many patients die, with Howard going to jail. When he is released, Howard visits his brother, exacting his revenge in an unusual way.

Southern Hospitality!: Abner Scanlon was a gigolo who disliked work and preyed on rich women. When he marries a young girl from one of the South's richest clans, he discovers that she has no money at all. Greedy for money, Abner sells the family's antique vase and begins living it up, leading to a violent outburst and Aunt Martha dying from a heart attack. When he removes great-great grandfather's picture out of a valuable frame in order to sell the frame, Claudia's father dies. Claudia later hears a scream from the attic, and enters to find Abner dead on the floor, pierced by a sword....

Dying to Lose Weight!: In a small town populated by many fat people, a weird Dr. Perdo comes to town, offering to help those people through the use of a tiny weight-loss capsule. Four accept his offer and the capsule works on them to perfection. But then, the four people suddenly die horrible deaths, as if they had starved to death. Six months later, Perdo, in disguise, returns to the town, but is discovered and runs into the cemetery to hide in the mausoleum of one of his victims, where he comes face-to-face with the thing that had killed his victims: a giant tapeworm!

The Mask of Horror: Ken Anders stops off at an eerie costume shop to get a costume for a party, and the weird owner outfits him with a mask and costume that is supposed to represent his true self: that of a rotting corpse. His fiancée refuses to go to the party with him, so he leaves devastated. He puts the mask on and heads to the party, and meets a woman dressed as a vampire and falls for her. They head into the garden to unmask and he discovers she really is a vampire, who then attacks him. Anders drowns her in a lily pond....but then notes his reflection in the pond with terrifying results!

Lend Me a Hand!: Eminent physician Dr. Johnson is the victim of a car accident and loses his hand, which means his career is finished. After reading an article in a medical journal about keeping tissue alive by a chemical and mechanical apparatus, the doctor decides to kill a drunk to get a hand to replace the one he lost, with some very unfortunate results!

Sink-Hole!: A lonely woman, who had joined a lonely hearts club, accepts a marriage proposal by mail, but when she meets him, he is actually much older than she had realized. After she meets the new area health inspector, Rick Hudson, and falls for him, she murders her husband and dumps him into the well on their property so she can carry on a romance with Hudson. Then she discovers that Hudson is married and leaving town. Disappointed beyond hope, she goes over to the well to draw some water to quench her mounting thirst and gets a REAL surprise!

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-20 19:36:07.  [CVDB931461]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-09 20:32:32. [Issue ID 2405789]</Notes>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Day>25</Day>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Ray Bradbury,William Gaines,Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Ray Bradbury,William Gaines</Writer>
  <Penciller>Graham Ingels,Howard Larsen,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Howard Larsen</Penciller>
  <Inker>Graham Ingels,Howard Larsen,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Howard Larsen</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Johnny Craig</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Dark Horse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-ec-archives-the-vault-of-horror-2-volume-2/4000-931461/</Web>
  <PageCount>216</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1377509" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1662557" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1947186" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1668523" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1765743" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1645812" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1626089" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1376391" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1633409" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1681599" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1582005" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1636167" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1636704" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1434714" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1548365" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1310587" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1205866" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1668856" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1739517" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1518672" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1585441" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1513614" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1527550" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1403115" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1543423" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1562133" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1409459" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1489959" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1593098" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1773658" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1598671" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1350659" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="1503912" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="1412950" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="1430282" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="1570685" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="1526914" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="1520169" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="1465245" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="1572811" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="1676739" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="1315086" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="1561660" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="1459630" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="1553113" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="1601468" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="1592993" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="1470603" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="1462817" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="1396079" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="1334651" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="1850649" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="1700010" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="1731034" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="1823644" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="1883767" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="1696399" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="1533049" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="1641116" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="1444338" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="1556079" />
    <Page Image="61" ImageSize="1640912" />
    <Page Image="62" ImageSize="1631776" />
    <Page Image="63" ImageSize="1481386" />
    <Page Image="64" ImageSize="1473560" />
    <Page Image="65" ImageSize="1405972" />
    <Page Image="66" ImageSize="1584671" />
    <Page Image="67" ImageSize="1354062" />
    <Page Image="68" ImageSize="911723" />
    <Page Image="69" ImageSize="1660572" />
    <Page Image="70" ImageSize="1636548" />
    <Page Image="71" ImageSize="1664737" />
    <Page Image="72" ImageSize="1685653" />
    <Page Image="73" ImageSize="1702461" />
    <Page Image="74" ImageSize="1533782" />
    <Page Image="75" ImageSize="1277346" />
    <Page Image="76" ImageSize="1632374" />
    <Page Image="77" ImageSize="1718201" />
    <Page Image="78" ImageSize="1844370" />
    <Page Image="79" ImageSize="1764209" />
    <Page Image="80" ImageSize="1757970" />
    <Page Image="81" ImageSize="1584854" />
    <Page Image="82" ImageSize="1265771" />
    <Page Image="83" ImageSize="1224240" />
    <Page Image="84" ImageSize="1112917" />
    <Page Image="85" ImageSize="1471973" />
    <Page Image="86" ImageSize="1466676" />
    <Page Image="87" ImageSize="1461330" />
    <Page Image="88" ImageSize="1521901" />
    <Page Image="89" ImageSize="1493382" />
    <Page Image="90" ImageSize="1547322" />
    <Page Image="91" ImageSize="1336700" />
    <Page Image="92" ImageSize="1394619" />
    <Page Image="93" ImageSize="1248736" />
    <Page Image="94" ImageSize="1392908" />
    <Page Image="95" ImageSize="1469248" />
    <Page Image="96" ImageSize="1546484" />
    <Page Image="97" ImageSize="1375555" />
    <Page Image="98" ImageSize="1474504" />
    <Page Image="99" ImageSize="1421437" />
    <Page Image="100" ImageSize="1456398" />
    <Page Image="101" ImageSize="1701916" />
    <Page Image="102" ImageSize="1019035" />
    <Page Image="103" ImageSize="1828000" />
    <Page Image="104" ImageSize="1668786" />
    <Page Image="105" ImageSize="1759342" />
    <Page Image="106" ImageSize="1732252" />
    <Page Image="107" ImageSize="1673177" />
    <Page Image="108" ImageSize="1623461" />
    <Page Image="109" ImageSize="1485758" />
    <Page Image="110" ImageSize="1695080" />
    <Page Image="111" ImageSize="1658281" />
    <Page Image="112" ImageSize="1484399" />
    <Page Image="113" ImageSize="1583167" />
    <Page Image="114" ImageSize="1630948" />
    <Page Image="115" ImageSize="1423407" />
    <Page Image="116" ImageSize="1337294" />
    <Page Image="117" ImageSize="1356688" />
    <Page Image="118" ImageSize="1363946" />
    <Page Image="119" ImageSize="1550425" />
    <Page Image="120" ImageSize="1363589" />
    <Page Image="121" ImageSize="1393843" />
    <Page Image="122" ImageSize="1451456" />
    <Page Image="123" ImageSize="1401269" />
    <Page Image="124" ImageSize="1564043" />
    <Page Image="125" ImageSize="1423694" />
    <Page Image="126" ImageSize="1413257" />
    <Page Image="127" ImageSize="1354114" />
    <Page Image="128" ImageSize="1356066" />
    <Page Image="129" ImageSize="1407763" />
    <Page Image="130" ImageSize="1514073" />
    <Page Image="131" ImageSize="1519172" />
    <Page Image="132" ImageSize="1472314" />
    <Page Image="133" ImageSize="1420842" />
    <Page Image="134" ImageSize="1487733" />
    <Page Image="135" ImageSize="1532441" />
    <Page Image="136" ImageSize="793365" />
    <Page Image="137" ImageSize="1609477" />
    <Page Image="138" ImageSize="1535843" />
    <Page Image="139" ImageSize="1546220" />
    <Page Image="140" ImageSize="1460787" />
    <Page Image="141" ImageSize="1543784" />
    <Page Image="142" ImageSize="1499702" />
    <Page Image="143" ImageSize="1599125" />
    <Page Image="144" ImageSize="1610222" />
    <Page Image="145" ImageSize="1571746" />
    <Page Image="146" ImageSize="1688708" />
    <Page Image="147" ImageSize="1709092" />
    <Page Image="148" ImageSize="1651729" />
    <Page Image="149" ImageSize="1575781" />
    <Page Image="150" ImageSize="1335030" />
    <Page Image="151" ImageSize="1281210" />
    <Page Image="152" ImageSize="1242989" />
    <Page Image="153" ImageSize="1606817" />
    <Page Image="154" ImageSize="1394979" />
    <Page Image="155" ImageSize="1378704" />
    <Page Image="156" ImageSize="1434000" />
    <Page Image="157" ImageSize="1382621" />
    <Page Image="158" ImageSize="1533961" />
    <Page Image="159" ImageSize="1299873" />
    <Page Image="160" ImageSize="1168530" />
    <Page Image="161" ImageSize="1446182" />
    <Page Image="162" ImageSize="1378772" />
    <Page Image="163" ImageSize="1282936" />
    <Page Image="164" ImageSize="1345405" />
    <Page Image="165" ImageSize="1445193" />
    <Page Image="166" ImageSize="1470333" />
    <Page Image="167" ImageSize="1257825" />
    <Page Image="168" ImageSize="1250830" />
    <Page Image="169" ImageSize="1527230" />
    <Page Image="170" ImageSize="1466030" />
    <Page Image="171" ImageSize="1659643" />
    <Page Image="172" ImageSize="1558855" />
    <Page Image="173" ImageSize="1701131" />
    <Page Image="174" ImageSize="1575246" />
    <Page Image="175" ImageSize="1562377" />
    <Page Image="176" ImageSize="1682755" />
    <Page Image="177" ImageSize="1356583" />
    <Page Image="178" ImageSize="1739054" />
    <Page Image="179" ImageSize="1676828" />
    <Page Image="180" ImageSize="1633915" />
    <Page Image="181" ImageSize="1768219" />
    <Page Image="182" ImageSize="1611417" />
    <Page Image="183" ImageSize="1507879" />
    <Page Image="184" ImageSize="1425518" />
    <Page Image="185" ImageSize="1346467" />
    <Page Image="186" ImageSize="1249514" />
    <Page Image="187" ImageSize="1630963" />
    <Page Image="188" ImageSize="1656906" />
    <Page Image="189" ImageSize="1593769" />
    <Page Image="190" ImageSize="1626448" />
    <Page Image="191" ImageSize="1621117" />
    <Page Image="192" ImageSize="1734906" />
    <Page Image="193" ImageSize="1543413" />
    <Page Image="194" ImageSize="1597630" />
    <Page Image="195" ImageSize="1490843" />
    <Page Image="196" ImageSize="1624136" />
    <Page Image="197" ImageSize="1609745" />
    <Page Image="198" ImageSize="1574739" />
    <Page Image="199" ImageSize="1547439" />
    <Page Image="200" ImageSize="1468056" />
    <Page Image="201" ImageSize="1100682" />
    <Page Image="202" ImageSize="1078189" />
    <Page Image="203" ImageSize="1497509" />
    <Page Image="204" ImageSize="903166" />
    <Page Image="205" ImageSize="768393" />
    <Page Image="206" ImageSize="818007" />
    <Page Image="207" ImageSize="892116" />
    <Page Image="208" ImageSize="477058" />
    <Page Image="209" ImageSize="452783" />
    <Page Image="210" ImageSize="473705" />
    <Page Image="211" ImageSize="354707" />
    <Page Image="212" ImageSize="852826" />
    <Page Image="213" ImageSize="130117" />
    <Page Image="214" ImageSize="19653" />
    <Page Image="215" ImageSize="1422007" />
  </Pages>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Collection</Format>
  <Characters>The Old Witch (host),Robert Hornsby,Irma Leechman</Characters>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>