<ComicInfo>
  <Title>The Deathsnake, Part Three; Saturday Night in Palmettoville; On the Loose</Title>
  <Series>The Deathsnake</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-03 22:38:05.  [CVDB160294]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 23:51:27. [Issue ID 351874]</Notes>
  <Year>1995</Year>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Writer>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Writer>
  <Penciller>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Penciller>
  <Inker>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Inker>
  <Letterer>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>John Blackburn</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Tom Verre,Jeremy Pinkham,Carol Gnojewski</Editor>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Adult</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deathsnake-3/4000-160294/</Web>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Banks (guard),Jack Brady (warden)</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="69714" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="388950" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="473750" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="409778" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="474392" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="476272" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="374794" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="353960" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="436382" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="422572" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="517216" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="461084" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="491126" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="436076" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="459320" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="438654" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="446086" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="369244" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="406490" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="408442" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="414542" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="414966" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="309776" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>The Deathsnake, Part Three: Banks tells Jack that the two convicts were beaten, their guard handcuffed, and the body of Coley missing from its grave. At which point, Coley uses dynamite on Jack's precious bridge.

Saturday Night in Palmettoville: In Palmettoville, Rev. Turner has a mob all hot &amp; angry about the Bishop Theatre showing Coley's latest film, "Voodoo Lovegod". With Coley now a fugitive, it's turned into a lynch mob. Sammy O'Hara, last seen in IDOL OF FLESH, is on hand to cover the "event". Harry discovers that Chief Beasley is not a typical cop, and befriends him. Coley goes to Miz Liza for more of the voodoo drug, then sneaks into the Courthouse to confront Judge O'Hara with the evidence against Warden Jack Brady. Shocked at the brutality and insanity of Brady &amp; his daughter, the Judge decides to repeal Coley's jail sentence. At that point, Jack, Delilah &amp; Daniel show up, determined to kill Coley. Things get really nasty, and Coley's life is only saved via his use of the voodoo drug-- and the Judge shooting Delilah in the head. Atop the Courthouse, Jack confronts Coley one final time. 6 months later, back in California, Kit is shocked when Coley turns up-- horny as ever.

On the Loose: Jack and Brady survey the damage. Jack figures that instead of heading for safety in Florida, Coley will come back to Palmettoville. In the swamp, Coley decides to do just that, mistakenly thinking Jack will have helicopters after him if he heads for Florida. But more, Coley's business in Palmettoville isn't finished. Carrying the stolen evidence, he heads back to town, thinking, "I'll show THEM th' deathsnake."

</Summary>
  <AgeRating>Adults Only</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>