<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Kent Menace</Series>
  <Number>0</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Volume>2021</Volume>
  <Genre>Fantasy,Superhero</Genre>
  <Summary>Ahoy Mates! Here's your chance to discover Scott Braden and Mike Malbrough's KENT MENACE:, the all-new weird hero whose comic book debut Diamond Comic Distributors President &amp; CEO Steve Geppi says "crackles with energy and overflows with possibility." Valiant Entertainment Senior Editor Lysa Hawkins describes the Mysterious Mariner thusly: "A little dash of pulp, a sprinkle of camp, KENT MENACE is what happens if Doc Savage, Namor, and The Tick [were] fused into one!" Book passage now for the introductory issue of the Supernatural Sailor's epic saga with KENT MENACE #0: THE DIRECTOR'S CUT, featuring two stories chronicling the very beginning of KENT MENACE's mighty journey from comic book character to three-dimensional weird hero! This special issue includes comic stories by co-creators Scott Braden and Mike Malbrough, an introduction by TRIPWIRE MAGAZINE founder Joel Meadows, a prose story by Meggan Groves Robinson, and dynamic illustrations by the incredibly talented Eraklis Petmezas; acclaimed artists Jeff Dillon, Marty Grosser, and Mike Shipley; supreme embellisher Juan Castro; Hollywood concept artist Mark Wheatley; celebrated cartoonist Steve Conley; the original Nick Pentz; and painter-extraordinaire Dillon Samuelson - along with some additional surprises to boot! So, climb aboard for an adventure you've been waiting to discover your entire life!</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-30 20:46:13. [Issue ID 855928]</Notes>
  <Publisher>American Mythology Productions</Publisher>
  <Day>28</Day>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Year>2021</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/kent-menace-0/4000-855928/</Web>
  <AgeRating>Teen</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Meggan Groves Robinson,Mike Malbrough,Scott Braden</Writer>
  <Penciller>Eraklis Petmezas,Jeff Dillon,Marty Grosser,Mike Malbrough,Mike Shipley</Penciller>
  <Inker>Eraklis Petmezas,Jeff Dillon,Marty Grosser,Mike Malbrough,Mike Shipley</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Mike Malbrough</CoverArtist>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>