<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Composition; Cathode Slave; All Girls Together; Rollerskates; "She Likes Rude People"; Fishead Goes Undercover; Tobey's Tips For Fanboys; Mile Marker</Title>
  <Series>Action Girl Comics</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Count>19</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-11 13:41:10.  [CVDB142009]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 11:59:18. [Issue ID 304892]</Notes>
  <Year>1995</Year>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <CoverArtist>Jessica Abel</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Sarah Dyer</Editor>
  <Publisher>Slave Labor</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/action-girl-comics-3/4000-142009/</Web>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Jack,Audrey,Professor Sims</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1194524" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="711090" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="637916" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="934174" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="730380" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="516986" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="696636" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="665164" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="676358" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="369712" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="554282" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="793948" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="481570" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="480626" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="554124" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="549582" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="517104" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="670660" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="253752" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="514528" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="473058" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="457102" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="414434" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="507602" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="440178" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="613274" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="654230" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Composition: Audrey is writing a musical fugue while thinking about breaking up with her boyfriend, Jack.  She falls asleep at the piano.  Jack arrives, she plays her fugue for him, and the message comes through in the music even with no words.  He takes back the locket he gave her, then leaves.

Cathode Slave: A woman talks about how her productivity declines when the new Fall TV season starts, but realizes she is obsessed, and decides that it's OK as she sits down to watch a "Roseanne" rerun.

All Girls Together: A woman treats herself to a magazine.  The articles all make her feel like she needs new clothes, a new hairstyle, to lose weight, to exercise more, and that her relationships fail because she's neurotic.  As she puts down the magazine she thinks that she always feels better after a good read.

Rollerskates: A girl goes rollerskating, but has trouble keeping her balance until she starts singing the "Rollercoaster of Love" out loud.  Just when all is going well, she trips over a sidewalk curb.  A man wearing no pants offers her a hand, she jumps up, he says he didn't mean to scare her, she rollerskates back home.

"She Likes Rude People": Several examples of people who are rude or obnoxious in public.  She likes rude people because there are so many of them.

Fishead Goes Undercover: Fishead goes undercover as a general/military dictator in order to catch who is selling illegal weapons such as missile, tanks, torture devices, airplanes, etc.

Tobey's Tips For Fanboys: A woman offers tips on how to have a more normal life to the stereotypical superhero comic fanboy.

Mile Marker: House painters have to stop working when a rain storm arrives.  While they are packing up their supplies, a motorcycle with 2 riders goes by at very high speed.  Not long after a semi truck drives by.  A few miles down the road the painters see the truck at the side of the road, the driver is flagging them down.  The motorcycle they had seen earlier is lying on the road, but no sign of the riders.  They look around, then see them lying on the road, twisted like rag dolls, dead.

</Summary>
</ComicInfo>