<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Roxanna,Werewolf By Night</Characters>
	<Colorist>Mariana Manco</Colorist>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Joe Andreani</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-108996</GTIN>
	<Inker>Leonardo Manco</Inker>
	<Letterer>Janice Chiang</Letterer>
	<Locations>New York State</Locations>
	<Month>5</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:18:39 [Issue ID 4000-108996] urn:comicvine:4000-108996</Notes>
	<Number>4</Number>
	<PageCount>23</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="237790" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="307698" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="396781" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="428741" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="354035" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="386855" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="373506" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="402014" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="343342" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="365678" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="390724" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="370977" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="359263" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="467880" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="424174" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="338144" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="377771" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="395755" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="410494" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="403200" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="355973" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="350051" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="231708" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Leonardo Manco</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
	<Summary>Jack Russell continues his quest for the third of the three pieces of the talisman he hopes will cure his lycanthropy. Entering a portal within a carnival fun-house, he finds himself in a hellish landscape identical to the one he's had visions of during his transformations. It is a realm of skeletal remains and viscera, human, lupine and in-between. One of the wolfen cadavers speaks to him, and Jack tries but fails to transform into the Werewolf.

Elsewhere in the nether-realm, the Wolf-Demon places the third piece into a wooden chest, then raises his head, sensing Jack's arrival. He goes to Jack in the guise of a young boy, bearing the chest. Jack sees through the illusion and becomes the Werewolf, while the demon reveals its true form. The Werewolf attacks, but the effort is futile as the Wolf-Demon explains his essence is made up of all the lycanthropes in Jack's bloodline, and Jack cannot face such overwhelming power.

Changing tactics, Jack hurls a broken branch at the chest, knocking it open and freeing the third piece.

Approaching it, Jack accepts his wolfen alter ego, and the three pieces embed themselves in Jack's chest, forming the image of a silhouette of a wolf's head against the full moon.

The next thing Jack knows, he emerges screaming from the fun-house. Collecting himself, he catches a glimpse of the man who led him on this journey, and tries to chase after him, but loses him in the crowd. Roxanna, Jack's exasperated girlfriend, catches up with him, asking where he's been for the past hour. Jack cryptically replies that he got a tattoo.

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-4-the-end-of-the-line/4000-108996/</Summary>
	<Tags>New York State,Roxanna,Werewolf By Night,Werewolves</Tags>
	<Teams>Werewolves</Teams>
	<Title>The End of the Line</Title>
	<Volume>1998</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-4-the-end-of-the-line/4000-108996/</Web>
	<Writer>Paul Jenkins</Writer>
	<Year>1998</Year>
</ComicInfo>