<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Clash of Titans; Be True to Your School</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>31</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Ronnie thinks about comic book heroes he wants to write about as he waits for the bus. He sits with Spike, who also likes comics, but whereas Ronnie believes in superheroes as ideals and metaphors, Spike is just in it for the ultra-violence. Still, their conversations give Ronnie ideas for what he might eventually put in his portfolio for Marvel.

All day, Ronnie thinks about comics and writing. He believes his specialty is realism--for instance, if Daredevil broke in through the window, he'd get tangled in the Venetian blinds.

Ronnie does get defensive about comics. For instance when Woody asks about the character he plays in their role-playing game, Ronnie yells about how he's not Cyclops, even though he is extremely similar.

All the friends meet in the cafeteria. Ronnie loves Brandy and they've been dating. He idealizes her as Jean Grey. They all get in a discussion about how Woody shouldn't be possessive about Jenny and Ronnie, not paying attention, agrees that boys shouldn't be possessive about girls. This leads to a discussion in which Jenny agrees to go out with Woody, sparking Ronnie's jealousy.

Later they play the game, which is a very surreal version of superhero comics. They have fun until Spike, who is annoyed with Ronnie for not liking his comic drawings, decides to kill Ronnie's character.

Ronnie stomps out and goes home. His parents, who are both Black, live in a nice middle-class home. His mother supports his writing but his dad gets mad at him for not picking up some duct tape, and moreso, for only hanging out with white kids. Ronnie points out that they are the ones who moved to an all-white town. He's not comfortable with other Black kids, especially ones from the city who see him as too White.

He goes up to his room and listens to classical music while writing a comic story in his head, featuring himself as Cyclops and Brandy as Jean Grey. He dreams of the power to save everyone.

His mom comes in and calls him to dinner. He seems unfulfilled as he goes downstairs.

In "Be True to Your School," Max gets a letter about his high school reunion and is distressed because he hated its parochialism so much. Zot and Jenny persuade him to go but everyone is a jerk, as expected. 9-Jack-9, who in this universe was Max's friend in high school, starts killing and/or annoying everyone as revenge. Zot starts teasing Jack with information from the yearbook, and then Max gets his parents to show up. They annoy Jack til he leaves.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:25.  [CVDB32711]</Notes>
  <Year>1990</Year>
  <Month>05</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Eric Yarber, Ivy Ratafia, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-31-clash-of-titans-be-true-to-your-school/4000-32711/</Web>
  <PageCount>30</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Brandy, Elizabeth Madison, George Tanaka, Jenny Weaver, Max, Ronnie, Spike, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="176632" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="170905" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="182071" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="174553" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="187925" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="178248" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="205702" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="201134" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="216454" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="190883" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="185377" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="181840" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="177280" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="194450" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="181968" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="160099" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="242750" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="239803" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="151617" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="194181" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="219580" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="154290" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="185118" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="156468" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="187338" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="167758" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="172218" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="180941" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="186038" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="95212" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
