<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Ethan's Girl,Adam,Kenna,Merv,Cole,Pickett Boy,Alice,Wes Wilden,Bernard,Pa Pickett,Taylor,Ethan Daniels</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jonathan Luna</Colorist>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-107016</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna,Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jonathan Luna</Letterer>
  <Locations>Pennystown</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:08:50 [Issue ID 4000-107016] urn:comicvine:4000-107016
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 05:05:59. [Issue ID 107016]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna,Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Girls</Series>
  <Summary>Like many men, Ethan has always envisioned a dream girl, someone who could defy the mundane trappings of reality and become a living fantasy. But when Ethan's dreams are finally fulfilled, will it really be that fantastic.

*Synopsis*
Bernard enters his son's room and tries to talk about the miraculous stoppage of rain that also seemed to knock out all the windows in town. His son Adam (and his friends) is unimpressed.

At Ethan's house, he can't believe that he found a naked girl in the road and then brought her home. She wakes up and approaches him, then ravenously eats his dinner. Ethan begins to panic and decides to go for help. He is stopped, however, by the girl seducing him. The girl is not in Ethan's bed the next morning and he hears her sounding sick in the bathroom. He decides to get help and has to avoid Bernard (who is intent on crediting Ethan with the miracle from the night before) and Merv (who is intent on taking Ethan out to blow up pumpkins) and heads to the police station.

At the police station, Ethan finds Wes and Taylor chatting. Wes pretends to arrest Ethan for the mysterious rain stoppage from the night before but then lets him go and the three discuss the naked girl that Ethan found. Wes, Taylor, and Ethan head to Ethan's house and he leads them to the bathroom. He peaks in and sees huge eggs around the girl. He falls back in shock and Wes looks in to see grown girls - identical to the one Ethan found - hatching from the eggs.

Just outside of town, the Pickett boys wait to avenge the death of Ma Pickett at the hands of the mysterious girl.

* *</Summary>
  <Tags>Ethan's Girl,Adam,Kenna,Merv,Cole,Pickett Boy,Girl Army,Alice,Wes Wilden,Bernard,Pa Pickett,Pennystown,Taylor,Ethan Daniels</Tags>
  <Teams>Girl Army</Teams>
  <Title>Part 2</Title>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/girls-2-part-2/4000-107016/</Web>
  <Writer>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Writer>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Count>24</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Jonathan Luna</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>