<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>He Shoulda Knowed Betta!; Fashion Is Silly; Mrs. Miller; Pivotal Scenes from My Life as a Stage Actress; Quitter; Puberty Shmewberty!; Going Dutch; How I Became Beautiful; Stay Gold Pony Boy; Tobey's Holiday Dinner</Title>
  <Series>Action Girl Comics</Series>
  <Number>11</Number>
  <Count>19</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-11 13:41:21.  [CVDB142017]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 22:15:13. [Issue ID 304900]</Notes>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <CoverArtist>Sarah Dyer</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Sarah Dyer</Editor>
  <Publisher>Slave Labor</Publisher>
  <Genre>Biography</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/action-girl-comics-11/4000-142017/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1880066" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="613058" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="598104" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="648120" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="590956" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="723196" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="342238" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="647770" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="434424" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="673334" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="636134" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="672270" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="632936" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="641404" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="700190" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="709484" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="487276" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="974806" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="839572" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="512248" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="540426" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="496822" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="571560" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="553294" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="580442" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="725100" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="573550" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="830780" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>He Shoulda Knowed Betta!: Chris is eating a messy tuna sandwich and Jim is looking at a scrapbook he made of John Romita Spider-Man newspaper comic strips.  Chris asks to look at it, Jim is reluctant but agrees, and Chris spills a huge bit of tuna sandwich on an open page.  Chris then tells Jim it's his fault because he should have known better.

Fashion Is Silly: While sitting in a dentist's office waiting to have oral surgery, the author reads a fashion magazine from the 1980s that is over 10 years old, and recalls some of the stupid fashions that were popular, like bad perms, guys with pony tails, acid wash jeans, pants with multiple pockets on the legs, leg warms with high-heel shoes, shoulder pads and stirrup pants.

Mrs. Miller: When an elderly neighborhood resident passes away, the author goes to the estate sale that is run by the state since the deceased had no family.  The author didn't know the woman well, but recalled selling her Girl Scout Cookies when the author was a child.  The house was full of books and art at very low prices.  The author buys a few items, and wonders what the deceased - Mrs. Miller - would have thought about her and the state going through her things.

Pivotal Scenes from My Life as a Stage Actress: Leslee doesn't get the part she wanted in a third grade school play, but Chrissy Toberman (her Leslee considers to be her arch enemy) got the part, and wanted to trade.  During the play Leslee has to stand on a chair while speaking, and during the performance she falls down.  The teacher tells her she's OK and that the show must go on.  The worst part for Leslee wasn't that she fell or that the kids laughed, it was that Chrissy saw her fall, and Leslee imagines that Chrissy snickered at her humiliation.

Quitter: A young man recounts how he wanted to be an artist and thought a degree was required, so he went to art school where he learned nothing because he was too intimidated by other, more talented students, and he pushed away those who tried to help.  Eventually he quit and didn't draw at all for years.  But eventually he started drawing again and learned to get out of his own way and just draw.

Puberty Shmewberty!: Scooter and Tink are bored by the sex education class being taught be Miss Dunlap so they claim fake pre-menstrual tension and temporary water weight to get out of class and go to the nurse's office, but instead they hang out on the playground eating candy cigarettes and imagining growing up to be a gangster's moll or owner of a bumper car amusement park ride.  Later they play dodge ball during gym class where they get hit by the balls.

Going Dutch: Jen recounts some of her experiences as a grocery store clerk in Pennsylvania Dutch country.  She warns to not eat the "delicacy" called Scrapple because of what it's made of (scraps of pig meat, including snouts).  She recalls the area as being almost without any pretense at all.  Her boss reminds her of Ned Flanders from the TV show "The Simpsons."  The bag boys talk about their cars.  And her inspiration is an older cashier, Ethel, who was a dancer and cocktail waitress in New York City in the 1940s, who tells her to live hard and fast because at 22 you're just young and stupid anyway.

How I Became Beautiful: Alexandra's mom was a Mary Kay lady, so Alexandra got to wear makeup to school when she was 11.  Melissa recounts how she saved her allowance to afford a tube of Pearly Pink #7 lipstick, which she put on after she got to school because she thought her parents wouldn't approve.  After seeing Loni Anderson on the TV show "WKRP in Cincinnati," Melissa got a perm and that is when she felt she "became beautiful."

Stay Gold Pony Boy: Patty recalls watching teen flicks with her sister Jan, such as "The Outsiders" (based on the book by S.E. Hinton), and John Hughes movies like "Sixteen Candles," "The Breakfast Club" and "Pretty In Pink."

Tobey's Holiday Dinner: Chris &amp; Tom have a bunch of friends over for a holiday dinner.  Chris does all the work, while Tom entertains the friends, because he's oblivious to her sarcasm.  As she tells herself she'll never do this again, a guest proposes a toast to Chris as the best hostess ever.

</Summary>
  <Characters>Chris,Jim</Characters>
</ComicInfo>