<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Tambi Baker,Casey Femur,Marie Peters,Katchoo,Emma,David Qin,Francine</Characters>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-179693</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:47:37 [Issue ID 4000-179693] urn:comicvine:4000-179693
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:31:24. [Issue ID 179693]</Notes>
  <Number>27</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>David finds himself at odds with the Big Six who want him to join their ranks and fill his sister's role. But Tambi has made it known to David that joining the covert group will cost him his life. Who is Tambi working for now, and why has David suddenly become the key ingredient for America's impending fall from power? This is the answer Katchoo is determined to find out before it's too late!

A four year old girl sits in a field of burning wreckage. Her mother dying in the field. The narrator tells of her story and how this night will effect everything she does and lead her to an early grave in just 12 years.

Katchoo sits in the still burning cabin when Emma appears. She sees burnt bodies everywhere and eventually finds David still in his seat. Emma watches without a word as the fire gets worse. She carries him until the a huge explosion knocks them down. Farmers come and try to help. they find David apparently dead in Katchoo's lap.

Francine is crying hard and says somethings happened, the plane must have crashed. They put on the news and the top story is the plane crash and the burning wreckage is on screen. Francine has her ticket and cries why didn't she stop Katchoo going. Francine calls her mother and lets her know too.

Elsewhere Tambi is training when she gets a call, she turns on the TV and asks the caller: what have they done! The callers tells her everything is sorted now and that Darcy's company come solely to them. Tambi threatens them if anything has happened to Katchoo. When the phone goes down she swears vengeance.

At the hospital Marie arrives and finds Katchoo on a gurney, unable to talk, and comforts her.</Summary>
  <Title>Dark The Sun</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-27-dark-the-sun/4000-179693/</Web>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>