<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-201</GTIN>
  <Inker>Al Feldstein,Fred Peters,Graham Ingels,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Fred Peters,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:33 [Issue ID 4000-201] urn:comicvine:4000-201
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:48:38. [Issue ID 10226]</Notes>
  <Number>14</Number>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1144" ImageSize="146900" ImageWidth="800" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1147" ImageSize="262908" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1125" ImageSize="334437" ImageWidth="839" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="307229" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="314910" ImageWidth="832" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1115" ImageSize="325634" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="321671" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1111" ImageSize="321901" ImageWidth="821" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1125" ImageSize="338600" ImageWidth="832" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1147" ImageSize="279187" ImageWidth="850" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1125" ImageSize="350209" ImageWidth="825" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1243" ImageSize="406855" ImageWidth="921" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1118" ImageSize="331207" ImageWidth="832" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1133" ImageSize="325517" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="291387" ImageWidth="822" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1125" ImageSize="330314" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1107" ImageSize="312051" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1115" ImageSize="369741" ImageWidth="839" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1129" ImageSize="343785" ImageWidth="843" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1115" ImageSize="336543" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1129" ImageSize="305819" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="345378" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="296831" ImageWidth="843" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1140" ImageSize="312128" ImageWidth="825" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1112" ImageSize="320616" ImageWidth="857" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="1125" ImageSize="290302" ImageWidth="850" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="1136" ImageSize="210622" ImageWidth="854" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="1133" ImageSize="276479" ImageWidth="843" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="321315" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Fred Peters,Graham Ingels,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,Fred Peters,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Crime SuspenStories</Series>
  <Summary>Sweet Dreams!: Martin was sorry that he ever married Pamela, and Pamela's medical condition gives him a great opportunity to do away with her. But the idea backfires in a way that he'd never suspect.

The Perfect Place!: Ernest Jenkins is looking to buy a secluded house in the country in order to have absolute privacy for his writing.....or so it seems on the surface. But Ernest has ulterior plans: to murder his wife, brick her up in the basement of the new house, then marry another writer, Agnes Ludlow. Unfortunately for Ernest, it seems that Jess Carney had done the same thing with his wife Amy, confessed to the Sheriff, who now serves a warrant to Jenkins to search the basement!

The Electric Chair: Pete comes home to find his wife in the arms of another man, and promptly chases him away before shooting and killing Mary. Sentenced to die in the electric chair, and not wanting to die that way, Pete flees the courtroom and makes his way of escape to the subway tunnel. Unfortunately, Pete runs into an on-coming train and dies when he touches the third rail.

The Hangman's Noose: Peter arrives home to find his wife in the arms of her lover, and he promptly pulls out a gun and kills her lover. Knowing that the death penalty in England is by the hangman's noose, and not wanting to die that way, he flees the scene into the subway tunnel, being pursued by bobbies. He attempts to enter a car, but the doors close on his tie and he is dragged (and hanged ironically) to his death.

The Guillotine!: Pierre arrives home to discover his wife in the arms of another man, so he pulls out a gun and kills them both. Sentenced to death by the guillotine, Pierre times his escape and tries to elude the gendarmes through the metro tunnel and leaps from the platform onto the rails. Unfortunately, a train is coming....he trips and falls, hitting his head.....and the train guillotines him!

Private Performance: A thief, eyeing a rich woman's jewels for some time, decides to commit robbery one evening at her home after she and her husband had retired. Once inside, he suddenly witnesses the couple arguing and the man kill his wife. Unfortunately for the thief, the man spots him and vows to kill him as well, chasing him to the basement. There the thief learns what the man had done for a living, and it was the last thing he ever learned.

</Summary>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-14/4000-201/</Web>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines</Writer>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>27</Count>
  <Title>Sweet Dreams!; The Perfect Place!; The Electric Chair; The Hangman's Noose; The Guillotine!; Private Performance</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Dr. Firestone (Pamela's doctor),Martin Kaine (villain),Pamela Kaine (Martin's wife, death)</Characters>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>