<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Tim Hunter,Cyril</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Linda Medley,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Jamison,Linda Medley</Colorist>
  <Editor>Cliff Chiang,Stuart Moore</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-45931</GTIN>
  <Inker>Linda Medley,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Linda Medley</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Locations>Faerie</Locations>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:52:13 [Issue ID 4000-45931] urn:comicvine:4000-45931
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:16:56. [Issue ID 62825]</Notes>
  <Number>62</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="368094" ImageWidth="975" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="301411" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="258942" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="274029" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="265127" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="248834" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="296187" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="290595" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="270997" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="250471" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="239511" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="260362" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="269847" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="233893" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="290069" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="243923" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="299043" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="283741" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="314144" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="300346" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="288053" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="289449" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="265077" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Linda Medley,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Linda Medley</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Tim, having once again given up his magic, leaves London in hiding, to avoid the Other.

Cyril, who is still wearing the glamour stone that makes him look like a troll, is attacked and made fun of as he walks the streets, frustrated that they don't give him the respect due to a Bardsey Boy.

Tim sees him, rescues him from the crowd, and gets him to remove the stone. They bond briefly over the fact that everyone they know is dead. Tim doesn't want to deal with him, but is concerned that he may give up his location. Cyril insists that he come along with Tim.

Cyril immediately makes himself an irritating traveling companion, eating part of the now-chocolate Araquel head that Tim had been saving. They go to Blackpool, and Tim starts losing his patience with Cyril. He asks how Cyril got the dead body of the teacher at Bardsey. Cyril puts the stone back on. He starts to tell his story.

His mother told him he didn't have a father, which was really due to an affair, but Cyril took it to mean he was like Christ, who he believed was his brother. He started to descend into religious obsession and insanity, playing with dead animals. He found a cave under Bardsey and startled the teacher, Mr. Gavin, while exploring it. Gavin fell, fatally wounded. He touched Cyril's chest while dying, which Cyril took as the only gesture of friendship he had ever had. Cyril now believed, "Jesus was sent for the living. I was sent for the dead."

They continue walking, and Tim lets Cyril carry his bag, with all his things, including Thomas's directions. Tim crosses a train track, but Cyril's foot gets stuck. As a train comes, Cyril begs for help, but Tim looks on, unmoved, consciously not helping. The train passes, but on a parallel track. Cyril knows Tim was going to let him die, and runs off with Tim's bag, now his implacable enemy. Tim lets him go.

Includes an original Books of Faerie back-up feature entitled "The Scrying Pool." The creature Gyvv (from issue 58) meets a woman at a pool (from issue 57). They discuss the end of Faerie, and whether it went well "this time." They see Huon the Small in the scrying pool, and his grandson, king Magnus. Magnus's son was Amadan, but he did not recognize him as his heir due to his non-Faerie mother. Amadan seemingly killed the Duke of Grimwar, leading to Auberon eventually being king. They also discuss Molly, and her importance, and whose son she married. Then they decide to start Faerie all over again, leading into the Books of Faerie series.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:21:47.  [CVDB45931]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-62-wrong-side-of-the-tracks-the/4000-45931/</Summary>
  <Teams>The Wild Hunt</Teams>
  <Title>Wrong Side of the Tracks; The Scrying Pool</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-62-wrong-side-of-the-tracks-the/4000-45931/</Web>
  <Writer>Bronwyn Carlton Taggart,Peter Gross,Bronwyn Carlton,Peter Gross,Bronwyn Carlton</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>