<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2402</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2402</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>BORAG THUNGG, EARTHLETS! I am The Mighty Tharg, your genial green guide to all that is ghafflebette - welcome to 2000 AD! 

The zarjaz line-up that commenced last prog continues in another issue pulsing with Thrillpower, as the plots thicken in Rogue Trooper, Brink, Nightmare New York and The Out, while the Judge Dredd two-hander Silence draws to a close (but the Williams, Wyatt and Lynch droids will reunite for a new story at the beginning of next year). Yes, October is looking pretty, pretty scrotnig from where I&#8217;m standing - and since I&#8217;m always standing at the threshold of cuttingedge graphic entertainment, I know what I&#8217;m talking about!

Alas, such commitment to the very finest in future fiction, brought to you by some of the most talented creator droids to have been constructed by the expert metallurgists of Quaxxann, doesn&#8217;t come without a cost - and unfortunately the rising overheads of shuttle delivery have meant that the GGC&#8217;s cover price had to rise by twenty pence last week.

But don&#8217;t forget that you can save groats by taking out a dual physical subscription, and you&#8217;ll have access to all manner of special offers. Check out the deets, my Squaxx, at shop.2000AD.com!

*Judge Dredd &#187; Silence (Part 2)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law! Now, notorious criminal fixer and assassin Major Domo is wanted for the murder of Judge Maitland...

*Nightmare New York &#187; Nightmare New York(Part 2)*
NEW THRILL! Lower Manhattan, 1845. Paradise Square is at the centre of Five Points in Old New York, where five street corners meet. The early days of the North American metropolis are marked by a mix of poverty, organised crime and hardscrabble lives, where ragpickers rub shoulders with Christian missionaries. Young Lil, living rough on these dank streets, has just turned eighteen...

*The Out &#187; The Out: Book 4 (Part 2)*
The furthest edge of the universe. Cyd Finlea was a photo-journalist working for the publishers Global Neographic, travelling deep into outer space - otherwise known as THE OUT - and cataloguing the alien societies that she encounters. She left Earth ten years ago and has been seeking other ex-pat humans - but now, having lost her old pal Cheerio and said goodbye to her daughter Joey, she&#8217;s going further...

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 24)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Rogue Trooper &#187; When A G.I Dies (Part 2)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where the atmosphere has been rendered poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the pollutants - G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they&#8217;re searching for the traitor that sold them out...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-10-05 14:28:13.  [CVDB1072398]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>02</Day>
  <Writer>Arthur Wyatt, Dan Abnett, Garth Ennis, Kek-W, Rob Williams</Writer>
  <Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard, Jake Lynch, John Burns, Mark Harrison, Patrick Goddard</Penciller>
  <Inker>I.N.J. Culbard, Jake Lynch, John Burns, Mark Harrison, Patrick Goddard</Inker>
  <Colorist>Jim Boswell</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Rob Steen, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Dylan Teague, Trevor Hairsine</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2402-prog-2402/4000-1072398/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Bagman, Bridget Kurtis, Cyd Finlea, Gunnar, Helm, Judge Dredd, Rogue Trooper</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1665204" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1578598" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1104957" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1133667" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1159593" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1399334" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1321723" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1060712" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1565785" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1440622" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1532363" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1410790" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1478122" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1349783" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1489703" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1219839" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1580340" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1542663" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1402633" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1393096" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1318450" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="914380" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="835019" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="946100" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1412363" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1353222" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1335657" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1169539" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1225349" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1108627" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1148162" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="922335" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
