<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Holly Ransome,Cyril,Wobbly,Bill Hunter,Tim Hunter,Araquel</Characters>
  <Colorist>Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh</Colorist>
  <Editor>Cliff Chiang,Stuart Moore</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-44721</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:56 [Issue ID 4000-44721] urn:comicvine:4000-44721
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:17:27. [Issue ID 61461]</Notes>
  <Number>45</Number>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="555195" ImageWidth="1003" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="506778" ImageWidth="1000" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1527" ImageSize="546903" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="454824" ImageWidth="1000" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1532" ImageSize="608336" ImageWidth="998" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="428623" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1529" ImageSize="439708" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1531" ImageSize="528725" ImageWidth="992" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="606411" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1532" ImageSize="565911" ImageWidth="996" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="548524" ImageWidth="998" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="376264" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="498578" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1521" ImageSize="467469" ImageWidth="981" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="502624" ImageWidth="985" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="587111" ImageWidth="1003" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1525" ImageSize="542371" ImageWidth="992" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1527" ImageSize="527780" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="528180" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="462945" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="499664" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="548538" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="567224" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="676948" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="474123" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="545761" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Part 1 of the 6-part "Slave of Heavens." Tim has released his power into the world with hopes of making it a better place for everyone to live -- but when he learns that the magic he's given up has been stolen by the same changeling who has stolen his face, his past, and his family, he returns to London to confront the thief. Unfortunately, that thief is now quite possibly the most powerful magician of the age, and he would like nothing better than to see Tim dead.

The wedding between Bill Hunter and Holly has finally arrived, and so has the mysterious wedding guest, Tim's Auntie Blodwyn, mentioned once or twice before; she is shown here only in a veil, her face jokingly never revealed.

Tensions between Tim (actually the changeling) and Cyril increase; Cyril is turning increasingly Christian-extremist and thinks Tim is a tool of Satan.

Tim and Araquel must figure out how to escape the Dark Tower now that Tim released all his magic. Not knowing what else to do, Araquel picks up Tim and they fly upwards.

The giant wave of Tim's released magic flashes through the church as the wedding ceremony is performed. It focuses on the changeling-Tim, whose true form is revealed. Cyril is now even more convinced that he is evil.

Tim and Araquel take a rest, and Tim wonders if they're going the right way. Acting on a whim, he jumps off the stairs into the black abyss, and Araquel follows.

They show up in a cornfield, where Charon agrees to fly them to the land of the living in his classic biplane, after Araquel does a little convincing with his fiery sword.

The changeling, who is now accompanied by the Wobbly, tries to convince the family that he is really Tim, at least partly out of his own desires to believe so. The Wobbly, who was orchestrating this whole event, tries to convince the changeling to discard the family so he can get rid of them.

As they fly, Araquel explains to Tim that the reason Charon has a plane and not a boat has to do with Tim's early childhood ideas of death, gained from watching TV. His released magic has changed "reality." Araquel also has to stop Tim from eating the in-flight peanuts, which would keep him in the land of the dead like Persephone's seeds.

They land outside the church and confront the changeling and Wobbly. Cyril is even more jealous when he sees that Tim has an angel, like the ultra-religious Cyril wants to have. The changeling uses Tim's magic, which he now controls, to bind both the Wobbly and Tim. He says he never wanted what the Wobbly was pushing on him, and destroys the Wobbly. He releases Tim, but says he's going to keep the magic.

Tim pretends to be OK with that, and offers some peanuts in friendship to the emotionally-needy changeling. He eats them, and is killed by the nuts of the dead. Araquel remarks on Tim's premeditated murder of the changeling.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:21:01.  [CVDB44721]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-45-slave-of-heavens-part-1-the-/4000-44721/</Summary>
  <Title>The Veil (Slave of Heavens Part 1)</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-45-slave-of-heavens-part-1-the-/4000-44721/</Web>
  <Writer>John Ney Rieber,John Ney Rieber</Writer>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>