<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Joh,Tim Hunter,The Wild Hunt,Accasbel,Bacchus,Cyril Ransome,Bahrbaetous,Alpanu Lasas</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Jamison</Colorist>
  <Editor>Cliff Chiang</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-46646</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Gross,Vincent Locke,Vince Locke,Vince Locke</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:36 [Issue ID 4000-46646] urn:comicvine:4000-46646
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:20:25. [Issue ID 63623]</Notes>
  <Number>69</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1538" ImageSize="914863" ImageWidth="995" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1546" ImageSize="607497" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1547" ImageSize="581016" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1556" ImageSize="518304" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1543" ImageSize="568482" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1566" ImageSize="550312" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1549" ImageSize="561182" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1566" ImageSize="679605" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1569" ImageSize="602977" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1554" ImageSize="667143" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1571" ImageSize="503345" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1555" ImageSize="484143" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1587" ImageSize="525537" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1578" ImageSize="490727" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1574" ImageSize="517267" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1556" ImageSize="470194" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1570" ImageSize="517953" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1558" ImageSize="495806" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1575" ImageSize="458898" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1554" ImageSize="572530" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1564" ImageSize="493230" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1552" ImageSize="494713" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="543754" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Vince Locke,Peter Gross,Vince Locke</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Tim, in his magic disguise as "Mary," works for Drunk (Bacchus) to make a new brew for the Inn Between Worlds.  As Mary works to the point of exhaustion, Drunk explains why the other people at the Inn are so afraid--they are worried about the Wild Hunt, which has broken free of its extradimensional bonds and is once again hunting down rogue spirits.

This era's Barbatos and his servant Hauptmann discuss their desire to get the soul of the Other (the otherworldly evil Tim), after meeting him recently.  Barbatos sees his soul as his route to the upper crust of Hell.

Cyril sees the ice cream truck they're driving and tries to order a cone.  Barbatos, learning that he knows Tim, offers him anything from his truck in return for information.

At a patrician soiree in Budapest, a society woman is recognized by a stranger. It turns out that she is a lower-tier goddess of vanity and indulgence, Alpanu Lasas, and the man is the leader of the Wild Hunt.  He tells her that they will come for her tomorrow morning.

Mary and Drunk continue making their beer, both putting a bit of themselves in it (Mary's breath, Drunk's fingernail fungus).

Alpanu tries to get help from other gods who are now living amongst humans, but to no avail.  Then another stranger comes up to her and offers help.

Tim's friend Joh tries to spy on the beer-making process but is confronted by Drunk.  She says she knows his secrets, but he says he also knows hers.  However upon learning that she cares for Mary--because she has a crush on Tim--he lets her watch after all.

Alpanu, now in the wilderness, fights off one Hunt member, and is found by Cupid, who is now also a member of the Hunt.  She is given the same choice that Cupid was--to challenge a member of the Hunt and join if she wins.  She picks the one who she just knocked off a ledge, and thus wins.

Cyril asks for a cauldron that can raise the dead as his price for information.  They show how it works by bringing a bird back to life.  Cyril tells Barbatos that the real Tim ran away, and that he knows where his magic is.  They find the magic in a bottle in Tim's mother's grave.  Then Cyril asks for help digging up his own dead mother.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:22:07.  [CVDB46646]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-69-cauldrons-kettles/4000-46646/</Summary>
  <Title>Cauldrons &amp; Kettles</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-69-cauldrons-kettles/4000-46646/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>