<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Robot,Invincible,Deborah Grayson,Cecil Stedman,April O'Neil,Donald Ferguson,Bi-Plane,Rex-Splode,Allen,Bulletproof,The Immortal,William Clockwell,Omni-Man,Art,Dupli-Kate,Atom Eve</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bill Crabtree</Colorist>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-125183</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Ryan Ottley,Ryan Ottley</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Robert Kirkman,Rus Wooton</Letterer>
  <Locations>Tailor Shoppe,Reginald Vel Johnson High School,The Pentagon,The Moon,Space,Earth,Arlington, Virginia,Virginia</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:15:14 [Issue ID 4000-125183] urn:comicvine:4000-125183 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/276831
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 07:33:41. [Issue ID 125183]</Notes>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Ryan Ottley,Ryan Ottley</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Invincible</Series>
  <Teams>Global Defense Agency,Guardians of the Globe</Teams>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/invincible-13-perfect-strangers-epilogue/4000-125183/</Web>
  <Writer>Robert Kirkman</Writer>
  <Year>2004</Year>
  <Title>Perfect Strangers (Epilogue)</Title>
  <Summary>Mark Grayson is just like most everyone else his age, except that his father is the most powerful superhero on the planet. And now he's begun to inherit his father's powers. It all sounds okay at first, but how do you follow in your father's footsteps when you know you will never live up to his standards? "Perfect Strangers," Epilogue?There is nothing below him. There is nothing above him. For as far as Mark can see, there is nothing all around him. What happened to Mark last issue to put him in this place? What is this place? And what does it have to do with his future as a superhero?

Invincible is picked up by the government and taken to the Pentagon. In the meantime the whole world is watching the fight between Invincible and Omni Man, on tv...including Deborah Grayson. Invincible wakes up after being unconscious for two weeks, and Cecil introduces himself, as a man who knew his father very well ..or at least he thought he did. Atom Eve, and William both establish that they know Mark's secret identity. Cecil makes sure the world thinks that Nolan Grayson died in a horrible car crash...although Mark, and Deborah will always know the truth. Robot is demoted as the leader of the Guardians of the Globe because of the way they have been working together, and the near defeats. Cecil tells Mark that they have the whole conversation between him and his father recorded, and takes him to a secret room. That is where he tells him that the government needs a replacement for Omni-Man and Invincible agrees to the job. In the meantime William and Eve begin to get very close. Invincible receives a message from Cecil about trouble in space, and he meats Allen the alien who warns him about a Viltrumite living among the earthlings. Invincible explains that it was his father, and what happened recently. So Allen asks what he is going to do now? Invincible replies,"Finish high school I guess"...</Summary>
  <StoryArc>Perfect Strangers</StoryArc>
  <CoverArtist>Bill Crabtree,Ryan Ottley</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>