<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Holly Ransome,Circe,Gwendolyn,Tim Hunter,William Hunter</Characters>
  <Colorist>Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh</Colorist>
  <Editor>Julie Rottenberg</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-42174</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Richard Starkings,Richard Starkings,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Locations>London</Locations>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:29 [Issue ID 4000-42174] urn:comicvine:4000-42174
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:16:43. [Issue ID 58546]</Notes>
  <Number>22</Number>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1541" ImageSize="546113" ImageWidth="985" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="531265" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1534" ImageSize="539716" ImageWidth="971" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="522162" ImageWidth="973" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="527201" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="547898" ImageWidth="967" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1538" ImageSize="557582" ImageWidth="968" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="658031" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="474467" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="468616" ImageWidth="973" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="498955" ImageWidth="967" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="487178" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="547003" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="582381" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1537" ImageSize="467162" ImageWidth="974" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1527" ImageSize="460274" ImageWidth="964" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1545" ImageSize="479043" ImageWidth="973" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="512644" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="477993" ImageWidth="967" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="479302" ImageWidth="973" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="494942" ImageWidth="982" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="465630" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="715453" ImageWidth="973" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1534" ImageSize="538395" ImageWidth="983" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="548084" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="473962" ImageWidth="967" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="508096" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Tim's dad, Bill, has cleaned up his act since being burned and then healed, and actually goes for a morning jog.  Gwendolyn, upstairs, is also happy to be of help to the family.

Circe brings Tim, in cat form, back to her tattoo parlor, and un-charms his mind so he can think again.  She tells him some of the mistakes he made when he took cat form, making it too easy for him to lose his mind to the cat's natural thoughts.

Then she realizes that he didn't just borrow a cat's body, he reshaped his own body into a cat's, which is is such an impressive piece of magic that she is now scared of him.  She intended to use her magic to read his soul and then transform him.  Now she needs to be more direct.

Holly Ransome, who helped bring Bill back from the hospital some time ago, shows up at his doorstep to ask him out.  When Gwendolyn answers the door, she is taken aback, thinking she's Bill's wife.  But Gwen, realizing Holly's interest, explains the situation and asks her in.

Circe thinks Tim may be a servant of an evil group like the Dark Tower or the Margrave, who are introduced later. She can't believe he fooled Molly, who seemed so sharp. She uses magical tools to pull out his self, and is surprised to see that he seems to be good. The more she magically cuts him open, the more good she reveals inside of him, until she is humbled by his purity.

Bill gets home from his jog, and quickly hits it off with Holly.  He asks about her boy, Cyril, who's not there.

Tim wakes up, once again in boy form, and angry at being charmed and put in a cage.  Circe apologizes. She tells him that she knows he heard what Molly said--that he could grow up to hurt her.  Circe had planned to use her magic to find his soul's animal spirit-form, and have him confront what evil it may have represented, thus saving Molly.  But, she found that he has no animal spirit form, he's the most human soul she has ever seen. Knowing that, she won't do anything to him.

But Tim, concerned for Molly, asks her to do something anyway.  She tattoos him.  He goes home, and when he uses magic to help out a neighborhood cat, and then talks smack to his tattoo, he drops in pain.  He has two giant tattoos on his chest: a scorpion and a butterfly, and the scorpion stings him painfully every time he is disrespectful.

He walks into his backyard, and Bill and Holly see him with the tattoos.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:19:50.  [CVDB42174]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-22-needlepoint/4000-42174/</Summary>
  <Title>Needlepoint</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-22-needlepoint/4000-42174/</Web>
  <Writer>John Ney Rieber,John Ney Rieber</Writer>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>