<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Planet Earth, Part 1; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;!</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>11</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>After the first ten color issues. Zot! was rebooted as a black and white comic. The numbering continued from the original ten issues but McCloud considered it a &#8220;full reboot&#8221; and said that &#8220;we would have called it a &#8216;New Number One&#8217;&#8221; except that that was too &#8220;fashionable&#8221; to do so.

Jenny sits on her Earth, thinking about Zot and wondering what he is doing.

What he is doing, is fighting a villain: Doctor Ignatius Rumbault Bellows, a steampunk madman in a missile-launching flying machine. Zot and Peabody defeat him, but he flies off, leaving a bomb in his wake. Zot successfully defuses it and saves the people nearby. Zot is having a great time being a hero.

Jenny, however, is bored and misses Zot. She has told her new friend in her new town, Terry, about him. Terry thinks he&#8217;s just a regular guy from our Earth and thinks its about time he keeps to his word and shows up.

Jenny spends her time in school like any other 14 year old. (Zot is now 15). Woody, popularly considered a nerd, has a crush on her. Terry tries to get him to buzz off but Jenny gives him a nicer let-down, which he then interprets as interest.

Jenny and Terry ride bikes to Jenny&#8217;s house, where Butch makes fun of Terry for being an &#8220;alien,&#8221; aka Latino. Jenny considers Butch to be &#8220;the creep,&#8221; meaning their relationship has gotten worse since they were in Zot&#8217;s world. Jenny&#8217;s parents aren&#8217;t around much; her dad travels and her mom doesn&#8217;t get back til 8:00, so the kids have to make their own dinner.

Despite the fact that Butch reaches out with options for dinner, Jenny brushes him off; he feels lonely too.

Jenny takes a shower; she leaves a necklace that Zot gave her, which can act as a homing device for Zot to find her, on the counter. Zot unthinkingly teleports into the bathroom, embarrassing both of them, but at least she&#8217;s still behind the shower curtain. Her scream of surprise brings both Butch and her mom to the door but she gets rid of them with an excuse.

She meets him outside in a few minutes with his friends Josh Hacker (who built Floyd) and Dick Digger. They retrofit a car so it can fly. They talk about Jenny as if she&#8217;s Zot&#8217;s girlfriend, but both Jenny and Zot deny it. Peabody tries to stop them from using technology from their dimension in this world, but they deactivate him. They go pick up Terry at Jenny&#8217;s insistence and fly to nearby New York City.

Jenny is excited at first to be with Zot but Terry is understandably freaked out. When they land in a rough neighborhood, filled with drug addicts and porn theaters, Jenny is also very uncomfortable. Zot acts like it&#8217;s all exciting and thinks Jenny needs to wake up to the great aspects of her own world.

A kid steals a lady&#8217;s purse and Zot steps in, grabbing the purse. The kid promises to never do it again but some of his accomplices stomp on Zot. Zot appeals to the people around them for help, but they don&#8217;t want to get involved. Zot is shocked; such a thing wouldn&#8217;t happen on his world.

Zot makes as if it&#8217;s not too bad and returns the purse. His friends joke about how this breaks his perfect record and that it&#8217;s a good thing no one from their dimension saw this ignominious event.

Zot promises to see Jenny tomorrow and feels bad that she doesn&#8217;t like her world. He does start to realize that maybe he needs to understand things about her world a little better as well. Suddenly, Dr. Bellows jumps out from behind him!

The issue also includes Matt Feazell&#8217;s parodic one-pager, &#8220;The Adventures of Zot in Dimension 10 &#189;!&#8221;

In this stick-figure comic, Zot and Jenny watch TV but 9-Jack-9 and Antisocialman interfere. Antisocialman forces Jack to become part of the show, which he then watches with Zot and Jenny.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:42.  [CVDB27654]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Month>01</Month>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Denis Mcfarling, Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-11-planet-earth-part-1-the-adventures-of-zot-i/4000-27654/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Antisocialman, Bellows, Butch Weaver, Digger, Hacker, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Theresa Maria Veras, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="15731" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="317378" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="439825" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="327359" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="393701" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="373249" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="418303" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="434278" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="416912" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="303428" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="436034" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="438164" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="385783" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="383096" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="421516" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="452756" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="437459" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="349728" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="595551" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="290619" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="325639" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="453473" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="398717" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="497176" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="410542" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="430399" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="333913" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="364954" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="535813" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="415543" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="447290" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="397274" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
