<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>"Lucky" Taylor,Babette,Dr. Medusa,Creature Commandos [Griffith,Lt. Matthew Shrieve],Nazis,Velcro</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-22578</GTIN>
  <Inker>Rich Buckler,Romeo Tanghal,Fred Carrillo</Inker>
  <Locations>Paris,The Eiffel Tower,Le Louvre,France</Locations>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:23:18 [Issue ID 4000-22578] urn:comicvine:4000-22578
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 00:07:45. [Issue ID 36817]</Notes>
  <Number>117</Number>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="550922" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="383798" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="364004" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="370373" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="354251" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="358875" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="386854" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="397743" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="368808" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="377572" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="375598" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="367427" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="368080" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="380417" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="365355" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="366421" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="350749" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="387890" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="360518" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="371741" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="387465" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="370639" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="394535" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="359899" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="295938" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="342264" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Rich Buckler,Romeo Tanghal,Fred Carrillo</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Weird War Tales</Series>
  <Summary>While visiting the Eiffel Tower in Paris, the Creature Commandos witness a very young girl named Babette fall over the edge of the tower's railing. Velcro dives over after her, changing into a bat and saving her from certain death.

attacked by the French policeThe others race down to the ground where they find Velcro under attack by the French police who want to kill him because they see him as a monster menacing a young child. Myrna draws Velcro's attackers' attention by revealing her snakes, but when the police attack her, Lucky attacks them and nearly hurts them very badly. Myrna is able to talk him down from doing that, and Lt. Shrieve intervenes in his usual vulgar way to stop the fight. He's got a big smile on his face though, because the transfer he'd requested had come though and he wasn't going to have to be their commander anymore.

Initially, the commandos were pretty happy about the development too, because it meant they wouldn't have to put up with Shrieve's constant insults anymore, but when they reported to command to find out who their new commanding officer was going to be, they found out that it was a volunteer posting and no one else wanted the job, so they were placed on indefinite leave until a replacement could be found.

Left to their own devices, Myrna and Lucky went to see the Louvre museum for the day. Unfortunately, they were soon asked to leave because it was feared they would start a panic.

Velcro and Griffin had a similarly tough time out and about, and so, little while later, when the four of them meet up again, all of them are feeling like they're really tired of being treated the way they're usually treated by people... in other words, like freaks. Myrna had been reading this article in the paper, about a pilgrimage to the shine at Lourdes, where, in 1858, the Virgin Mary was supposed to have appeared to a peasant girl named Bernadette Soubirous. Hundreds of people make the trip there every year on the 20th of August to pray for a miracle to heal them of their ills. Myrna suggests they should try going as well, since they don't have anything else to do, and the others agree.

When they get there though, they find the Nazis have taken the pilgrims hostage. They battle the Nazis, and, unexpectedly, Lt Shrieve shows up and helps them. The pilgrims are freed and Shrieve ends up taking his post back as their commanding officer, though, sadly, he's still the same guy with the same old cruel insults on the tip of his tongue.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-09-19 12:52:36.  [CVDB22578]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/weird-war-tales-117-a-miracle-for-monsters/4000-22578/</Summary>
  <Tags>Creature Commandos,The Eiffel Tower,France,Elliot Taylor,G.I. Robot,Vincent Velcoro,Medusa,Paris,Warren Griffith,Le Louvre</Tags>
  <Teams>Creature Commandos</Teams>
  <Title>A Miracle for Monsters!; Family Portrait</Title>
  <Volume>1971</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/weird-war-tales-117-a-miracle-for-monsters/4000-22578/</Web>
  <Writer>Robert Kanigher,Robert Kanigher</Writer>
  <Year>1982</Year>
  <Count>124</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Science fiction,War</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Colorist>Jerry Serpe</Colorist>
  <Editor>Julius Schwartz,E. Nelson Bridwell</Editor>
</ComicInfo>