<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Part 1 of 4</Title>
  <Series>Polarity</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2013</Volume>
  <Summary>From the mind of SAY ANYTHING frontman Max Bemis comes POLARITY, a manic-depressive spin on the superhero genre. Timothy Woods is a bipolar artist stuck in the world of hipsters, meaningless sex, and vain art -- better known as Brooklyn. But after he survives a near fatal car accident, Timothy discovers that his mental instability is more than just a disorder, and that his bipolar medication hasn't just been subduing depression and uncontrollable mania...it's been suppressing his super powers! Now it's time for Timothy to stand up to his disease alongside an onslaught of wretched human villainy as he finally finds his place in the world.

Each issue comes with a free download for a new original song written and performed by Max Bemis!

SynopsisTim walks out of his apartment. He gets stares because he isn't wearing any pants. He thinks he a messianic character that operates in the nude. He kneels in the street. His belief that he is invulnerable is dashed when he is run over by a Jetta.

Two years later: Tim hosts an art exhibit full of his work. He is popular because of how his art is doing. He attributes any success to the delusions he had before he knew he was bipolar.

Tim feels out of place at the exhibit. His friend Adam calls him on it and then wonders if Tim will be making a move on Lily, an old college crush. Tim doubts it since he is at the show with his current girlfriend Alexis, an awful hipster with awful hipster friends. Alexis asks if they two can go back to his place and Tim agrees.

Lying in bed, Alexis admits to Tim that she finds him less interesting now that he's on medication. In sum, she tells him that his art currently sucks. Upset, Tim leaves to sit at a bar alone. As luck would have it, he would not sit alone for long; Lily shows up and Tim strikes up a conversation. He is terribly shy and realizes that his medication is holding him back when all he really wants to do is impress Lily. She leaves. He throws caution to the wind and orders some alcohol.

Tim spirals out of control. He flushes his medication and let's himself go. After nearly three weeks, however, he begins noticing that he can read minds.

Adam shows up and sees Tim's disarray. He offers to take Tim to the hospital but Tim just gets mad and kicks Adam out. As Adam leaves, Tim decides to find a person whose mind he has read that seems to be spying on Tim.

Tim creeps out and follows the thought-path to a building. He finds a man sitting alone in a bare room on the phone reporting that he's lost contact with the person he is monitoring. Tim taps him on the shoulder and the man jumps up and pulls a gun. It's not quick enough as Tim head butts the man's head into oblivion. As the body falls to the floor, Tim wonders if this is real or only the realest-feeling delusion he's ever had.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-11-25 21:27:49.  [CVDB395734]</Notes>
  <Year>2013</Year>
  <Month>04</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <Writer>Max Bemis</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jorge Coelho</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jorge Coelho</Inker>
  <Colorist>Felipe Sobreiro, Rico Renzi</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Steve Wands</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Frazer Irving, Rico Renzi, Sherri DuPree Bemis, Tradd Moore, W. Scott Forbes</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Bryce Carlson, Jasmine Amiri</Editor>
  <Publisher>Boom! Studios</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/polarity-1-part-1-of-4/4000-395734/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Characters>Adam, Agent Spencer, Alexis, Benicio, Dr. Mays, Lily, Tim Woods</Characters>
  <Locations>New York City</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1249066" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="275919" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="918638" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1107186" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1157184" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="845194" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="962771" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="948137" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="980930" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="591883" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="991098" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="981641" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="996956" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1035269" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="936089" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2000198" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1594621" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1984936" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1463961" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1034211" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="804374" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1136310" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="410334" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="761029" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="173768" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
