<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2404</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2404</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>I am The Mighty Tharg, all-knowing alien editor of this pulse-pounding plunge into Thrill-power!

I trust you&#8217;re all as content as a groondark in a sluice-pit with the current scrotnig line-up, Terrans - I mean, it truly is zarjaz so I can&#8217;t see why there&#8217;d be any complaints - and I can imagine that the only thing that&#8217;d make you Squaxx even happier is if I announced a whole slate of new strips starting in the Judge Dredd Megazine.

Well, you&#8217;re in luck - Meg 473, out this very week, features a stunning roster of thrillers, guaranteed to shatter your circuits!

We have a new series for the Abnett and Winslade droids&#8217; Lawless, Devlin Waugh is back for his latest supernatural case, courtesy of Ale&#353; Kot and PJ Holden, and there&#8217;s more Cursed Earth fungal body-horror in Death Cap by TC Eglington and Boo Cook. Add to that a team-up for the ages in Fargo &amp; McBane by Ken Niemand and Anna Readman, the debut of a Cadet Rico series from Liam Johnson and Rob Richardson, and a very special Dredd one-off, guest-starring a few familar faces, in Lawmen of the Future by the Niemand and Cornwell creator-bots.

All this and much, much more!

*Judge Dredd &#187; Hater (Part 2)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law! Even though the nuclear war with East-Meg One ended some forty-two years ago, resentments still simmer..

*The Out &#187; The Out: Book 4 (Part 4)*
The furthest edge of the universe. Cyd Finlea was a photo-journalist working for the publishers Global Neographic, travelling deep into outer space - otherwise known as THE OUT - and cataloguing the alien societies that she encounters. She left Earth ten years ago and has been seeking other ex-pat humans - but now, having lost her old pal Cheerio and said goodbye to her daughter Joey, she&#8217;s going further...

*Nightmare New York &#187; Nightmare New York(Part 4)*
NEW THRILL! Lower Manhattan, 1845. Paradise Square is at the centre of Five Points in Old New York, where five street corners meet. The early days of the North American metropolis are marked by a mix of poverty, organised crime and hardscrabble lives, where ragpickers rub shoulders with Christian missionaries. Young Lil, living rough on these dank streets, has just turned eighteen...

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 26)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Rogue Trooper &#187; When A G.I Dies (Part 4)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where the atmosphere has been rendered poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the pollutants - G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they&#8217;re searching for the traitor that sold them out...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-10-19 06:25:40.  [CVDB1074065]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>16</Day>
  <Writer>Dan Abnett, Garth Ennis, Kek-W, Kenneth Niemand</Writer>
  <Penciller>David Roach, I.N.J. Culbard, John Burns, Mark Harrison, Patrick Goddard, Silvia Califano</Penciller>
  <Inker>David Roach, I.N.J. Culbard, John Burns, Mark Harrison, Patrick Goddard, Silvia Califano</Inker>
  <Colorist>Giulia Brusco, Peter Doherty</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Rob Steen, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Dan Cornwell, Dylan Teague</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2404-prog-2404/4000-1074065/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Bagman, Bridget Kurtis, Cyd Finlea, Gunnar, Helm, Judge Dredd, Rogue Trooper</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1755405" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1601446" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1502292" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1507913" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1357805" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1604562" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1602585" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1577279" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1512755" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1081156" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1279122" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1449171" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1352392" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1346214" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1428588" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1346879" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1417015" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1418309" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1505398" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="979710" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1105468" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="954237" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1143318" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1024038" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1100969" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1097485" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1237554" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="913085" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1045974" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="918884" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1871510" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1412403" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
