<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Vault-Keeper (host),Donna (Steve's wife, death),Jebco (servant),Steve (death)</Characters>
  <Count>29</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-100713</GTIN>
  <Locations>Haiti</Locations>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:43:05 [Issue ID 4000-100713] urn:comicvine:4000-100713
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:51:26. [Issue ID 223243]</Notes>
  <Number>28</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(1)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Vault of Horror</Series>
  <Summary>Till Death...: Steve's new wife falls ill, dies and is buried. Steve's servant, Jebco, tries to fill the void, but the despair is too great. But Jebco says there is a way to have her back, and secretly he removes the corpse of Donna from her grave and puts it through a voodoo ritual.....and she walks again....as a zombie! Steve is overjoyed until she begins to decompose. When Steve, in vain, tries to kill her,  he drinks poison to end it all. But loyal Jebco puts him through the same voodoo ritual, and he returns as a zombie....to be with his love....forever!

The Chips Are Down!: Sigmund was buzzed on his intercom that Colonel Turner was there to see him and his two partners, Henning and Field. The Colonel was there to tell them that their sawmill had been chosen ror a highly secret government contract to produce thin wooden discs, at a rate of 60,000 per month. They agreed, but then wondered how they could produce that many until Field arrived at a solution with a new type of saw. Later, Henning and Darby muse over a way to keep all the profits for themselves, cutting Field out by engaging him in poker matches and taking him to the cleaners by winning his share in the saw mill.....which they did. After he walked out of the game, he shot himself and was buried.....and as Darby and Henning walk away, they muse over the marked deck they had used on Field. What they didn't see was a rotting hand rising from Field's grave that followed the two back to the mill, where screams are heard. The next morning, the mill foreman walked into open up and saw Darby and Henning standing stiffly next to the cutting machine in a pool of blood. When he touched them, they fell over.....minutely sliced into thousands of thin layers!

For How the Bell Tolls!: Long ago, in a far-away land, there was a castle which had a belfry and a large bell hanging in it. Every time there was a special occasion, the royal bell ringer plied his trade, watched for over 34 years by his apprentice, but never given the chance to ring the bell once in all that time! On the Queen's birthday, the royal bell ringer, now very old, was told to ring it all day long, but his apprentice wanted to do it. When he was told no, he pulled down an axe from the wall and killed the royal bell ringer just as the King walked in. But the paid for the crime as the clapper for the bell.

We Ain't Got No Body!: The rotting corpse of Henry Bodwin confronts his brother Norton, and reminds him about when his two buddies and he conspired to kill him over the will in which Henry had made Norton his beneficiary: for $20,000 with double indemnity. The trio pushed Henry under the wheels of a train, killing him, but all they ever found was the man's torso....no arms or legs. The check for $40,000 was a reason for the three to celebrate, until strange events led to retribution by Henry and peace in the grave at last.

</Summary>
  <Teams>Zombies</Teams>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/vault-of-horror-28/4000-100713/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Albert B. Feldstein,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Al Feldstein,Albert B. Feldstein</Writer>
  <Penciller>George Evans,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Davis,George Evans,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Inker>George Evans,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Davis,George Evans,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Johnny Craig</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Albert B. Feldstein</Editor>
  <Title>Till Death...; The Chips Are Down!; For How the Bell Tolls!; We Ain't Got No Body!</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>