<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Vault-Keeper (host),Jerry Adams,Drusilla (cameo)</Characters>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Editor>Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-100722</GTIN>
  <Inker>Angelo Torres,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Davis,Angelo Torres,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:58 [Issue ID 4000-100722] urn:comicvine:4000-100722
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:50:50. [Issue ID 223252]</Notes>
  <Number>37</Number>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1428" ImageSize="101160" ImageWidth="1008" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1434" ImageSize="172552" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1384" ImageSize="146902" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1384" ImageSize="161854" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1383" ImageSize="173951" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1374" ImageSize="152627" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1374" ImageSize="161946" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1374" ImageSize="161069" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1374" ImageSize="158306" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1374" ImageSize="170169" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1393" ImageSize="141276" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="165928" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="165485" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="155078" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="157684" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="162145" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="160618" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="151030" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="181558" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="144502" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1380" ImageSize="129407" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="159217" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="146213" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="141974" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="157886" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="1366" ImageSize="136769" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="1366" ImageSize="111221" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="1366" ImageSize="144116" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageHeight="1353" ImageSize="156182" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="151099" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="148651" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="152358" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageHeight="1372" ImageSize="155525" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageHeight="1452" ImageSize="132684" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageHeight="1430" ImageSize="157609" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="128957" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Al Williamson,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Davis,Al Williamson,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Vault of Horror</Series>
  <Summary>Surprise Party!: Jerry Adams arrived in a small town on a rainy night, checked into a motel and headed out to see a movie. He hits a detour and turns off on a dirt road [which isn't on any map] and gets lost, gets out and walks a it until he spots a house. As he approaches it, he sees that a party is in progress, and is invited to join in. He thoroughly enjoys himself, dancing the hours away w/his beautiful hostess. Then it dawns on him that the band plays only one tune the entire night, and his hostess tells him that it was the tune being played on the night of the fire. When he tells the crowd his name, they suddenly turn on him.....the flesh falling from their faces, as they explain that, back in 1884, his hostess was celebrating her engagement to Roger Wertham, but a rival suitor, named Adams, set fire to the house, killing everyone in it. Since then, on the same night, all the people "return" to re-enact that night until their deaths could be avenged. Now, that Jerry Adams has shown up, they now avenge themselves on him, his ancestor!

Chop Talk!: Emil and Anna said their last goodbyes to each other in the park.....their affair was to be over. But Emil decided to end it permamently: he killed her, and her husband came along, witnessed the act, stuck Emil and carried his dead wife away. But he returned and grabbed Emil and turned him into the Police....a trial was held and Emil was sentenced to have his head chopped off. Little did he know his executioner was Heinrich, the husband of the dead woman, and he proceeded to tell Emil how a person dies at the block. Emil lost consciousness and dreamed of that gory moment....then suddenly awoke. For days he agonized, until the day he decided to accept his fate and went to the block cheerfully. When Heinrich saw this, he lost his temper....killed Voight, then swallowed poison to be with his Anna. Suddenly, a voice called out to Emil Voight in a strange afterlife.....the voice of Heinrich, who proceeded to kill Emil again and again and again.....for all eternity!

Take Care: The former butler to Avery Ballusk waited on the owner hand and foot, but seemed only interested in inheriting his money after Ballusk's death, which soon came, at the end of a rope. The butler disappeared soon after, and a trial could provide no evidence that the "butler did it"! It is to this house that appointed trustee and his caretaker companion venture into the home for the first time to look it over.......but they never walk out......alive!

Oh! Henry!: Lionel Hart, plainclothes detective, had made many arrests, not listening to phony stories from the guilty. One day he caught an old lady for shoplifting, and she pleaded for him to understand that the food she took was for her sick, paralyzed husband, Henry. But Hart wouldn't listen and he took her in, got a conviction and had her thrown into jail. A month later he decided to check the woman's story out, and went over to her home and found her husband dead in his wheelchair! Blaming himself, he had the woman released, and went to make amends. But was he in for a surprise!

</Summary>
  <Tags>Zombies,The Crypt-Keeper,Drusilla,The Vault-Keeper,The Old Witch</Tags>
  <Teams>Zombies</Teams>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/vault-of-horror-37/4000-100722/</Web>
  <Writer>Carl Wessler,Johnny Craig,Jack Oleck,Otto Binder,Johnny Craig,Carl Wessler,Jack Oleck,Otto Binder</Writer>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>29</Count>
  <Title>Surprise Party!; Chop Talk!; Take Care; Oh! Henry!</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>