<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Tim Hunter</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Jamison</Colorist>
  <Editor>Cliff Chiang,Stuart Moore</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-45967</GTIN>
  <Inker>Gary Amaro,Gary Amaro</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Locations>London</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:32 [Issue ID 4000-45967] urn:comicvine:4000-45967
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:20:20. [Issue ID 62865]</Notes>
  <Number>63</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1555" ImageSize="699070" ImageWidth="995" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1555" ImageSize="472189" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1565" ImageSize="518380" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1572" ImageSize="536895" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1576" ImageSize="433754" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1575" ImageSize="397506" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1560" ImageSize="435699" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1563" ImageSize="498688" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1570" ImageSize="534065" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1593" ImageSize="469114" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1565" ImageSize="440021" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1561" ImageSize="458875" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1564" ImageSize="477210" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1565" ImageSize="429460" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1587" ImageSize="427452" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1571" ImageSize="463696" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1586" ImageSize="519878" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1575" ImageSize="500928" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1569" ImageSize="451405" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1555" ImageSize="492019" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1574" ImageSize="510551" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1554" ImageSize="465849" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="481206" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Gary Amaro,Gary Amaro</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>A long-unseen character from THE SANDMAN returns for this special issue, guest-written by Peter Hogan (THE DREAMING) with art by original THE BOOKS OF MAGIC series artist Gary Amaro. When young mage Tim Hunter is kidnapped by mystically-inclined gangsters, he learns of an ancient power operating at the heart of London's underworld.

Two men are collecting money for a local mobster. One, Julian, is a sorcerer, but the other, Edward, doesn't really see what he does, so he is annoyed and trying to prove he's better than this.  The sorcerer thinks it's odd that the boss likes to get paid in both money and flowers.

They pass by Tim, and the magician recognizes him.  He wants to see if he can be made to work with them.  Tim brushes off their interest, but then Julian threatens Tim's Aunt Blodwyn, who lives in the town.

Tim agrees to go with them. Julian explains how he uses magic to make money illegally; Tim is unimpressed with his knowledge. They meet the crime boss, Mr. Robbins.  Tim recognizes that the man is actually Robin Goodfellow, or Puck.

Robbins lets the others out of the room and transforms into his faerie self.  He wants to know what Tim's doing there, thinking he's trying to reveal him, but Tim explains that he was just forced to come.  Robbins explains that he doesn't need more magicians, he is happy enough with normal human debauchery and degradation.

Robbins wants to kill Tim to keep his secret, but Tim makes a pact that he'll forget about Robbins if Robbins leaves him alone.  Robbins agrees, but wants to punish Julian for causing the situation, and says Tim must help.

They go out in the country, and Robbins tests Julian by saying he needs to open an ancient faerie doorway there.  Julian is completely not up to the test and can't do it.

Tim also believes he can't do it, but when he randomly gestures at it, it opens.  Julian is pulled through the gate.  Robbins gives Tim a silver charm necklace that Julian dropped, saying it is more real than Julian knew.

Robbins and Edward--who turns out to also be a faerie--are about to drive off, leaving Tim.  Tim gives back the necklace so as to not be in his debt.

An editorial note says this guest-writer and guest-artist story takes place between issues 52 and 53, but that doesn't make sense, since that is when Tim was starting at Bardsey, and this story takes place in Brighton, where Tim has just arrived in issue 62.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:21:49.  [CVDB45967]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-63-the-good-fella/4000-45967/</Summary>
  <Title>The Good Fella</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-63-the-good-fella/4000-45967/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Hogan,Peter Hogan</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>