<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Captain Constanta,Hans Schmitt,Judge Dredd,Mallory Hope</Characters>
	<Colorist>Jim Boswell,Warren Pleece</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Tom Foster</CoverArtist>
	<Format>Digital</Format>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-958088</GTIN>
	<Inker>Jimmy Broxton,Luke Horsman,Nick Dyer,Steven Austin,Warren Pleece</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>11</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:38:44 [Issue ID 4000-958088] urn:comicvine:4000-958088</Notes>
	<Number>2310</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="843740" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1333627"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1639136"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1512023"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1356841"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1610304"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1496838"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1206401"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1181319"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1281702"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1351359"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1147163"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1076782"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1276988"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1032597"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="929864"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1043067"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1219524"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1437697"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1372052"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1284907"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1258557"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1459858"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1445967"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1190072"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1110183"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1171163"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1158864"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1169128"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1115116"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1440827"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="1397488"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Jimmy Broxton,Luke Horsman,Nick Dyer,Steven Austin,Warren Pleece</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(digital) (Minutemen-juvecube)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>I am Tharg The Mighty, the cosmic conduit through which all Thrill-power flows!

Welcome to the latest scrotnig edition of the Galaxy’s Greatest Comic, your one weekly bright spark of hyper-zarjazness as the northern hemisphere of your planet descends into the dark depths of winter. We’re just two weeks away from the gargantuan Prog 2312 and the traditional festive blow-out so stories are close to wrapping up to make way for a new roster to commence in the 100-page mega-issue.

Future cop Judge Dredd has a fight on his hands in ‘The Rematch’ by the Niemand and Austin droids, and Zoe and Jules must take flight in the penultimate part of Enemy Earth, plus there’s the latest instalment of Hope, a complete Terror Tale from John Tomlinson and Nick Dyer, and Ian Edginton and Warren Pleece bring us the prologue to the new Fiends of the Western Front arc as the vampire heads west, turning up in Nebraska in 1882!

Cover: Tom Foster

Judge Dredd - The Rematch (Part 1) (Kenneth Niemand - Steven Austin)Mega-City One, 2144 AD. Home to over 180 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, with the poisoned Black Atlantic on one side and the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west. Unemployment is rife and crime is rampant. Only the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law!

Terror Tales - The Vision Thing (John Tomlinson - Nick Dyer)Experience the terrifying side of Thrill-power with these one-off tales from beyond the veil of sanity. Whether they be ghostly goings-on that send shivers up the spine or splatterfests that sear the retina and paralyse the mind, nothing is what it seems in these glimpses of a terrifying realm beyond our own. Marcus Biggs is a go-getter in the advertising industry, a self-styled ‘alpha pup’ — but does he lack vision...?

Enemy Earth - Book One (Part 9) (Cavan Scott - Luke Horsman)The near future. Mother Nature has turned against the people that live upon the Earth’s surface. Now, the planet’s flora and fauna have mutated and are viciously attacking humanity. As society crumbles, and survivors seek safety, young Zoe, who has lost her own family, has discovered an underground bunker in London, in which a young boy has been living for five years with his protective robot...

Hope - …in The Shadows Reel Two (Part 7) (Guy Adams - Jimmy Broxton)An alternate 1940s USA. WWII is over, victory having been secured by occult means, and consequently magic is a part of everyday life. Mallory HOPE is one such skilled operative, though calling on the dark arts takes its toll on the user. He’s also a P.I., hired for all manner of down n’ dirty jobs — and an investigation into a cursed movie has led to the reappearance of Hope’s missing wife, Alice, who has plans for the film...

Fiends of the Western Front - Wilde West - Prologue (Ian Edginton - Warren Pleece)In 1980, the diary of German soldier Hans Schmitt was discovered in Berlin, detailing events that occurred in 1941, when he encountered the terrifying vampire Captain Constanta and his Romanian platoon. But Schmitt was not the first person to meet Constanta — the vampire has popped up throughout history, in various countries and under various guises. Now, he’s in Nebraska in 1882...

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-24 21:18:51.  [CVDB958088]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2310-prog-2310/4000-958088/</Summary>
	<Tags>Captain Constanta,Hans Schmitt,Judge Dredd,Mallory Hope</Tags>
	<Title>Wilde West; ... in the Shadows Reel 2 Par 7; Book 1: Part 9; The Vision Thing; The Rematch</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2310-prog-2310/4000-958088/</Web>
	<Writer>Cavan Scott,Guy Adams,Ian Edginton,John Tomlinson,Kenneth Niemand</Writer>
	<Year>2022</Year>
</ComicInfo>