<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Through The Door!!</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Zot and Jenny float outside the door, with only one option to escape their pursuers--to go through.

Zot has a hard time getting the Key to fit in the door, and even once he does, he can't push it open--until Jenny points out that it's a door you pull, not push. But even then, when they open it, they see that the door just opens on a brick wall!

Zot loses it, but Jenny realizes that she can put her hand through the wall--it's an illusion. She and Zot leap though and close it right before the conspiracy zealots catch up. The population of Sirius IV begins to split, with some believing Zot is the Chosen One as described in the prophecy and others thinking he's a blasphemer.

Jenny and Zot go through a wild mind-bending, senses-expanding journey and eventually wake up in a sort of sci-fi Roman utopia. Gregory, the first king of Sirius, welcomes them. He says that he, they, and the recent queen, are all there with their original spirits in robot bodies that replicate their real ones.

They are in a utopian future of Sirius. When Zot and Jenny die, their spirits can come back to this time and live in these robot bodies again. He says that the two of them will help lead Sirius to this utopian outcome.

Gregory brings Zot to robots of his parents. Their actual spirits are in the robots. They explain that they defected from Sirius to Earth when they were much younger and worked to keep the corrupt king from starting a war with Earth. They succeeded, but 9-Jack-9 did kill them in the end.

That night, Jenny thinks about asking the people of the future if she and Zot get married but decides she doesn't want to know. Zot has a dream where a young girl, who turns out to be the spirit of Sirius, tells him how she created the Doorway to give people hope.

Zot and Jenny say goodbye to everyone (including a robot/spirit of Drufus) and go back to Sirius, with the Key. They meet up with Max and the monks, but they can't remember what happened to them beyond the Doorway.

The people and leaders of Sirius continue to argue over Zot and Jenny's role now that they're back.

There is a back-up feature where McCloud includes some of the original sketches of some of the characters.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:39.  [CVDB270272]</Notes>
  <Year>1985</Year>
  <Month>03</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Colorist>Denis Mcfarling</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode, Dean Mullaney</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-8-through-the-door/4000-270272/</Web>
  <PageCount>33</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Butch Weaver, Dekko, Drufus, Father Kimm, Floyd, General Harcort Schrapp, Jenny Weaver, King Gregory the First, King of Sirius IV, Luthor Von Clokmann , Max, Sam Twik, Sirius IV, Vic Taylor, Weevis Swimbler, Zarbim Borlock, Zot, Zot's Dad, Zot's Mom</Characters>
  <Teams>The Devoes</Teams>
  <Locations>Sirius IV</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="179283" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="108515" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="146115" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="213263" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="144029" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="172983" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="137496" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="118615" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="134835" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="330849" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="171475" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="161886" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="148561" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="163907" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="156395" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="165020" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="133012" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="177921" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="317012" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="167916" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="147176" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="149835" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="156419" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="154581" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="142046" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="130839" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="183610" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="173947" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="120274" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="137837" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="146003" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="97475" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="111078" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
