<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Count>1</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-267434</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:55:47 [Issue ID 4000-267434] urn:comicvine:4000-267434
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 19:09:26. [Issue ID 771837]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Astro</Series>
  <Summary>Astro is the story of a little blue spaceman in a series of adventures told in a simple artwork only form.

He is flying through space in his rocket when it gets hooked on the web of a space spider. He escapes with a basket and floats off into space. He drifts for an age until he crashes to earth in a dilapidated alleyway. The basket pops open and a triangle with a green bubble on it falls out and bit by a pink spotted dog. The green bubble turns red and goes off like an alarm as it whizzes around Spaceman's head.

The spaceman wakes and walks through this odd snow covered city with the dog in-tow. He meets some local children who are painting on a wall and gesticulates the story of his escape from the spider. He and the triangle join in and they paint an alien landscape and a starry sky. The children turn and find Astro has walked away.

He trudges through the dark and silent streets looking sadly to the sky. A van with surfboards on top pulls up. The driver seems to ask where he needs a lift to. He indicates the stars, the driver thinks and tells them to get in. In the back the pink dog meets two characters playing cards. One has a black and white face with large pointed teeth and the other is a blue and green striped octopus-like creature. The driver hands the spaceman a funny cigarette. The dog farts in the van much to the annoyance of the guys in the back.

The spaceman slides around a painted world and his suit becomes yellow with paint. children paint a rocketship with the face and pink spots of the dog. The hungry space-spider appears and chases him. He wakes in the van being offered a drink and a doughnut.

hey travel far and it is day now and they pass a man riding a giant green millipede and then a series of massive blue and white striped balloons in the shape of fish.

The van arrives at Sunni Beach. The van driver swaps his woolly hat for a cap as they reach the sea and the snow replaced by lush grass.On the beach Spaceman's foot gets hit by a frisby and a pink humanoid cat girl comes over to collect it and points out where she is staying. Spaceman is smitten as the dog brings him a starfish, he picks it up and it reminds him of the stars. Seeing the dogs footsteps coming up from the waters he realizes where it came from he heads down to the ocean. He strides beneath the waves as dog pulls a huge octopus from the sea. In the depths he finds a cavernous hole in the seabed. Peering inside he spies a glowing starfish and swims down finding that it is huge.

Back on the beach everyone has gathered around a fire for the evening. The cat-girl is holding onto Spaceman's flying triangle which turns orange as Spaceman emerges from the water. He stares up at the stars and his triangle whizzes around him glowing red. Cat-girl and dog walk over and she holds his hand. He removes his helmet for the first time and they walk back to the campfire. Dog and triangle play together on the beach as the campfire glows.</Summary>
  <Title>Astro</Title>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/astro-1-astro/4000-267434/</Web>
  <Year>2006</Year>
  <Penciller>Nils Hamm</Penciller>
  <Inker>Nils Hamm</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Nils Hamm</CoverArtist>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>