<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Anabelle DiMarco,Beast,Jenna Washington,Sela Mathers</Characters>
	<Colorist>Mark McNabb,Thomas Mason,Tori Mason</Colorist>
	<Day>28</Day>
	<Editor>Ralph Tedesco</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-118956</GTIN>
	<Inker>Tommy Castillo</Inker>
	<Letterer>Artmonkeys Studios</Letterer>
	<Month>2</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:26:41 [Issue ID 4000-118956] urn:comicvine:4000-118956</Notes>
	<Number>13</Number>
	<PageCount>23</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1055140" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="419955" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="406018" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="363615" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="375249" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="480020" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="572416" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="656814" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="452792" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="412033" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="470410" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="503676" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="417194" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="529811" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="488903" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="492712" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="474862" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="507420" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="373073" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="510988" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="478190" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="462027" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="520895" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Tommy Castillo</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Zenescope Entertainment</Publisher>
	<Series>Grimm Fairy Tales</Series>
	<Summary>A young girl is desperate to escape an abusive relationship before it's too late and a meeting with her professor, Sela, might provide her a way out... when a young man is transformed into a hideous beast he is granted a short time to change his ways and reverse the curse, but can he overcome his abusive mindset or will his rage consume him and ruin any chance he has at redemption?

It starts with the modern story of an abusive boyfriend who suspects his girlfriend of cheating on him with one of her co-workers. He is physically abusive to her and as she runs, Sela gives her a story to consider, that of Beauty and the Beast. It tells the story of a selfish prince that used the people around him and who treated the women in his life as expendable. Finally one girl arrives and curses him with showing the world his true appearance inside and which will be made permanent once all the flowers fall from a single rose flower if he cannot find someone to love him. He decides he must change his ways and he nurses back to health a young woman he finds in the woods, but once she informs him that she must return to her fiance, he grows enraged and forces her to stay as his captive. The action cuts back shortly to modern day where both her co-worker asks her out and then her boyfriend apologizes. As it cuts back to the fairy tale it demonstrates her rescuers, including her female cousin who is killed by the Beast, but also her fiance who saves her. Back in the modern day the boyfriend finds out that his girlfriend has agreed to date the her co-worker and swears revenge.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 20:07:29.  [CVDB118956]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/grimm-fairy-tales-13-beauty-and-the-beast/4000-118956/</Summary>
	<Title>Beauty and The Beast</Title>
	<Volume>2005</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/grimm-fairy-tales-13-beauty-and-the-beast/4000-118956/</Web>
	<Writer>Joe Tyler,Ralph Tedesco</Writer>
	<Year>2007</Year>
<Genre>Fantasy,Horror</Genre></ComicInfo>