<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294836</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:16 [Issue ID 4000-294836] urn:comicvine:4000-294836
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:40. [Issue ID 10785]</Notes>
  <Number>18</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>The Messenger From Beyond: Small-time crook Zero Martin is shot by mobster Big Eddie and dies on the operating table. A pact with dead gangsters from beyond brings him back to life. The ghosts may use Martin’s body to avenge their deaths; and a ruthless Martin becomes the new crime czar – until one of the ghosts seeks out a deadly confrontation.

Scared to Death: Medical student Guy Bradbury is victim of a cruel prank. Three of his friends scare him with a corpse, because Bradbury believes in supernatural phenomena. Bradbury is accidentally mutilated and fakes his own death. Years later he returns to teach his doctor friends a grim lesson.

The Inhuman Creature: Unconquered mount Karachi claims two victims and is furthermore haunted by a wild man attacking the next mountaineering expeditions. When the first victim’s son, Jean Beauchamp, arrives on the mountain top, he is shocked to learn that the “monster” is none other than his missing father.

Crypt of the Living: In the Texas countryside sheriff Peters has to deal with father and daughter Eaglesham – risen from the tomb to claim back their land. The supposedly walking dead, however, are a couple of impostors trying to get hold of a valuable Uranium lode.

</Summary>
  <Title>The Messenger From Beyond; Scared to Death; The Inhuman Creature; Crypt of the Living</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-18-scared-to-death/4000-294836/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>