<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Cavewoman: Rain</Series>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>We learn the fate of Professor Cook. Meriem missed him with the stake from the previous issue. During the fight with Klyde her memory was damaged and she believes she is twelve years old again and doesn't remember anything past that. Doesn't remember Marshville coming back to the past and doesn't remember fighting with Klyde ever. Professor Cook tries to explain all this to her and she starts to believe him when he has her look at herself. Not the body of a twelve year old. She sort of remembers him and thinks they're in love. She runs off to find food before he can explain.

She appears to have reverted back to her feral self during those few years after Gramp died. She kills a dinosaur and that kill is taken by a larger one. She uses her skills to make a trap and catches and kills the meat thief. She observes Prof. Cook trying to radio Capt. Lavery who unbeknownst to him, is unconscious and quickly being surrounded by carnivores. She also watches him gather skunk spray (as seen in her Original Series) with out hurting the animal.

Klyde is scaring everyone in the museum so Lumpy tries to talk to Klyde with sign language. His friend Will goes with him. Lumpy tells Klyde that they are friends and it's ok but Klyde runs off. His memory isn't right either .

Bruce and the woman, Annette, are trying to dodge bites from giant crocodiles and stumble back into a little pit where the crocs can't get them. The little hole has dead bodies and beetles in it and Annette freaks out. One of the beetles burrows into Bruce's cheek. Annette makes the observation that the dead people weren't killed by the crocs because the bodies would be torn up. The beetles killed them. Bruce tells her not to worry about it because they're getting out. He eyes a storm drain.

More of the museum collapses and he anticipates a tidal wave. They make it to the grate and he swings her up. Before she can get him a crocodile takes a snap at him and barely misses. A huge eel is seem coiled around the crocodile. Bruce gets electrocuted by it. Electric eels. Annette lowers a belt down and pulls him up just as a tidal wave sweeps through the room. Once up through the grate he has her check his back and the end up both covered in beetles. Now they are stuck between that grate and another one higher up with the water level below them rising. They get to talking and Annette is the sister of the man who saved Bruce from the giant snake in Chapter 5. Bruce pulls out some booze and they make a toast to his memory.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 20:55:52. [Issue ID 59688]</Notes>
  <StoryArc>"Cavewoman: Rain" Rain</StoryArc>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Day>7</Day>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cavewoman-rain-7/4000-43154/</Web>
  <Characters>Francis Reicher II,Meriem Cooper,Klyde,Timothy Higgins,Patricia Lavery,Bob Cook,Bruce Kabbit,Will O'Brian</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>Prehistoric Jungle,Marshville</Locations>
  <Writer>Budd Root</Writer>
  <Penciller>Budd Root</Penciller>
  <Inker>Budd Root</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bradley Walton,Cara Walton</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Budd Root</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>James Pruett,Joe Pruett,Tim Parsons</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Title>Chapter Six; Basement Comics Presents</Title>
  <Genre>Satire-parody,Drama,Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
</ComicInfo>