<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Dr. Joanne Tumolo (flashback),Ben Richards (flashback),Commander Kraken (villain),Intelligence Officer Belag,Namor, the Sub-Mariner (flashback),The Cat [Greer Grant Nelson] (also in flashback)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Stan Goldberg,Stan G.,Stan G.</Colorist>
  <Editor>Roy Thomas</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-13100</GTIN>
  <Inker>Bill Everett,Paty Cockrum,Bill Everett</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jean Izzo,Jean Izzo</Letterer>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:39:21 [Issue ID 4000-13100] urn:comicvine:4000-13100
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 15:53:14. [Issue ID 26128]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <PageCount>21</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="605051" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="573668" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="533985" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="594355" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="590325" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="538457" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="650132" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="580813" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="506796" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="522639" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="454231" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="522953" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="570095" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="536977" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="550575" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="558238" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="568551" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="579010" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="567386" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="512609" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="611080" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Paty Cockrum,Paty Greer,Bill Everett,Paty Greer,Bill Everett</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>The Cat</Series>
  <Summary>The Cat's hyper senses pick up the trail of one Commander Kraken! And a lake house retreat goes to the dogs!

On the splash page, we saw the Cat driving a speedboat on Lake Michigan, with a cabin cruiser in pursuit. She was spotlighted from behind by two searchlights. She detoured through a marina to try to shake her pursuers, but struck an embankment and was thrown into the water. Her pursuers fished her out, puzzled by the unconscious woman in the strange feline attire.

We then saw, in a flashback, how Greer ended up in her situation. After the Owl escaped, she retrieved her civilian clothes and locked herself back in the closet in his building. The police let her out and escorted her back to Dr. Tumulo's hospital. At her doctor's suggestion, Greer moved her old professor to a house in the country. When Ben Richards called to see how Dr. Tumulo was doing, Greer talked him into taking her along scuba diving from his boat. While diving in Lake Michigan, her super-sensitive hearing detected a sonar signal coming from the bottom. After Ben took her dining and dancing, Greer palmed his boat keys and returned that night to investigate.

The unmasked Cat awoke as her captors were taking a pressurized elevator to a transparent dome on the lakebed. There, she witnessed uniformed men and women working in a futuristic setting. When I.O. Belag questioned her, Greer demanded to know what they were doing? Just then, an intruder alarm sounded. Belag hurried out, leaving Greer with a guard. She knocked him out with a left cross, then hid his body. She put on her cat-themed headgear again, then escaped down a corridor. When someone approached from the other direction, she ducked into a compartment. There she found racks of U.S. Navy dress uniforms. The Cat assumed she was in some secret government project. She used her claws to climb a wall, and looked down for the cause of the sounds of a struggle.

Below her, the Cat saw Belag and his crew being held at gunpoint by Commander Kraken and his band of pirates. The Sub-Mariner had destroyed Kraken's previous vessel, and he intended to take the dome as his new base. The Cat leapt to their defense, defeating the pirates and sending Kraken fleeing. Then she asked Belag why he hadn't told her he was a government agent? Belag replied they weren't sure who she was. She told them she was Greer Nelson, and how she came to be the Cat. They agreed to keep each other's confidences. Greer returned to the surface while Belag and his captain discussed their project. They concluded they'd finished their research and would alter their plans.

Back on the lake shore, Greer doffed her Cat uniform. She turned at a loud noise, and witnessed a huge half-orb rise from the lake. Her friends had been aliens, and her pride in her abilities had prevented her from realizing it.</Summary>
  <Tags>Commander Kraken,Dr. Joanne Tumolo,Tigra,Namor</Tags>
  <Title>From Far Beneath the Mirror of the Moon!</Title>
  <Volume>1972</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-cat-3-from-far-beneath-the-mirror-of-the-moon/4000-13100/</Web>
  <Writer>Linda Fite,Linda Fite</Writer>
  <Year>1973</Year>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>