<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-90476</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T13:54:04 [Issue ID 4000-90476] urn:comicvine:4000-90476
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:14:18. [Issue ID 202471]</Notes>
  <Number>12</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(remix)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Adventures into Terror</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-terror-12/4000-90476/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>31</Count>
  <Title>Horror in the Graveyard; The Hangman's Noose; The Little Pests; The 13th Floor; The Man Who Cried Ghost</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>Horror in the Graveyard: A man makes a deal with ghouls in order to be spared.

The Hangman's Noose: A seller of inferior rope hits his business partner with a crowbar and thinks he has killed him, so he fashions one of the ropes into a hangman's noose and props the body into it so it appears as a suicide. He gets a cop to follow him back to the warehouse as a witness, but when he arrives, he is confronted by the man he thought he killed. He tells the officer that he was only knocked out by the crowbar and the rope was so cheap that it could not support his weight and broke.

The Little Pests: After a husband disposes of his murdered wife's body in the pond, his new girlfriend complains so much to the county about the mosquitoes around the house that they drain it.

The 13th Floor: A building manager is approached by a ghoul who wants to rent the 13th floor. He says there is no 13th floor but the ghoul threatens to kill him if he refuses the month rental and he draws up a lease. The 13th floor only appears when the ghoul's associates enter the elevator but is unseen by humans. The manager demands to see the space and is delighted to discover it exists, seeking to rent it out. The ghoul explains the floor does not exist for humans but the manager refuses to pay heed. Once the elevator door shuts the manager's body becomes suspended in-between the 12th and 14th floors.

The Man Who Cried Ghost: A bored cemetery caretaker crank calls the police about being menaced by ghosts, but then the ghosts show up for real and haul him away.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Paul S. Newman,Paul S. Newman</Writer>
  <Penciller>Bernie Krigstein,Ed Winiarski,Manny Stallman,Dick Ayers,Eddie Robbins,Bernie Krigstein,Ed Winiarski,Manny Stallman,Dick Ayers,Eddie Robbins</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bernie Krigstein,Ed Winiarski,Manny Stallman,Dick Ayers,Ernie Bache,Eddie Robbins,Bernie Krigstein,Ed Winiarski,Manny Stallman,Dick Ayers,Ernie Bache,Eddie Robbins</Inker>
  <Letterer>Dick Ayers,Dick Ayers</Letterer>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>