<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Aleyta,American Crusader,Astra,Astron,Black Phantom,Black Venus,Captain Video,Catman,Commando D,Fem Paragon,Green Lama,Kitten,Ms. Victory,Nightveil,Proxima,Queen Reina,Rad,Scarlet Scorpion,Shade,Stardust,Yankee Girl</Characters>
	<CoverArtist>Mark Heike</CoverArtist>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-36684</GTIN>
	<Inker>Brad Gorby,Mark Heike</Inker>
	<Month>1</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.2.0 on 2024-11-30T20:44:38 [Issue ID 4000-36684] urn:comicvine:4000-36684</Notes>
	<Number>67</Number>
	<PageCount>36</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="230606" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="230424"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="175367"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="182910"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="180362"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="178044"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="196022"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="194855"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="192168"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="191843"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="183703"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="179208"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="190502"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="189479"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="180063"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="208072"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="192738"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="191662"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="179994"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="197447"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="208349"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="177826"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="185395"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="225577"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="218316"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="170933"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="189747"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="171982"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="148444"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="184398"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="178146"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="211493"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="184048"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="138173"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="202060"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="184768"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Brad Gorby</Penciller>
	<Publisher>AC Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>FemForce</Series>
	<Summary>FemForce #67 All Color!! My Sister, My Enemy-Final Chapter. As the powerhouse known as Fem-Paragon pummels Jennifer, Joan Wayne's motherly protectiveness kicks into overdrive, and she comes to the rescue. While Nightveil staves off chaos on Dark Dhagor, the freed Stardust sets a timer to slingshot Rur back to it's normal spot in the universe. As the heroes turn the tide in the battle with the Rurian ground troops, Stardust has one last hurdle- to win over the brainwashed Aleyta. Once that is done, she (with the help of Captain Video/Videxx) exposes the entire Rur war as staged to benefit the power-mad Proxima.

The troops retreat, lest they be stranded when Rur returns to position. The heroic Aleyta reveals that the super-powers Proxima's scientists gave her have lethal side effects, just before she expires. Joan and Jen have a measure of reconciliation , in light of the sacrifices each made for the other in the fight, and Dusty tells David Burke once and for all that they have no future. This untitled story is written by Bill Black and Mark Heike, drawn by Dave Roberts and Mark Heike, and inked by Chris Allen. It guest stars Queen Reina, Commando D, The Scarlet Scorpion, Yankee Girl, Catman and Kitten, The Shade, Black Venus, American Crusader, Green Lama, Paragon, Astra and Astron.

And, The Trial Of The Black Phantom cocludes with "Beyond The Veil". In the clutches of a mad "judge" and his cruel executioner, the 'Phantom is sentenced to hang. By now, used to unbelievable luck, the blonde gunslinger is expecting a last-milisecond rescue- that doesn't come! But, instead of death, she is transported to a strange nether world, where a centuries-old Native American spirit tells her she will live forever! Story by Nick Northey and Mark Heike, pencils by Northey and Heike, inks by Chris Allen. Color cover by Brad Gorby and mark heike, full color throughout. Standard comic book format.</Summary>
	<Teams>FemForce,Sentinels of Justice</Teams>
	<Title>My Sister, My Enemy - Part III</Title>
	<Volume>1985</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/femforce-67-my-sister-my-enemy-part-iii/4000-36684/</Web>
	<Year>1993</Year>
</ComicInfo>