<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Satan</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-204126</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:05 [Issue ID 4000-204126] urn:comicvine:4000-204126
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:10. [Issue ID 136598]</Notes>
  <Number>9</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>A Pact with the Devil: Suicidal John Masters enters into a pact with the devil and gets ten golden years of wealth and fortune. When his time is up, Masters tries to run. But Satan and his minions follow suit on his heels and drive him to suicide.

The Subterranean Beast: Allan Mills discovers a monstrous monkey captivated between rocks in a cave. By feeding the beast, Mills tries to command him. The ape shows more interest in Mills’ girlfriend Ruth. Freed by an earthquake, the beast searches for Ruth, but is used by Mills to run amok in the nearby village. The crazed Mills hits Ruth and the giant gorilla-creature takes him underground into the bowels of the earth.

Killer from Beyond: Thief and killer Benny Renz is ratted out to the police by his partner, Simon Fox. Fox and his girlfriend Lili buy the Renz home and tear it down looking for the hidden loot. The ghost of Renz has a laugh as the quarrelsome couple kill each other.

The Monster in Flesh: Antol Meers is shunned by society for his ugliness. One day he can’t take it anymore and beats up beautiful people. He gets a prison sentence and encounters a therapist who believes in change. Meers enjoys plastic surgery and becomes a society dandy. His soul, however, remains evil. Meers continues to commit crimes until he's caught again and put on the electric chair.

</Summary>
  <Tags>Satan</Tags>
  <Title>A Pact with the Devil; The Subterranean Beast; Killer from Beyond; The Monster in Flesh</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-9-subterranean-beast/4000-204126/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Drama,Horror-suspense,Crime</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>