<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Green Hulk,Red Hulk,Blue Hulk</Characters>
  <Colorist>Sotocolors,SotoColor,Chris Giarrusso,SotoColor,Chris Giarrusso</Colorist>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Editor>Alex Starbuck,Axel Alonso,Jeff Youngquist,Jennifer Grunwald,Jordan D. White,Mark D. Beazley,Nate Cosby,Nelson Ribeiro,Nathan Cosby</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-279785</GTIN>
  <Inker>Carlos Silva,Dario Brizuela,Chris Giarrusso,Dario Brizuela,Carlos Silva,Chris Giarrusso</Inker>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:02:49 [Issue ID 4000-279785] urn:comicvine:4000-279785
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:49:52. [Issue ID 847170]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>37</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1310477" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="428783" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="773637" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="820547" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="809277" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="823865" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="770386" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="863486" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="799755" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="731421" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="726644" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="723458" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="634251" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="707490" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="723650" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="740414" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="668088" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="682696" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="677635" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="807015" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="684594" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="746195" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="752232" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="692386" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="637595" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="781318" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="665466" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="685424" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="701117" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="735350" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="705405" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="750037" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="725541" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="673591" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="431109" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="394459" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="168646" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Carlos Silva,Dario Brizuela,Chris Giarrusso,Dario Brizuela,Carlos Silva,Chris Giarrusso</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Hulk-Sized Mini-Hulks</Series>
  <Summary>Hulk Sunburn: All the Hulks are red after laying out by the pool.

Hulk Bubblegum: Who can blow the biggest bubble?

Hulk Carnival: The Hulks break the Ferris wheel.

Hulk Library: The Hulks are too noisy for the library.

Hulk Bakery: Red Hulk and Blue Hulk ruin Green Hulk's first day working at the bakery.

Hulk Schoolbus: The Hulks get kicked off the school bus for getting everyone to throw things at the driver.

Hulk Skiing: Green Hulk and Red Hulk race down a slope which is too advanced for them.

Hulk Science: The Hulks don't follow directions in science class and their experiment turns out wrong.

Hulk Market: The Hulks race their shopping carts and make a mess.

Hulk Sleepover: Everyone wants all the covers and everyone else is hogging them.

Hulk Cat: Green Hulk finds a cat but it is too much for them to handle.

Hulk Camping: The Hulks don't know how to set up a tent.

Hulk Snow: The Hulks start a snowball fight with the wrong heroes.

Hulk Sniffles: Playing in puddles makes you catch a cold.

Hulk Rain: The Hulks go to the bakery to pick up Mama's pie order, but it's raining so they have to play in the puddles.

Hulk Dentist: Blue Hulk goes to the dentist and the other Hulks get in trouble for fooling around with the equipment.

Hulk Tonsils: Green Hulk has to have his tonsils out but it means he can eat lots of ice cream.

Hulk Date: When Red Hulk meets She-Hulk he wants to ask her out but her cousin Green Hulk says no.

Hulk Movie: The Hulks talk too much at the movies which makes everyone else mad.

Hulk Gym: The Thing plays a trick on Green Hulk by speeding up his treadmill.

HulkDonald's: Green Hulk has to work at HulkDonald's to pay for the damage he caused.

Hulk Driving: Green Hulk fails his driving test when he smashes the car into the HulkDonald's restaurant.

Hulk Dog: The Hulks want a pet but they mistake Wolverine for a dog.

Hulk Chef: The Hulks don't follow directions in the kitchen and bake up a cake monster.

Hulk Mama: Green Hulk takes the other Hulks home to meet his mom.

Hulk Beach: Red Hulk and Blue Hulk bury Green Hulk in the sand while he is sleeping.

Hulk Ice: The Hulks are cold so they build a fire, but Iceman puts it out because it's melting his ice.

Hulk Airport: The Hulks ride a baggage cart and make a mess.

Hulk Web: Green Hulk and Spider-Man get into an argument about their cartoon theme songs.

Hulk Zoo: Green Hulk frees all the animals in the zoo, then gets locked up himself.

Hulk Splash: Who can make the bigger splash in the pool?

Hulk Art Class: The Hulks get splattered with paint after a fight and can't tell which is which.

</Summary>
  <Teams>Fantastic Four,Mini-Hulks,Avengers</Teams>
  <Title>Hulk Sunburn; Hulk Bubblegum; Hulk Carnival; Hulk Library; Hulk Bakery; Hulk Schoolbus; Hulk Skiing; Hulk Science; Hulk Market; Hulk Sleepover; Hulk Cat; Hulk Camping; Hulk Snow; Hulk Sniffles; Hulk Rain; Hulk Dentist; Hulk Tonsils; Hulk Date; Hulk Movie; Hulk Gym; HulkDonald's; Hulk Driving; Hulk Dog; Hulk Chef; Hulk Mama; Hulk Beach; Hulk Ice; Hulk Airport; Hulk Web; Hulk Zoo; Hulk Splash; Hulk Art Class</Title>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/hulk-sized-mini-hulks-1-art-class/4000-279785/</Web>
  <Writer>Audrey Loeb,Audrey Loeb</Writer>
  <Year>2011</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Chris Giarrusso</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Superhero,Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
  <Letterer>Chris Giarrusso,Chris Giarrusso</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>