<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1216225</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero,Crime</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:37:52 [Issue ID 4000-1216225] urn:comicvine:4000-1216225 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1216225
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-19 18:55:56. [Issue ID 457589]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>Principles of Power, Chapter 2: Self-Deception</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-2-principles-of-power-chapter-2-self-decep/4000-457589/</Web>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Summary>Moles, murder, and mayhem. As C.O.W.L. prepares to enter negotiations with the city, scandal threatens the organization. Can The Grey Raven keep C.O.W.L. from tearing itself apart? Plus, what really happened between him and Sparrow?

Fresh off their capture of a thug last issue, C.O.W.L. partners Grant Marlow and Eclipse give Marlow's son a ride to school.  The boy, Jack, has been impudent to their boss recently, and now he's embarrassed about his dad, who doesn't have powers.

Meanwhile their boss, Geoffrey Warner, listens to a ghost-writer narrate back Warner's history of C.O.W.L.  The writer can't help but note Warner's biased slant on the organization, which centers on himself and cuts out his old partner, Sparrow.  Warner is worried about the union's contract with the city, which is coming up for renegotiation.

Investigator John Pierce has his own worries: he found out that C.O.W.L. may have been supplying their arch-enemies with their technology, and isn't sure what to do with this information. 

Marlow talks with Eclipse about his insecurities about the job, especially with his son's lack of respect for him.  They get a call about a minor super-powered thug causing some trouble, and chase him.  It turns out he works for Camden Stone, a mobster.  Eclipse wants to call back-up, but Marlow is sick of indecision and charges after him.  The super-strong thug beats him up pretty badly, but Marlow manages to shoot him.

Pierce decides to show his evidence to Arclight, one of C.O.W.L.'s top agents, but also known for his unhappiness with C.O.W.L. management.  Arclight is interested, but wants Pierce to get more evidence before acting.

Features a bio on Arclight (Thomas Haydn).</Summary>
  <Day>30</Day>
  <Characters>Blaze,Sparrow,Geoffrey Warner,John Pierce,Eclipse,Michael,Arclight,Sarah Pierce,Grant Marlow</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Chicago,Indiana</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Rod Reis,Rod Reis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Rod Reis,Rod Reis</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Trevor McCarthy</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Andy Schmidt</Editor>
</ComicInfo>