<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Garganta,She-Cat,Synn</Characters>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Bill Black</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-105171</GTIN>
	<Genre>Superhero</Genre>
	<Inker>Mark Heike</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Walt Paisley</Letterer>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.2.0 on 2024-11-30T20:44:43 [Issue ID 4000-105171] urn:comicvine:4000-105171</Notes>
	<Number>103</Number>
	<PageCount>46</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="168339" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="263353"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="180471"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="179761"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="201000"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="203807"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="199624"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="206995"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="189352"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="210549"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="201776"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="203152"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="200364"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="187690"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="192540"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="186263"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="196120"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="189080"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="192605"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="178864"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="178545"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="195305"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="202780"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="189284"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="179082"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="194245"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="207133"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="204891"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="210941"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="196355"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="197651"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="196822"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="203059"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="185401"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="187589"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="179756"/>
		<Page Image="36" ImageSize="176015"/>
		<Page Image="37" ImageSize="178281"/>
		<Page Image="38" ImageSize="196398"/>
		<Page Image="39" ImageSize="196385"/>
		<Page Image="40" ImageSize="183674"/>
		<Page Image="41" ImageSize="175588"/>
		<Page Image="42" ImageSize="231967"/>
		<Page Image="43" ImageSize="232153"/>
		<Page Image="44" ImageSize="145985"/>
		<Page Image="45" ImageSize="146760"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Brad Gorby,Dick Ayers,Eric Coile</Penciller>
	<Publisher>AC</Publisher>
	<Series>FemForce</Series>
	<Summary>This is part 3 of the three-part "Yesterday Syndrome" storyline. And then there were two. With Ms. Victory devolved out of existance, only She-Cat and Nightveil (in her non-powered Blue Bulleteer persona) are left, and they are in the clutches of Lady Luger, in the bunker of the German High Command, in the waning minutes of The War in Europe. History plays out as it should for all therin, except for the Femforcers. As Nightveil winks out of existance, She-Cat slides back further in time, to 1938. Meanwhile, in the present, general Strock sends a contingent of paranormals int the Enigma Cloud, now found in the asteroid belt beyond Mars, in search of the missing Femforce. What Paragon and the others find there is Bolt, and four strange alien entities that split off from him when he was rejoined with his human side; The Multibolts. Learning little from him, Bolt is soon teleported away by the strange being known as The Shimmerer. Where should he wind up but in 1938, with She-Cat, who has tricked The Black Shroud into confronting her there physically, in a time period when he is vulnerable to attack. With The Shimmerers help, Bolt and 'Cat move forward through time again, undoing the deaths of the Femforce. When they return to the present, they find there adventure in the time continuum has apparently altered events, and onlt the FF remember howc they happened. "She-Cat... Last Hero Standing!" is written by Bill Black, drawn by Brad Gorby and Dick Ayers, with inks by Mark Heike. Guest starring Yankkee Girl, Fritz Voltzman, Rumblebolt, Blazebolt, Freezebolt and Flexibolt; General Strock and Commando D. Then, it's another giant woman bonanza, in "The Big Deal", written by R. Lee Brown, drawn by Eric Coile, and inked by Mark Heike. Not only did the Garganta formula that Stella Stargaze slipped Marla Allison turn her into a giantess and give her destructive eye-beams, it made her crazy as well. Even a Garganta growing up in height to match her can't stop the rampaging actress, only a cold shower brings her back down to size. Great GTS cat-fight action. Color cover with interiors black and white with graytones. Standard comic book format.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-14 15:03:30.  [CVDB105171]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/femforce-103-the-yesterday-syndrome-part-3/4000-105171/</Summary>
	<Teams>FemForce</Teams>
	<Title>The Big Deal; She-Cat--Last Hero Standing</Title>
	<Volume>1985</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/femforce-103-the-yesterday-syndrome-part-3/4000-105171/</Web>
	<Writer>Bill Black,R. Lee Brown</Writer>
	<Year>1997</Year>
</ComicInfo>