<ComicInfo>
  <Title>ETHOS: Heroes Lost #1 - The Jumping Off Point</Title>
  <Series>ETHOS: Heroes Lost</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Web>https://www.rlblack.ink/shop/p/ethos-heroes-lost-1-digital-download</Web>
  <Summary>A scarred and deformed man escapes from a secret laboratory in World War II Germany after being brought back from the dead and is chased by a company of Nazi Super Soldiers bent on steering him toward some terrible purpose. He has no memory, no name, and is yearning to make a connection to this horrific world that endlessly torments him. Will he discover the truth of how he was brought back to life? Will he find a way to survive in this dark and twisted environment?

Taking elements of Mary Shelley's "Frankenstein," Bram Stoker's "Dracula," the Hammer Horror film series, and the horror comics of the 50s and 60s, this 84-page romp brings all the pulpy monster action you're looking for with a modern twist. If you like Mike Mignola's "Hellboy" or Image Comics' "Killadelphia," you will love Ethos: Heroes lost.

Artist and writer R.L. Black skillfully creates a gorgeous environment with distressed inks, retro-styled dot coloring, and deteriorated paper textures to give you the feel of a vintage comics experience. The magnificent art mixed with the profound concept based on his own recovery from alcoholism and drug addiction creates a unique and immersive reading experience.

This is the first issue in an ongoing series as the main character, the "Nameless Monster," finds his way through the second world war and finally joins a movement far more significant than he could have imagined.</Summary>
  <Notes>[RELDATE:2023-03-31]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Vantage Comics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Horror, World War II, Monsters, Pulp Action</Genre>
  <PageCount>84</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>Supported through Kickstarter, ripped with Calibre DeDRM.</ScanInformation>
  <Year>2023</Year>
  <Month>03</Month>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Writer>R.L. Black</Writer>
  <Penciller>R.L. Black</Penciller>
  <Inker>R.L. Black</Inker>
  <Colorist>R.L. Black</Colorist>
  <Letterer>R.L. Black</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>R.L. Black, Jason Wright</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>