<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Apocalypse Soon</Title>
  <Series>Ghost Rider</Series>
  <Number>12</Number>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Summary>Johnny Blaze has—against the will of the Ghost Rider bonded to his soul—decided to try to help the people of New York City against the unstoppable juggernaut that is The Hulk…by attacking The Hulk, head-on! Johnny just wants to do some good…but isn’t that what he always says before he does something ultimately catastrophic?

Planning on traveling to Buffalo, the Devil takes over a commercial pilot set to take off and rips the face off of his co-pilot. Just before he is able to take flight chains wrap around the nose of the jet and rips the front off of the plane, then begins attacking the Devil full force. As an explosion rocks the runway Johnny finds himself with a major decision: continue fighting the Devil, or try to help rescue crews by saving the passengers of the doomed flight leave the burning wreckage. Choosing vengeance, Johnny comes after the devil again and the plane explodes.

The next morning Johnny wakes up on the side of a highway next to his bike. Trying to come to grips with the deaths of all the people on the plane he sets out for Buffalo where he will confront the Devil once again. Coming across a diner he sees a newscast of the events that are occurring in New York. With the Hulk endangering the lives of everyone in Manhattan, Johnny wants to lend a hand. Arguing with the evil inside himself (who wants to continue to Buffalo on the trail of the Devil), he bursts into flames and assures the Demon in him that he is in control and that they will do as he pleases.

Johnny blazes to New York and then through the streets of the city past army, rescue crews, and escaping pedestrians alike until he comes face-to-face with the Incredible Hulk himself!</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-22 11:23:45.  [CVDB110671]</Notes>
  <Year>2007</Year>
  <Month>08</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Daniel Way</Writer>
  <Penciller>Javier Saltares, Javier Saltares</Penciller>
  <Inker>Scott Hanna</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dan Brown</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Joe Caramagna</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Gabriele Dell'Otto</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Aubrey Sitterson, Axel Alonso, Joe Quesada, Michael O'Connor</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ghost-rider-12-apocalypse-soon/4000-110671/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Characters>Black Bolt, Ghost Rider (Blaze), Hulk, Thing</Characters>
  <Locations>New York City, New York State</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1449099" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="835145" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1726687" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1611776" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1594985" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1423003" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1861313" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1986037" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2066177" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1579251" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1504660" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1463271" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1670724" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1202021" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1467115" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1608068" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1406422" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1233536" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1744662" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1747269" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="2033995" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1913036" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1848282" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1551228" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="2623625" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>