<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Beth Smith,Corporal Rstakner,Gene Vagina,Morty Smith,Nrrlkt'l,Rick Sanchez,Summer Smith,Brad,Jerry Smith</Characters>
  <Day>27</Day>
  <Editor>Ari Yarwood,Robin Herrera</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-527205</GTIN>
  <Inker>CJ Cannon,CJ Cannon</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!,Crank!</Letterer>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:00:46 [Issue ID 4000-527205] urn:comicvine:4000-527205
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 14:45:50. [Issue ID 1560114]</Notes>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1088113" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1239368" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1239587" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1279759" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1276050" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1290343" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1376148" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1361554" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1560077" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1284658" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1324437" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1230466" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1340784" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1173050" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1430288" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1399834" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1419300" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1452814" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1473597" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1517708" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1181096" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1269022" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1079844" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1140073" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="952902" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1545810" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>CJ Cannon,CJ Cannon</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Oni Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Rick and Morty</Series>
  <Summary>Rick and Morty are stuck inside the severed head of another dimension's Morty, and things are getting... weird. They still have a narrow chance of saving their own dimension from alien invasion... but only if Morty can get the science right!

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                     | Creator(s) | Sidebar Location |
---------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover            | CJ Cannon  | 1                |
 RI    | Retailer Incentive Cover | K.C. Green | 2                |
SynopsisThings in the Morty head are not as precise as Rick would like and he has trouble maneuvering their space craft. Since they are in a Morty's mind, Morty finds a simple solution to getting them home: he hits a control button labeled "Home". Upon landing, Rick notes that they have lost some time between the heads, as it appears that the aliens have attacked Earth. Rick wants to waste no time getting to his garage, as he assumes that whatever the aliens are looking for are there.

Before arriving at the garage, Rick and Morty are confronted by two aliens. Rick tries one of his fancy moves but slips. Morty notes that Rick's moves may not work in a Morty head. No bother, as the aliens are quickly dispatched by Summer. Summer is overjoyed to see that Morty alive. The trio moves and Summer explains that the aliens attacked and then kidnapped Jerry. No one knows why yet.

The trio arrives at Morty's school and meet up with Beth and a handful of human survivors. Rick learns that the aliens have been in control for 19 months. Beth is trying to get a plan going to rid the Earth of aliens. This alarms Rick, as a plan in a Morty's head could go south real fast. Rick takes Morty to a classroom and tries to teach him everything relevant about the "cosmic dance". Morty doesn't get it.

Beth assembles her troops and announces that they have acquired plans for the place Jerry is being held. The plan is to infiltrate the base and kill Jerry, who has apparently been aiding the aliens in building a super weapon. No one knows the details, but is has something to do with the family's toaster. Just then, the aliens attack and take Rick, Morty, Beth, Summer, and several others hostage. Morty laments how dumb he is and how he can't help. Rick then realizes that Morty is right - Morty is an idiot and doesn't know how things work. As such, Morty's mind doesn't really know how to restrain Rick, who quickly shucks his handcuffs and kills the captors.

At the alien base, Jerry is found and his captors killed. Beth then accosts Jerry about helping the enemy. She gets shot and he takes her to the side and explains that he was operating under the assumption that everyone was dead and it didn't matter. Rick sees the toaster and notes that it is too late - Jerry has tampered with it beyond repair and they are all going to die. Morty refuses to believe it and explains that the Morty's head they are in would have a similar belief. Rick sees the logic here and begins harvesting power from the toaster to amp his portal gun.

Rick and Morty successfully exit the Morty's brain by literally blowing out of the skull. Rick runs to find his toaster and Morty's family returns home to find him alive. Rick runs out with the toaster - which is now glowing - and demands that Jerry explain what he did with it. Then the aliens land.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-02 14:02:48.  [Issue ID 527205]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-13-head-space-part-two/4000-527205/</Summary>
  <Tags>Beth Smith,Corporal Rstakner,Gene Vagina,Morty Smith,Nrrlkt'l,Rick Sanchez,Summer Smith,Brad,Jerry Smith</Tags>
  <Title>Head-Space, Part Two</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-13-head-space-part-two/4000-527205/</Web>
  <Writer>Tom Fowler,Tom Fowler</Writer>
  <Year>2016</Year>
  <Count>61</Count>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Colorist>Ryan Hill</Colorist>
</ComicInfo>