<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>30</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1245341</GTIN>
  <Genre>Drama,Crime,Historical</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:37:59 [Issue ID 4000-1245341] urn:comicvine:4000-1245341 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1245341
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:51:37. [Issue ID 1245341]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>Principles of Power - Chapter 3: Perception</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-3-principles-of-power-chapter-3-perception/4000-460997/</Web>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Summary>Who is Radia? And why does Chicago fear her? Meanwhile, Geoffrey discovers that C.O.W.L.’s future is anything but guaranteed, and John’s investigation into the union takes an unexpected turn. 

Radia and her somewhat dull, non-understanding boyfriend go to a baseball game and she ends up being treated as an object, however adoringly, by the public and the alderman who had been attacked by Skylancer in the first issue. She feels like she isn't being treated the same as the male heroes.

Grey Raven continues to argue with the mayor about the C.O.W.L. union's contract with the city. The city wants the option to hire non-union heroes.

Radia goes to a C.O.W.L.-coordinated photoshoot and interview with a lad's magazine. When Arclight also shows up, they direct all the serious questions to him, and give her fluff.

She later runs into Eclipse, who is angry about how the mobster Camden Stone's goon put his partner Grant Marlow in the hospital. Eclipse turns out to be one of the only people who treats Radia as an equal, so she agrees to help put pressure on Stone, outside the union rules.

Meanwhile John Pierce continues his search for more evidence that C.O.W.L. was helping the villainous-but-defunct Chicago Six by providing them with technology. When he goes to a warehouse where the union's tech designs are stored, he finds it all missing.

Eclipse and Radia show up to one of Stone's joints and wreck it, telling him to leave Chicago. They both feel better than they have in a long time, and begin a friendship based on mutual respect.

Negotiations with the city having fallen through, the Grey Raven calls for C.O.W.L. to go on strike.

Features a bio and pin-up of Radia (Kathryn Mitchell), and a written feature by Sarah Jaffe.</Summary>
  <Characters>Alderman Lowe,Geoffrey Warner,Richard Daley,John Pierce,Radia,Arclight,Eclipse,Blaze,Camden Stone</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Indiana,Chicago</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jen Aprahamian,Rod Reis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jen Aprahamian,Rod Reis</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Trevor McCarthy</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Andy Schmidt</Editor>
</ComicInfo>