<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Louise,Patch (dies),Blackie Barker (dies)</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-206002</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:13:34 [Issue ID 4000-206002] urn:comicvine:4000-206002
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 17:56:37. [Issue ID 28460]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Giant-Size Kid Colt</Series>
  <Tags>Kid Colt</Tags>
  <Title>Showdown at Steer's Skull!; Battle at Blood Creek!; When a Man's Afraid!; Six-Guns Can Talk!; The Menace of Bulldog Yates!; Lawmen Never Die!; Kid Colt, Coward!</Title>
  <Volume>1975</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/giant-size-kid-colt-2-showdown-as-steers-skull/4000-206002/</Web>
  <Year>1975</Year>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Genre>Western-frontier</Genre>
  <Summary>Colt finds Blackie is driving people off their land through murder; his own family were killed by a land grabber who raised him like a son. When his surrogate father was killed by farmers Blackie vowed vengeance on all farmers. Colt finally kills Blackie.

Colt finds the cattle and sheep ranchers of Blood Creek are at war with each other. To sort the situation out, he brings in Sam to arrest everyone until a judge can repair matters.

Ben is in a gunfight with Clem and winds up wounded in the shoulder. Ben thinks he's too afraid to continue being a deputy but when Clem later returns, Ben faces him and this time defeat Clem, conquering his fears.

Colt is demonstrating some tricks with his guns to schoolchildren when Ricky collapses, suffering a flesh wound from a bullet. Colt thinks he shot the boy but the bullet belongs to a .38, rather than Colt's .45s. Sutton turns out to be the one trying to ruin Colt's reputation but Colt defeats him.

To catch Kid Colt unaware Bulldog gives a derringer to Nancy so she can get the drop on him. However, once Bulldog has Colt at gunpoint he admits he won't marry Nancy. Nancy throws the derringer to Colt and he shoots Bulldog in the hand then departs.

An old sheriff happens across Wolf Gorgon, dazed from falling off a horse. The sheriff takes him back to town and jails him. When the Gorgon Gang come to town, the sheriff holds his gun on Wolf to force them into surrendering, placing them all in his cells. Afterwards the old man admits his gun wasn't loaded.

Tumbleweed's population want Colt to get rid of Bordon, but Colt refuses, even when Bordon tries to provoke a fight. However, when Bordon turns on other people, Colt draws on him and bests him, even though Colt's arm is badly injured from an earlier fight - his only reason for avoiding a fight earlier.

Colt comes upon the remains of a recently-destroyed wagon train. Abe is dying in the wreck and asks Colt to tell Tex to keep their company going. Colt relays the message and helps the company complete a shipment, then exposes Tex's fiance Colin as the one sending raiders after them, hoping to drive the Starrs into selling their business. Colt kills Colin in a shootout.</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Gary Friedrich,Stan Lee,Joe Gill,Gary Friedrich,Stan Lee,Joe Gill</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dick Ayers,Don Heck,Jack Keller,Sol Brodsky,Dick Ayers,Don Heck,Jack Keller,Sol Brodsky</Penciller>
  <Inker>Vince Colletta,Don Heck,Jack Keller,Sol Brodsky,Vince Colletta,Don Heck,Jack Keller,Sol Brodsky</Inker>
  <Colorist>George Roussos,George Roussos</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Artie Simek,Karen Subek,Sam Rosen,Jon D'Agostino,Artie Simek,Karen Subek,Sam Rosen,Jon D'Agostino</Letterer>
  <Editor>Len Wein</Editor>
</ComicInfo>