<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1317624</GTIN>
  <Genre>Crime,Historical,Drama</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:37:56 [Issue ID 4000-1317624] urn:comicvine:4000-1317624 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1317624
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:51:21. [Issue ID 1317624]</Notes>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>The Greater Good - Chapter 2: Doppler Shift</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-8-the-greater-good-chapter-2-doppler-shift/4000-478575/</Web>
  <Year>2015</Year>
  <Summary>Thanks to Camden Stone, Geoffrey Warner has the villains he desperately needed. But at what cost? And how long can Geoffrey keep the lie going?

The police interrogate Arclight over his role in John Pierce's death, which he has admitted to.  Arclight lies to make it sound like John attacked him, and it was self-defense.

Doppler kidnaps city Alderman Lawrence Hayes as part of Camden Stone's attempt to increase the visibility of costumed villains--as requested by C.O.W.L. leader Geoffrey Warner.  When Pierce is buried, reporters ask about the kidnapping, and Warner points out the need for the city to renew the union's contract.

Evelyn confronts Arclight; she doesn't believe his self-defense story, and wants the truth.  She is suspicious of Warner.  Arclight flies off.

Eclipse gets harassed by fellow union members Frank and Don about going to "scab" Pierce's funeral.  He's getting increasingly unsure of what to do in this strike environment.  When he sees Radia she wants him to go after Jimmy Macauley, a superpowered Stone enforcer.  He says no, and she is disappointed by his capitulation.

Warner knows about what Radia and Eclipse have been doing and tells her to stop.  She continues to be angry at him and C.O.W.L. due to their misogynist ways and doesn't care.  She still wants to make a difference.

Two new costumed villains simultaneously attack an armored car and a fancy restaurant, further spreading chaos and fear.  What is C.O.W.L. to do--save the city and ignore the strike, or honor the strike and let evil reign?

Features a bio on Camden Stone.</Summary>
  <StoryArc>The Greater Good</StoryArc>
  <Characters>Frank,Camden Stone,Evelyn Hewitt,Arclight,Radia,Geoffrey Warner,Blaze,Eclipse,Alderman Hayes,Sarah Pierce,Doppler,Don</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Chicago,Indiana</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Rod Reis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Rod Reis</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Trevor McCarthy</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Andy Schmidt</Editor>
</ComicInfo>