<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Underdog 1975</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2018</Volume>
  <Summary>Holy dancing disco bellbottoms, Underdog! It's 1975 again! American Mythology has uncovered beautiful unpublished Underdog stories from the original Gold Key comic series that have never been seen before! These stories are by the original creative teams of Steve Skeates and John Albano and were discovered in a collector's stash. We've resurrected these archeological finds and given them some TLC to create Underdog 1975. We're also including some groovy reprint stories from the Gold Key series to make this a one of a kind time capsule issue. Go back in time with us to a simpler era with incredible cartoon characters. Underdog 1975 comes with four covers, Rogues Main by Adrian Ropp, Throwback Homage by Bill Galvan, Classic by Patrick Owsley and a special Retailer Retro Animation Incentive Edition.

*Contents:*
These two lost stories: Written by Steve Skeates, Pencils by George Wildman, Inks &amp; Colors by Matt Hansel, Letters by Natalie Jane.

"The Rubber Duck" - The All-Mighty Duck escapes from prison, takes a dip in polluted pond water, and becomes Rubber Duck! He tries to use his powers to rob a bank, but Underdog is nearby, so he's out of luck!"Dog's Worst Enemy" - Six enemies are intro'd at the very start, and then the story gets to its heart! A foe challenges Underdog, and gives him a tough time, but Underdog beats him while talking in rhyme!Written by Steve Skeates, Art by George Wildman, these six stories were originally presented in Underdog, V1 #23 (Gold Key, February, 1979).

"Bigfoot" - Bigfoot attacks the town, because his sore feet are giving him the blues! Underdog helps him out by getting him a giant pair of shoes!"Machine-Made Madness" - A mad computer makes Underdog rob a bank so he can have some counting fun, but it's not long before Underdog wins, and the machine's plans are undone!"Chasing Cars Again" - Simon Bar Sinister hits Underdog with yet another defective ray, but even under its influence our hero still manages to save the day!"Weak in the Knees" - Underdog stops a troll, but then Pie-Man hits him with a pie that makes him quite weak! But then a vitamin from his belt helps him win when it gives his stystem a tweak! A nice bit here aimed at keeping kids alive is that they called his pill a vitamin instead of U-235."Down the Tube" - Two underground aliens pluck people from the surface with their giant vacuum pump, but they put them all back after Underdog beats their rump!Coloring Page - Finally there's a splash page that's in all black-and-white - a page on which readers can color or write!*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                                                 | Creator(s)     | Sidebar Location |
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover (Rogues)                               | Adrian Ropp    | 1                |
 Var   | Throwback Homage Variant Cover                       | Bill Galvan    | 2                |
 Var   | Classic Variant Cover                                | Patrick Owsley | 3                |
 RI    | 1:3 Retailer Incentive Retro Animation Variant Cover | Animation Art  | 4                |
</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-14 00:13:24.  [CVDB650957]</Notes>
  <Year>2018</Year>
  <Month>01</Month>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Writer>Steve Skeates</Writer>
  <Penciller>George Wildman, George Wildman, John Albano</Penciller>
  <Inker>George Wildman, John Albano, Matt Hansel</Inker>
  <Colorist>Matt Hansel</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Natalie Jane</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Adrian Ropp, Bill Galvan, Patrick Owsley</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Mike Wolfer, S.A. Check</Editor>
  <Publisher>American Mythology Productions</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/underdog-1975-1/4000-650957/</Web>
  <PageCount>12</PageCount>
  <Characters>Professor Simon Barsinister, Riff-Raff, Sweet Polly Purebred, Underdog</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="2226941" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2170071" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="2311448" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="2049296" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1864078" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2526742" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="2587456" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2163614" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2353009" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2590142" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2517921" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="2588891" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
