<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1248282</GTIN>
  <Genre>Crime,Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:37:57 [Issue ID 4000-1248282] urn:comicvine:4000-1248282 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1248282
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:51:27. [Issue ID 1248282]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>Principles of Power - Chapter 4: Unity</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-4-principles-of-power-chapter-4-unity/4000-463438/</Web>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Summary>As City Hall continues to threaten Geoffrey Warner, Blaze must find a way to unite C.O.W.L....even as John's investigation brings a dark cloud over the organization.

Reginald Davis (Blaze), second in command at C.O.W.L., talks with his wife and nephew about the union's strike. His wife thinks he's being too much of lapdog to the Grey Raven and not enough of his own man.

At the strike, the picketers are concerned, it's against their conscience as heroes to not help people in need of help.  Eclipse and Radia leave for more of their "errands" against Camden Stone.

On the Grey Raven's advice, Blaze finds Arclight, who has been over the edge drinking and beating up on a hooker and her pimp, who wanted to blackmail him over his use of their wares.  Arclight thinks he's totally in the right but Blaze beats him up and tells him to get his head on straight.

John Pierce talks with the Grey Raven about what he's found about how C.O.W.L. plans ended up in the hands of the Chicago Six.  The Raven tells him he knows all about it; the alderman that Skylancer was supposedly trying to kill was actually giving him the plans because of an affair with his secretary.  Warner asks Pierce to wait before bringing this to the press, because they don't need bad news during the strike.

Pierce agrees but is suspicious of Warner.

Eclipse and Radia, now in non-C.O.W.L. disguises, continue to beat on Stone's criminals.

Blaze talks with Warner about Arclight; he wants to fire him, but Warner says the same thing he did to Pierce: they can't have bad publicity during the strike.  Blaze also agrees, but realizes his wife was right about his relationship with Warner, and can't let this keep happening.

Back at the strike, a fight starts between the police and C.O.W.L.  Someone dangerously and recklessly shoots a building with a fire blast, using their powers when they should have stopped due to the strike.

Features a bio of Blaze.</Summary>
  <Characters>Jim Macauley,Arclight,Frank,Radia,Eclipse,Don,Blaze,Alderman Lowe,Recon,John Pierce,Geoffrey Warner</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Indiana,Chicago</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Rod Reis,Stephane Perger</Penciller>
  <Inker>Rod Reis,Stephane Perger</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Trevor McCarthy</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Andy Schmidt</Editor>
</ComicInfo>