<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Invincible; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;: The Four-Sided Triangle</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>32</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Brandy, whose room is full of kitschy and bohemian knick-knacks, gets ready for the day with an impossibly enthusiastic attitude. "Impossibly," because her life is very hard, unknown to her friends, and she spends her day trying to "fake it to make it" in terms of having a positive outlook.

She wakes up her younger siblings and cooks them a wacky set of omelettes. Her brother, Danny, brings up the fact that their mom is a drunk, and is currently sleeping it off upstairs, but Brandy and her sister Rory cut him off--they don't want to deal with the reality of it.

Brandy calls her mom's work to say she's sick, but clearly they are aware of the problem and are not interested in many more excuses from her. Brandy has made this call many times before. She tries to put a brave face on it when she hangs up, telling her siblings that she loves the receptionist.

She goes up to say good-by to her mom and throws out all the liquor bottles.

She sees the landlord on the way out, who asks about the two months of rent they owe. She optimistically says they'll be sure to pay this month's rent soon but not last month's.

She continues to try to be happy in school, believing that you can see every problem as a time to learn. But there are whispers about her family and poverty behind her back, and she punches a kid out for talking about her mom. She only gets a carton of milk for lunch because it's all she can afford; in previous issues, Jenny and Ronnie have talked about how great she looks because she's so thin, but now we see it's because she can't afford to eat more.

Ronnie buys her a sandwich. Brandy has a crush on Zot, who eats with them. They talk more about the idea of men being possessive of the women they like, and Brandy says nobody owns her. As proof, she sets up dates with all the other boys at the table. Each one will take her out for a couple hours that day.

This annoys both Jenny--because now Zot will go out with Brandy--and Ronnie, who likes Brandy.

Her first date is with Spike, who shows her a bunch of horror movies, which gross her out. George doesn't show up, and Brandy wonders if he's actually gay, and feels bad for putting him on the spot. Woody takes her out to dinner, and after Brandy makes an inspired speech about how people are too uptight about sex, he tries to kiss her. She didn't mean to invite him to do that and pushes him away, leaving both of them embarrassed.

She has Zot take her to the gym and show her how he flies, which she loves. It's a symbol of how life can be uplifting. However, she tells Zot that she's not like Jenny, she likes their own world, even with all it's imperfections, although she'd like to visit Zot's world sometime.

Finally she goes to Ronnie's for her last date. Ronnie has gone all-out, covering the entire room with signs proclaiming his love, flowers, a tuxedo, and a fancily-set table. Brandy can't believe he has done this because of how expensive it is. He sold some of his old X-Men issues to pay for it, and those were his favorite. However, she means more to him than the comics. However, as someone who has to count every dime, she can't get over the cost. She does love him, and they eventually bond.

She takes him to a playground and talks about how old pictures of people, showing them when they're young, still makes the people look old somehow. She is sure, however, that she will always look young. She balances on a beam, enjoying the night.

In "The Four-Sided Triangle," Zot's friends from home think he spends too much time with Jenny. They decide to fix him up with Cynicalman instead. When Cynicalman shows up, Jenny is in the middle of yet another moment where she can't decide between Zot and Woody. She agrees to go out with Cynicalman. She tries to cheer him up but fails and becomes like him. Zot and Woody rush over to try to help but aren't successful. Zot's friends, who are now tired of Zot being around and the center of attention all the time, decide to help. They make a fake ad that cheers up Cynicalman, which then makes Jenny happy too.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:27.  [CVDB32946]</Notes>
  <Year>1990</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Eric Yarber, Ivy Ratafia, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-32-invincible-the-adventures-of-zot-in-dimensi/4000-32946/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <Characters>Brandy, Butch Weaver, Cynicalman, Digger, Elizabeth Madison, Floyd, George Tanaka, Hacker, Jenny Weaver, Ronnie, Spike, Vic Taylor, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="297963" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="185413" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="211819" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="204653" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="203153" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="217489" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="200909" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="210638" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="213969" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="212186" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="203332" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="204660" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="229410" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="185464" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="222594" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="184472" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="183396" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="165897" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="139547" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="230187" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="247763" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="223554" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="185216" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="166444" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="206119" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="212287" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="222070" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="220375" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
