<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Colorist>Eva de la Cruz,Matthew Soffe</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Cliff Robinson,Dylan Teague</CoverArtist>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1043389</GTIN>
	<Inker>Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Laura Helsby,Luke Horsman,Simon Davis</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>1</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:24 [Issue ID 4000-1043389] urn:comicvine:4000-1043389</Notes>
	<Number>2367</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1701803" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1501815"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1822229"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1917011"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1823107"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1820575"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1886772"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1920443"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1294162"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1290587"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1370328"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1653355"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1188934"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1261829"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1294911"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="993185"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1022978"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1167880"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1185444"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1581976"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1607969"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1271902"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1323758"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1456379"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1166879"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="2065923"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="2442917"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1759610"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1858658"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="2363599"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1278960"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="954892"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Laura Helsby,Luke Horsman,Simon Davis</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(january 2024)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Two new Thrills join Judge Dredd, Thistlebone and Enemy Earth this prog, Terrans — firstly, Paul Cornell and Laura Helsby collaborate on chronocollapsing, reality-shaking 3riller The English Astronaut; and secondly, Alex De Campi and Eduardo Ocana are back for the second series of deep-space caper Full Tilt Boogie, the first arc of which premiered in 2020 (Progs 2185-2194, to be exact). If you missed it, it’s been collected as a GN and is available from shop.2000AD.com in paperback, hardback and digital formats — but I’ve also supplied you Squaxx with a handy catchup in the Prog those that need their memories refreshing…

One of the scrotnig wonders of the modern GGC era is the expansion of my graphic-novel library. With the Treasury of British Comics unearthing gems from decades ago, my GN programme also sees 2000 AD books released every month — such as the latest entries in the Complete Judge Dredd Case Files and Strontium Dog Search &amp; Destroy volumes, which are out now. Never before has so much Thrill-power been so readily available!

*Judge Dredd » A better world (Part 4)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law! Now, Accounts Judge Maitland has been conducting an experiment in Sector 304 in a bid to reduce crime...

*Tharg's 3rillers Present » The English Astronaut (Part 1)*
Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story — a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre! Earth, November 1963, and Major Thomas Anderson is about to become the subject of a British Experimental Space Programme project. Locked into the Injection Seat, he’ll take a cocktail of drugs that will dislocate him from the current year and plunge him into 2024...

*Full Tilt Boogie » Full Tilt Boogie: Book two(Part 1)*
Out in the deep reaches of the cosmos, teenager Tee — together with her grandmother and cat — is a bounty hunter/hired help, operating from her spaceship the FULL TILT BOOGIE. Capable and resourceful, Tee was paid to rescue the Luxine Prince Ifan from his debtors’ prison. In the process, she encountered a resurrected Anubite warrior, a member of the enemy race with whom the Luxine Empire was at war...

*Enemy Earth » Enemy Earth: Book Three (Part 8)*
The near future. Mother Nature has turned against the people that live upon the Earth’s surface. Now, the planet’s flora and fauna have mutated and are viciously attacking humanity. As society crumbles, and survivors seek safety, young Zoe, who has lost her own family, has rescued Jules, who’s the prime minister’s son. Now, the pair have been reunited with the PM, and they’re journeying to India...

*Thistlebone » The Dule Tree (Part 4)*
Britain, 2020. It’s been over a year since journalist Seema Chaudry accompanied cult survivor Avril Easton back to the village of Harrowvale, where she suffered at the hands of THISTLEBONE worshippers, a crazed occult group that believed in an ancient woodland deity. One man in the village, Malcolm Kinniburgh, was keeping the Thistlebone legend alive — but now he’s dead, and his house is being cleared...

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-21 19:02:28.  [CVDB1043389]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2367-prog-2367/4000-1043389/</Summary>
	<Title>ad</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2367-prog-2367/4000-1043389/</Web>
	<Writer>Alex de Campi,Arthur Wyatt,Cavan Scott,Paul Cornell,Rob Williams,T.C. Eglington</Writer>
	<Year>2001</Year>
</ComicInfo>