<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Day>24</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-119064</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jay Anacleto</Inker>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:50:30 [Issue ID 4000-119064] urn:comicvine:4000-119064
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 11:54:23. [Issue ID 115272]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>18</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="666840" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="467665" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="720748" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="480101" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="750134" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="579255" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="585028" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="592786" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="558268" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="632766" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="632558" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="545411" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="433900" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="575566" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="451330" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="545803" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="334439" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="325822" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jay Anacleto,Jay Anacleto</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Athena Inc. The Manhunter Project</Series>
  <Summary>A certain black ops agency has come up with the perfect operative. She can't be caught. And even if she is there is no way to link her to any action because she doesn't even know she's an agent. Heck, she doesn't even look like their agent. How do they do it? Through the magic of genetics, of course. Our agent has a genetic trigger in her head and once that is thrown she changes into a completely different woman, different hair color, fingerprints, shoe size, mind - you name it. Witness a life out of balance. Gwen Morse is a member of the globetrotting elite, moving from one gala to the next. She's the paparazzo's darling, traveling to the most exotic locations, dining on the finest food, rubbing elbows with the biggest celebrities...one would think Gwen had the perfect life. But being a trendsetter is, well...boring, at least to Gwen. She dreams of another life, one where she's an international spy. The danger...the intrigue. But, as they say, be careful what you wish for. Because what she doesn't know is...well, that would be telling. Be there from the beginning of this high-tech action adventure. From Russ Manning Award-winning artist Jay Anacleto and writer/co-creator of Aria and Witchblade, Brian Haberlin.

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/athena-inc-the-manhunter-project-1/4000-119064/</Summary>
  <Volume>2002</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/athena-inc-the-manhunter-project-1/4000-119064/</Web>
  <Writer>Brian Haberlin,Brian Haberlin</Writer>
  <Year>2002</Year>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Bill,Sister Mary [Sister Mayhem],Mom,Morgan,Joan,Gwen Dawson,Tom Reynolds,Brother Johnnie,Randall,Benny,Allen</Characters>
</ComicInfo>