<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>King Tut: Truck Driving Pharaoh</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Volume>2013</Volume>
  <Genre>Fantasy,Comedy,Horror</Genre>
  <Summary>King Tut vs. the Radioactive Trailer Trash. King Tut battles nuclear mutants! He’s also involved in a shotgun wedding!

Just after defeating and escaping a vampire cult, King Tut and his new servant Frankie Laredo are trying to figure out what to do with the King's former queen, who has been turned into a vampire man. Frankie gets an idea and has them pull into a truck stop. Frankie goes in to get direction and then send the queen in and she goes into a vampire feeding frenzy giving King Tut and Frankie a chance to drive away in the chaos, leaving King Tut's bride behind.

The pair don't get far when a little girl runs out in front of the truck and appears to get hit. The pair get out to check on the girl, who screams and runs off. Frankie chases, while King Tut stays with the truck.

When Frankie catches the girl, her eyes begin to glow green, and Frankie realizes he is surrounded by mutants. The leader, Fred, explains they are The Radioactive Trailer Trash and that Bobby-Sue, the little girl, brought Frankie to their camp to marry Fred's daughter Betty. Frankie tries to argue, but Fred will not take no for an answer and takes Frankie hostage.

Meanwhile back at the truck, King Tut gets bored waiting and decides to wander around. He comes across some mutant cannibals in the woods and is forced to fight them off using his specter and other powers. Once they are defeated King Tut searches father into the woods, looking for Frankie.

King Tut arrives at the camp of mutants just in time to object to marriage of Frankie and Betty. Fred demands King Tut wrestle Bubba, or the group will eat both him and Frankie. King Tut excepts but when it looks like he is going to lose, Frankie cheats and shoots Bubba in the head with a shotgun.

In the chaos King Tut and Frankie make a break for it leaving the mutants behind. The pair make it back to the truck, while Fred is forced to consul his daughter over her ruined wedding.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-07-16 07:38:21. [Issue ID 894753]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Trauma Comics</Publisher>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Year>2019</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/king-tut-truck-driving-pharaoh-2/4000-894753/</Web>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <AgeRating>Mature</AgeRating>
  <Characters>Bobby-Sue,Fred,Tutankhamun,Frankie Laredo,Betty,Ankhesenamun,Bubba</Characters>
  <Teams>The Radioactive Trailer Trash</Teams>
  <Writer>Simon Sanchez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dean Juliette</Penciller>
  <Inker>Dean Juliette</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dean Juliette</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Dean Juliette</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>