<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Normal; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;:  A Date with Density</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>33</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>This issue deals with Jenny's friend Terry, as she realizes she has a burgeoning affection towards her former best friend Pamela. Terry attempts to deal with her lesbianism in secret at first, due to a previous incident in her school; when a boy, Harry, was found to love dancing classes and had skill in ballet, people assumed he was homosexual. A prank ensued, causing him to lose some hearing, and have an inner ear problem that destroyed his balance, and ending his dancing career. The prank is shown to have left him writhing in pain just after the incident. Pamela, the girl Terry likes, is Harry's sister. She is openly gay.

Terry is also friends with some stridently-straight popular girls, and has a hard time socializing with them, given her identity, but is also afraid to say anything that might make her come across as different.

Unable to deal with these contradictions, she insults her group of friends, who are all playing their unusual version of a role-playing game. They stand up for themselves as being happily weird, and Terry apologizes.

The next day at lunch they sit together again and talk about Zot's most recent attempt to stop crime, which was successful, but resulted in an injured wrist. They discuss the incident with Harry. Jenny encourages Woody to write about homophobia in the school paper but he says no. He is afraid he'll get attacked (verbally or physically) for it, because people will think he's gay too. Jenny is angry that he won't stand up for what is right, as Zot does when he fights crime. Woody admits he is not brave about this sort of thing.

Terry can't listen to this anymore and runs outside. She is eventually found by Zot, who had already figured out that she's gay. He comforts her and assures her that she is perfectly normal, and in his world everyone is welcome, including lesbians like Terry. She cries, still not feeling "normal," and he says, in a famous line, "look what they've done to you," meaning, look how they've gotten you to think of yourself as something "wrong." He tells her that he and Jenny will stay as her friends, no matter what.

That night, Terry tries to imagine many scenarios where she talks with Pam, but can't figure out what to say. The next morning, Pam says hello in the hallway, but Terry, afraid of being shunned, doesn't say anything and walks past her.

This seems like the end of the comic. The next page is a letters page. However, there is another page of the comic after that. In it, Terry turns around and calls out to Pam. They get together and talk.

This issue is one of the most well-known issues of Zot!, in part because it dealt with homosexuality in a positive way at a time when that was unusual in comics, and in part because of the twist ending. McCloud has said that he has heard from many readers who didn't realize the final page existed, and thought the story ended with Terry walking away from Pam without speaking.

In "A Date with Density," the friends (from both worlds) play their idiosyncratic version of a role-playing game. They talk about heroes and characters from both universes and engage in a silly version version of the date-a-rama from the "real" universe's previous issue with Brandy. Some of the others engage in an equally goofy version of pretending to be Zot fighting crime.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:29.  [CVDB33297]</Notes>
  <Year>1990</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Ivy Ratafia, Michael Dashow, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-33-normal-the-adventures-of-zot-in-dimension-1/4000-33297/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>Brandy, Digger, Elizabeth Madison, George Tanaka, Hacker, Jenny Weaver, Pam Singer, Peabody, Ronnie, Spike, Theresa Maria Veras, Vic Taylor, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="295665" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="175546" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="233868" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="153673" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="169036" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="210443" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="215758" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="196124" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="156461" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="192599" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="204983" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="188053" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="217233" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="209902" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="199699" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="190046" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="155088" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="181187" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="142782" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="231760" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="125295" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="255772" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="209045" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="194394" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="197032" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="201586" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="195209" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="198434" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="219430" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
