<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Abby Holland,Alec Holland,Anton Arcane</Characters>
	<Colorist>Francesco Francavilla</Colorist>
	<Count>42</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Chris Conroy,Matt Idelson</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-338473</GTIN>
	<Inker>Francesco Francavilla</Inker>
	<Letterer>Travis Lanham</Letterer>
	<Locations>Louisiana</Locations>
	<Month>8</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:13:06 [Issue ID 4000-338473] urn:comicvine:4000-338473</Notes>
	<Number>10</Number>
	<PageCount>21</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2100775" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1048951"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1400900"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1509201"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="856114"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1290423"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1524989"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="3369267"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1154190"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1811759"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1738729"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1721949"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1594019"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1658848"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1934750"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1985111"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1172686"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1123452"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1056714"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1419899"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="721612"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Francesco Francavilla</Penciller>
	<Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Swamp Thing</Series>
	<Summary>The deadly return of ANTON ARCANE!

This is the beginning of a new chapter in the SWAMP THING saga and a perfect time to start reading!

This issue begins with a mysterious narrator telling someone about Abigail. After defeating Sethe, Alec and Abby find a pickup truck and begin to drive back to Louisiana. The narrator tells that when Abigail was young she accidentally killed her mother when she was a baby by controlling a piece of dead matter in her brain. As they Abby drives the narrator explains that he took her in but she would resist him by hiding away in the Green. The narrator explains that Abby is coming near and that he must unfortunately cut the conversation short and bashes the listeners head in. 

They arrive at Abigail's old house in the middle of the swamp. When she pulls back the tarp that she covered him with and remarks at his wounds before helping him towards the swamp. She's surprised to see a glowing green grove in the middle of the swamp. Alec explains that it is the Parliament of Trees that he managed to draw from Brazil through the Green to here at this Louisiana swamp. He goes into the swamp and begins to sleep while Abby goes towards the house.

A shadow is cast over Alec and we see the issue come round full circle as the narrator is revealed to be this figure, ANTON ARCANE! Inside the old house, Abby hears the creak of a door, and pulls her gun. She is horrified by the sight of Arcane's Un-Men. Arcane steps out of the shadows and tells her he has killed Swamp Thing and is here to take her home.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-11-19 06:56:05.  [Issue ID 338473]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-10-arcanes-lullaby/4000-338473/</Summary>
	<Tags>Abby Holland,Alec Holland,Anton Arcane,Louisiana,Parliament of Trees,The Un-Men</Tags>
	<Teams>Parliament of Trees,The Un-Men</Teams>
	<Title>Arcane's Lullaby</Title>
	<Volume>2011</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-10-arcanes-lullaby/4000-338473/</Web>
	<Writer>Scott Snyder</Writer>
	<Year>2012</Year>
</ComicInfo>