<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Batman,Benjamin Franklin,Bobby Tisdell,Daredevil,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Jeff Preston,Jessica Jones,Mephisto,Michael Hawthorne,Scott Adsit,Shane Preston,Vetis</Characters>
	<Colorist>Val Staples</Colorist>
	<Count>45</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Jordan D. White</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-410319</GTIN>
	<Inker>Mike Hawthorne</Inker>
	<Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
	<Locations>Hell,New York City</Locations>
	<Month>8</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:05:06 [Issue ID 4000-410319] urn:comicvine:4000-410319</Notes>
	<Number>11</Number>
	<PageCount>24</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1948130" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1402959" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1943107" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1726029" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1908024" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="2495109" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1419638" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1310947" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1758707" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1963112" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1551374" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="2262372" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="2089932" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1677941" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1874014" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1796952" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1497281" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1697803" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1804379" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1749649" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1777908" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1794763" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="2036774" />
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="805240" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Mike Hawthorne</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Deadpool</Series>
	<Summary>Concluding the 2nd arc of MARVEL NOW! Deadpool!

Can Wade trust hell to keep their side of his contract?

Will all of Deadpool's new friends end up dead because of him?

Are turkey sandwiches better than ham?

2 of these 3 questions will be answered!

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                               | Creator(s)    | Sidebar Location |
----------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover                      | Tony Moore    | 1                |
 Var   | Wolverine Through the Ages Variant | Amanda Connor | 2                |
 RE    | Retailer Exclusive - Hastings      | Matthew Waite | 3                |
 

SynopsisAgent Preston's family is tied up and Deadpool cooks them dinner according to Agent Preston's directions. They all admit that the situation is weird. Agent Adsit arrives and hears that Agent Preston is in Deadpool's head. He doesn't believe it until Deadpool lets out the closely guarded secret that Adsit only has one testicle. Adsit is shocked that Preston could be in Deadpool's head. Preston's husband is shocked that she would know that. Deadpool welcomes Adsit to the team and asks him to find a life model decoy to put Preston's mind into.

In Hell, Michael is performing tricks for some other dead people. Mephisto makes a glorious entrance by busting out the back of some poor soul. He asks Michael what information he's got that goes beyond what he already knows about Vetis wants to take Mephisto's spot as leader. Michael provides further information about Vetis's practice of hoarding souls to build up his power. This gets Mephisto's attention and the two begin negotiating bringing Michael back to life.

On a rooftop, Deadpool spies his next victim on Vetis's list. Oddly enough, it looks like Luke Cage. Deadpool watches as Luke goes up to Jessica Drew's apartment and offers her some ice cream. Jessica gets suspicious of Luke's continued use of the name "baby," as well as his failing to bring her favorite ice cream. She punches him in the nose and Luke transforms into a short, fat guy named Bobby Tisdell, Deadpool's target. Deadpool barges in and attempts to catch Bobby, but he transforms into the Black Widow and escapes.

Deadpool follows Bobby/Black Widow down the street. Some police officers see Black Widow being chased and try to apprehend Deadpool. He whoops them and heads into Times Square. Too crowded to find Bobby, Deadpool shoots into the air and finds Bobby running away as people hit the ground. Bobby changes into a cheerleader and enlists a burly man to take care of Deadpool.

The burly man does a horrible job and Deadpool continues the chase. It's a short chase when Deadpool runs into Daredevil. The two fight but Deadpool proves to be no match. Deadpool then uses a distraction to get Daredevil off his back - he shoots a civilian in the leg.

With Daredevil out of the way, Deadpool catches Bobby and pulls him by his cheerleader hair. He then breaks Bobby's neck. Vetis immediately shows up and sucks up Bobby's soul. Vetis then lets the cat out of the bag and explains that Michael and Deadpool are next on the kill list. Deadpool lets his own cat out of the bag and explains that he already killed Michael and Vetis won't be able to suck up his most prized soul. Vetis gets very angry. He had a clause not to personally hurt Deadpool's recent victims; he has no clause against personally hurting Deadpool.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-10 10:20:53.  [CVDB410319]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-11-dare-to-be-deviled/4000-410319/</Summary>
	<Tags>Batman,Benjamin Franklin,Bobby Tisdell,Daredevil,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Hell,Jeff Preston,Jessica Jones,Mephisto,Michael Hawthorne,New York City,New York Police Department,Scott Adsit,Shane Preston,Vetis</Tags>
	<Teams>New York Police Department</Teams>
	<Title>Dare to Be Deviled</Title>
	<Volume>2012</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-11-dare-to-be-deviled/4000-410319/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Posehn,Gerry Duggan</Writer>
	<Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>