<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Amanda,Harold Lorre</Characters>
	<Count>7</Count>
	<Country>US</Country>
	<Editor>James Kuhoric,William Christensen</Editor>
	<Format>Miniseries</Format>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-892388</GTIN>
	<Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Month>10</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:47:33 [Issue ID 4000-892388] urn:comicvine:4000-892388 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/892388</Notes>
	<Number>5</Number>
	<PageCount>20</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1601985" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1359009"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="2518951"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1989876"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1936391"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="2770106"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="2797817"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="3575267"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="2239330"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="2898502"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="2796426"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="2629902"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="2378616"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="2352726"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="2395964"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="5717043"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="5898630"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="6333819"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="5233078"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="2707096"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
	<Series>Crossed Psychopath</Series>
	<Summary>It's Crossed vs Crossed as huge clans battle to the death! The band of survivors Harold Lorre has connected with have cleverly tricked two giant tribes of Crossed into fighting each other. The hope is they weed each other out and give the scared humans a chance to get far away. But no one suspects that Lorre himself might be a greater danger than the posse of Crossed they are hiding from. Lorre has certain needs that he must satiate. Join us as David Lapham and artist Raulo (Capt Swing) Caceres descend into a story about the worst aspects of human behavior, a tale of unspeakable evils, violent assaults on both mind and body, and of longing for death and the sweet release it will bring. When civilization crumbles in one terrifying moment; when people are gleefully breaking into unthinkable acts of violence all around you; when everyone you love has died screaming in agony: What do you do? There is no help. There is no hope. There is no escape. There are only the Crossed. Crossed: Psychopath #5 is available with a Regular cover by Jacen Burrows, a Wraparound cover by series artist Raulo Caceres, a Torture cover also by Caceres, and a special rare Red Crossed retailer incentive.</Summary>
	<Teams>The Crossed</Teams>
	<Volume>2011</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-892388/</Web>
	<Writer>David Lapham</Writer>
	<Year>2011</Year>
</ComicInfo>