<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Fart Wars</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Title>The Hick; Star Snores; Fart Wars: Again</Title>
  <Volume>1997</Volume>
  <Genre>Superhero,Humor,Science fiction,Satire-parody,Anthropomorphic-funny animals</Genre>
  <Summary>The Hick: One-page parody of The Tick, showing his equivalent - The Hick - cow tipping.

Star Snores: Radioactive Adolescent Black Belt Hamster fly through space in their ship, until they intercept a message that a planet Rodentia - populated by mice and hamsters - is about to be destroyed by a battle station Bad Breath Star. They crash their ship into the station, cause the station laser to hit a different ship, and take on the evil leader lizard. As they fly away from the explosion, Jackie suddenly wakes up - it was all a dream, and they're still in their trailer mobile home on Earth. Told by Clint there's a tornado coming, Jackie panics and runs away.

Fart Wars: Again: An evil galactic empire builds a battle station that can destroy planets with toilet paper. The evil Roll Vaders attacks a Rebel cruiser - two droids escape but are promptly destroyed. Unrelatedly, a sandcrawler runs over Skunk's shed, and he decides to fetch his gf Macy, who just quit her job at the battle station. Enraged Roll Vader tries to unleash power of the station, but he's stopped by a teamup of Skunk, Macy and Nira-X destroy the station in an X-Wing. Station crashes on a planet below, and a happy Hutt-like film producer celebrates record profits.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 21:52:32. [Issue ID 381943]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Entity-Parody</Publisher>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
  <Characters>The Hick</Characters>
  <Writer>Don Chin,Bill Maus,Don Chin,Bill Maus</Writer>
  <Penciller>Cynthia Martin,Gérald Forton,Bill Maus,Cynthia Martin,Gérald Forton,Bill Maus</Penciller>
  <Inker>Cynthia Martin,Gérald Forton,Bill Maus,Cynthia Martin,Gérald Forton,Bill Maus</Inker>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
  </Pages>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/fart-wars-1/4000-254771/</Web>
</ComicInfo>