<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Francine,Freddie Femur,Casey Femur,David Qin,Katchoo</Characters>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-179692</GTIN>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:47:51 [Issue ID 4000-179692] urn:comicvine:4000-179692
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:36:04. [Issue ID 179692]</Notes>
  <Number>26</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>Francine returns from Tennessee determined to find a man and begin a new life. But when she goes back to the rent house to get her things, she finds that David and Katchoo have already left, and they¹re not coming back! Will she accept their invitation to join them in an idyllic life in Hawaii, or will she stick to her decision to become the suburban mom of her dreams? It¹s a tough day for the girls that is rudely interrupted when Francine discovers Freddie has the nude painting of her hanging in his living room!

Francine is in a wedding dress stood on the ledge of an apartment building and she is having second thoughts. He relatives are asking what she is doing and she says she is thinking. Someone grabs her ankle and she falls but held up by the ankle. Her face is now level with a lower window with Katchoo inside and below on the pavement is a duck in a tuxedo. Katchoo asks if she can save her but she falls before she can take her hand.

Francine wakes on the bedroom floor as Katchoo checks in on her. She's decided not to join them on the New York trip. When Katchoo fails to ask why they argue about Katchoo's lack of caring and Francine's lack of commitment and when asked what Kat's intentions are with David she tells her she's doing what Francine should be doing with her. Katchoo shouts that though she loves Francine she can't commit while David has risked his life and given her his love over and over and she can't ignore it anymore.

A Broken Francine is left alone when Casey calls. Freddie has left her and Francine goes to comfort her. Francine comforts the devastated Casey who tells her its impossible when you love someone who love someone else.

On the plane Katchoo needs a drink when the plane suddenly loses control pitching people and object all over the cabin. They regain control and apologies as they seem to have lost hydraulic tail control but are only 60miles from the airstrip. David gets up to help the injured and Katchoo phones Francine who is out. Katchoo knows the plane is not going to make it. David asks if she was baptized, she confirms she was as a baby. He tells her she has to confess to Christ again now to be saved. She refuses and lists things she loves ending with "All I'll miss is you Francine"

At Casey Francine is in the bathroom and glimpses Katchoo in the mirror, she turns to talk to her and finds no-one there. She is gripped by a terrible fear and starts screaming</Summary>
  <Title>Running Late</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-26-running-late/4000-179692/</Web>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>