<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Algon (flashback, death),Taboo (villain, flashback, death, resurrection)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Petra Goldberg,Petra Goldberg</Colorist>
  <Editor>Len Wein</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-137495</GTIN>
  <Inker>Don Perlin,Don Perlin</Inker>
  <Letterer>John Costanza,John Costanza</Letterer>
  <Locations>Monterey,California,Los Angeles,Malibu</Locations>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:01:50 [Issue ID 4000-137495] urn:comicvine:4000-137495
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:46:12. [Issue ID 28484]</Notes>
  <Number>28</Number>
  <PageCount>20</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="5813669" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="4303742" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="4407961" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="4711426" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="4635159" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="4477523" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="3640776" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="4131874" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="4189774" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="3679129" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="3955530" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="4188455" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="3937012" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="3713016" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="4229129" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="4436814" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="4259445" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="4581941" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="4067198" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="4087744" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Don Perlin,Don Perlin</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
  <Summary>Approaching Lissa's 18th birthday, the gang fears she will succumb to the Russoff curse…!

Following his battle with Dr. Glitternight and his soul-creature, the Werewolf roams the California shoreline until dawn, once again becoming Jack Russell.

Two weeks later, Jack, Topaz and Buck Cowan receive a visitor to Buck's beach house: Jack's sister, Lissa who turns eighteen the next day. The event is a somber, as the foursome dread the possibility of Lissa succumbing to the Russoff curse.

That evening, they are attacked by a swarm of vicious bat-like creatures controlled by Glitternight. Despite Topaz's insistence that her adoptive father, Taboo, is dead, the sorcerer demands she tell him Taboo's whereabouts within two weeks, or he will make them pay. After Glitternight's departure, Jack recalls Taboo's death [see WEREWOLF BY NIGHT #14].

Nine days later, Topaz tells the others of a dream she just had: in the dream, the foursome sailed to an island castle where they found Taboo. To Jack, it sounds like his ancestral castle which was rebuilt on Blackgar's island near Monterey. With the full moon rising that night, they decide to rent a motorboat and take it out to the secluded island, where Jack (and possibly Lissa) can transform without threatening innocent people.

They enter the castle and are surprised to find Taboo waiting for them. Taboo explains he is indeed dead, but his soul was stolen and given substance by Dr. Glitternight's magic. Shortly, Jack transforms, and Glitternight arrives along with his bat-things. The Werewolf attacks the sorcerer.

Lissa feels the pain of transformation coming on, and Topaz, Taboo and Buck hustle her to a room where they shut the door, blocking out the vicious creatures. Topaz and Taboo use their powers to try to stave off Lissa's change, but Glitternight breaks into the chamber and bathes Lissa in his mystic black light. The conflicting magic spells force Lissa to become a demon-wolf hybrid who now faces the Werewolf as he enters the room.</Summary>
  <Tags>Monterey,California,Lissa Russell,Taboo,Dr. Glitternight,Algon,Werewolves,Malibu,Los Angeles,Werewolf By Night,Buck Cowan,Topaz</Tags>
  <Teams>Werewolves</Teams>
  <Title>The Darkness from Glitternight</Title>
  <Volume>1972</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-28-the-darkness-from-glitternigh/4000-137495/</Web>
  <Writer>Doug Moench,Doug Moench</Writer>
  <Year>1975</Year>
  <Count>43</Count>
  <Genre>Adventure,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>