<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Christine Trelane,Jack Hawksmoor,Doctor,Swift],The Authority [Apollo,Engineer,Kaizen Gamorra,Jackson King,Jenny Sparks,Midnighter</Characters>
  <Colorist>Laura Martin,Laura DePuy,Wildstorm FX,Laura DePuy,Wildstorm FX</Colorist>
  <Editor>Rachelle Menashe,Rachelle Brissenden</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-53619</GTIN>
  <Inker>Bryan Hitch,Paul Neary,Paul Neary</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bill O'Neil,Bill O'Neil</Letterer>
  <Locations>Garden of Ancestral Memory,London,New York City,Gamorra,Moscow</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:04:43 [Issue ID 4000-53619] urn:comicvine:4000-53619
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 22:27:33. [Issue ID 72153]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="905806" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="752655" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="742276" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="960443" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="942490" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="820026" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="758299" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="789713" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="859640" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="698410" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="806510" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="799076" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="601220" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="719166" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="769892" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="838550" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="877645" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="795315" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="684313" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="716965" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="927007" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="724788" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="729378" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="938942" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="642561" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="566577" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Bryan Hitch,Bryan Hitch</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Authority</Series>
  <Summary>In Moscow several dozen lab-created super powered beings (with super human strength, speed and laser vision) destroy buildings and people. In New York, Jackson King, former Weatherman of Stormwatch, complains that he can't do anything about the superhuman crisis in Moscow because of his lack of funding. He's also furious that Jenny Sparks and Stormwatch Black are nowhere to be found. Just as he says this, Jenny Sparks walks through a Door and asks to know everything that's going on. She's going to stop it.

The superhumans were created by Gamorra, an old enemy of Stormwatch. While Jackson was explaining to Jenny what was going on, Gamorra was doing the same. He was also bragging about how he'd come to be where he was today.

Seventy years ago the Brothers Gamorra were born in Parousia. By age ten they ran their village. By sixteen they ran the country. By eighteen they had remade Parousia into an island factory for terror. And by twenty, Kaizen Gamorra had killed both his brothers. He and his brothers used to have a symbol, a circle with three dots. In respect for his brothers, Kaizen Gamorra had used his super soldiers to carve the symbol on the Earth. He figures that with no Stormwatch to stop him, he can rule it all.

From King, Jenny learns nothing new. She doesn't let him know that though. When she returns to Jack Hawksmoor and Swift in the Carrier she explains why. When The Authority starts changing things on a big scale, Jackson King will be able to keep the "Powers That Be" off their backs, but only if he thinks he can control them.

Jenny sends Jack to check out the damage in Moscow and he does. The city is so devastated that when Hawksmoor gets there he starts to have a bloody nose. He also finds Gamorra's circle (though he doesn't know what it is) and a lot of background radiation.

Back on the Carrier, Jenny talks to Engineer and tries to find the Doctor. Jeroen Thorndike isn't actual on the same plane of existence as the rest of the team though. He's talking with the previous (dead) Doctor in the Garden of Ancestral Memory. Jeroen wonders if he has enough experience when the other Doctor tells him each new Doctor has all the knowledge and experience of the previous ones and tries to reassure him.

In a room somewhere in the Carrier, Jenny starts talking with Engineer about the old Stormwatch, about how she didn't want the old Doctor or the previous Engineer to die. Engineer says she knows and she's still amazed everyday that the Engineer could send her the nanobots she uses the very second he died.

Overhead, Apollo and Midnighter walk and talk about the current situation. Midnighter says that they should never have joined Jenny, should never have taken "Midnighter and Apollo" out of retirement. Apollo tells him that they are Midnighter and Apollo and that they're doing the right thing.

Time passes.

The group meets up in the mission room and Engineer tells them all that thanks to Hawksmoor they can pinpoint where the superhuman attackers came from, Gamorra Island, and where they're going next, London. Jenny Sparks does not like that at all. She was born in London.

Gamorra's soldiers start destroying London but don't get very far. Apollo takes out a group of them in one earth-shattering strike, Midnighter kills some more with his own unique style, Engineer guns some down with special machine guns grown from her arms, the Doctor turns others into birds, Hawksmoor punches off some heads, Swift decapitates a few in a fly-by, and Jenny Sparks electrocute the rest.

Game Over.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-10-19 07:40:07.  [CVDB53619]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-authority-1-the-circle-part-1/4000-53619/</Summary>
  <Tags>Jeroen Thornedike,Moscow,Jackson King,Synergy,Garden of Ancestral Memory,New York City,Gamorra,Kaizen Gamorra,London,Jack Hawksmoor,Engineer,The Circle,Midnighter,Apollo,Doctor,The Carrier,Swift,The Children Of Kaizen Gamorra,Jenny Sparks,The Authority</Tags>
  <Teams>The Children Of Kaizen Gamorra,The Authority</Teams>
  <Title>The Circle - One of Four</Title>
  <Volume>1999</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-authority-1-the-circle-part-1/4000-53619/</Web>
  <Writer>Warren Ellis,Warren Ellis</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Count>29</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>