<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers Go to College; Those Loveable Furry Freak Brothers; The Freaks Pull a Heist!</Title>
  <Series>The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>13</Count>
  <Volume>1971</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-23 21:36:13.  [CVDB270828]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 20:47:46. [Issue ID 264687]</Notes>
  <Year>1971</Year>
  <Penciller>Gilbert Shelton,Gilbert Shelton</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gilbert Shelton,Gilbert Shelton</Inker>
  <Publisher>Rip Off Press</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-fabulous-furry-freak-brothers-1-the-fabulous-f/4000-270828/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <Characters>Roaches</Characters>
  <Teams>The Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers</Teams>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="524776" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="434658" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="773632" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="684754" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="690014" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="423386" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="548088" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="612404" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="512856" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="498060" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="804198" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="760764" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="804958" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="651892" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="809546" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="781698" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="621734" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="569618" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="759418" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="798046" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="699054" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="728652" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="681608" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="385294" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="566438" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="575932" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1016730" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="865546" />
  </Pages>
  <Genre>Humor,Anthropomorphic-funny animals,Detective-mystery,Satire-parody</Genre>
  <Summary>Phineas gets mugged.

The broke trio put on Santa suits and go out pandhandling.

The trio set out to prove that their new phone is bugged by the FBI.

Phineas dresses up in a cop costume to teach the other two a lesson.

Phineas is interviewed on national T.V.

Fat Freddy's new waterbed plus the cat's claws equals....

Phineas goes to the Ol' Smokey National Forest.

Fat Freddy buys an old chopper after seeing Easy Rider in the movie theater.

Franklin borrows Fat Freddy's car to score a pound of dope.

Fat Freddy has bought a water bed.

The cat kills a roach that's scouting the area.

Phineas and Franklin clean up the pad due to a rumored police crackdown.

Franklin and Phineas raid a secret pot patch in the middle of the woods.

Fat Freddy goes to Ripoff Park to score a lid and gets robbed by drug addicts.

A fly bugs the cat.

The bros. go to the polls to vote.

The bros. hitch a ride to Washington D.C.

The cat ignores the leftover turkey that's on the table.

Fat Freddy buys a turkey at the slaughterhouse and cooks it himself.

Fat Freddy buys a twelve-gauge shotgun with the bros. food money.

The bros. booby trap their hallway to keep the feds from getting to their dope.

Fat Freddy buys cat food for his cat based on a TV commercial.

Franklin and Phineas cave in to Fat Freddy's demands for a birthday party.

The cat is worried about getting stepped on.

Fat Freddy tries to get into the three-day rock festival without a ticket.

Fat Freddy avoids taking unknown drugs from the surprise stash but still gets into trouble at the bar.

Fat Freddy can't remember the phone number he was given after walking down the street.

The cat's water bowl is empty.

Fat Freddy gets a job dressing up as Santa Claus but the kids keep asking for drugs.

Tricky is tricked into going to Harlem wearing a Lester Maddox button.

Fat Freddy receives a letter stating that he's drafted.

Norbert sneak into the bros. apartment to look for illegal weed so he can arrest them but winds up getting high off nitrous oside.

The brothers take a flight to Nashville to deliver an emergency supply of weed but encounter three plane hijackers.

The brothers drive to Mexico to score some weed.

Ordering pizza while in jail.

Fat Freddy's grass falls on the roof of a police car.

Fat Freddy is sent out with the brother's last fifteen dollars to score a lid of grass.

The brothers go to Disneyland.

Fat Freddy goes to the state university to show the campus radicals what revolution is all about.

Phineas creates a life-size remote control car and runs it on the street.

Fat Freddy blows the rent money on a giant magic marijuana seed.

Unable to buy any junk food because he's short on cash, Fat Freddy gets into a violent withdrawal state. The brothers decide to pull a heist on a grocery store in order to get Freddy some food.

The brothers expose the truth about that killer weed marijuana.</Summary>
  <Day>15</Day>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(00name 0000)</ScanInformation>
  <Writer>Gilbert Shelton</Writer>
  <Letterer>Gilbert Shelton</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>