<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Colorist>Nick Brokenshire,Nick Brokenshire</Colorist>
  <Day>21</Day>
  <Editor>Chase Marotz,Jake Williams,Chase W. Marotz</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-961279</GTIN>
  <Inker>Nick Brokenshire,Nick Brokenshire</Inker>
  <Letterer>Shawn Lee,Shawn Lee</Letterer>
  <Locations>The Bronx</Locations>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T00:52:38 [Issue ID 4000-961279] urn:comicvine:4000-961279
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-09 15:20:43. [Issue ID 2467542]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1572863" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="612639" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="2061409" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1505489" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1703366" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2997689" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1859413" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1566577" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1670320" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1803762" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1577824" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1398905" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="3280467" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1806586" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1627282" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1965448" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1936947" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1890923" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1331788" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1871226" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1669696" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1612217" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1765686" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1294604" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1738909" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="2129998" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="2145726" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1338445" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1204289" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Nick Brokenshire,Nick Brokenshire</Penciller>
  <Publisher>IDW</Publisher>
  <Series>Dead Seas</Series>
  <Summary>Ghosts are real and dangerous. But they're also valuable, their ectoplasm capable of curing countless diseases. There's only one problem: harvesting the wonder drug can be just as deadly. Prisoner Gus Ortiz is willing to take the risk in return for a reduced sentence-anything to see his daughter again. All it will take is a few months at sea scraping ectoplasm off the walls of the Perdition, a floating prison containing the most vicious ghosts on Earth. Surrounded by dark waters, Gus soon realizes that angry spirits are the least of his worries.The Poseidon Adventure meetsThe Haunting of Hill House in this supernatural thriller.

CreditsCavan Scott - StoryNick Brokenshire - Art, Cover A Art, Cover C Colors, Online Exclusive Variant ArtShawn Lee - Letters, Art Director, Design &amp; ProductionJake Williams - Editorial AssistsChase W. Marrotz - EditorArio Anindito - Cover B ArtKelley Jones - Cover C Art—Nachie Marsham, PublisherBlake Kobashigawa, SVP Sales, Marketing &amp; StrategyMark Doyle - VP Editorial &amp; Creative StrategyTara McCrillis - VP Publishing OperationsAnna Morrow - VP Marketing &amp; PublicityAlex Hargett - VP SalesJamie S. Rich - Executive Editorial DirectorScott Dunbier - Director, Special ProjectsGreg Gustin - Sr. Director, Content StrategyKevin Schwoer - Sr. Director of Talent RelationsLauren LePera - Sr. Managing Editor.Keith Davidsen - Director, Marketing &amp; PRTopher Alford - Sr. Digital Marketing ManagerPatrick O’Connell - Sr. Manager, Direct Market SalesShauna Monteforte - Sr. Director of Manufacturing OperationsGreg Foreman - Director DTC Sales &amp; OperationsNathan Widick - Director of DesignNeil Uyetake - Sr. Art Director, Design &amp; ProductionJack Rivera - Art Director, MarketingIndiciaDEAD SEAS #1. DECEMBER 2022. FIRST PRINTING. © Cavan Scott &amp; Nick Brokenshire. IDW Publishing, a division of Idea and Design Works, LLC. Editorial offices: 2355 Northside Drive, Suite 140, San Diego, CA 92108. The IDW logo is registered in the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office. Any similarities to persons living or dead are purely coincidental. With the exception of artwork used for review purposes, none of the contents of this publication may be reprinted without the permission of Idea and Design Works, LLC. IDW Publishing does not read or accept unsolicited submissions of ideas, stories, or artwork. Printed in Canada.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-05 10:32:25.  [Issue ID 961279]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/dead-seas-1/4000-961279/</Summary>
  <Tags>The Bronx</Tags>
  <Volume>2022</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/dead-seas-1/4000-961279/</Web>
  <Writer>Cavan Scott,Cavan Scott</Writer>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <AgeRating>Suggested for Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>