<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Iggy Nutmeg,Willy,Crazy Shirley,Heathcliff</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-217652</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T13:57:14 [Issue ID 4000-217652] urn:comicvine:4000-217652
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:29:47. [Issue ID 273318]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
    <Page Image="67" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(-04.)  (Mal32-Mouse5150-DCP)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Star Comics Magazine</Series>
  <Teams>The Muppets,Ewoks,Muppet Babies</Teams>
  <Volume>1986</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/star-comics-magazine-3/4000-217652/</Web>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Count>13</Count>
  <Tags>Miss Piggy,Muppet Babies,Top Dog,The Muppets,Heathcliff,Kermit the Frog,Ewoks</Tags>
  <Title>Shoveling It In; In Training; The Swim of Things; The Check-Up; In the Den of the Quorks (Flight to Danger Part 3); The Devil Beast (Flight to Danger Part 2); Flight to Danger; Meep Meep! (The Dream Machine Part II); The Dream Machine [Part I]; A Day at the Circus; Heathcliff Goes Hollywood</Title>
  <Genre>Anthropomorphic-funny animals,Humor,Science fiction,Children,Adventure</Genre>
  <Summary>Shoveling It In: Heathcliff's in disguise because he's trying to avoid Crazy Shirley.

In Training: Heathcliff pursues Harry the mouse, who's riding on Iggy's toy train.

The Swim of Things: A vacationing couple nearly catches Top Dog doing his competitive swimming strokes, but he reverts to the dog paddle just in time.

The Check-Up: Joey takes Top Dog to the veterinarian, and confusion results when they try to keep his intelligence a secret.

In the Den of the Quorks (Flight to Danger Part 3): The Quorks demand that the Ewoks build gliders for them, but Wicket and Kneesaa figure out a way to trick the Quorks so that they can escape.

The Devil Beast (Flight to Danger Part 2): The Ewoks learn that the savage Quorks have stolen the wood. They are attacked by a giant flying creature who captures Wicket and takes him to the Quork city.

Flight to Danger: Wicket, Teebo, and Kneesaa are named guests of honor for the Ewoks' Harvest Festival, which means they are charged with going and bringing back the special wood from which their gliders are made. But when they reach their destination, they learn that the trees of the sacred wood have all been stolen.

Meep Meep! (The Dream Machine Part II): After traveling through a western show and a talk show, Gonzo, Fozzie, and Miss Piggy are finally returned home to the nursery before Nanny finds out what happened.

The Dream Machine [Part I]: Bunsen and Beaker demonstrate their new dream machine, which transports Miss Piggy, Fozzie, and Gonzo into a television show.

A Day at the Circus: Iggy is not feeling well so the Nutmegs make Heathcliff stay home to take care of him while everyone else goes to the circus. Heathcliff gets his pet friends to put on a circus of their own, but he also has to stop some robbers from stealing the family's furniture.

Heathcliff Goes Hollywood: When movie star Marvin Cat comes to town and turns the head of Heathcliff's girlfriend Sonja, Heathcliff tries to get into the movie business himself.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Lennie Herman,Dave Manak,Stan Kay,Angelo De Cesare,Hal Smith,Lennie Herman,Dave Manak,Stan Kay,Angelo De Cesare,Hal Smith</Writer>
  <Penciller>Warren Kremer,Marie Severin,Warren Kremer,Marie Severin</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jacqueline Roettcher,Jon D'Agostino,Marie Severin,Jacqueline Roettcher,Jon D'Agostino,Marie Severin</Inker>
  <Colorist>Peter Kremer,George Roussos,Marie Severin,Peter Kremer,George Roussos,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Grace Kremer,Rick Parker,Grace Kremer,Rick Parker</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>