<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Adventures of Fat Freddy's Cat</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Count>7</Count>
  <Title>The Sacred Sands of Pootweet</Title>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Genre>Anthropomorphic-funny animals</Genre>
  <Summary>Fat Freddy and his cat travel to the oil-rich nation of Pootweet.

Fat Freddy's Cat visits a bookstore.

Phineas comments on the high cost of cat food.

Fat Freddy's Cat takes a nap in an aromatic rooftop vent.

Fat Freddy tries to solve a fly problem.

Fat Freddy's Cat tries to be friendly with Phineas.

A brave mouse attempts to put a bell around the neck of Fat Freddy's Cat.

Fat Freddy's Cat tells his nephews of their uncle "The Flash".

Fat Freddy's Cat leaves the house mice a big wheel of cheese.

Fat Freddy buys his cat a scratching post.

Fat Freddy's Cat must figure out a way to get to some delicious chicken bones.

Fat Freddy's Cat eats Fat Freddy's freshly rolled joints.

Fat Freddy's Cat hears Fat Freddy making something in the kitchen.

Fat Freddy's Cat is angered by a television cartoon.

Fat Freddy's Cat is locked out of the house.

Fat Freddy's Cat has a sudden bout of hyperactivity.

Fat Freddy buys a smoke detector.

Fat Freddy must feed his cat a pill.

Fat Freddy returns from a grocery shopping trip.

Fat Freddy's Cat prefers canned tuna over his cat food.

Fat Freddy's Cat meets a cat without a tail.

Fat Freddy's Cat tries to get Fat Freddy out of bed on a cold day.

Fat Freddy has run out of cat food.

Fat Freddy's Cat help Fat Freddy make a decision regarding beer.

Kommander Kockroach sends out a cockroach for recon duty.

Fat Freddy's Cat says "meow".

Fat Freddy's Cat smells offensive.

Fat Freddy's Cat makes a mess in the kitchen.

Fat Freddy's Cats nephews are bored.

Fat Freddy's Cat leaves the house for New Year's Eve.

Fat Freddy discovers his Christmas tree has been eaten.

Fat Freddy's Cat tries to get Fat Freddy out of bed.

Fat Freddy makes a "television" for his cat.

Fat Freddy's Cat wonders if turkeys are stupid.

Fat Freddy's Cat thinks he's found a snake.

Fat Freddy's Cat wants to go outside.

Fat Freddy is excited to decorate for Halloween.

Fat Freddy's Cat's nephews want to play in the street.

Fat Freddy's Cat watches the autumn leaves fall.

Fat Freddy's Cat wants to go outside.

Fat Freddy's Cat has fleas.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-16 19:51:23. [Issue ID 153618]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Rip Off Press</Publisher>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Year>1980</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Fat Freddy's Cat</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
  </Pages>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-of-fat-freddys-cat-5/4000-153618/</Web>
  <Writer>Gilbert Shelton</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gilbert Shelton</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gilbert Shelton</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Gilbert Shelton</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>