<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-164917</GTIN>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:42:59 [Issue ID 4000-164917] urn:comicvine:4000-164917
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 22:04:06. [Issue ID 258847]</Notes>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Mythstalkers</Series>
  <Summary>In 1893, five disparate adventurers began a quest that would eventually change the face of the civilized world. This is their story. In 2006, a time traveler went back to the Victorian Age to prevent five adventurers from changing the face of the civilized world. This is his story. In ancient times, gods walked the earth and monstrous creatures dwelt in the corners and shadows of the world, and now they're determined to come back. This is their story. Mythstalkers. We've got a story for everyone. Three stories whet your appetite for Victorian High Adventure this month! Watch as Lord Marston and Mrs. Chatterton lie, cheat and steal their way into the citadel of the Queen of Night! Gape as Victor and Colonel Durant fight a legion of gangsters and nursery bogies to recover Victor's soul from Batson and Quill! Marvel as Sir Charles single-handedly defends the Society headquarters from a siege led by the vengeful Valende! All this... and Coble continues his spate of blatant anachronism!</Summary>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/mythstalkers-7/4000-164917/</Web>
  <Year>2003</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>