<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Brande,Christine Blaze,Devan Lawless,Exotica,Grifter,Jenny Faraday,Lord Acheron,Maul,Max Faraday,Providence,Spartan,Tobruk,Void,Voodoo,Warblade</Characters>
	<Colorist>Tad Ehrlich</Colorist>
	<Count>13</Count>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Rachelle Brissenden</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-153581</GTIN>
	<Inker>Alex Garner</Inker>
	<Letterer>Dave Lanphear,Richard Starkings</Letterer>
	<Locations>New York City</Locations>
	<Month>8</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:37:39 [Issue ID 4000-153581] urn:comicvine:4000-153581</Notes>
	<Number>6</Number>
	<PageCount>20</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="472034" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="248622"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="388394"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="482347"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="273592"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="476322"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="297920"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="560589"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="476828"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="516473"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="531359"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="345507"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="504788"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="557711"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="432605"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="541550"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="301171"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="562096"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="456883"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="517133"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Divine Right: The Adventures of Max Faraday</Series>
	<Summary>Details of Christie Blaze's involvement in Operation Divine Right are revealed as Max discovers both the true source of his powers and Susanna's location.

New York City, Halo Building .

Void is meditating when suddenly she sense something. She teleports throughout the Halo Building seeing what each of the Wildcats are doing until finally she arrives on the roof where Providence is waiting for her.

Providence tells her about Max Faraday and how he unknowingly seeks to become "the third". They agree on a truce to find out more.

In the Hollow Realm , Blaze tells Faraday the truth about the realm. She tells them that Professor Senreich helped uncover an ancient artifact they dubbed The Creation Wheel . It had symbols on it that referred to events from The Bible. The symbols were a code they called the Creation Equation because it held the key to unlocking the very power of creation itself.

Faust was the one who translated the equation into computer code and she allied with The Rath . They then used the code to make a man-made Creation Wheel which they launched into orbit. It created the Hollow Realm and all the creatures that are part of The Rath.

She further tells him that the Hollow Realm is supposed to be Holo-Realm, as in Holographic projections. The Fallen believe they are fallen angels but Blaze tells Max they're nothing more than electormagnetic images given form and substance by the Creation Wheel. Max uses his powers to verify this but also finds Blaze is just like The Fallen; a fact The Fallen failed to tell Blaze.

Blaze is enraged and lashes out at The Fallen. But they are still convinced they are on God's side in a war between Heaven and Hell. Just then, Lord Acheron rides nearby with a phalanx of The Rath. Tobruk reveals that Lord Acheron is his brother.

Meanwhile, Jenny and Devan have snuck off together and are going swimming in small pool. They're about to share a moment together when something swims between Devan's legs. A serpent creature emerges from the water and attacks them. Jenny has an I.O. hangun from the safehouse and shoots the creature but it keeps on coming. But the others show up and Brande kills the creature. Afterward, they all continue their trek through the Hollow Realm.</Summary>
	<Teams>Rath,The Fallen,WildC.A.T.s</Teams>
	<Title>Truth Or Consquences</Title>
	<Volume>1997</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/divine-right-the-adventures-of-max-faraday-6-truth/4000-153581/</Web>
	<Year>1998</Year>
</ComicInfo>