<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Last Stand of the Spirits of Vengeance</Title>
  <Series>Ghost Rider</Series>
  <Number>30</Number>
  <Count>35</Count>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Summary>"The Last Stand of the Spirits of Vengeance" kicks into high gear! With Zadkiel and his army on the verge of conquering heaven itself, a force is gathering to oppose them, a group unlike any we've ever seen. But will their ranks include Johnny Blaze or has he given up the fight once and for all? Find out for yourself in this exciting new ###-kicking installment of the red hot GHOST RIDER!

In Tokyo, Japan, a young man on a motorcycle races to his home. Only to find his master dead. Danny Ketch is in the house. It turns out the master killed himself. He was a caretaker. A Dan talks down about the man he get punched threw a wall. The japanese boy is a Ghost Rider. Dan then changes . The Japanes ghost rider tries to smash Danny with a metal club but Dan in the end takes away his power and his life.

3 hours later Blaze, Sara, and two spirits on vengeance arrive at the seen to late. But Blaze des not care about what might happen if Zadikeil gets all the power from the spirits of vengeance. He leaves. It is then revealed that there are two spirits of Vengence left. they go out to get them.

Meanwhile Dan hides on the roof talking to Zadikeil threw a dove. Little does Dan know the Zadikeil is having a war with heaven as they speak. As zadikeil leaves Dan, he sends him some of his fallen angels.

Meanwhile in Brooklyn New York, two former cops meet in an apartment. One of the men is MIcheal Badilino who somehow escaped from Hell and a man with a hook named Kowalski. Micheal sells Kowalski Johnny Blaze's hellfire gun.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-22 12:12:39.  [CVDB148590]</Notes>
  <Year>2009</Year>
  <Month>02</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Jason Aaron</Writer>
  <Penciller>Tan Eng Huat, Tan Eng Huat</Penciller>
  <Inker>Tan Eng Huat, Tan Eng Huat</Inker>
  <Colorist>José Villarrubia</Colorist>
  <Letterer>VC, Joe Caramagna</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Arthur Suydam, Richard Corben</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso, Sebastian Girner, Joe Quesada</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ghost-rider-30-last-stand-of-the-spirits-of-vengea/4000-148590/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Bai Gu Jing, Ghost Rider (Blaze), Ghost Rider (Ketch), Molek, Sara, Vengeance, Vengeance (Kowalski), Yoshio Kannabe, Zadkiel</Characters>
  <Teams>Asura, Black Host</Teams>
  <Locations>Brooklyn, Heaven, Tokyo</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="393191" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="450758" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="406286" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="496317" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="363227" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="529896" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="543080" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="658813" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="620120" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="457796" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="557164" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="541372" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="379491" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="490729" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="776007" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="490744" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="486962" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="598046" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="548351" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="521417" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="390590" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="502610" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="438264" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="439288" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="770766" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>