<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>King Tut: Truck Driving Pharaoh</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Volume>2013</Volume>
  <Genre>Fantasy,Comedy</Genre>
  <Summary>A museum sometime at night, the King Tut exhibit is being packed up and crated off to New York. The two truck drivers and the museum curator don't notice a mysterious figure sneak into the semi container. 

Then later, the drivers pulls over to pick up two, ladies of the evening, unaware that in the container the mysterious figure opens the sarcophagus of King Tut's queen, slices his arm and drops blood in and awakens the long dead queen. Meanwhile in the cab of the truck the two women, are revealed to be men and vampires. They kill the two drivers and attempt to steal the truck.

In the container, one of the vampires finds the newly alive queen, bite her and kill her. This act awakens King Tut who uses his specter and powers to kill the vampires in the container, but when he gets to the cab the driver vampire calls for back-up. 

A high speed chase ensues that leads to King Tut crashing the semi into a cave and being knocked unconscious. He awaken in the lair of the vampires, tied up and powerless. The head vampire reveals that her and her coven used to be men that wanted a sex change, but it was too costly so they hired a mad scientist to do the operations. He used vampire bat blood to cover costs and the resulted turn them all into vampires whose bit changes their victims genders.

They are powerful but not immortal, and that is were King Tut come in, they plan to drain his blood and become immortal, but before they can complete their plan, the mysterious man arrives again and helps King Tut get away. They blow up the lair on their way out and the mysterious man offers to be King Tut's servant. The pair believe to get a way without incident but then it is revealed King Tut's queen is now a vampire and a man.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-07-16 07:38:07. [Issue ID 894752]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Trauma Comics</Publisher>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Year>2013</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/king-tut-truck-driving-pharaoh-1/4000-894752/</Web>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <AgeRating>Mature</AgeRating>
  <Characters>Tutankhamun,Frankie Laredo,Ankhesenamun</Characters>
  <Teams>Vampires</Teams>
  <Writer>Simon Sanchez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dean Julliette,Don Marquez,Dean Juliette</Penciller>
  <Inker>Dean Julliette,Don Marquez,Dean Juliette</Inker>
  <Colorist>Otavio Liborio,Dean Juliette</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Dean Juliette</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Don Marquez</CoverArtist>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>