<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Elaine</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bob Sharen,Mark Badger,Bob Sharen</Colorist>
  <Editor>Carl Potts,Jim Shooter</Editor>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comixology:822168</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Mark Badger,Mark Badger</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Ken Bruzenak,Ken Bruzenak</Letterer>
  <Locations>France,Virginia</Locations>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:28:09 [Issue ID 4000-25879] urn:comicvine:4000-25879 urn:comixology:822168
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 14:45:44. [Issue ID 40431]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1438529" ImageWidth="1988" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1684723" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1613420" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1820897" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1844323" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1564454" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1627501" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1822485" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1614933" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1836044" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1655655" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1666756" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1897248" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2079094" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1809812" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1716645" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1620041" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1559244" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1924505" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1303249" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1358740" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1279214" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1212148" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1350807" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1264570" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Mark Badger,Mark Badger</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Digital) (Shadowcat-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Gargoyle</Series>
  <Summary>With a new resolve, Isaac, Derwyddon, and Germaine confront the gargoyles wreaking havoc on their town!

Isaac Christians, Derwyddon, and Germaine arrive in Blackston, Virginia, ushered in by the music of Pan's pipes. There, they find a Bacchanalian revelry being led by gargoyles. The leader of the gargoyles greets Christians, Derwyddon, and Germaine with unexpected cordiality. As the gargoyle speaks, Christians' memories of World War I are rekindled. Derwyddon protests, and condemns, the horror the gargoyles have wrought in Blackston. The gargoyles merely laugh at Derwyddon. Germaine shows surprising compassion, as Christians continues to wrestle with his memories of the war.

The Gargoyles attack Derwyddon. Christians feels powerless to aid Derwyddon. Marshaling all of his eldritch power, Derwyddon cancels the spell animating the gargoyles, returning a host of them to unmoving stone. The gargoyles retreat in the face of Derwyddon's power, fear finally finding purchase in their leader's heart. Derwyddon's power, though, reaches it's limit. Christians, Derwyddon, and Germaine, flee to the church, in hopes of sanctuary. Derwyddon conjures forth a floral barrier to keep the gargoyles at bay. Derwyddon collapses In exhaustion.

Christians is consumed by his memories of World War I. Christians had lied about his age to join the army. Shortly after arriving in France, Christians' newfound friend, Clarence Johnson, was gunned down in front of him. Christians fled straight into the waiting arms of a German soldier. Said soldier was slain by Christians' friend from home, Buster Henderson. Christians, and Henderson, took shelter in an abandoned farmhouse. As the German army closed on their position, Christians froze in terror, allowing his friend, Henderson to be gunned down.

American soldiers soon arrived to drive the Germans off. Christians, traumatized by his cowardice in the face of war, was never the same man again. He could not return home. He could not face the love of his life, and Henderson's, Elaine Willoughby. Not until he atoned for his inaction. Derwyddon sees his Gods in the God of Christianity, and draws strength from it. Derwyddon drives the ancient spirits, possessing the populace of Blackston, out. Derwyddon is struck down by the leader of the gargoyles. Christians finds the courage to grapple with the gargoyle

The unleashed bio-mystical energy, released in their struggle, transfers their souls into each other's bodies. Once more, Christians has become the Gargoyle. Trapped in Christians' mortal body, the spirit of the gargoyle rails in impotent fury. The Gargoyle slays Christians, forcing the gargoyle's spirit to return to stone. Derwyddon departs. Willoughby's spirit usurps Germaine's, claiming control of her body. The Gargoyle unburdens his heart to Willoughby, as her spirit returns to the ether. The Gargoyle, at long last, has achieved his atonement.</Summary>
  <Teams>United States Army</Teams>
  <Title>Battlefield!</Title>
  <Volume>1985</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/gargoyle-4-battlefield/4000-25879/</Web>
  <Writer>J.M. DeMatteis,J. M. DeMatteis,J. M. DeMatteis</Writer>
  <Year>1985</Year>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Mark Badger</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>