<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Celestia,Justin Braddock,Kaila,Theros</Characters>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Editor>Darren G. Davis</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-119732</GTIN>
  <Inker>Armando Durruthy,Rick Ketcham</Inker>
  <Letterer>Dreamer Design</Letterer>
  <Locations>Africa,Sudan</Locations>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:19:57 [Issue ID 4000-119732] urn:comicvine:4000-119732
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 09:34:57. [Issue ID 119732]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Black Tide</Series>
  <Summary>Magic, myth, science and history combine as we discover our world as it was, where history has brought us and where we go from here in this all-new super-powered ongoing series. Meet three fascinating heroes that truly prove once and for all that "the sum is greaterthan its' parts." Justin, Kaila and Theros are the combined key to immense power. When united-they are unbeatable. When they are odds with each other, their power is devastatingly dangerous. Together, they once caused a war so intense an entire continent crumbled and sank into the sea. At this very moment, they are united and battling super terrorists and high crimes against the world. Under the cover guise of a black ops organization called Deceivers, they fight ancient Earth enemies who are far more deadly than any single one of them. But with demons-both internal and external-still haunting them, can they be trusted to save mankind...or will their conflicts with each other destroy us all? Hidden from mankind and hated by each other, a chance meeting has finally united Justin, Kaila and Theros-The Triune. The question is..."Are they Earth's savior or future source of destruction?"</Summary>
  <Volume>2001</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/black-tide-1/4000-119732/</Web>
  <Year>2001</Year>
  <Writer>Debbie Bishop</Writer>
  <Penciller>Mike Miller,Mike Miller</Penciller>
  <Colorist>James Rochelle</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Andy Park,Chris Bachalo,Dave Stewart,James Rochelle,JMD,Mike Miller,Rick Ketcham</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>