<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Cavewoman: Rain</Series>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>Professor Cook and Bruce bury Meriem and Prof. Cook says a few kind words. Two weeks later the citizens of Marshville have taken shelter in the Marshville Museum of Science to wait for the rains to stop. Food is running low and the electricity is out. The only water they can get is coming from the storm drains. While waiting for a stew to be ready, some of the people gathered around tell stories of Meriem's various heroics. On the second floor of the Museum some men are performing an autopsy on Klyde. They are a little jumpy. Bruce tells the kids about how she survived that time she saved them (back in her original series). She told him she knew she'd be OK after she stopped breathing and Lumpy gets his hopes up that's she's alive even though it's been two weeks.

There is a rumbling and part of the building caves in sending Bruce and a girl he used to know into a sewer with large Crocodile like reptiles. Lumpy tells Prof. Cook that Bruce might believe it too and that he went to her grave to see. The Professor heads there right away to help Bruce. It's around this time that Klyde wakes up. He isn't dead and the men flee the room with Klyde behind them. Klyde stops and sees all of the people on the first floor from a balcony and they see him. Professor Cook arrives at her grave to see it overflowing with life. Plants and dinosaurs are surrounding it. He shoos them away and tries to fend the larger ones off with a club. He turns and sees Meriem standing behind him. He tries to say something but she tackles him. He says her name, confused, and she stabs him with a stake.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 03:30:17. [Issue ID 59687]</Notes>
  <StoryArc>"Cavewoman: Rain" Rain</StoryArc>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cavewoman-rain-6/4000-43153/</Web>
  <Characters>Cavewoman</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>Prehistoric Jungle,Marshville</Locations>
  <Writer>Budd Root</Writer>
  <Penciller>Budd Root</Penciller>
  <Inker>Budd Root</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bradley Walton,Cara Walton</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Budd Root</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Joe Pruett</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Title>Chapter Six</Title>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
</ComicInfo>