<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Winston Churchill,Jodrell Bank,Sir John Dashwood,Lucy,Colonel Trichel</Characters>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Editor>Michael Heisler</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-105698</GTIN>
  <Locations>The Moon,Germany,England</Locations>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:35:53 [Issue ID 4000-105698] urn:comicvine:4000-105698
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:40:47. [Issue ID 89444]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="335449" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="292599" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="505231" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="477107" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="544082" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="450015" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="375543" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="414884" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="427760" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="387076" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="352946" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="353032" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="384934" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="438718" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="491274" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="445323" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="351042" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="401998" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="419405" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="446870" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="338437" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="399727" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="384187" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="407299" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="434138" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="488415" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="514033" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="452471" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="134995" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Ministry of Space</Series>
  <Summary>The dying days of World War 2. The US Army is running Operation Paperclip, getting the makers of the V2 out of Germany and into America before the Russians overrun their position. And this is where history takes a hard twist. Because the Army arrive to find the Germans, and all their machinery, are gone. Taken by the British. MINISTRY OF SPACE is an alternate history, the story of a a British space programme that outraced the rest of the world. Now that Britannia rules the waves of space, a utopian green-field England plies ships to the Moon, to Venus, to Victoria Station in low Earth orbit. This is the Ministry that sent a colonisation flotilla to Mars in 1963. The Ministry that destroyed a city and ran an exploration program unseen in human history. A Golden Age-- and what it cost. The black budget that financed the move into space. The deaths of the test pilots, taken from the surviving Spitfire flyers of the Battle Of Britain. And, in 2000, the end of the Golden Age, as America and Russia begin moving into space. the secret revealed, and the destruction of a man who sacrificed himself for the Ministry of Space. This is the story of how we could have gone to space. Maybe the way we "should" have gone to space. This is the story of the Ministry Of Space. Warren Ellis is the award-winning writer/creator of Transmetropolitan, Planetary and The Authority, named as one of the hottest writers of the moment by ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY and ROLLING STONE. Chris Weston is the acclaimed artist of key sequences of THE INVISIBLES, SWAMP THING and LUCIFER. Laura DePuy is the award-winning colorist of JLA: HEAVEN'S LADDER and PLANETARY.</Summary>
  <Teams>Royal Air Force</Teams>
  <Volume>2001</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ministry-of-space-1/4000-105698/</Web>
  <Writer>Warren Ellis,Warren Ellis</Writer>
  <Year>2001</Year>
  <Penciller>Chris Weston,Chris Weston</Penciller>
  <Inker>Chris Weston,Chris Weston</Inker>
  <Colorist>Laura Martin,Laura DePuy,Laura DePuy</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Chris Weston,Laura Martin</CoverArtist>
  <Title>untitled</Title>
  <Genre>Science fiction</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Letterer>Chris Weston,Chris Weston</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>