<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Trucker Fags in Denial</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2004</Volume>
  <Summary>From the twisted minds behind such notorious publications as Answer Me!, The Redneck Manifesto, Shit Magnet, Bad Meat, and Glam Warp comes the sordidly hilarious tale of Butch and Petey, two aging, obese truckers so steeped in denial of their homosexuality, they're about to burst! Follow these two lovable losers as they trek across the USA in their battered eighteen-wheeler, doling out misdirected hatred to all they encounter, and eventually succumbing to their long-repressed lust for each other! Trucker Fags in Denial marks writer Jim Goad's first crack at writing a feature-length comic book since his recent 3-year bid in an Oregon prison. Artist Jim Blanchard, perhaps best known in the comic world as the Harvey-nominated inker for the final 15 issues of Peter Bagge's HATE comics, has never been to prison. Don't miss this sleazy, lovingly-crafted underground comic opus!

Contains graphic sex and nudity. A humourous exploration of the relationship between two bigoted long-distance truckers.

When Butch and Petey are forced to spend the night together in a hotel room thanks to a mix up, they soon discover that they are sexually attracted to each other and begin to experiment. But the two men are so prejudiced that neither can come to terms with their sexuality, forcing them to constantly rationalise their actions. When this is no longer enough to appease their guilt and frustration, the pair start killing homosexual men on the road, while still enjoying a sexual relationship with each other.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-25 19:17:55.  [CVDB386602]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 15:32:44. [Issue ID 815161]</Notes>
  <Year>2004</Year>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Day>30</Day>
  <Writer>Jim Goad</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jim Blanchard</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jim Blanchard</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jim Blanchard</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Jim Blanchard</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Gary Groth,Kim Thompson</Editor>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/trucker-fags-in-denial-1/4000-386602/</Web>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <Characters>Butch,Petey</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1392128" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="716354" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1879902" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1909734" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="2289002" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2430054" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1623470" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1563528" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1623282" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2106214" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2519672" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1512362" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="3673782" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="2709278" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="3244522" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1957958" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1843546" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2802560" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="2644918" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2565280" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="2332320" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="2756036" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="2224914" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="2253574" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1582530" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="2336990" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="2050850" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="5440078" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="2685074" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="912400" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1352036" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1023388" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="1401234" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="482432" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="1808540" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="651908" />
  </Pages>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
  <AgeRating>Adults Only</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>