<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Midnighter,Hawksmoor,Doctor,Jenny Sparks,Apollo,Swift,Engineer</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ian Hannin,Ian Hannin</Colorist>
  <Editor>John Layman</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-66947</GTIN>
  <Inker>James Hodgkins,John McCrea,James Hodgkins</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bill O'Neil,Bill O'Neil</Letterer>
  <Locations>Amsterdam,London Bridge,Space,Rome,Garden of Ancestral Memory,London</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:14:57 [Issue ID 4000-66947] urn:comicvine:4000-66947
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:22:15. [Issue ID 86060]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="745593" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="809701" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="812874" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="781379" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="805688" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="756416" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="809093" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="814357" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="888578" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="852204" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="917647" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="713911" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="771414" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="786799" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="838550" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="810653" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="726475" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="626288" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="716584" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="802243" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="657682" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="629219" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="779676" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1028760" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="944522" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>John McCrea,John McCrea</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Jenny Sparks: The Secret History of the Authority</Series>
  <Summary>Jenny Sparks' diary reveals how the ashes of StormWatch led to the creation of The Authority in a remarkable 5-issue miniseries. It's a story well known to fans of STORMWATCH and THE AUTHORITY: After StormWatch met its untimely end, a new team — The Authority — rose from its ashes, facing threats on a global scale and beyond. But what happened between the death of one team and the birth of another? The answers are found in JENNY SPARKS: THE SECRET HISTORY OF THE AUTHORITY, a five-issue miniseries that delves deep into the characters — some familiar, some still enigmatic — that comprise the most powerful team in the Wildstorm Universe . Written by Mark Millar (THE AUTHORITY, SUPERMAN ADVENTURES) with art by HITMAN's John McCrea (who also provides the covers) and inker James Hodgkins (LUCIFER), the miniseries uses Jenny Sparks's diary — now in the hands of her replacement on the team — as its core, detailing her first meetings with the new team's members. In issue #1 — which features a variant cover by the original THE AUTHORITY art team of Brian Hitch and Paul Neary (now on JLA) — the first entry the new leader reads is dedicated to the Doctor. Where did he come from? How did he find the colossal, fifty-mile-wide structure — currently the team's base of operations — on the edge of the Bleed ? Future issues showcase Apollo, the Midnighter, and the Engineer, with appearances by Swift, Jack Hawksmoor and other members of both the Authority and StormWatch in an epic spanning a century of adventures.      Jenny Sparks lies lifeless with her teammates surrounding her. The world stands silent whilst the funeral takes place in London.15th February 1999, Jenny arrives in Amsterdam and meets up with Swift. The pair walk through the streets and talk briefly about the person they are about to meet. Jenny runs over the guest's personal history with Swift, indicating that his life had recently taken a turn for the worst, and that he had turned to heroin for comfort.Jeroen Thornedike shows no interest in Jenny’s propoal to join her team.Jeroen briefly touches on the moment he received his calling as the Doctor, then reiterates he has no interest in joining the team. He then teleports Jenny and Swfit away. In StormWatch's old underwater headquarters, Jenny discusses other potential members with Jack Hawsmoor and Swift. Jack indicates that Midnighter and Apollo have agreed to join to the team, and that the the Engineer is more than willing to sign up.Jenny's attention turns back to the Doctor. She is determined to have the Doctor join the Authority. She tracks Jeroen to Amsterdam, and sneaks up on him inside a sex shop. Jeroen still insists he has no interest in joining her team, and has nothing further to say to her. Left with no choice, Jenny forces Jeroen's hand. She takes a gun and shoots herself in the head. Realising he can't leave Jenny dead, Jeroen pushes through the crowd, and uses his magical abilities as the Doctor to heal her. Jeroen is then congratulated by past Doctors in the Garden of Ancestral Memory. Swift and Jack Hawksmoor have a strange encounter with the Engineer, who recognises the underwater location as the old StormWatch base. The Engineer makes reference to being almost eighty years away from where Jenny needs her and confirms that she is on a time jump from 2001. She is looking for Jenny Sparks, not Quantum. Jack questions the Engineer on her theory. She apologises for the confusion, stating she has said more than she should have, then departs.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-10-21 16:34:19.  [CVDB66947]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/jenny-sparks-the-secret-history-of-the-authority-1/4000-66947/</Summary>
  <Tags>Midnighter,The Authority,Doctor,Jeroen Thornedike,Amsterdam,Jack Hawksmoor,Jenny Sparks,London Bridge,Space,Rome,Garden of Ancestral Memory,Doctors of Earth,Apollo,London,Swift,The Carrier,Engineer</Tags>
  <Teams>Doctors of Earth,The Authority</Teams>
  <Title>Doctor's Orders</Title>
  <Volume>2000</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/jenny-sparks-the-secret-history-of-the-authority-1/4000-66947/</Web>
  <Writer>Mark Millar,Mark Millar</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>