<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Season of Dreams Pt. 3; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;! (#15)</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>15</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Max, Peabody, and Butch continue to circle around Zybox. A storm is brewing. They can't attack him while he has the kids inside.

When they land, they see that everyone is hynotized, just like on their trip here. Max asks Floyd to sneak in, using his anti-surveillance technology.

Peabody and Butch go up the tower's elevator.

Jenny talks about Zybox with Ernie, its inventor. He explains that it is still following programming, it's just that he accidentally took away most of its rules when he was angry. However, it can't hurt people.

Zot and Vic wake up; Floyd severed the connections that had kept them in a coma.

Floyd brings them their guns and puts the room in a temporary no-surveillance zone so Ernie can talk without Zybox hearing.

Jenny, Zot, Vic, and Floyd race toward the exit. However, Zybox keeps putting traps in their way.

Ernie and Zybox talk. Zybox asks if Ernie knows his plan, and he says yes and that he will help. Zybox asks why he was programmed to believe in a soul when there is no proof of it. Ernie says he wanted him to have faith in something.

The hypnotized people all around the world start to move. They begin preparations to kill themselves.

Zybox explains that if 5 billion people all die simultaneously, the small amount of energy that is their souls will be noticeable, unlike when they die in small numbers. He hopes to catch one soul for himself.

Peabody and Butch meet up with the kids and help fight off some robots. Butch realizes he has turned back into a monkey inside Zybox's internal dimension. However, they have an increasingly difficult time fighting off even more robots.

Ernie asks to see Zybox's core so he can see if it changes when he catches a soul.

Zybox turns off. Zot uses the time to fly up and prepares to shoot Zybox in the face. However, a lightning strike beats him there, and blows Zybox's head up.

Max finds Ernie, who is caught upside-down and dying. He explains that he jumped into the core, which would have killed him. Since Zybox wasn't allowed to kill anyone, he had to turn off, giving Zot the chance to fly out--and stopping him from giving the order for all of humanity to kill thsmselves. However, Ernie dies anyway.

Ernie's watch lays against Zybox's microphone. Its ticking is relayed to people across the Earth. They all start dancing to it, but they will all forget in the morning. Zot and Jenny dance as well.

Construction crews from Zot's world take apart Zybox as the people of Jenny's Earth sleep. One of Ernie's friends pulls Ernie's son away from the video game that he was hypnotized into playing.

In the back-up story about Dimension 10 1/2, Zot fights Bellows.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:51.  [CVDB28664]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Denis Mcfarling, Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-15-the-season-of-dreams-pt-3-the-adventures-of/4000-28664/</Web>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <Characters>Bellows, Butch Weaver, Ernie Cortez, Floyd, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Vic Taylor, Zot, Zybox</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="179011" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="477627" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="414062" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="981517" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="498888" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="417686" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="379243" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="462921" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="471611" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="462295" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="441673" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="371410" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="430343" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="436629" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="404649" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="411353" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1050368" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="348352" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="408684" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="642209" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="588736" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1030486" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="470378" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="531912" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="447421" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="439273" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="479932" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
