<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1375</GTIN>
  <Inker>Ken Bald,Paul Gustavson,Emil Gershwin,Ken Landau,Paul Gustavson,Emil Gershwin,Ken Landau</Inker>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:36:09 [Issue ID 4000-1375] urn:comicvine:4000-1375
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:11:35. [Issue ID 11586]</Notes>
  <Number>34</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Ken Bald,Paul Gustavson,Charles Nicholas,Emil Gershwin,Ken Landau,Paul Gustavson,Charles Nicholas,Emil Gershwin,Ken Landau</Penciller>
  <Publisher>American Comics Group</Publisher>
  <Series>Forbidden Worlds</Series>
  <Volume>1951</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/forbidden-worlds-34/4000-1375/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Title>Day of Reckoning!; Secret of the Goratti; My Fanged and Fiendish Darling; Rezendevous with Death</Title>
  <Genre>Adventure</Genre>
  <Summary>Day of Reckoning!: Fred Greene, a uranium prospector, witnesses a UFO crashing in the hills. When he investigates, he comes across a race of malevolent aliens from the planet Xereses who plan to wipe out all life on Earth using their advanced weaponry in the near future. Fred threatens to warn humanity but the aliens leader, Toabor, uses a hypnotic ray on him, so Fred will not remember what will happen to the Earth.

Secret of the Goratti: Chilos and Tarne find out about an ancient cult from the middle ages called the "Goratti" that were able to turn objects into gold through occult means. After finding their ancient castle, the pair inadvertently awaken the decaying remains of the Goratti. After spying on them from afar they realize that human sacrifice is the way they create Gold. When the greedy Chilos tries to get Terne captured by the Goratti so he will be turned into Gold by them, he himself is captured and suffers that fate.

My Fanged and Fiendish Darling: Karen Hadley becomes a werewolf creature and relishes in the thrill of the hunt. Her husband Bill is blind and doesn't suspect her true nature. When he miraculously gets his sight back and finds out what she is, he kills her with a silver knife.

Rezendevous with Death: Vic and Fran go to see Frans' Uncle Otto at his old house out in the country. Otto's rich wife Edna had mysteriously disappeared. When the duo get there they find Otto dead. After looking through the house they find the rotting remains of Edna walled up in a wall. Edna's ghost appears to Fran and tells her that Otto had murdered her in an attempt to get her wealth. She reveals where she had hidden the money (which Otto was never able to find) to Fran. When Fran shows the money to Vic, he kills her to take it all for himself. Just then the ghost of Otto shows up and kills Vic for the money.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Fred Greene,Dr. Holmes,Toabor (villain, alien)</Characters>
  <Writer>Paul Gustavson,Paul Gustavson</Writer>
  <Letterer>Paul Gustavson,Paul Gustavson</Letterer>
  <Editor>Richard E. Hughes</Editor>
</ComicInfo>