<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Deathmatch</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Volume>2012</Volume>
  <Summary>The battle royale continues as the world's greatest superheroes are forced to fight each other to the death in a mysterious, otherworldly prison. Who will be crowned the victor in this month's grudge match? More importantly, who will be the loser? And will the cabal of Sable, Meridian, Sol Invictus, and the Manchurian be able to decipher the mysteries of the prison before one of them is selected to enter the arena?

Written by industry legend Paul Jenkins (SENTRY, INHUMANS) and drawn by comics superstar Carlos Magno (PLANET OF THE APES, TRANSFORMERS), DEATHMATCH is a dark, psychological deconstruction of the superhero genre that can't be missed.

Plot DescriptionThe issue opens up with both Sable and The Rat examining one of the bodies of the fallen light guards. Just before Sable can get a better understanding of the body, it instantly disappears as a small group of light guards enter the wing, threatening to kill both of the should they put up a struggle. Just before they are captured, Sable knocks out The Rat after The Rat asks her to do so. After Sable is released from the light guards, her and the heroes try to figure out what it is that makes them fight one another so blindly. Just as they are discussing their situation, another battle of Deathmatch starts up on the monitors, this time it is between Cube and Monkey.

*The Main Battle:*
Monkey VS The CubeJust before the battle begins, Cube insults Monkey and before Monkey could respond he shoots a large assembly of his poisonous tentacles in Monkey's direction, which wrap themselves around his body. Almost instantly, Monkey responds by biting and pulling through the various strands of tentacles to free himself.

Appearing to be in fear of Monkey, Cube retreats through the Colosseum's thick brush which one of the viewing heroes describes as unsmart because "Cube can't use his poisonous tentacles in the thick undergrowth. He is going the wrong way."

As Cube continues to run away, Monkey double kicks Cube's back and plants himself on top of Cube. He then ferociously gnaws on Cube's face, but to his surprise Cube smiles and responds with a joke, saying "And the Oscar goes to Cube."

Cube's face literally opens up and releases a set of tentacles which wrap themselves around Monkey's face. It is revealed that Cube was putting on an act in order to get Monkey closer to him. After a few seconds, Monkey's face melts into itself and Cube is deemed the winner of the match.

----

Back at the holding area, Dragonfly and Mink discuss the match up as well as Sable's true identity. Dragonfly is curious about it, but Mink refuses to help Dragonfly figure it out stating that he is better off not knowing the truth. Before they could continue a commotion in the main square brings all the captured heroes and villains together. To their surprise, the monitors reveal all the next match ups between the villains and heroes. After the revelation a wave of battles ensue.

*Next Battles:*
Omni-Engine VS SupercolliderOmni-Engine , who is a human machine, garrotes Supercollider's throat with a laser wire in the middle of the Deathmatch arena as she screams in pain.

Amalgam VS Shadow RunnerAmalgam , who has the ability to control her enemies by inhabiting their forms, goes toe to toe with Shadow Runner, who is a creature of black magic and is as obscure to the rest of the superheroes as can be.

During the battle, Shadow Runner allows Amalgam to inhabit his body and afterwards she is literally killed by her own madness after what she sees in Shadow Runner.

George Truman VS Dog 54-AlphaGeorge Truman , who is a patriot and a loving man who's sole goal is to unite the people of the world through peace and love, fights against Dog 54-Alpha, who was once a pound puppy brought in by Silver Man.

George Truman "cries like a baby" as he strangles Dog 54-Alpha to death.

Sol Invictus VS Replic-8Sol Invictus , who is born of the sun, is sent into the arena against his earth-born brother, Replic-8.

Dragonfly remembers a time when the duo stood side to side against all odds and overcame and saved the earth after the rest of the heroes fell. He suggest that if they kill one another than there is no hope for any one of them to defy their situation.

Before Sol Invictus and Replic-8 are forced to fight they swear on their life that they will not fight one another after comforting one another.

As soon as they come face to face in the arena they erupt in battle. Replic-8 multiplies into multiple bodies and attacks Sol Invictus who thwarts his attack with one single blow.

During the battle, Sable confronts Mister Chuckles about being the cause of the Deathmatch arena. He denies the accusation after revealing his disfigured face under his mask stating that watching dogs die is not funny because he loves dogs. They decide to make an alliance, but Mister Chuckles stats that he can't wait to kill her in the arena.

--

It is then revealed that Sol Invictus killed Replic-8 in the death match. Now angered by his actions, he threatens to tear the prison apart with his bare hands, but is told by Meridian that breaking out is impossible because he tried himself. Meridian then suggests that they should just stop trying to break out and focus on the battles and just play the game. Sable then questions Meridian about him using human lives as collateral damage. Meridian then threatens Sable, but is stopped by Dragonfly. Dragonfly then attacks Meridian verbally about forgetting his role as a leading superhero. Berserk then confronts Meridian, but before anyone can stop him, Meridian fires his laser bolts through Berserk's head, killing him instantly.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-07-09 08:14:47.  [CVDB382828]</Notes>
  <Year>2013</Year>
  <Month>01</Month>
  <Day>20</Day>
  <Writer>Paul Jenkins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Carlos Magno</Penciller>
  <Inker>Carlos Magno</Inker>
  <Colorist>Archie Van Buren, Blond, Michael Garland</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Ed Dukeshire</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Archie Van Buren, Blond, Jung-Geun Yoon, Trevor Hairsine, Whilce Portacio</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Eric Harburn</Editor>
  <Publisher>Boom! Studios</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deathmatch-2/4000-382828/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>Abnormal Girl, Amalgam, Berserk, Cube, Dog 54-Alpha, Dragonfly, Fallout Man, George Truman, Hater, Manchurian, Meridian, Mink, Mister Chuckles, Monkey, Omni-Engine, Perpetu-Hedron, Professor H. Higgins, Replic-8, Sable, Shadow Runner, Sol Invictus, Supercollider, The Collective, The Glyph, The Mutate, The Rat</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1678501" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1625762" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1478776" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="3047390" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="2613599" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2299585" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="2787525" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2561315" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2632971" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2747023" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2858867" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="2638759" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="3730021" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="3061124" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2869293" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2447363" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2173320" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2494786" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="3284032" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="3636408" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="3328346" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="3501416" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="2629465" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="2247174" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1910844" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="2820911" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="2538685" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1983648" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="607703" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
