<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1297037</GTIN>
  <Genre>Crime</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:38:00 [Issue ID 4000-1297037] urn:comicvine:4000-1297037 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1297037
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:51:44. [Issue ID 1297037]</Notes>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>The Greater Good - Chapter 1: At the Brink</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-7-the-greater-good-chapter-1-at-the-brink/4000-474577/</Web>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Summary>The times they are a changin. After the shocking murder of a C.O.W.L. hero, members of the organization must put aside their differences in order to find the killer...before Detective Evelyn Frost and the Chicago Police do.

Doppler, the first of a new crop of costumed super-villains, run by mobster Camden Stone at the secret behest of C.O.W.L. leader Geoffrey Warner, starts his career by robbing a convenience store. The idea is to make people scared of costumed criminals once again, thus putting pressure on Mayor Daley to renew C.O.W.L.'s union contract.

Warner, conflicted by his actions and the fire one of his heroes anonymously caused at city hall a few days ago, is having stress in his marriage.  To make matters worse, Blaze comes into tell him that John Pierce was killed, seemingly for being a scab in regards to their union strike.

The death ripples through the community.  Eclipse gets anxious about his own secret crime-fighting activities with Radia.  Blaze takes over the investigation from the city detective Evelyn Hewitt.

Warner visits Arclight, who he knows is Pierce's killer.  Warner is mad, but Arclight explains that he destroyed John's evidence against C.O.W.L. giving tech to the Chicago Six, so Warner should actually be happy.  But Warner tells Arclight he needs to give himself up.

Grant gets out of the hospital after his beating from a supervillain.

Warner and Stone meet to renew their illicit dealings.

Detective Hewitt (aka Thompson aka Frost) talks to Pierce's wife and says that she was the person John was going to give the C.O.W.L-Chicago Six tech evidence to--and that she is the only person who knew that John was once an undercover member of the Six.

Features a bio on Eclipse and three pin-ups by different artists.</Summary>
  <StoryArc>The Greater Good</StoryArc>
  <Characters>Frank,Sarah Pierce,Don,Evelyn Hewitt,Blaze,Radia,Camden Stone,Eclipse,Geoffrey Warner,John Pierce,Doppler,Grant Marlow,Arclight</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Chicago,Indiana</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Breno Tamura,Chris Evenhuis,Rod Reis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Breno Tamura,Chris Evenhuis,Rod Reis</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Trevor McCarthy</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Andy Schmidt</Editor>
</ComicInfo>