<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Evil Ernie: Youth Gone Wild - Encore Presentation</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>The reprinting of Evil Ernie 2 from 1992 with some new additional cover art and black and white art after the main story.

In Ernie's mind Lady Death encourages him to aspire to more than just petty murders. He dreams of war across the USA and deposing the president and taking the seat of power for himself.

In the real world the doctors want to use the dream probe to help Ernie but its seems like only Price really listens to Ernie and he is afraid id Ernie gets more time with this Lady death he rave about i might just make him worse. Price is restrained before he can simply shoot Ernie as he is installed in the machine. Ernie mets his queen again and she tells him that with great power comes great responsibility. As they kiss the machine explodes killing Ernie.

the attending nurse pins a small smiley face button to Ernie's collar as he lies in the morgue. She bought it for him to celebrate his cure, which sadly never came to pass. Light shimmers and the benign smiley button shakes, grows a pair of crossed bones behind as its smile becomes a toothy maniacal grin and starts to growl.

Ernie rises from the gurney and dresses in a leather jacket, violently decapitating the stunned nurse. he tears his way through the staff and finds the dead in the morgue have risen to join him in his mayhem.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 02:53:07. [Issue ID 382988]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Chaos! Comics</Publisher>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
  </Pages>
  <Title>The Cure That Kills</Title>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/evil-ernie-youth-gone-wild-encore-presentation-2-t/4000-127222/</Web>
  <Characters>Leonard Price,William Stone,Judy Young,Billy Young,Mary Young,Lady Death,Smiley,Evil Ernie</Characters>
  <Teams>Zombies</Teams>
  <Writer>Brian Pulido</Writer>
  <CoverArtist>Ronald Cruz,Steven Hughes</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>