<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Antony,Benjamin Franklin,Corrado Coloruno,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Jeff Preston,Michael Hawthorne,Shane Preston,Vetis</Characters>
	<Colorist>Val Staples</Colorist>
	<Count>45</Count>
	<Day>30</Day>
	<Editor>Axel Alonso,Jordan D. White</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-398981</GTIN>
	<Inker>Mike Hawthorne</Inker>
	<Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
	<Locations>New Jersey</Locations>
	<Month>6</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:05:18 [Issue ID 4000-398981] urn:comicvine:4000-398981</Notes>
	<Number>8</Number>
	<PageCount>24</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1154675" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1636887" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="2203079" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1934652" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1780892" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1858693" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1590063" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1738066" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1974321" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="2107915" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1884080" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1823282" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1717998" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1695249" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1814209" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="2040461" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="2032902" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1764679" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1660587" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1652170" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1732110" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1620541" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1882374" />
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="805240" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Mike Hawthorne</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Deadpool</Series>
	<Summary>Then...Deadpool is hired by a demon to reclaim damned souls!

Plus...Wade gets in touch with his feminine side!

Synopsis

Deadpool and Agent Preston hold a meeting in a very Chuck E. Cheese-ish part of Deadpool's mind. The goal is to have Preston help Deadpool get his money from Agent Gorman while also trying to find a way to get Preston out of his mind. Deadpool assures Preston that Michael the Necromancer is currently working on the problem.

In reality, Deadpool has just hogtied an ice cream man while heading towards Preston's home. She gets excited and moves Deadpool's body to the window of her son. Deadpool enters the room and meets Preston's son Jeff. Deadpool tells Jeff that his mom isn't dead. Preston then begins talking through Deadpool and assures Jeff that she'll get back to him somehow. Just then, however, Preston's husband Shane enters the room and blasts Deadpool in the butt as he leaps out the window.

Back at the ice cream truck, Deadpool lets the ice cream man go but steals his truck. Vetis appears and explains that Deadpool still owes him for the botched Iron Man job. He tosses Deadpool a scroll with five names on it that Vetis wants killed as penance, with dire consequences if Deadpool fails.

Deadpool meets with Michael the Necromancer and Benjamin Franklin to discuss his situation. Basically, if Deadpool doesn't kill the five people on the scroll then Vetis will kill Michael, which can't happen because he is needed to get Preston out of Deadpool's head. Franklin and Michael are sent out to find some old books left by a man known as "The Ancient One" to help them solve the Preston-in-Deadpool's-mind problem while Deadpool goes in search of a body to place Preston in - starting with the names on Vetis' scroll.

The first person on the scroll is Corrado Coloruno, a man who sold his soul for invulnerability, and whom just robbed a place. Deadpool drops in on the getaway car and stabs the driver through the head. Deadpool then commandeers the vehicle and drags Corrado behind it. Invulnerable, Corrado climbs into the car and Deadpool shoots him in the eye. Ineffective. Deadpool steers the car into a construction site and tries to shoot Corrado in the braid (via the nose). Ineffective. As a last resort, Deadpool cuts off Corrado's breathing by dousing Corrado in molten metal. It hardens and Corrado suffocates to death. Preston is disgusted at how Deadpool operates.

Outside the construction site, Deadpool sees a very attractive woman and tries to talk her up. Deadpool is ambushed and knocked unconscious. The woman and two men then harvest blood and a kidney while making it abundantly clear that this type of thing happens all the time. They leave Deadpool on the side of the road to heal while they return to their employer.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-10 10:20:38.  [CVDB398981]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-8-running-with-the-devil/4000-398981/</Summary>
	<Tags>Antony,Benjamin Franklin,Corrado Coloruno,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Jeff Preston,Michael Hawthorne,New Jersey,Shane Preston,Vetis</Tags>
	<Title>Running with the Devil</Title>
	<Volume>2012</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-8-running-with-the-devil/4000-398981/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Posehn,Gerry Duggan</Writer>
	<Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>