<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Adam,Spawn (Simmons),Mammon,Wanda Fitzgerald</Characters>
  <Count>352</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-111304</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Tom Orzechowski</Letterer>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:54:44 [Issue ID 4000-111304] urn:comicvine:4000-111304
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-20 04:04:39. [Issue ID 111304]</Notes>
  <Number>146</Number>
  <PageCount>20</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="570973" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="257613" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="363050" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1062713" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="518623" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="562682" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="491824" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="430255" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="542603" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="643975" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1212062" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1234417" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="464560" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="580991" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="578040" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="656326" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1243345" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="598456" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="395141" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="472413" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Angel Medina,Angel Medina,Greg Capullo,Todd McFarlane</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Spawn</Series>
  <Summary>OverviewSomething has drawn Al Simmons to a small New England town, a seemingly idyllic community. He soon discovers that beneath its picturesque surface the town hides a dark secret–a yearly ritual in which an innocent is sacrificed and an infernal price is paid. Delving into the village's shadowy past, the Hellspawn uncovers a secret pact that goes back almost to the dawn of creation… and learns of an unexpected bargain between Heaven and Hell. SpoilersWandering the country in hopes of stopping Mammon and regaining the memories he stole, Al Simmons comes across a small town with a mysterious tradition. In order to ensure the safety of its citizens, the townsfolk have created a Tiend celebration that results in a sacrifice. Feeling his involvement is required, Spawn tries to stop the sacrifice. But his heroic motives result in Spawn coming face to face with The Forgotten Ones. Angelic creations of God, The Forgotten Ones had refused to fight against their creator; nor would they take up arms against their rebel brothers. Because of these actions, The Forgotten Ones were banished, but they also claim another in the tribe: Mammon. Although it could result in the end of their existence, The Forgotten Ones permit Spawn to try and save the sacrifice and stop the Tiend. Upon completing the ceremony, Spawn is able to save the girl. The Forgotten Ones warn Spawn that stopping this sacrifice has only caused a chain reaction and more sacrifices will need to be made.</Summary>
  <Title>Destination Anywhere, Part 2</Title>
  <Volume>1992</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/spawn-146-destination-anywhere-part-2/4000-111304/</Web>
  <Writer>Brian Holguin,Todd McFarlane</Writer>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Inker>Greg Capullo,Todd McFarlane</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Greg Capullo</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>