<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Laila,Anson,Vrauwe</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digikore Studios</Colorist>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1123838</GTIN>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Kurt Hathaway</Letterer>
  <Locations>Malaysia</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:39:56 [Issue ID 4000-1123838] urn:comicvine:4000-1123838 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1123838
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 17:31:51. [Issue ID 1123838]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="2761101" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1924780" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="2431866" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="5646459" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="2441440" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2389091" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="2321980" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2279952" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2283543" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2287256" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2084312" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="2713185" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="6193073" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="2955510" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2405338" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2874745" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="3069727" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="5567001" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="2965704" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2453166" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="2709283" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="2327948" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="2713977" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="480432" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
  <Series>The Extinction Parade</Series>
  <Summary>The best-selling Zombie writer in history finally unleashes an all-new epic for comics! Be ready for the summer's biggest comic event as millions of zombie fans come looking for with the first chapter of Max Brooks' Extinction Parade! One of the founders of the zombie renaissance, Max Brooks has sold millions of books in dozens of languages. His first book The Zombie Survival Guide not only singlehandedly jump-started the zombie prep subculture, it's graphic novel companion Recorded Attacks debuted as #1 on the New Times Bestseller list. His second book World War Z (already a multi-million copy NYT bestseller in its own right) has been adapted by Brad Pitt into what is sure to be one of the biggest blockbuster movies of 2013.

Now Brooks takes the zombie genre to a whole new level with his new comic series Extinction Parade featuring stunningly rendered art by super-star Raulo (Crossed, Captain Swing) Caceres. Building on the seed of his hit 2010 short story, Brooks has crafted a truly epic series spanning over 250 pages. Not only does Extinction Parade's multilayered depth and meticulously researched detail raise it to the standard of his previous work, it also introduces fans to an entirely new, fresh and terrifying subgenre: Vampires Vs Zombies.

As humans wage their loosing fight versus the hoards of the subdead, a frightening realization sets in with the secretive Vampire race: our food is dying off. This is the story of Vampires decent into all-out war with the mindless hungry hordes of the zombie outbreak as humanity tries to survive them all. Three species in mortal conflict. This is how a species dies. Available with Regular, Wraparound, End of a Species and Bloodwashed Retailer Incentive covers by Raulo Caceres. Also, available with a special black Leather cover, limited to just 1000 copies!

*List of covers and their creators:*
CoverNameCreator(s)Sidebar LocationRegRegular CoverRaulo Caceres1VarEnd of a Species CoverRaulo Caceres19VarLeather Cover (Red/Silver/Gold) *Raulo Caceres16, 17, 20WrapWraparound CoverRaulo Caceres21SetArmy of the Bloodlines: Brawn **Raulo Caceres3, 4, 5SetArmy of the Bloodlines: Blades **Raulo Caceres9, 10, 11SetArmy of the Bloodlines: Blast **Raulo Caceres6, 7, 8RIBloodwashed Retailer Incentive CoverRaulo Caceres18REForbidden Planet Retailer Exclusive CoverRaulo Caceres15REHastings Edition Retailer Exclusive CoverRaulo Caceres14REMidtown Comics Retailer Exclusive CoverRaulo Caceres13REMile High Edition Retailer Exclusive CoverRaulo Caceres12REHalloween ComicFest Retailer Exclusive Cover ***

Raulo Caceres2Notes:

* The Leather cover is limited to 1,000 copies in total. However this variant is actually available in three different colors: Red (600 copies), Platinum/Silver (300 copies), and Gold (100 copies). The price tag for all covers, regardless of the color and its limitation, is $4.99. The "Gold" cover was made available at SDCC 2013 only.

** The Army of Bloodlines covers were available in three different sets (Brawn, Blades, and Blast) with three different covers (A, B, C) with a total of nine different Army of Bloodlines covers. Each set (of 3 covers) costs $30 and is limited to 1,000 copies. The sets were sold exclusively at the following comic conventions in 2013:

"Brawn" at SDCC
"Blades" at Toronto Fan Expo
"Blast" at NYCC
*** This variant was available for FREE from most comic shops on Halloween ComicFest on October 25th, 2014. Also, it is just the left side of the Wraparound cover of the same issue.</Summary>
  <Teams>Vampires,Zombies</Teams>
  <Volume>2013</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-1123838/</Web>
  <Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>