<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2392</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2392</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>I am The Mighty Tharg, all-powerful alien editor of this universally acclaimed SF anthology!

New stories abound in this ghafflebette issue, Terrans - first up, we have the start of a Judge Dreddthriller from the always-popular creative combo of John Wagner and Colin MacNeil, Machine Rule, that looks again at the Mechanismo question. Long-term Squaxx will be well aware that the idea of robots passing judgement has been a controversial one in Mega-City history (new readers would do well to check out collections like Mechanismo and Machine Law if they want to get up to speed), but recently the Mark 8s have been regular presence on the streets. But what if they decided they were doing a better job than the human Judges&#8230;?

Also commencing this prog is the first full length series of Herne &amp; Shuck from David Barnett and Lee Milmore, after their previous appearances in a pair of 3rillers in Progs 2297-2299 and 2343- 2345, still trying to find a safe place to take young Carys, pursued by various folk-horror entities.

And we have another complete Future Shock, from the Peaty and Mutti droids, joining Brink and Silver. All in all, pure Thrill-power, my humes!

*Judge Dredd &#187; Machine Rule (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law! The Mark 8 Mechanismo robot Judges have been on the streets for several years now...

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 15)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Herne &amp; Shuck &#187; Suffer The Children (Part 1)*
The UK, 2024. Herne is a troubleshooter and hired help for many different magical factions in the country. Accompanied by Shuck, a demon in dog form, he travels the country picking up work where he can, whether it be exorcism or a rescue. Recently, he was tasked with saving a young girl called Carys, only to find out she was scheduled for ritual sacrifice. The pair are now trying to get the child to safety...

*Tharg's Future Shocks &#187; FaceShopping (Part 1)*
Out in the vast reaches of the universe, there are an infinite number of stories waiting to be told. These cautionary tales pass from traveller to traveller in the spaceports and around campfires on distant planets, acquiring the status of legend, their shocking ends a salutory lesson in hubris. Anything is possible in these twisted trips into the galaxy&#8217;s dark side. Abandon your preconceptions, and expect the unexpected&#8230;

*Silver &#187; Unearthed: book 1 (Part 3)*
Earth, the year 2001. A group of armed survivors sought out the resting place of a five hundred-year-old vampire, who may just help them against the alien Sepsis, who invaded the planet a few decades earlier. The vamp, called Baroness DeSilva, has proved powerful in battling extra-terrestrials, and now she and one of the humans are trying to get back to the resistance headquarters...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-25 00:09:55.  [CVDB1064370]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>24</Day>
  <Writer>Dan Abnett, David Barnett, James Peaty, John Wagner, Michael Carroll</Writer>
  <Penciller>Andrea Mutti, Colin MacNeil, I.N.J. Culbard, Joe Robinson Currie, Lee Milmore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Andrea Mutti, Colin MacNeil, I.N.J. Culbard, Joe Robinson Currie, Lee Milmore</Inker>
  <Colorist>Chris Blythe, Quinton Winter</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Jim Campbell, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Mike D. Perkins</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2392-prog-2392/4000-1064370/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Black Shuck, Bridget Kurtis, Judge Dredd</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1346974" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1398962" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1382575" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1101132" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1156955" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1193226" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1029803" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="982867" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1649231" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="730801" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="831771" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="921527" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1018128" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="858632" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1493103" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1551864" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2225852" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1825740" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1584663" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1443124" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1021853" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1088143" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1058871" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1126856" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1078063" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1216502" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1341650" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1110780" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1012635" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1122019" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1618829" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="967166" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
