<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Army of Darkness: Shop Till You Drop Dead</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Summary>After 20,000 years of Utopian civilization, the Deadites are terrorizing humanity again thanks to Ashley J. Williams. Now the enlightened civilization has two choices: either stand with Ash, or unceremoniously eject him and the evil to the past. Ash finds himself propelled back to his own time, only to discover that S-Mart is now a haven for the undead! To save the girl, he must face his Deadite-possessed friends and find a way to eliminate the evil spirit now inhabiting the aisles of everyone's favorite discount store chain. The human race need a hero now more than ever, but what they got was a halfwit with a chainsaw for a hand and a chin of steel!

In the year 2501, Ash is being over run by Cyber-Deadites when he figures out the only way to defeat them and get back to reality is to destory the Mainframe, and that is just what he does. But back in reality in Deca city One the deadun, a creature much like the Deadites, have evoled and are no longer mindless.

He is rescued by Captain Grey and taken back to Doctor Sagittarius who uses the program Ash brought back from the mainframe to send Ash back to the present. (Along with the Necronomicon Program)

In the Present at the S-mart, Ash's store, the deadites have taken over. Ash has to kill his possessed co workers and his Boss Mr. Smart, to save Sheila. His last act it to throw the Necronomicon into a time portal before kissing the Babe and saying "Its good to be King"</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-01 13:27:47.  [CVDB111531]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 20:57:53. [Issue ID 304466]</Notes>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Writer>James Kuhoric</Writer>
  <Penciller>Nick Bradshaw</Penciller>
  <Colorist>Scott Kester</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Bill Tortolini</Letterer>
  <Publisher>Devil's Due Publishing</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/army-of-darkness-shop-till-you-drop-dead-4/4000-111531/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Ash,Evil Ash,Sheila</Characters>
  <Teams>Deadites</Teams>
  <ScanInformation>(2 covers) (Digital-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="332830" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="353192" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="354946" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="352652" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="331558" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="298336" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="318456" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="373398" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="408576" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="335362" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="374364" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="309200" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="366792" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="338412" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="381392" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="406822" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="498010" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="362674" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="373642" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="384836" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="363942" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="345062" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="503620" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="640014" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="499590" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>