<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Title>Lights</Title>
  <Series>Sheets</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Web>https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CGML34Q3</Web>
  <Summary>From the creator of the bestselling Sheets, a Barnes and Noble Best Book of 2018!

Following the events of Sheets and Delicates, Lights brings Brenna Thummler's characters, artwork, and ghostly charm back to life.

Marjorie Glatt's life was forever changed the day she discovered a group of ghosts hiding in her family's laundromat. One of those ghosts was Wendell: a lonely phantom turned Marjorie's best friend. When he and Marjorie are joined by ghost-enthusiast Eliza Duncan, the three friends band together in friendship, bravery, and all things paranormal.

Wendell died far too young and now must wander the Land of Humans with nothing more than a sheet for a body. He knows how he died—a tragic drowning accident—but lately he's grown curious about his past life. He wants to know more about why he died, not just how he died. It's not easy, though, since Wendell's memory of his human life has grown increasingly blurry. With Marjorie and Eliza's help, they set out on a journey to find out more. When they hear a rumor about Wendell's death, they wonder if it might not have been an accident after all. Meanwhile, Marjorie and Eliza's friendship is tested when Marjorie starts to befriend the very people who used to bully Eliza.

In the third and final installment of the Sheets trilogy, Wendell will finally uncover the truth of his human life. Marjorie and Eliza will learn that some people really can change. Most of all, they start to see that everything can cast shadows, but if you look hard enough, you can find the light.</Summary>
  <Notes>Scraped metadata from Amazon [ASINB0CGML34Q3], [RELDATE:2023-09-05]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Oni Press</Publisher>
  <Genre>Middle Grade, Young Adult, Fantasy, Paranormal, Fiction</Genre>
  <PageCount>363</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>DrVink. Library loans through OverDrive and Kindle; ripped with Calibre DeDRM. Library loans through Hoopla, plus other sources; webrip. Denoised and upscaled with waifu2x-caffe or other tools.</ScanInformation>
  <Year>2023</Year>
  <Month>09</Month>
  <Day>05</Day>
  <Writer>Brenna Thummler</Writer>
  <Penciller>Brenna Thummler</Penciller>
  <Colorist>Brenna Thummler</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Brenna Thummler</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>
