<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Smiley Bone,Phoney Bone,Gran'ma Ben,Fone Bone,Kingdok,Thorn</Characters>
  <Count>35</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-42087</GTIN>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:21:45 [Issue ID 4000-42087] urn:comicvine:4000-42087
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 17:35:52. [Issue ID 334579]</Notes>
  <Number>22</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Cartoon Books</Publisher>
  <Series>Bone</Series>
  <Summary>The two Rat Creatures find the fainted body of Kingdok and blame themselves for his wounding. They decide to desert the pack rather than face the consequences. As Thorn dresses Gran'ma Ben's wounds in the aftermath of the fight, Ben tells her the reason she was sent to Deren Gard as a child; Thorn is the “Veni-Yan Cari”, the Awakened One, a person who is most in touch with “The Dreaming”. Ben goes on to explain how she, Thorn, will be at risk from enemies in her dreams; indeed, she has already been threatened by The Hooded One, who Gran'ma suspects is in contact with the Lord of the Locusts, and may be one of the “Venu”, a sect of mystics who study dreams and are traditionally clad in hooded robes. The Hooded One is interested in Thorn because she has more power than even the Lord of the Locusts, and seeks to control her. Angered by further revelations that her past has been concealed from her, Thorn turns her back on Gran'ma Ben and leaves for the Barrelhaven alone. Fone Bone makes to follow her, and Gran'ma Ben gives him her sword, as well as a pendant bearing the royal crest with instructions to show it to Lucius. When they arrive at Barrelhaven, they find Phoney Bone has taken control of the town and barricaded the roads.</Summary>
  <Title>Council in the Dark</Title>
  <Volume>1997</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/bone-22-council-in-the-dark/4000-42087/</Web>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <Writer>Jeff Smith</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jeff Smith</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jeff Smith</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jeff Smith</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Jeff Smith</CoverArtist>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>