<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Colorist>Ned Ivory,Nei Ruffino</Colorist>
  <Day>14</Day>
  <Editor>John Cafiero</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-961740</GTIN>
  <Genre>Fantasy,Horror,Action/Adventure</Genre>
  <Inker>Jeff Zornow</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>David C. Hopkins,Ned Ivory</Letterer>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T03:20:04 [Issue ID 4000-961740] urn:comicvine:4000-961740
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 08:37:56. [Issue ID 2465651]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1373904" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1065694" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1230151" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1099378" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1618782" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="5898733" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1398850" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1517154" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1456985" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1404938" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2055721" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1401502" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1374906" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="2151162" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1878015" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1475093" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1919651" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1928354" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1558117" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1667865" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1690977" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1392254" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="5685524" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1387647" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1119358" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1414576" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1080200" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1472421" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jeff Zornow</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Series>Sweetie Candy Vigilante</Series>
  <Summary>NYC JUST GOT A WHOLE LOT SWEETER… THERE’S A NEW CANDY BOSS IN TOWN!

Sweetie Candy Vigilante #3 gives us our first glimpse into the surreal world that thrives beyond the walls of Sweetie’s elusive Candy Vigilante factory headquarters (discretely located in the industrial outskirts of Brooklyn, NY). Now that Pixie has been “chosen” to join the sweet, secret society, she’s introduced to mix masters (and highly skilled axe-throwing assassins) Hansel and Gretel! Yes, the epic witch killing duo are real, all grown up, and no longer eat stranger’s houses. So please, no jokes about gingerbread. They’re still trying to break the stigmatism…

Meanwhile, Candy Wolf spills the jelly beans on Sweetie’s backstory and family lineage! Turns out, her father is the “Candy Man” himself: Zucker Cane, (of the New York landmark Cane’s Sweet Shop). He trained Sweetie and factory home-schooled her with his magical secrets of confectionary wizardry.

Pushed to the limits by the mysterious disappearance of her parents, the gentrification of New York destroying “Mom and Pop” shops, and a fitness obsessed mayor declaring war on sugar — actually outlawing candy, cake and ice cream in the process — she’s declared a war of her own on anyone who treads on her birthright to sweetness, and those who enjoy a little sugar in their lives. Possessing skills far beyond her father, she’s been testing secret formulas on herself, and now…it’s all GOOD! Sweetie said so, and she’s the new Candy Boss in town! So make your life a whole lot sweeter with Sweetie Candy Vigilante #3: Candy Boss. After all, tis the season!

Watch for Sweetie Candy Vigilante’s return with issue #4 in February!

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-02-12 08:32:28.  [CVDB961740]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/sweetie-candy-vigilante-3-candy-boss/4000-961740/</Summary>
  <Title>Candy Boss</Title>
  <Volume>2022</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/sweetie-candy-vigilante-3-candy-boss/4000-961740/</Web>
  <Writer>Suzanne Cafiero</Writer>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>