<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Cavewoman: Rain</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Title>Missing McDonalds</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>A dialogue free issue that takes place about half a year before Mereim's hometown of Marshville is sent to the past.

Meriem is asleep in a high tree dreaming of her Grandfather and her eating McDonalds. She wakes up in the talons of a large winged dinosaur. After getting the best of it and now riding it she gets flung off and falls through trees, down a cliff side and lands hard. A little weary but uninjured she notices giant spiders and bees coming at her so she dives into a nearby lake. A large dinosaur swallows her but she fights her way out and knocks it in the head.

She climbs the large cliff and listens to her stomach rumbling when she finally reaches the top. She eyes a tiny lizard and just as she is about to eat it she sees a pack of feasting dinosaurs (maybe Raptors). They charge her as she runs to a hole in a tree and jump above it. A large fist comes out of the hole and nails one of the dinosaurs. It's Klyde and he begins to fight them all by himself. It looks there are too many for him but Meriem thinks back to when he attacked her and she hesitates helping him. He kills them and she gets away. She finds an insect and right before she puts it in her mouth she thinks back to McDonalds and can't eat it. She looks up at the sky with tears in her eyes and the only words written in the story appear:

"The mightiest struggles are fought from within ourselves though the key to winning is simple...keep smiling"</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 03:31:20. [Issue ID 59684]</Notes>
  <StoryArc>"Cavewoman: Rain" Rain</StoryArc>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Day>3</Day>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cavewoman-rain-3-missing-mcdonalds/4000-43150/</Web>
  <Characters>Klyde,Meriem Cooper,Francis Peacock Reicher</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>Prehistoric Jungle</Locations>
  <Writer>Budd Root</Writer>
  <Penciller>Budd Root</Penciller>
  <Inker>Budd Root,Greg Adams</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bradley Walton</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Budd Root,Greg Adams</CoverArtist>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
  </Pages>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
</ComicInfo>