<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Want You To Want Me: Part 2: No Man is an Island</Title>
  <Series>Deadpool</Series>
  <Number>16</Number>
  <Volume>2008</Volume>
  <Summary>Deadpool is turned away by Cyclops. But as Dagger explains; he's just looking for a place where he could feel wanted much like all the other mutants were who apart of the X-Men. Considering them hypocrits, he decides to head home. After Cyclops finds out that a certain Mr. Kincaid (Mercury's father) is 'in the pocket' of Osborn's pocket, he decides to take matters into his own hands and send out Archangel's legal team to resolve the situation. In another matter, Cyclops and Wolverine ask Domino to keep an eye on Deadpool and invite him to join the X-Men. On a rooftop, Domino confronts Deadpool, who ignores her until she admits she's there to offer him a part in the X-Men. In disbalief - he turns a gun on her, saying that she is here to kill him. Getting her to step back onto a cracked rooftop window, he shoots the weak glass beneath her and she falls down into a pile of 372, 844 pancakes. Sharing the pancakes not long after, he explained how he knew all along that she wasn't here to kill him, due to the fact that no back-up crew came to help Domino. Reporting back to Cyclops, Domino explains the situation and that Deadpool would join on one condition... he gets to wear his own home-made uniform. Cyclops agrees and Deadpool is in! Seeing Mr. Kincaid on the TV, Deadpool asks who he is and Domino explains that Cyclops is already dealing with it, but Deadpool has his own plan... ASSASSINATION!"</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-04 15:24:19.  [CVDB175163]</Notes>
  <Year>2009</Year>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Writer>Daniel Way</Writer>
  <Penciller>Paco Medina</Penciller>
  <Inker>Juan Vlasco</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marte Gracia</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Jason Pearson</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso, Jody LeHeup, Joe Quesada</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-16-want-you-to-want-me-part-2-no-man-is-a/4000-175163/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Characters>Armor, Betsy Braddock, Cannonball, Celeste Cuckoo, Colossus, Cyclops, Dagger, Deadpool, Domino, Emma Frost, Hellion, Magma, Mark Kincaid, Mercury, Mindee Cuckoo, Prodigy, Rogue, Warpath, Wolverine</Characters>
  <Teams>X-Men</Teams>
  <Locations>San Francisco, Utopia/Asteroid M</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="508799" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="401676" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="447134" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="499549" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="497568" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="670658" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="541288" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="656910" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="526615" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="541294" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="396604" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="396289" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="455640" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="473454" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="399286" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="476151" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="606031" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="529101" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="603819" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="606207" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="437835" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="440972" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="597158" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="398144" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="363799" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
