<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-361846</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:40:03 [Issue ID 4000-361846] urn:comicvine:4000-361846
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 01:38:03. [Issue ID 244832]</Notes>
  <Number>10</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Pines</Publisher>
  <Series>Out of the Shadows</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/out-of-the-shadows-10/4000-361846/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>10</Count>
  <Title>The Fettered Phantom; The Corpse That Lived!; Revenge of the Little People; The Sergeant; 'Til Death Do Us Part; Weird Watson; Room of Terror; Destroy My Enemy</Title>
  <Genre>Humor,Horror-suspense,Non-fiction,War</Genre>
  <Summary>The Fettered Phantom: A ghost leads a writer to the place where he has been slain and buried.

The Corpse That Lived!: A woman is buried with her jewels. When grave robbers open the coffin, the lady stirs again. She recovers and lives happily ever after. 
The woman is said to have been the mother of novelist Sir Walter Scott.

Revenge of the Little People: The circus midget "Major" Martin marries the lovely trapeze artist Lila, but is betrayed by her and killed for his money. Lila is haunted by apparitions of ghost midgets, who sabotage her act and let her drop to certain death.

The Sergeant: A sergeant is killed in World War II, but returns from the dead to lead his platoon through enemy lines to safety.

'Til Death Do Us Part: The husband of a dominating wife is sent over to inquire about the rich neighbors. The two secluded living sisters share a dark secret, which ruins everbody's lives.

Weird Watson: The Shadow-like Watson buys himself an alligator for a pet.

Room of Terror: In a library room four students encounter an alien apparition.

Destroy My Enemy: Meek Elmer Grimes commands a murderous pirate-genie in a bottle. Fulfilling a death contract the genie turns on his master.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>