<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-805668</GTIN>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Locations>Virginia</Locations>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:53:52 [Issue ID 4000-805668] urn:comicvine:4000-805668 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/805668
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 18:23:15. [Issue ID 805668]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <PageCount>14</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="969048" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2321117" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1383688" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1710737" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1752670" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1619709" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1694054" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1322237" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1610054" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1382947" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1488776" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1346371" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1129332" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="243938" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Plague of the Living Dead</Series>
  <Summary>Stone Mountain, Virginia: 1971. Three soldiers have escaped their military captors and are on the run, possessing the knowledge that the US Army has been conducting experiments with zombie soldiers in the jungles of Vietnam. Todd Clark, Steve Green and Terry Ellis know that had they not escaped, their names would have been added to the list of soldiers missing in action, the terrible events that they witnessed in the Far East sealing their fate. Their family and friends in Stone Mountain did not know to where the men were deployed only one short year ago, nor do they know that they had been covertly rotated back to this country, held prisoner only a few short miles from home and the neighboring Fort Stone.

Having finally made their way home, Todd, Steve and Terry now face the gut-wrenching truth: Stone Mountain has been overrun by the living dead. Blood flows through the streets as the ghouls continue their onslaught, decimating armed troops attempting to contain the outbreak...</Summary>
  <Teams>Zombies</Teams>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-805668/</Web>
  <Writer>John Russo</Writer>
  <Year>2007</Year>
</ComicInfo>