<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Eyes of Dekko Pt. 2; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189; 18</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>18</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Max invites Dekko in to Zot's birthday party. Most people are freaked out by the presence of the criminal cyborg but others take it as just another weird thing that happens at Max's parties.

Max can tell Dekko is not fully cured but they decide he can stay. He gives Zot a box of chocolates and says he won't annihilate the universe til the chocolates are all eaten.

Zot, Jenny, and others talk about Dekko. Jenny feels sympathy for him because she knows why he went insane--that he loved Sarah but she left him. Jenny explains the story to Zot (changing it slightly, saying that they were Max's students instead of Max also being a student); Zot is surprised Max hadn't told him. They continue to have fun at the party and Zot keeps giving away chocolates.

Dekko and Max talk about art; Dekko rants about the necessity for perfection in all things.

Dr. Glass bursts into the party. He says that Dekko burned down the mental hospital where Dekko was a patient. Amazingly, no one was hurt. He signed it with his initials in burning fuel. This makes it his artwork; he had also designed the actual building back in his early days as an artist. He explains that he manipulated the medical system and the doctor to let him go. He says again that he's going to destroy everything, but not til the chocolates are gone. They call the cops but it will take a while for them to get there.

Dekko and Zot play ping pong. Zot loses and has to eat a chocolate.

Jenny talks with Dekko. She thinks his plan is to destroy his own universe--which is to say, kill himself. She sympathizes with the pain he feels.

Max plays some Bach, hoping to convince Dekko of the wonder of reality. Jenny desperately wants Max to not give up on Dekko, but Max says that Dekko is aware of all the arguments in favor of humanity and art and hope, and has made his own informed choice against them. Max and Dekko say they will miss each other.

Zot plans to eat the last chocolate, but Butch takes it and eats it first.

We then see things from Dekko's internal perspective. He sees an increasingly abstracted world. He kills Dr. Glass and then wipes out all of reality, seeing only a blank white space. Sarah shows up and says she thinks it's perfect, except for their own existence within the void. She makes herself disappear. Dekko, agreeing, also erases himself.

Back in reality, we see that Dekko has shut himself down. Dr. Glass is unhurt and everything is normal. Zot takes Jenny home. They kiss, she goes to sleep, and wake sup to a beautiful day with no school.

Note: 9-Jack-9 only appears in his human identity as John Sheers.

In The Adventures of Zot in Dimension 10 &#189;, the robot continues to go amok.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:57.  [CVDB29462]</Notes>
  <Year>1988</Year>
  <Month>04</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-18-the-eyes-of-dekko-pt-2-the-adventures-of-zo/4000-29462/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Butch Weaver, Dekko, Digger, Hacker, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Sarah Melpignano, Vic Taylor, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="212571" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="231735" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="220409" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="203850" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="249053" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="223691" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="185209" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="212934" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="210818" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="204886" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="239343" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="233115" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="228416" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="211509" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="229060" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="224784" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="247667" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="91815" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="177920" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="144056" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="108250" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="24636" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="283243" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="193574" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="212811" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="292577" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="251804" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="293712" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="258829" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
