<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Sky-Blue Pink; Tales from the Family Reastaurant; My Fugly Fabulous Face; Never; Miss Africa Day; The Devil's Doing; Who Am I?; Zero Hour; Tobey's Terror Tales: 'Puppets from Hell'; Action Girl &amp; Flying Girl in: Big Present</Title>
  <Series>Action Girl Comics</Series>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Count>19</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-12 08:40:09.  [CVDB142013]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 11:59:54. [Issue ID 304896]</Notes>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <CoverArtist>Sarah Dyer</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Sarah Dyer</Editor>
  <Publisher>Slave Labor</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/action-girl-comics-7/4000-142013/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Action Girl</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1130692" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="777822" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="927974" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="657854" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="776144" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="777782" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="479400" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="797438" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="783476" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="455174" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="615688" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="579136" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="432750" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="703930" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="653674" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="782372" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="830396" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="890048" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="668456" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="619688" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="512144" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="254446" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="612960" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="684936" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="508578" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="606222" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="445776" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="418422" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>A woman recounts some of her teen antics from the summer of 1956, especially how she and her girlfriends waited all summer for the release of a new lipstick color from Revlon called Sky-Blue Pink that was just pink lipstick with a little bit of blue in it.

Gwen recounts the odd foods, bizarre customers, and the strange antics of her co-workers at her summer job in a Pennsylvania Dutch-style family restaurant.

A woman describes the percieved imperfections of various parts of her faces (nose, eyebrows, forehead, chin, etc), but it's all OK because she has a beautiful smile.

A woman who is ill and sleeping on a couch, curled up in a blanket, has hallucinations involving romance with a cornfield scarecrow.

Tells how catfish lost their scales because during creation the Devil was about to fry the catfish and had already scraped off the colorful red, blue and yellow scales when the Good Lord came along and stopped him.  The Devil threw the catfish back in the water, but the scales never grew back, which is why catfish today have no scales.

A woman describes various aspects of herself, such as that she likes cats, likes to cook, likes books, believes in good karma, and likes gummy bears.

Beth decides she doesn't want the same old noodles for supper and decides to go out for Chinese food, three friends come with her.  They tease her about getting the same thing every time.  To challenge her, Ant orders a random item from the menu, even though she has no idea what is in it.  The waiter offers a menu in English, but Ant declines.  When the food arrives they all lose their appetite upon seeing Ant's food - which is chicken parts like claws, eyeballs and intestines.

The author recounts how two friends (Dean &amp; Erin) took her &amp; her boyfriend to a puppet show based loosely on "Faust" that was awful, and how she had nightmares later of the puppets coming to life and biting her.

Flying Girl drops a note down to Action Girl telling her to meet at a certain time and location on Saturday.  Action Girl shows up, Flying Girl blindfolds her and takes her into a building.  Once inside she tells her to jump as the blindfold is removed.  It turns out that they are in a new vertical wind tunnel that will open to the public the next week - Flying Girl brought Action Girl here as a present so that Action Girl could feel what it's like to fly.</Summary>
</ComicInfo>