<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Cavewoman: Rain</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>This issue starts out right where the last left off. Meriem gets chomped by Klyde. She scratches at his eyes and he throws her to the ground. She's down and hurt and Klyde is coming. The kids from the comic shop are trying to warn her but she isn't moving. Lumpy throws himself over her to protect her. Klyde stops and tells him to move through sign language. Lumpy tells him that the big lizards will hurt Lumpy and Meriem can't stop them because she is weak. Klyde runs to stop them and Meriem gives Lumpy a kiss on the cheek for his bravery. She finds a dead dinosaur to eat to speed up her healing factor.

The comic shop owner and the kids scramble into a moving truck to escape some large carnivores. Meriem tries to slow them down and Klyde tackles them both. They speed away as Klyde is beating the dinosaurs. When he finishes with them he chases after the van. The kids are throwing out boxes of comics to try and lighten it up. Kirby's Fantastic Four gets reluctantly tossed. Meriem thinks she can slow Klyde down. A man dressed in a Star Trek uniform named Williams offers to help Capt. Lavery and Bruce. She agrees and him and Bruce discuss the "Curse of Roddenberry". The idea that an extra is brought in just for one scene to get killed for drama. The three of them hear a rumbling and see another twister headed their way. They take cover under a bridge. Under that bridge though is a gigantic snake. It strikes at Bruce but Williams pushes him out of the way and is grabbed. The snake coils and squeezes. Capt. Lavery shoots it and it lets go just as the twister arrives. The snake gets picked up and swept away. Williams dies.

The giant snake lands right in front of Sgt. Marstone and his hunting party. They find Meriem and Klyde fighting and Marstone shoots a grenade round injuring both Klyde and Meriem. Meriem is down but Klyde rushes and attacks the group. Gramp appears to Meriem and tells her she needs to stop Klyde for good. She knows and jumps on Klyde's back repeatedly stabbing him in the neck with her knife. Marstone is going to fire again but Professor Cook warns him not to or else he'll blast him with the flamethrower his armored speedster is equipped with. They both fire. Marstone's feet get burned and his shot goes high knocking a wall down on Meriem and Klyde. Marstone rushes over and punches Professor Cook in the face. Bruce see this and slugs Marstone in the face. It doesn't even hurt him and Bruce is pounded to the ground. Lavery stops him and Marstone offers her a free shot like Bruce got. She whacks him in the throat, then the groin and then kicks him in the face when he's down.

Meriem stirs from the rubble and Klyde springs out with her in his fist. e slams her to the ground. Lavery empties her gun into Klyde's back but it has no effect. He rushes her and Professor Cook yells for her to get out of the way. She does and Klyde slams into his car. The Professor hits a switch and Klyde is electrocuted. Klyde slumps to the ground after it's switched off. Bruce tries to get to Meriem as Professor Cook is trying to restart her heart but it's too late. She's gone.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 03:29:16. [Issue ID 59686]</Notes>
  <StoryArc>"Cavewoman: Rain" Rain</StoryArc>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cavewoman-rain-5/4000-43152/</Web>
  <Characters>Klyde,Cavewoman</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>Prehistoric Jungle,Marshville</Locations>
  <Writer>Budd Root,Budd Root</Writer>
  <Penciller>Budd Root,Jim Shumaker,Budd Root</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bradley Walton,Budd Root,Budd Root</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bradley Walton,Cara Walton,Bradley Walton,Cara Walton</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Budd Root</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>James Pruett,Joe Pruett</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <Title>Chapter 5</Title>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
<Genre>Jungle,Risque</Genre></ComicInfo>