<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Eightball</Series>
  <Number>22</Number>
  <Count>23</Count>
  <Title>Around Ice Haven with Random Wilder; Our Children and their Friends; The True Story of Leopold And Loeb; Melancholy Serenade; Seventeen; David Goldberg is Missing; Vida and Her Grandmother; Mr. &amp; Mrs. Ames: Detectives For Hire; Charles; Violet in Love; Harry Naybors: Comic Book Critic; Rocky: 100,000 B.C.; The Hole; Seersucker; Julie Patheticstein; Mrs. Ames; Kim Lee; Officer Kaufman; "Mosquito"; Blue Bunny; Random Wilder in Toilet Time; Charles and his Therapist; The Ransom Note; Random Wilder, Again; David Goldberg is Alive; Our Children, Revisited; Violet: Alone Forever; Vida Goes to Hollywood; Harry Naybors Explains Everything</Title>
  <Volume>1989</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 15:10:06. [Issue ID 240170]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Year>2001</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(Fixed)(Icehaven)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Random Wilder,Mrs. Ida Wentz,Carmichael</Characters>
  <Writer>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Writer>
  <Penciller>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Penciller>
  <Inker>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Inker>
  <Colorist>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Following the successful completion of the Ghost World movie, Clowes returned to his hit comic book series with this full-color issue containing 27 vaguely interrelated stories ranging from one to three pages in length, drawn in a variety of styles, featuring various all-new characters (an angry bachelor, a love-sick teenager, an over-sensitive 10-year-old, a comic-book critic, a husband and wife detective team, a depressed caveman, etc.) as they cross paths in the small Midwestern town of Ice Haven. It's Clowes' first stand-alone issue, complete unto itself, and it may be Clowes' best attempt yet to explore the often puzzling ways people interrelate. Don't miss it!

"29 stories in full color."</Summary>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/eightball-22-ice-haven/4000-110384/</Web>
  <CoverArtist>Daniel Clowes</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>