<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>T.K.O.: The Final Round</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>10</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Zot thanks Vic for everything he's done to stop the conspiracy on Sirius. Vic says he'll lend his digital remote, Floyd, to Zot as he finishes the conspiracists off.

The queen also thanks Vic, for being a friend to her son, the late Prince Drufus, but Vic won't let her off the hook and blames her for making him into such an unhappy boy.

Butch, fresh off his win over the enemy army, tries to give Zot some tips on being a hero, but they're absurd. Instead, Vic and Max come up with a plan.

The next day, Zot and Floyd break into the conspiracist's tower. The remaining conspiracist has broadcast his plans to attack Earth, and branded Zot an enemy of the state. The people don't all believe him but he says he'll kill anyone who disagrees.

Zot and Butch (with his army of de-evolutionists) attack different parts of the castle. Butch takes over the broadcast unit while Zot attacks the general. Zot gets the general to admit that he had the king order Zot's parents' death, without realizing it would be broadcast everywhere, thanks t Floyd.

The general takes Zot by surprise with an exploisive, but Jenny comes in and starts to beat him up. Eventually he starts to fight back but then Zot punches him out.

Since the fight was broadcast, now everyone wants Zot to be the new ruler. However, he doesn't want to. He thinks he's too young and they should lead themselves.

Zot and his friends all go home. Butch eventually loses control over the de-evolutionists. Max is able to turn Butch back into his human form when he goes back through the portal to Earth. Jenny also goes home after getting Zot to agree to visit her soon, and to also at least try to help the people of Sirius.

Adam Philips and Kurt Busiek credited as Consultants (for the ZOT story).</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:40.  [CVDB25665]</Notes>
  <Year>1985</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Colorist>Denis Mcfarling</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode, Dean Mullaney</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-10-t-k-o-the-final-round/4000-25665/</Web>
  <PageCount>31</PageCount>
  <Characters>Butch Weaver, Drufus, Father Kimm, Floyd, General Harcort Schrapp, Grand Poo-Bah, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Queen of Sirius IV, Raymond Taylor, Vic Taylor, Zarbim Borlock, Zot</Characters>
  <Teams>The Devoes</Teams>
  <Locations>Sirius IV</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="197786" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="148248" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="153150" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="188939" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="159279" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="172657" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="181094" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="362274" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="179929" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="170212" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="199386" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="174046" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="176424" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="136005" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="138262" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="183335" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="479057" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="137507" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="133724" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="152720" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="159343" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="162074" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="152845" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="74609" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="185823" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="174563" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="135273" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="172907" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="181172" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="36941" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="82881" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
