<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Abby Holland,Alec Holland,Calbraith A.H. Rodgers,Sethe,Swamp Thing</Characters>
	<Colorist>Nathan Fairbairn</Colorist>
	<Count>42</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Chris Conroy,Matt Idelson</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294200</GTIN>
	<Inker>Yanick Paquette</Inker>
	<Letterer>John J. Hill</Letterer>
	<Locations>Louisiana</Locations>
	<Month>12</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:13:19 [Issue ID 4000-294200] urn:comicvine:4000-294200</Notes>
	<Number>2</Number>
	<PageCount>21</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2189624" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="2144673"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1942324"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="2363729"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="2756964"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1815533"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1827117"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1583804"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1738513"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="5756283"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="4773121"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1737257"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1509552"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1631597"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1928000"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1867462"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1710387"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1670252"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1475291"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1258314"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="544346"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Yanick Paquette</Penciller>
	<Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Swamp Thing</Series>
	<Summary>Alec Holland thought he knew the history of the Swamp Thing – but he was wrong. The creature's roots run deeper than he knows, and the Parliament of Trees intends to make him understand the responsibility he wants so desperately to avoid! With this issue, the mythology of the Swamp Thing branches out in ways you never saw coming – don't miss it!

 

We start off with a flashback, into the past of Calbraith A. H. Rodgers. He is flying a plane in WWII when he is shot down and crashes into a swamp. His body is taken over by the swamp and he becomes that generations Swamp Thing. He tells Alec that he has been sent by the Parliament of Trees to deliver a message. The Green wants him back to become the new Swamp Thing. Alec is still reluctant and so Rodgers connects with his mind to show him of the impending doom.

He shows him a creature known as Sethe, a force of death and rot that is gathering an army to destroy the world. Alec states that he does not want to become the Swamp Thing again, and Rodgers tells him that he never was. The Parliament could not save his body to attach to the Swamp Thing so they attempted to recreate his consciousness. Having finished, Rodgers begins to leave and just as he does he warns Alec; he should beware of a girl with white hair.

He goes back to his room when he sees the desk clerk and says hi. Back in his room Alec begins to dress and pack when the desk lady (who is now being controlled by Sethe) comes into the room and attacks him with an axe. He dodges the strike and runs outside only to be met with a group of Sethe followers. Suddenly a girl on a motorcycle, packing a shotgun helps him and they ride away. They stop off and when they do the girl takes off her helmet and introduces herself as Abigail Arcane all whilst pointing a gun at his head.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-11-19 06:50:47.  [Issue ID 294200]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-2-when-it-comes-aknockin/4000-294200/</Summary>
	<Tags>Abby Holland,Alec Holland,Calbraith A.H. Rodgers,Louisiana,Parliament of Trees,Sethe,Swamp Thing</Tags>
	<Teams>Parliament of Trees</Teams>
	<Title>When it Comes A'Knockin'</Title>
	<Volume>2011</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-2-when-it-comes-aknockin/4000-294200/</Web>
	<Writer>Scott Snyder</Writer>
	<Year>2011</Year>
</ComicInfo>