<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Abner Marsh,Valerie Mersault,Joshua York,Cynthia,Jean,Damon Julian,Sour Billy Tipton</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digikore Studios</Colorist>
  <Count>10</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Editor>William Christensen</Editor>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-778791</GTIN>
  <Inker>Ruben</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Locations>New Orleans</Locations>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:38:40 [Issue ID 4000-778791] urn:comicvine:4000-778791 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/778791
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 17:29:14. [Issue ID 778791]</Notes>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1556678" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="623050" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1267709" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1463748" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1581853" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1634282" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1586078" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1833607" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1823138" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1717066" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2134485" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1838053" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1639857" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1559468" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1561986" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1602198" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1860330" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1864169" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1702434" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1587216" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1315204" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1107359" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1232037" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="933581" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Rafa Lopez</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
  <Series>George R. R. Martin's Fevre Dream</Series>
  <Summary>The ten-issue vampire epic on the bayou from the writer of the A Song of Ice and Fire novels continues in issue six! From the New York Times Best-selling author, George R. R. Martin, comes a tale of vampire clans, death and debauchery, legendary blood masters, and even a few epic steamboat races on the muddy Mississippi. This is Martin's FEVRE DREAM, an antebellum story of power, loss, and the fever of bloodlust. York and Marsh have finally, truly come to an understanding. What began as a business partnership shrouded in carefully constructed lies has now been flung into the burning light of the truth, the whole truth, and the two men now stand together as brothers-in-arms against a common enemy and towards a common goal -- the salvation of the human race. But are one man and one vampire strong enough to stand against the evil of Damon Julian? When the dark bloodmaster sets foot on the Fevre Dream, a bloody fight is about to begin... Each issue of this stunning full-color epic is illustrated by Rafa Lopez, an artist whose skilled line captures every moonlit drop of blood in delicious detail. Adapted by the Hugo-nominated author Daniel Abraham, this version of FEVRE DREAM stays faithful to Martin's original dark vision, while bringing the torture and joy of his vampires to almost-human life. This haunting series is available with Regular and Wraparound painted covers by Felipe Massafera and a very limited Nightmare retailer incentive.</Summary>
  <Teams>Vampires</Teams>
  <Volume>2010</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-778791/</Web>
  <Writer>Daniel Abraham,George R.R. Martin</Writer>
  <Year>2010</Year>
</ComicInfo>