<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-57088</GTIN>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:18:18 [Issue ID 4000-57088] urn:comicvine:4000-57088
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 13:48:40. [Issue ID 75878]</Notes>
  <Number>19</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Atlas.1954)  (Pmack-Gambit-Novus)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Spellbound</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/spellbound-19/4000-57088/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>34</Count>
  <Title>Off His Rocker!; The Firing Squad; Witch Doctor; Peek-A-Boo!; Who's Knocking at My Door?</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>Off His Rocker!: A man gets rid of his uncle by tipping his rocking chair so he falls out the window. His conscience bothers him so that he thinks the rocker is still rocking, and he falls out the window himself.

The Firing Squad: A man becomes wealthy by accusing his neighbors of disloyalty to the Red Chinese and sharing in the redistribution of wealth. Various soldiers pass through the area looking for traitors until there is no one left to accuse. When the last general asks who is wealthy, his neighbors point to the man and he is executed.

Witch Doctor: A man looking for an island paradise finds a witch doctor who keeps his zombie thinking he is a living man by transfusing blood into him.

Peek-A-Boo!: In 1973 the first landing on Mars retreats quickly after Martians toss flesh dissolving grenades at them. They bring one back to Earth and it is stolen by a communist spy. He takes it back to the communist leaders where they open it and all die.

Who's Knocking at My Door?: A scientist develops the means of murdering everyone on the planet, but commits suicide after hearing a knocking on his door figuring that it is Martians come to place the only living human in a zoo. It turns out to be a tree branch in the wind.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Carl Wessler,Carl Wessler</Writer>
  <Penciller>Bob Fujitani,Al Luster,Tony DiPreta,Bob Powell,Cal Massey,Bob Fujitani,Al Luster,Tony DiPreta,Bob Powell,Cal Massey</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bob Fujitani,Al Luster,Tony DiPreta,Bob Powell,Cal Massey,Bob Fujitani,Al Luster,Tony DiPreta,Bob Powell,Cal Massey</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>