<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Rusty Merritt,Rustalinda,Kayo Jones,Miss Higgleby,Merlin,Morgan Le Fay,Sir Kay,Fay Morgan,Mr. Moylan,Frankie Nesbitt</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-2043</GTIN>
  <Inker>John Rosenberger,Leonard Starr,Ogden Whitney,John Rosenberger,Ogden Whitney,Leonard Starr</Inker>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:35:21 [Issue ID 4000-2043] urn:comicvine:4000-2043
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 02:50:28. [Issue ID 12346]</Notes>
  <Number>37</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>John Rosenberger,Leonard Starr,Ogden Whitney,John Rosenberger,Ogden Whitney,Leonard Starr</Penciller>
  <Publisher>American Comics Group</Publisher>
  <Series>Forbidden Worlds</Series>
  <Tags>Merlin,Morgan le Fay,Sir Kay</Tags>
  <Volume>1951</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/forbidden-worlds-37/4000-2043/</Web>
  <Year>1955</Year>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Ogden Whitney</CoverArtist>
  <Title>One Exciting Knight!; Step by Step---; Journey Into the Past!; Cyclone!</Title>
  <Summary>One Exciting Knight!: Bumbling Frankie Nesbitt is to play Sir Gawain in the school play about the legend of King Arthur. During one of his rehearsals he is hit in the head and dreams that he has gone back in time to the year 516. There he meets some of the Knights of the Round Table who give him a special sword to vanquish a dragon. Frankie is hit on the head again and wakes up back at his school in the modern day. Thinking it all a dream, Frankie notices he is holding the legendary sword Excalibur!

Step by Step---: Struggling writer Alex Stone can't catch a break and come up with a good story to sell. After taking some experimental drugs given to him by his doctor, Alex falls asleep. When he awakens he finds he has written a story. The story is so good that, not only does he sell it, but it makes him rich and famous as well. While vacationing in Italy with his new bride, he comes across shady characters out to get him. As this unfolds, he realizes that this is what happened in his story. His story is coming true and Alex needs to avoid the tragic ending that happened to the main character...himself!

Journey Into the Past!: Margaret Blythe comes to the Lawrence Estate to claim an inheritance. However she can't prove who she is to the others. That night she has a strange dream about the history of the house and that she is her ancestor Margaret Anders Lawrence in 1704. Margaret Anders puts her wedding license (with the state founder Roger Lawrence) into a secret vault in the house. When Margaret Blythe awakens she finds the wedding license still in the old vault in the modern day, thus proving that she was descended from the original Lawrences.

Cyclone!: Three cowboys on a train all have a dream about the legendary horse "Cyclone". In their dreams they were all thrown from the legendary horse. When they awaken, they are stunned to have the conductor come in and ask why the car was shaking and why he heard a horse whinnying!

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Editor>Richard E. Hughes</Editor>
</ComicInfo>