<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>13</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1356155</GTIN>
  <Genre>Crime,Drama,Historical</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:37:55 [Issue ID 4000-1356155] urn:comicvine:4000-1356155 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1356155
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:51:17. [Issue ID 1356155]</Notes>
  <Number>10</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>The Greater Good - Chapter 4: Full Disclosure</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-10-the-greater-good-chapter-4-full-disclos/4000-488605/</Web>
  <Year>2015</Year>
  <Summary>News gets out that Radia defeated Doppler and saved Alderman Hayes.  When some crooks contemplate what it means for some C.O.W.L. members to be back on the prowl, they are attacked by a mysterious, vicious vigilante (Sparrow) who tells them to confess to the police about what they saw when John Pierce was killed.

Radia heals in the hospital after her encounter with Doppler.  Geoffrey Warner confronts her for breaking the strike, but she doesn't care.  He threatens her by saying her can give someone else the Radia costume and name.  Outside he papers over their argument by saying that it was his idea for her to stop Doppler.

Warner meets with mobster Camden Stone later.  He wants Radia dead for what she did, and Warner, his ethics becoming more and more compromised, reluctantly agrees.

Evelyn continues her search for proof about John's murder without success, or support from her department.

Blaze confronts Eclipse about the fire at city hall, which was caused by an unknown hero during a scuffle on the picket line.  Blaze thinks Frank did it, and wants Eclipse to say he saw him do it.  He tries to blackmail Eclipse with information about what he and Radia have been doing to Stone's men outside of the strike.  Eclipse walks out, using his powers to mess with Blaze's power glove, but he's scared.

Two more costumed villains rob a pharmacy, but are interrupted by the cops. They kill two police officers in their escape, breaking the rules that Warner's rule with Stone about no killing.

One of the criminals intimidated by Sparrow turns himself in to Evelyn and tells her the truth about how Arclight murdered John Pierce.

Features a bio on Evelyn Hewitt (aka Frost aka Thompson, nee Harrigan!).</Summary>
  <Characters>Sparrow,Camden Stone,Evelyn Hewitt,Blaze,Eclipse,Geoffrey Warner,Radia</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Chicago,Indiana</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Rod Reis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Rod Reis</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Rod Reis</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>