<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Father Vincent Adobe,Roxanna,Werewolf By Night</Characters>
	<Colorist>Marie Javins</Colorist>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Ralph Macchio</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-108994</GTIN>
	<Inker>Leonardo Manco</Inker>
	<Letterer>Janice Chiang</Letterer>
	<Locations>New York State,Texas</Locations>
	<Month>3</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:18:41 [Issue ID 4000-108994] urn:comicvine:4000-108994</Notes>
	<Number>2</Number>
	<PageCount>23</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="331811" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1143626" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="351854" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="355676" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="316322" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="346139" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="299027" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="325381" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="329306" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="349209" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="346029" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="327128" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="371620" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="752546" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="363192" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="309437" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="319395" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="335129" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="342634" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="408742" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="351356" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="363221" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="309278" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Leonardo Manco</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
	<Summary>As Jack Russell drives cross-country, he recalls two conversations he had before leaving New York. In the first, Father Vincent Adobe tried to get Jack to open up to him about the secrets he's harboring. The other conversation was with his girlfriend Roxanna when he told her he had to leave town for a few days, and she got upset.

Now, on a quest to obtain the ancient blade which he thinks is a key to curing his lycanthropy, Jack drives up to the isolated mansion he believes houses the Cult of the Third Moon. He is turned away by a bodyguard, confirming his suspicions that this is the right place.

Jack finds a secluded spot in the woods nearby and transforms into the Werewolf, again experiencing visions of a hell and a demon that calls his name. He runs back to the mansion and bursts in through a window into the altar room where the cultists have just sacrificed an unwilling victim. The Werewolf demands the ritual knife, but the cultists produce firearms and shoot at him. The lead bullets do him no harm, and he shreds his foes. The cult leader watching from his wheelchair atop a staircase, is bumped by one of his minions, and topples down the steps. The leader, Walter Clark, a former actor who had come into possession of the knife, reaches for the blade despite his broken neck, but the Werewolf grabs his wrist. Before he dies, Clark tells the Werewolf that the knife, called the Wolfblade, will not be enough to cure him; he needs two other parts.

Days later, Jack and Roxanna visit a carnival. When she excuses herself to the ladies' room, he is approached by a small man who claims to be an agent of parties desiring Jack's allegiance. He, too, tells Jack there are two companion pieces to the Wolfblade, and offers to lead him to them. The man escorts Jack to the carnival fun-house telling him it will briefly house a fiery portal to Jack's personal hell. Before the ephemeral portal fades away, Jack agrees to take the ride.

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-2-life-in-the-fast-lane/4000-108994/</Summary>
	<Tags>Cult of the Third Moon,Father Vincent Adobe,New York State,Roxanna,Texas,Werewolf By Night,Werewolves</Tags>
	<Teams>Cult of the Third Moon,Werewolves</Teams>
	<Title>Life in the Fast Lane</Title>
	<Volume>1998</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-2-life-in-the-fast-lane/4000-108994/</Web>
	<Writer>Paul Jenkins</Writer>
	<Year>1998</Year>
</ComicInfo>