<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Love and Rockets</Series>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Title>Cry Baby Killer; Ghost of a Chance; Frank Lopez; Killer Song; Honeymoon for Young Lovers and You; Billy, be a Hero; The Fruit of Patience; Animus; Giving Up the Ghost</Title>
  <Volume>2016</Volume>
  <Genre>Drama,Science fiction,Fantasy</Genre>
  <Summary>This is volume four in the series. Uses the same oversize magazine format as volume one.

Vol. 1- 1982-1996 (50 issues in magazine format)
Vol. 2- 2001-2007 (20 issues in standard US comic book periodical format)
Vol. 3- 2008-2016 (8 issues as Love and Rockets: New Stories in trade paperback format)

Comes with at least one cover variant per issue available exclusively from the publisher. Each variant has its own individual front &amp; back cover.US comic book store release date 2020-11-21.Cry Baby Killer: Chat about boob size and fear (or lack of fear) of ghosts.

Ghost of a Chance: The family at Fritz's beach house as she plans to develop a singing career for Rosy.

Frank Lopez: A story focusing on Frank Lopez as he visits his Aunt Looseness, chats with some acquaintances on the sidewalk and then with Vivian and Tonta.

Killer Song: Steve, Guadalupe and Jimmy watch Killer perform live. Then multiple years-spanning flashbacks to Gato's interactions with Guadalupe when he was still alive.

Honeymoon for Young Lovers and You: Fritz arrives at Luba and Domingo's honeymoon to chat.

Billy, be a Hero: Hopey and Sadaf arrive at a baseball field to give young Mani some batting practice but a team of older players is already there.

The Fruit of Patience: Guadalupe's friends and family in Palomar for her wedding party, as she's now married to Steve Stranski in this story mostly narrated by Hector.

Animus: Isla separates from Lumina in order to divert the Hellmet that's chasing them. The Interplanetary Space Police captures Lumina, interrogates and then jails her but she escapes due to the See Stone. Princess Anima's severely charred corpse may be reviving.

Giving Up the Ghost: The family talks about the deceased Gato Reyna as his ghost lingers in the background. Killer talks with the ghost and then with Jimmy about the songs she sings. Domingo and Luba decide to get married.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev36 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-03-22 15:07:53. [Issue ID 1875476]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>20</Day>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Year>2018</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Web>https://www.comics.org/issue/1875476</Web>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (Salem-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Writer>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>