<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294538</GTIN>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:13 [Issue ID 4000-294538] urn:comicvine:4000-294538
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:29. [Issue ID 136604]</Notes>
  <Number>15</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>The Corpse Who Prowled by Night: A road construction disturbs the eternal rest of evil Silas Dunster. His corpse stalks the building crew and murders quite a few of them. Or so it appears.

The Demon Coat: Millionaire collector John Masterson comes into possession of king Tut’s Egyptian “demon coat”, a jacket which - once donned – scares its wearer to death with frightful visions. The killing coat passes from hand to hand until it’s finally destroyed.

The Haunted Forest: Yates and Manning, professional debunkers of the supernatural, tackle a last mystery no one dare solve up to now – the haunted forest. Every man going on came back a raving maniac. Yates and Manning travel inside and are confronted with attacking trees and giant spiders. Only Manning returns from the haunted forest – hopelessly mad.

The Dreaded Crypts of Horror: Rich Uncle Cyrus summons his four heirs to his mansion in the marshland. The money will be theirs if they survive a night in specially prepared rooms of horror.

</Summary>
  <Title>The Corpse Who Prowled by Night; The Demon Coat; The Haunted Forest; The Dreaded Crypts of Horror</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-15-the-corpse-who-prowled-by-night/4000-294538/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>