<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Caesar Valenzano,Tony Chu,Jacob Butterfield,John Colby,Paneer Sharma,Mike Applebee,Mason Savoy,Toni Chu,D-Bear</Characters>
  <Colorist>Taylor Wells</Colorist>
  <Day>30</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-270477</GTIN>
  <Inker>Rob Guillory,Rob Guillory</Inker>
  <Letterer>John Layman</Letterer>
  <Locations>Speedy Upholstery,Pennsylvania,Our Lady of the Broken Femur Hospital,Brazil,Philadelphia,Farmington-Kapusta International Telescope,Amazon Jungle</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:38:20 [Issue ID 4000-270477] urn:comicvine:4000-270477
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 17:07:46. [Issue ID 270477]</Notes>
  <Number>27</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Rob Guillory,Rob Guillory</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Chew</Series>
  <Summary>'Space Cakes,' Part One 

'Open the door, sir. I'm Toni Chu, Agent of NASA. I'm here to lick your paintings.'

Toni Chu is visiting her brother, Tony, in the hospital talking about what had transpired recently in her life. When Agent Valenzano walked into the room to give Tony a present, Valenzano recognized Toni, but didn't know when he first met her. It was revealed that Toni had met Valenzano when she was still working for N.A.S.A., when Valenzano was called back to work, Toni had to leave to go to the N.A.S.A. agency. When Toni arrived at work, she was greeted by Jacob Butterfield whom was a colleague of her during her career as a N.A.S.A. scientist. Jacob told Toni that he needed her help because the Psychedelic Chogs he had been breeding were stollen by D-Bear.

Toni went to the Chicken Speakeasy with her boss/partner Captain Paneer Sharma. When the two found D-Bear he made a run for it immediately, however Toni got a bite out of D-Bear and she saw his future which showed that he would get hit by a bus. Back at the hospital, Toni was visiting her brother again, but to her knowledge she found out he was already being visited by someone else. A distraught Tony thinking that his girlfriend was in his hospital room soon found out that a mysterious visitor had entered his room.

*A View To A Pill Plot Summary*
John Colby and a handful of F.D.A. doctors were visiting Tony Chu in the hospital to discuss with him about ingesting a designer drug. Tony Chu knew of the drug he was about to ingest and also how high the fatality rate was, but Colby assured his friend that he and the doctors would be checking his vital signs while he was under the drugs side affects. After 3 days of insane hallucinations, Tony finally came around and told Colby of where the drug was manufactured. In the end, the F.D.A. doctor mentioned to Tony that his ordeal wasn't over. He mentioned that Tony would feel a fever, chills, muscle spasms, and violent nausea for eight more hours. In the end, Tony journeyed back into the craziness of a designer drug. John Layman's P.S.A. was: "Hey Kids! Don't do fictional designer drugs with 80% fatality rates!"</Summary>
  <Tags>Jacob Butterfield,John Colby,Paneer Sharma,Mason Savoy,Farmington-Kapusta International Telescope,Caesar Valenzano,Speedy Upholstery,Unicorns,Food and Drug Administration,Pennsylvania,Our Lady of the Broken Femur Hospital,Philadelphia,Tony Chu,Brazil,D-Bear,Amazon Jungle,National Aeronautics and Space Administration,Space Cakes,Mike Applebee,Toni Chu</Tags>
  <Teams>Unicorns,Food and Drug Administration,National Aeronautics and Space Administration</Teams>
  <Title>Space Cakes, Part 2 of 5</Title>
  <Volume>2009</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/chew-27-space-cakes-part-2-of-5/4000-270477/</Web>
  <Writer>John Layman</Writer>
  <Year>2012</Year>
  <Count>60</Count>
  <StoryArc>"Chew" Space Cakes</StoryArc>
  <CoverArtist>Rob Guillory</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>