<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Fantastic Comics</Series>
  <Number>9</Number>
  <Count>23</Count>
  <Title>The God of the Cave Things</Title>
  <Volume>1939</Volume>
  <Genre>Historical,Jungle,War,Adventure,Science fiction,Superhero,Spy,Humor,Fantasy</Genre>
  <Summary>On an isolated south sea island pre-historic beasts still live. Professor Simm gains control of them and blackmails the USA to relinquish authority to him or face an invasion of beasts. Samson stops Simm, cages him with the beasts, and destroys the island by causing a volcano to erupt.

Flip uses the dimension machine to travel back to the 16th century to see if the legend of the Amazons is true. He arrives at a pivotal juncture, as the Amazons are about to be captured by European colonists. He frees them and they disappear into the deep forest, never to be seen again.

Sir Richard and Alice travel by ship to Egypt, on their way to the Holy Land, but are beset first by pirates, then sea monsters and sharks, before becoming shipwrecked and stranded on an island.

Yank infiltrates a region recently conquered by the Hondus and finds an American girl, Cecily Monson, who has been hypnotized. He snaps her out of the trance, and gets intelligence about the Hondus' next move, and the two escape.  The Americans foil the Hondus' plans, destroy their fleet, and Franklin Roosevelt gives the Distinguished Service medal to Yank.  Yank and Cecily begin a romance.

Captain Kidd sets out to find a lost explorer, Perez, who went missing on a mission to find the Lost Valley. The Captain gains the help of a native, Wongo, who leads Kidd to the valley, but pays the price, when the cyclopean monsters who inhabit the Valley get their hands on him. Kidd's efforts to save Wongo lead him to a fight with the head cyclops, who turns out to be Perez in disguise. Perez had hoped to scare others away from his find, but had become unhinged, and leaps to his death.

While seeking new routes from Mars to Io, Space and Diana encounter what they at first mistake for a natural phenomenon, a sandblast.  When a group of sandblasts orchestrate an attack on Space's ship, Space and Diana intuit that the entities are really intelligent alien beings and an advanced invasion force.

When the Professor overhears the Mob planning to rub him out, he attempts to get the police to arrest him, so that he will be in the safety of jail.  The Professor finds it more difficult than he imagined to get the police to take action.

The evil Moloka's band of space titans seeks to destroy the solar system and control the sun.  Stardust moves to stop him, but due to confusion on Moloka's part, Stardust plays the role of Moloka's advisor until he brings an end to Moloka's war machines and fleet.  Stardust strands Moloka on a planet made lifeless by his own aggression.

While out on patrol in his submarine, Sub is caught in a whirlpool which delivers him to the undersea lair of the Cave Things. Fighting to avoid captivity, Sub stumbles upon the Temple of Boloch, God of the Cave Things. He discovers that the god is a ruse, perpetrated by a surface dweller to deprive the Cave Things of their riches. Sub rids the Cave Things of their oppresor and escapes, leaving the Cave Things in peace.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:11:20. [Issue ID 942]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fox</Publisher>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Year>1940</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(august 1940)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Prof. Simm (villain, introduction, death),Samson</Characters>
  <Writer>Audrey Blum,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Victor Fox,Toni Blum,Boris Plaster,Toni Blum,Boris Plaster</Writer>
  <Penciller>Alex Anthony Blum,Bill Bossert,Charles Cuidera,Don Rico,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Grant Ferguson,Grieg Chapian,Alex Blum,Lance Ferguson,Boris Plaster,Henry Kiefer,Alex Blum,Grieg Chapian,Lance Ferguson,Bill Bossert,Boris Plaster,Fletcher Hanks,Henry Kiefer</Penciller>
  <Inker>Alex Anthony Blum,Bill Bossert,Charles Cuidera,Don Rico,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Grant Ferguson,Grieg Chapian,Alex Blum,Lance Ferguson,Boris Plaster,Karl Kief,Alex Blum,Grieg Chapian,Lance Ferguson,Bill Bossert,Boris Plaster,Fletcher Hanks,Karl Kief</Inker>
  <Letterer>Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Fred Schwab</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>Samson,death),introduction,Prof. Simm (villain</Tags>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/fantastic-comics-9-attack-of-the-prehistoric-monst/4000-255632/</Web>
  <Teams>Generals of Capella,Cyclopeans,Dinosaurs,Cave Things,Moloka's Lieutenants,Pirates,Hondo Army,United States Navy,Amazons,Sandblasts</Teams>
  <Locations>Space,Mars Observatory,Lost Valley,Mars,Io,Isle of Mystery,Nemus,Africa</Locations>
  <CoverArtist>Charles Cuidera</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Victor Fox</Editor>
</ComicInfo>