<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Save The Antichrist, Save The World</Title>
  <Series>Ghost Riders: Heaven's on Fire</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Volume>2009</Volume>
  <Summary>The acclaimed GHOST RIDER run of writer Jason Aaron reaches its fever-pitched conclusion with six more issues of insanity, all jam-packed with new villains, old allies and the same old grindhouse action that Flamehead fans have come to know and love. The renegade angel Zadkiel is out to thwart Biblical prophecy by assassinating a young boy bred by Satanists to rule the world, so if Ghost Riders Johnny Blaze and Danny Ketch are going to save the world, they'll first have to save the Anti-Christ. Guest-starring Hellstorm, the Son of Satan.

Hellstorm is called to visits an old church used by devil worshipers. As he arrives the place is a total massacre. Only one of the worshipers survived. It is revealed that the church was used for an experiment called Project Blackout. The attempts was to bore a son of the anti-christ. It turns out that Zadkiel's angels killed everyone but missed one of the kids. This kid might be the new son of the anti-christ. The angels were sent to kill him. As much as Hellstorm wants nothing to do with this, he takes the case and goes out to find the child, but only if he dies at his hand.

Else where at a new age store, Johnny Blaze and Sara encounter two agents of Zadkiel and are looking for info on what his plan is. The two engage the agents in battle and end up defeating them and getting the info they wanted. It turns out Zadkiel wants to kill the Anti-Christ so that no apocalypse would happen and Zadkiel can start his own for years to come. Now Ghost Rider and Sara must find the Anit-Christ before Zadkiel does.

Meanwhile on Wall Street. it is revealed that the anti-christ is a 12 year old ruthless investment banker Anton Satan. In his office, and agent of Zadkiel attempts to kill him but is stopped by Jaine Cutter. She takes Anton and tries to escape with him only to be stopped by Zadkiel. The two end up surrounded by a horde of his agents.

Meanwhile a Southern Nashville Prison Hospital, Blackout and The Deacon break The Orb out of his cell in order to get ready and kill Ghost Rider.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-22 12:11:02.  [CVDB166156]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 09:46:27. [Issue ID 672448]</Notes>
  <Year>2009</Year>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Writer>Jason Aaron</Writer>
  <Penciller>Roland Boschi</Penciller>
  <Inker>Roland Boschi</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dan Brown</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Joe Caramagna</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Jae Lee</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso,Joe Quesada,Sebastian Girner</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ghost-riders-heavens-on-fire-1-save-the-antichrist/4000-166156/</Web>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Orb,Zadkiel,Ghost Rider (Ketch),Sara,Blackout,Anton Satan,Deacon,Ghost Rider (Blaze),Hellstorm,Jaine Cutter</Characters>
  <Locations>Wall Street,Nashville,Washington D.C.,Las Vegas,Hollywood</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="250907" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="309689" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="404676" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="332539" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="381794" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="443763" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="412683" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="500181" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="484591" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="409399" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="431929" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="518110" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="439901" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="479239" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="410683" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="431358" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="496000" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="325458" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="372559" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="385231" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="479076" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="418230" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="384442" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="359579" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="380362" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="451445" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>