<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Pinocchio,Geppetto,Belinda,Jacob</Characters>
  <Colorist>Garry Henderson</Colorist>
  <Editor>Ken Kolasinski,Ralph Tedesco,Raven Gregory</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-141495</GTIN>
  <Inker>Dave Hoover,David Seidman</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!,David Seidman</Letterer>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:27:23 [Issue ID 4000-141495] urn:comicvine:4000-141495
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 12:59:31. [Issue ID 640498]</Notes>
  <Number>31</Number>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="971614" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1322207" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="905319" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="924102" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="866573" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="855051" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="814371" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="773839" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="653105" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="868095" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="578619" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="716492" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="751786" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="714831" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="753424" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="852976" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="830023" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="787139" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="749970" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="851971" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="639817" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="664676" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="769855" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="703596" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="672210" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="653941" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="827908" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="870563" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="955174" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Dave Hoover,David Seidman</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Zenescope Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Series>Grimm Fairy Tales</Series>
  <Summary>A single father has only his young son left in the world. It's a bond that can never be shattered, but what if your son isn't really the boy you thought he was? Will Belinda find a way to corrupt yet another young mind, or will a father's love be enough to protect his flesh and blood from evil? Two lives mirror one another if the first part of what might be the most intense and heart-wrenching Grimm Fairy Tales to ever hit store shelves!

The story of Pinocchio is told in reference to a modern father who is dealing with the death of his wife and being a single father. He confers with his son's teacher, with whom they later agree to see each other romantically. He returns home and finds the fairy tale book which Belinda has given to his son. He reads the story of Pinocchio, the wooden boy created because the carpenter, Gepetto, has lost his wife and son. The wooden boy strives to become real and goes so far as to run away from home and join a circus. A group of thieves are hired by Gepetto to find the boy, and although they take the reward money, they also plan to free the boy and sell him to a richer bidder. They give him a key to escape his cage, but with his pet cricket advising him, he decides to kill first the circus owner and then the two thieves, the latter of the two being witnessed by his father. The story cuts back to the modern day where the son returns from school and reveals that his teacher died from a suspicious murder that same day. After the school finds the father, he is certain that his son is guilty of the act.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 20:08:33.  [CVDB141495]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/grimm-fairy-tales-31-pinocchio/4000-141495/</Summary>
  <Title>Pinocchio</Title>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/grimm-fairy-tales-31-pinocchio/4000-141495/</Web>
  <Writer>David Seidman,Joe Brusha,Ralph Tedesco</Writer>
  <Year>2008</Year>
  <Count>126</Count>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
<Genre>Fantasy,Horror</Genre></ComicInfo>