<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Siphon,Casque,Kiani</Characters>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Editor>Frank Mastromauro</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-321557</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T22:00:04 [Issue ID 4000-321557] urn:comicvine:4000-321557
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 04:50:47. [Issue ID 1098501]</Notes>
  <Number>0</Number>
  <PageCount>18</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1128055" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1367743" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1156628" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1333999" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1659958" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1610393" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1422939" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1227373" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1269799" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1378484" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1576695" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1126479" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1461910" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1671364" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1490276" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1720171" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1806937" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2054227" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Aspen</Publisher>
  <Series>Michael Turner's Fathom: Kiani</Series>
  <Summary>The Blue's fiercest warrior returns as FATHOM: KIANI vol 2 begins! In Volume One, she discovered her true identity. Later, she was labeled a dissident by her own people. Finally, she was killed by Aspen Matthews... Now, Kiani is back-and she's pissed! This all-new Fathom saga kicks off with the return of one of the Aspen Universe's favorite heroines, Kiani, as she returns to the awe-inspiring underwater world of the Blue seeking vengeance for her past! The neutral truce between the Humans and the Blue has taken an emotional toll on the inhabitants under the surface-and their future as a unified body remains uncertain. Now, all bets are off as Kiani's true power and capabilities-as well as shocking secrets from the past-- are revealed in this pulse-pounding zero issue! Brought to you by Vince Hernandez, Oliver Nome and John Starr, this debut zero issue features a brand-new 12-page story that sets the stage for next month's upcoming premiere of FATHOM: KIANI vol 2 #1. Accompanied by an additional sketchbook section and never before seen designs and art, make sure to dive right in and pick up, FATHOM: KIANI!!</Summary>
  <Title>Rebirth</Title>
  <Volume>2012</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/fathom-kiani-0-rebirth/4000-321557/</Web>
  <Writer>Vince Hernandez</Writer>
  <Year>2012</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>