<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>The War of the Worlds</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Genre>Science fiction</Genre>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 20:50:09. [Issue ID 355102]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(Caliber Comics)  War of the Worlds,  Caliber Press  bdcd2922ded0b70d3d57946aa6029503  Anna’s Archive</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Based on concepts and stories originated by H.G. Wells! The "Martian Invasion" has begun again and now mankind must fight, not only for their homes, but for their very humanity. Aliens were the stuff of legends, fairy tails, to scare children or to entertain those wanting to escape the mundane existence of their lives. Few took aliens seriously, let alone saw them as a threat. Yet as mankind busied itself about their petty affairs, they were being scrutinized and studied, perhaps as narrowly as a scientist might watch under the microscope of the microbes that swarm and multiply in a drop of water. It happened slowly at first but by the third year, it seemed that the war was almost over...the war was almost lost. And humanity was not going to be the winner this time. Now the War of the Worlds has descended upon Kansas City, but the government and the military have abandoned the city, how do its remaining inhabitants stand a chance? Meanwhile, hundreds of miles away in a small plains town called Haven, humanity just might have been given a second chance at survival. But before they can use their chance, they'll need to save themselves from the invader''s ravenous "Hellweed", an alien plant lifeform that not only absorbs any life it can devour, but also seems to be changing the atmosphere around it.</Summary>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/war-of-the-worlds-1/4000-335879/</Web>
  <Teams>Martians (H. G. Wells)</Teams>
  <Writer>Randy Zimmerman</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gene Gonzales,Horus</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gene Gonzales,Horus</Inker>
  <Colorist>Gene Gonzales</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Gene Gonzales</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>