<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>TPB</Title>
  <Series>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2023</Volume>
  <Summary>Six months after the Teenagers With Attitude and the Heroes In A Half Shell teamed up to defeat the unholy alliance of Rita Repulsa and Shredder, a new threat forces them to reunite!

Unlikely alliances and unlikely sanctuaries abound as the Rangers and Turtles put their heads together and create a secret weapon&#8230; but it might change them in ways they can&#8217;t come back from!

Forbidden alliances collide as radically enhanced, mind blowing Zord combinations battle it out, and reunited friends face Krang as a true force to be reckoned with&#8211;but will it be enough to send him back to Dimension X?

Longtime Power Rangers architect Ryan Parrott (Rogue Sun) joins forces with superstar artist Dan Mora (World&#8217;s Finest, Once &amp; Future) to deliver the follow-up to the hit crossover!

Collects Mighty Morphin Power Rangers / Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II #1-5.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-21 00:27:18.  [CVDB1014675]</Notes>
  <Year>2023</Year>
  <Month>09</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <Writer>Ryan Parrott</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dan Mora</Penciller>
  <Inker>Dan Mora</Inker>
  <Colorist>Ra&#250;l Angulo</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Ed Dukeshire</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Dan Mora, Diego Sanches</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Dafna Pleban, Kenzie Rzonca</Editor>
  <Publisher>Boom! Studios</Publisher>
  <Genre>Action/Adventure, Superhero</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/mighty-morphin-power-rangersteenage-mutant-ninja-t/4000-1014675/</Web>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Alpha 5, April O'Neil, Baboo, Baxter Stockman, Bebop, Billy Cranston, Blue Power Ranger, Bulk, Casey Jones, Donatello, Ernie, Eye Guy, Finster, Goldar, Green Power Ranger, Jason Scott, Karai, Kimberly Hart, Krang, Leatherhead, Leonardo, Lord Zedd, Madame Woe, Master Splinter, Michelangelo, Pink Power Ranger, Pudgy Pig , Pumpkin Rapper, Raphael, Red Power Ranger, Rita Repulsa, Rocksteady, Scorpina, Shredder, Skull, Slash, Squatt, Terror Toad, The Rat King, Tommy Oliver, Traag, Trini Kwan, Yellow Power Ranger, Zack Taylor, Zordon</Characters>
  <Teams>Dimension X Rangers, Evil Space Aliens, Power Rangers, Putty Patrol, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</Teams>
  <Locations>Angel Grove, Angel Grove Youth Center, California, Dimension X, New York City, Ryker's Island, The Command Center</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1015299" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1493759" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1764590" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1132928" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1225190" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1447829" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1665465" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1608601" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="7045915" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="6141203" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1550660" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1794981" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1663002" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1265041" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1706311" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1645762" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1194162" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1770001" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1507326" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1570313" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1206163" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1142291" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1873144" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
