<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<CoverArtist>Jake Lynch</CoverArtist>
	<Day>18</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-506452</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,Jim McCarthy,Karl Richardson,Leigh Gallagher,Peter Doherty,Rufus Dayglo</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Ellie De Ville,Peter Doherty,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>11</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:44:09 [Issue ID 4000-506452] urn:comicvine:4000-506452</Notes>
	<Number>1957</Number>
	<PageCount>31</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="6724808" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1375631"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1160460"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1052580"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1037371"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1051663"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1085012"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="925076"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1274294"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1061134"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1025647"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1082662"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="943001"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="875968"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="844357"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1092857"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1068793"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1203723"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1230023"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1030415"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1060996"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="839300"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1371763"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="885258"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1017610"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1130623"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1267314"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1166475"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1111604"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1271768"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1331445"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,Jim McCarthy,Karl Richardson,Leigh Gallagher,Peter Doherty,Rufus Dayglo</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>*Dredd: That Extra Mile [1]*
Mega-City One, 2137 AD. Home to 50 million citizens, and still recovering from the decimation of the Chaos Bug, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, where crime is rampant, poverty is rife, and unemployment near universal. Only the zero-tolerance Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law!

*Defoe: The London Hanged [8]*
1671. It is five years since London was devastated by the Great Fire, the inferno caused by a comet passing over the capital. But from the ashes rose the undead, hungry for the flesh of the living. Protecting the populace was former Leveller Titus DEFOE, who led an elite squad of zombie hunters called the Brethren of the Night. But having defeated the evil magician Faust, who was controlling the stenches, Defoe has retired from zombie-hunting and returned to his old profession as a sedan-chair carrier, living in domestic happiness with fellow reek-seeker Tomazine Scarlet, her son Sean, and their new baby...

*Tharg's Terror Tales: Night Shifts [1]*
Experience the terrifying side of Thrill-power with these one-off tales from beyond the shadowy veil of sanity. Whether they be ghostly goings-on that send shivers up the spine or guts-to-the-wall splatterfests that sear the retina, nothing is what it seems in these glimpses of a horrifying realm beyond our own. Sitting alone at night, upon hearing a noise in the next room, do you investigate? Who knows what may be waiting for you...

*Brass Sun: Motor Head [8]*
The Orrery is a life-size clockwork solar system, a clutch of planets orbiting a vast BRASS SUN via immense metal spars, its origin and purpose long since forgotten. But the once-unified collection of worlds has regressed into eccentric fiefdoms, and ice is encroaching on the outer planets as the sun is dying. Young Wren has been charged with finding the scattered parts of the key that will restart the sun, and together with engineer Septimus she is embarking on an epic journey. But with an aspect of The Orrery’s creator The Blind Watchmaker living in her head, there are many who want Wren for themselves...

*Bad Company: First Casualties [8]*
It has been a decade since mankind fought a vicious war against the alien species the Krool on the planet Ararat. Young Private Danny Franks was just a raw recruit until he was drafted into the ragtag guerrilla unit known as BAD COMPANY, commanded by the psychopathic Kano. The conflict ended when Ararat exploded, and much of Bad Company was killed or listed MIA — now, as Earth prepares to mark the ten-year anniversary, Franks and fellow ex-soldiers Thrax, Mad Tommy and Fly-Trap are living in a veterans’ compound, dosed on psyche-chem to keep the nightmares at bay...

Cover: Jake Lynch

Judge Dredd - That Extra Mile (Part 1) (Alec Worley - Karl Richardson)Defoe - The London Hanged (Part 8) (Pat Mills - Leigh Gallagher)Tharg's Terror Tales - Night Shifts (Part 1) (John Smith - Peter Doherty)Brass Sun (Book Four) - Motor Head (Part 8) (Ian Edginton - INJ Culbard)Bad Company - First Casualties (Part 8) (Peter Milligan - Rufus Dayglo and Jim McCarthy)</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 1957</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-1957-prog-1957/4000-506452/</Web>
	<Writer>Alec Worley,Ian Edginton,John Smith,Pat Mills,Peter Milligan</Writer>
	<Year>2015</Year>
</ComicInfo>