<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Damon Julian,Abner Marsh,Valerie Mersault,Joshua York,Raymond Ortega</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digikore Studios</Colorist>
  <Count>10</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Editor>William Christensen</Editor>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-769629</GTIN>
  <Inker>Ruben</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Locations>New Orleans,Louisiana</Locations>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:38:37 [Issue ID 4000-769629] urn:comicvine:4000-769629 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/769629
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 17:29:06. [Issue ID 769629]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1604644" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="622042" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1861268" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1500473" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="966039" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1472760" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1625175" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1645950" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2120527" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1787824" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1998199" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1672114" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1890967" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1470534" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1909734" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2189621" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1925026" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1832840" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1421182" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1455131" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1084050" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1774641" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1588892" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1566667" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Rafa Lopez</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
  <Series>George R. R. Martin's Fevre Dream</Series>
  <Summary>The ten-issue vampire epic on the bayou from the writer of the A Song of Ice and Fire novels continues in issue four! From the New York Times Best-selling author, George R. R. Martin, comes a tale of vampire clans, death and debauchery, legendary blood masters, and even a few epic steamboat races on the muddy Mississippi. This is Martin's FEVRE DREAM, an antebellum story of power, loss, and the fever of bloodlust. Joshua York has given Abner Marsh more answers than he bargained for... but Marsh has been around a long time, and he knows something still isn't right. For one thing, York's newest guest, well, she ain't no lady. And the whispered accusations of the crew aren't very nice, but they are true: York never goes above deck in the daylight. But maybe Marsh's imagination is just getting the best of him. Surely a simple lunch with York should put all of his fears -- and those of the crew -- to rest, right? Each issue of this stunning full-color epic is illustrated by Rafa Lopez, an artist whose skilled line captures every moonlit drop of blood in delicious detail. Adapted by the Hugo-nominated author Daniel Abraham, this version of FEVRE DREAM stays faithful to Martin's original dark vision, while bringing the torture and joy of his vampires to almost-human life. This haunting series is available with Regular and Wraparound painted covers by Felipe Massafera and a very limited Nightmare retailer incentive.</Summary>
  <Teams>Vampires</Teams>
  <Volume>2010</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-769629/</Web>
  <Writer>Daniel Abraham,George R.R. Martin</Writer>
  <Year>2010</Year>
</ComicInfo>