<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Francine,Katchoo,Tambi Baker,David Qin</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digital Chameleon</Colorist>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-45123</GTIN>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:46:22 [Issue ID 4000-45123] urn:comicvine:4000-45123
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:06:53. [Issue ID 45123]</Notes>
  <Number>16</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>The girls plan a night in with a table overflowing with snacks and Xena on the television.. but something is missing... Fran and Katchoo eat everything in the house and Fran has some mints in her purse.  They discuss dressing up as Xena for Halloween as Fran tries to open a cupboard door. the door sticks adn then flies open smacking Kat in the head. She slumps to the floor and finds herself on the floor with Fran dressed as Xena helping her up to battle two almost naked sword welding men. Fran beats her enemy with finesse and jibes while Katchoo comically beats hers mercilessly with over head chops.  They charge out of a tower window followed by a volley of arrows and fall  a huge distance into the sea. Francine has to save Katchoo as she can't swim.   David is an aspiring bard but without a muse he can't even make poems that rhyme.  Of course he falls from an aggressive Katchoo.  Tambi appears in female warrior garb and Francine immediately attacks her without provocation. Tambi disarms her without even drawing a weapon and lifts Katchoo off her feet. David walks up and gives her a wet kiss that startles her and she steps backwards and falls off a cliff.  They discuss Kat's blow to the head and she tells them that she dreamt she was in the future and they lived together.</Summary>
  <Title>Princess Warrior</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-16-princess-warrior/4000-45123/</Web>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>