<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Wolf,Brother Jonah,Swamp Thing [Alec Holland],Lady Weeds,Neol,Aquaman [Arthur Curry]</Characters>
  <Colorist>Matthew Wilson,Matthew Wilson</Colorist>
  <Count>42</Count>
  <Editor>Chris Conroy,Darren Shan,Matt Idelson</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-455439</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jesus Saiz,Jesús Saiz</Inker>
  <Letterer>Travis Lanham,Travis Lanham</Letterer>
  <Locations>Philippines,Louisiana</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:13:17 [Issue ID 4000-455439] urn:comicvine:4000-455439
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:15:05. [Issue ID 1211601]</Notes>
  <Number>32</Number>
  <PageCount>21</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1752620" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2122163" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="4558410" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1735992" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1938741" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1540366" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1796142" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2376738" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1896353" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2153329" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2121998" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="4298844" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="2216141" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="2157967" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2031258" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2370397" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2129532" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2048045" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1829462" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2270147" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1727639" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jesus Saiz,Jesús Saiz</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Swamp Thing</Series>
  <Summary>Swamp Thing versus Aquaman! See the other side of the battle that exploded between these two forces of nature last month in AQUAMAN #31! Is Swamp Thing guilty of the crimes Aquaman is accusing him of?

 

(Continued from Aquaman #31 - In the Muck)

 

The issue opens with Alec underwater in the form built of seaweed commenting on the method of his breathing and the way the plants think down there. He finds a giant mass of green floating in the sea, killing the reef below. He tries to make contact with it but it does not follow orders or communicate back. He tries to combine physically with the mass but it begins to absorb him and he narrowly escapes. When he does he is suddenly jumped by Aquaman.

There is a flashback to a few hours earlier where we see Alec talking to Jonah and asking for information about a possible blob of algae. Jonah says he might have an idea so he calls upon the rest of the group. The Wolf tells Alec that he has foolishly invoked a Kreuzblutler. They explain that by having destroyed the Parliament of Trees the planetary biosphere has responded. Since the Parliament managed the Green, a separate offshoot has grown now that it has no opposition.

Flashing forward Aquaman calls on dugongs to eat at Alec. After he has been eaten Alec waits a moment to see what Aquaman's next move will be. He call on more fish to simply eat the algae mass. The Kreuzblutler replies by destroy all of the fish from the inside. Alec tell Aquaman that he is the only one who can deal with this. He combines with the Kreuzbluter and is transported into a separate Green. Outside the Kreuzblutler suddenly attacks Aquaman and he calls upon more backup.

Back inside the alternate Green, an avatar appears and fights Alec but he is quickly dealt with. Outside Aquaman has called massive machines to burn and cleanse the area that the Kreuzblutler has taken over, but Alec manages to take it over and dissolve it. Aquaman and Swamp Thing exchange threats and he leaves. Back in Louisiana when Alec arrives he met by The Wolf, Lady Weeds, and Jonah, they discuss his actions and the repercussions when suddenly Lady Weeds drives a knife through Alec's head.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-11-19 06:48:46.  [Issue ID 455439]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-32-blue-green/4000-455439/</Summary>
  <Tags>Brother Jonah,Lady Weeds,Louisiana,Philippines,Sea of Storms,Alec Holland,The Wolf,Aquaman,Zeekil Neol</Tags>
  <Title>Blue/Green</Title>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-32-blue-green/4000-455439/</Web>
  <Writer>Charles Soule,Charles Soule</Writer>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Rated T+ Teen Plus</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>