<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-487806</GTIN>
  <Inker>Bernie Krigstein,Frank Frazetta,George Evans,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Joe Orlando,Reed Crandall,Wally Wood,Will Elder,Al Williamson,Reed Crandall,Bernie Krigstein,Jack Kamen,George Evans,Joe Orlando,Wally Wood,Frank Frazetta,Al Williamson</Inker>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T23:54:44 [Issue ID 4000-487806] urn:comicvine:4000-487806
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-09 20:33:54. [Issue ID 1353030]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <PageCount>218</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1696711" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1201918" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="95394" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1857106" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="412965" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="541098" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="402350" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="402309" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="927687" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1109912" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="766687" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1001257" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1874268" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1843330" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1630844" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1646987" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1786209" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1724572" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1898906" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1739653" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1814277" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1792512" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1525291" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1765505" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1533791" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1509566" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1565177" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1584090" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1482189" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1160433" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1315966" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1194934" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="1264743" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="1662470" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="1679965" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="1590501" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="1470930" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="1537339" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="1441475" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="1682484" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="1655544" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="1789205" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="1803409" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="1574825" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="1784939" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="1250901" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="1915006" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="1664159" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="1459520" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="1666122" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="1767783" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="1783029" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="1801960" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="1707939" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="1842372" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="1751630" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="1606137" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="1589958" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="1586663" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="1517197" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="1735392" />
    <Page Image="61" ImageSize="1494473" />
    <Page Image="62" ImageSize="1588450" />
    <Page Image="63" ImageSize="1499489" />
    <Page Image="64" ImageSize="1806105" />
    <Page Image="65" ImageSize="1149707" />
    <Page Image="66" ImageSize="1530347" />
    <Page Image="67" ImageSize="1363132" />
    <Page Image="68" ImageSize="1590553" />
    <Page Image="69" ImageSize="1722955" />
    <Page Image="70" ImageSize="1686600" />
    <Page Image="71" ImageSize="1414298" />
    <Page Image="72" ImageSize="1203785" />
    <Page Image="73" ImageSize="1434574" />
    <Page Image="74" ImageSize="1477107" />
    <Page Image="75" ImageSize="1516845" />
    <Page Image="76" ImageSize="1481894" />
    <Page Image="77" ImageSize="1476610" />
    <Page Image="78" ImageSize="1318943" />
    <Page Image="79" ImageSize="1023666" />
    <Page Image="80" ImageSize="1889028" />
    <Page Image="81" ImageSize="1647747" />
    <Page Image="82" ImageSize="1523838" />
    <Page Image="83" ImageSize="1629331" />
    <Page Image="84" ImageSize="1634254" />
    <Page Image="85" ImageSize="1766586" />
    <Page Image="86" ImageSize="1947192" />
    <Page Image="87" ImageSize="1872677" />
    <Page Image="88" ImageSize="1714645" />
    <Page Image="89" ImageSize="1608437" />
    <Page Image="90" ImageSize="1444461" />
    <Page Image="91" ImageSize="1564131" />
    <Page Image="92" ImageSize="1587664" />
    <Page Image="93" ImageSize="1641032" />
    <Page Image="94" ImageSize="1676576" />
    <Page Image="95" ImageSize="1556913" />
    <Page Image="96" ImageSize="1763887" />
    <Page Image="97" ImageSize="1388928" />
    <Page Image="98" ImageSize="1938165" />
    <Page Image="99" ImageSize="1167410" />
    <Page Image="100" ImageSize="1637333" />
    <Page Image="101" ImageSize="1623709" />
    <Page Image="102" ImageSize="1658622" />
    <Page Image="103" ImageSize="1611658" />
    <Page Image="104" ImageSize="1635470" />
    <Page Image="105" ImageSize="1711206" />
    <Page Image="106" ImageSize="1409641" />
    <Page Image="107" ImageSize="1630721" />
    <Page Image="108" ImageSize="1505709" />
    <Page Image="109" ImageSize="1597291" />
    <Page Image="110" ImageSize="1761119" />
    <Page Image="111" ImageSize="1499846" />
    <Page Image="112" ImageSize="1725146" />
    <Page Image="113" ImageSize="1220947" />
    <Page Image="114" ImageSize="1508018" />
    <Page Image="115" ImageSize="1811833" />
    <Page Image="116" ImageSize="1292324" />
    <Page Image="117" ImageSize="1554630" />
    <Page Image="118" ImageSize="1539839" />
    <Page Image="119" ImageSize="1491890" />
    <Page Image="120" ImageSize="1595331" />
    <Page Image="121" ImageSize="1501122" />
    <Page Image="122" ImageSize="1461291" />
    <Page Image="123" ImageSize="1499357" />
    <Page Image="124" ImageSize="1627054" />
    <Page Image="125" ImageSize="1589692" />
    <Page Image="126" ImageSize="1588786" />
    <Page Image="127" ImageSize="1605492" />
    <Page Image="128" ImageSize="1569093" />
    <Page Image="129" ImageSize="1268028" />
    <Page Image="130" ImageSize="1561954" />
    <Page Image="131" ImageSize="1118566" />
    <Page Image="132" ImageSize="1936445" />
    <Page Image="133" ImageSize="1785643" />
    <Page Image="134" ImageSize="1795111" />
    <Page Image="135" ImageSize="1825064" />
    <Page Image="136" ImageSize="1798083" />
    <Page Image="137" ImageSize="1650509" />
    <Page Image="138" ImageSize="1762828" />
    <Page Image="139" ImageSize="2023362" />
    <Page Image="140" ImageSize="1629509" />
    <Page Image="141" ImageSize="1807031" />
    <Page Image="142" ImageSize="1767693" />
    <Page Image="143" ImageSize="1763380" />
    <Page Image="144" ImageSize="1733881" />
    <Page Image="145" ImageSize="1739581" />
    <Page Image="146" ImageSize="1734946" />
    <Page Image="147" ImageSize="1572404" />
    <Page Image="148" ImageSize="1769630" />
    <Page Image="149" ImageSize="1102640" />
    <Page Image="150" ImageSize="1589338" />
    <Page Image="151" ImageSize="1729545" />
    <Page Image="152" ImageSize="1667183" />
    <Page Image="153" ImageSize="1710039" />
    <Page Image="154" ImageSize="1796660" />
    <Page Image="155" ImageSize="1686469" />
    <Page Image="156" ImageSize="1638755" />
    <Page Image="157" ImageSize="1700569" />
    <Page Image="158" ImageSize="1539995" />
    <Page Image="159" ImageSize="1498532" />
    <Page Image="160" ImageSize="1684893" />
    <Page Image="161" ImageSize="1700085" />
    <Page Image="162" ImageSize="1654579" />
    <Page Image="163" ImageSize="1666459" />
    <Page Image="164" ImageSize="1652644" />
    <Page Image="165" ImageSize="1231700" />
    <Page Image="166" ImageSize="1354440" />
    <Page Image="167" ImageSize="1072800" />
    <Page Image="168" ImageSize="1555304" />
    <Page Image="169" ImageSize="1991038" />
    <Page Image="170" ImageSize="1855123" />
    <Page Image="171" ImageSize="1908037" />
    <Page Image="172" ImageSize="1881065" />
    <Page Image="173" ImageSize="1627341" />
    <Page Image="174" ImageSize="1478782" />
    <Page Image="175" ImageSize="1667922" />
    <Page Image="176" ImageSize="1580904" />
    <Page Image="177" ImageSize="1556224" />
    <Page Image="178" ImageSize="1553941" />
    <Page Image="179" ImageSize="1513562" />
    <Page Image="180" ImageSize="1497414" />
    <Page Image="181" ImageSize="1504048" />
    <Page Image="182" ImageSize="1921121" />
    <Page Image="183" ImageSize="908075" />
    <Page Image="184" ImageSize="1428999" />
    <Page Image="185" ImageSize="1568511" />
    <Page Image="186" ImageSize="1521396" />
    <Page Image="187" ImageSize="1567166" />
    <Page Image="188" ImageSize="1494804" />
    <Page Image="189" ImageSize="1602793" />
    <Page Image="190" ImageSize="1290539" />
    <Page Image="191" ImageSize="1431300" />
    <Page Image="192" ImageSize="1602625" />
    <Page Image="193" ImageSize="1673002" />
    <Page Image="194" ImageSize="1591694" />
    <Page Image="195" ImageSize="1641691" />
    <Page Image="196" ImageSize="1603136" />
    <Page Image="197" ImageSize="1574062" />
    <Page Image="198" ImageSize="1426239" />
    <Page Image="199" ImageSize="1830727" />
    <Page Image="200" ImageSize="1389244" />
    <Page Image="201" ImageSize="1425972" />
    <Page Image="202" ImageSize="1613038" />
    <Page Image="203" ImageSize="1888120" />
    <Page Image="204" ImageSize="1704233" />
    <Page Image="205" ImageSize="1879635" />
    <Page Image="206" ImageSize="1524923" />
    <Page Image="207" ImageSize="1559440" />
    <Page Image="208" ImageSize="1615149" />
    <Page Image="209" ImageSize="1795008" />
    <Page Image="210" ImageSize="1683529" />
    <Page Image="211" ImageSize="1722178" />
    <Page Image="212" ImageSize="1413783" />
    <Page Image="213" ImageSize="1663691" />
    <Page Image="214" ImageSize="1301035" />
    <Page Image="215" ImageSize="1667749" />
    <Page Image="216" ImageSize="1333081" />
    <Page Image="217" ImageSize="1576917" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Bernie Krigstein,Frank Frazetta,George Evans,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Joe Orlando,Reed Crandall,Wally Wood,Will Elder,Reed Crandall,Bernie Krigstein,Jack Kamen,George Evans,Joe Orlando,Wally Wood,Frank Frazetta</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Dark Horse</Publisher>
  <Series>The EC Archives: Shock SuspenStories</Series>
  <Summary>A man commits murder attempting to acquire enough money to win back his wife's affections. He doesn't know that she and her lover have already made a plot to run him down. When they manage to hit him with the car, they are pleased to find that his wallet is flush with cash.

Policeman McLeod notices a wild-eyed man carrying a bag with a suspicious rusty red stain on the bottom, and from the man's story, he believes that the bag contains the head of his boss. He chases after him and a city-wide manhunt begins. Soon, McLeod spots a man carrying a bag and shoots and kills him, only to discover that the dead man is not the maniac (who was already captured), but an innocent man carrying a bowling ball!

A husband is betrayed by his wife and funeral director when they plot to commit fraud to collect on his life insurance policy for his own murder. They plan to make him appear to be the victim of a mugging and then disappear in South America for a year. When his wife doesn't show with the money, he returns and they have him arrested and he ends up hanging for his own murder.

A poor girl knows her father will never be able to afford to buy a Cadillac, so she murders her mother and swears in court that the father did it, so after he is executed he gets his long sought after ride in a Cadillac hearse.

A diamond thief surgeon cuts open his two goons to smuggle diamonds into the country in their bodies. When he gets a big one worth $250,000 he tells the men he will operate on both of them, but place the diamond in only one so that they will not be tempted to disappear. The doctor sends them a note saying he will be delayed because he knows that this will play on their greed and they will turn on each other. They kill each other, but the doctor did not place the stone in either of them but himself. But the diamond was paste and it quickly caused the doctor's death due to poisoning.

An assassin unknowingly pursues his mark to the backstage of a theater and kills the man just before the curtain rises. It turns out that the assassin has walked in on the opening scene of a play about President William McKinley and the man who assassinated him!

Bela Kardiff murders all of his Hollywood contacts at a dinner honoring him after he has been typecast in horror pictures and then the company decides to dump him because they are not going to do horror pictures any longer.

A farmer tries to molest a retarded girl he keeps to work on the farm as a servant. She tells him that she's got a boyfriend that she sees in the evening. She goes out into the field to the scarecrow. The farmer gets the idea of disguising himself as the scarecrow so he can get what he wants from the girl. The farmer's wife is awakened by the sound of their love-making and goes out to the field with a pitchfork. When the girl tells the wife about her boyfriend, the wife tries to demonstrate to her that it's only straw by repeatedly stabbing the scarecrow with the pitchfork.

A newspaper columnist murders his gangster friend to get his wife and frames an innocent man for the crime through the power of his words.

A mob beats a vagrant to death for the rape of a sixteen year old girl that the town sheriff has been violating.

A college student, Warren Fuller, wants to join a frat so he makes up a story about a professor they don't like being a communist in order to get him fired. But the whole plan backfires when Warren's sister marries that professor.

An evil Siamese twin murders his brother's wife, but the state does not execute him as it would mean the death of the good one. The good one finally commits suicide to halt the evil of the other.

A detective arrests the burglar who murdered his wife. The detective brutally beats the man, hospitalizes him, and hounds him in the hospital about the death he will receive in the electric chair. The detective fixates on his vengeance to such a degree that the killer flees the hospital and is struck by a subway car. The detective is tortured by the uncertainty of whether the killer was electrocuted by the third rail or if the train struck him first.

Marty, a well-known embezzler on the lam, falls for a beautiful gal and uses a false name when introducing himself. However, he later discovers that she knows who he really is, and when she tells him that she wants $25,000 to keep quiet, he strangles her to death. But his conscience bothers him so much that he has an uncontrollable urge to confess the deed to anyone in earshot.

A stranger comes to town to visit a down on his luck boy named Jimmy. The townspeople warn him that they are on the lookout for someone that killed a 19 year old girl and to be careful. A mob beats to death this stranger, in reality a priest, when the man refuses to betray the confession of the killer.

A husband hires a contract killer to trail his wife and murder the man she meets. The woman reconsiders her affair, decides to call it off, and returns to her husband. The husband is glad to have her back before he remembers what he's done. He sees the figure in the door and the flash of the gun. The last thing he ever hears is his wife begging him not to die.

A story told in second person about the victim a hypnotist picks to do his dirty work for a killing after his wife leaves him for another man.

A community is up in arms when Mexican-Americans move to town and form a vigilante group to deal with them. However, one of the bigots murders his own daughter when she marries a Mexican.

A little girl murders her drunken father and frames her uncaring mother for the crime so that she can go live with her nice aunt.

A young man gets a girl pregnant and then murders her by throwing her out of a roller coaster car. The other riders, who hear her screams for help, summon the police. The killer then bolts and buries his incriminating clothes beneath the beach's boardwalk and tries to get a ride home with some girls. They soon cajole him into the surf, despite his protests that he can't swim, but quickly abandon him when they see their boyfriends arrive.

A boxer feels guilty for killing a man in the ring when the man's widow screams at him that he's a 'beast'. He perceives that his hands and face are taking on the appearance of a gorilla but a psychologist tells him that it's all in his mind. He sees a mirror on the street and resolves to look into it. He gaps in horror and then withdraws the pistol he had in his jacket to shoot himself. The store owner is puzzled by the suicide and tells the nearby police officer that he had recently purchased a trick mirror to spruce up business.

A bigot finds out that his life was saved as a child by a blood transfusion from a black man.

A man comes out of an car accident with amnesia and plastic surgery to reconstruct extensive facial burns to be met by a woman who claims to be his lover and that the two of them plotted to murder her husband for his insurance money. He travels to a cabin with her and when he slips and bumps his head, his memory returns. He strangles the woman because he recalls that he is not her lover but actually her husband who had overheard their plans to kill him and got the jump on the other man and switched clothes before getting caught in the fire he set in the car's gas tank.</Summary>
  <Title>Rundown; In the Bag; The Trap; Cadillac Fever!; The Operation; The Assassin; In Character; 4-Sided Triangle; The Pen Is Mightier; A Kind of Justice; The Hazing; ...My Brother's Keeper; Well Trained; For Cryin' Out Loud!; The Confidant; Raw Deal; As Ye Sow...; You, Murderer; The Whipping; The Orphan; Squeeze Play; Upon Reflection; Blood-Brothers; Only Skin-Deep</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ec-archives-shock-suspenstories-3-volume-3/4000-487806/</Web>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Carl Wessler,Jack Oleck,Otto Binder,Carl Wessler,Al Feldstein,Otto Binder,Bill Gaines</Writer>
  <Year>2015</Year>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime,Adventure,Drama</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Collection</Format>
  <Characters>Mr. Farrell (gambler, death),Joe Harris (villain, killer, death),George (casino dealer),Marsha Harris (villain, Joe's wife),Wally (villain, Marsha's lover)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
  <Editor>Daniel Chabon</Editor>
</ComicInfo>