<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>How Low Can You Go, Part II: What About Bob?</Title>
  <Series>Deadpool</Series>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Volume>2008</Volume>
  <Summary>Bob: Agent of HYDRA is back! But his not-so-tearful reunion with Deadpool is cut short by Tiger Shark who, for some reason, just won't get over wanting to cut off Wade's head! What&#237;s the deal with that? Perhaps there's something Bob's not telling Deadpool? The hottest new title on the stands swerves into a new and bigger direction this issue, heading right toward the dark heart of the Marvel Universe! Don't miss out!

Deadpool retrieves Bob's rifle while Bob is being drowning by the hands of Tigershark. When Deadpool got on the docks Tigershark was gone and Bob was still alive in the waters. So Deadpool pulled him on the docks and went to a motel (that Bob payed for). After one of Deadpool's fantasty dreams, Deadpool and Bob eat taco's until Bob pointed the rifle at Deadpool telling him that he's been hired to kill him and Tigershark is on his way. Then Bob said what he really was doing was asking Deadpool for protection because he knows he can't beat him. Deadpool then hid in the bathroom when Tigershark came in. Bob told Tigershark that he killed him and he was in the bathroom. When Tigershark entered the bathroom Deadpool fought Tigershark and won. Bob then told Deadpool that Norman Osborne hired them both to kill him. So Deadpool sent Norman a fax saying he wants 1 billion dollars in the next 12 hours and also said he killed Bob.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-04 15:23:18.  [CVDB151131]</Notes>
  <Year>2009</Year>
  <Month>04</Month>
  <Day>30</Day>
  <Writer>Daniel Way</Writer>
  <Penciller>Paco Medina</Penciller>
  <Inker>Juan Vlasco, Sandu Florea</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marte Gracia, Ra&#250;l Trevi&#241;o</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Cory Petit</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Jason Pearson</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso, Jody LeHeup, Joe Quesada</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-7-how-low-can-you-go-part-ii-what-about-b/4000-151131/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Characters>Black Widow, Bob, Agent of HYDRA, Bullseye, Deadpool, Eric O'Grady, Ghost, Headsman, Norman Osborn, Paladin, Tiger Shark</Characters>
  <Teams>Thunderbolts</Teams>
  <Locations>Avengers Tower, California, New York City, New York State</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="890553" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="667901" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="893920" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="987835" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1031442" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1164802" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="980994" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1062618" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1006110" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="919991" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="705056" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="798310" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="763711" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="801381" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="677056" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="706500" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="868901" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="852129" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="920387" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="754561" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="936639" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="841392" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="644215" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="809796" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="520895" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
