<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Francine,Benjamin Peters,Marie Peters,Katchoo,Frank Peters,Freddie Femur</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digital Chameleon</Colorist>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-44874</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:47:45 [Issue ID 4000-44874] urn:comicvine:4000-44874
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:34:16. [Issue ID 44874]</Notes>
  <Number>14</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>*The day before the now infamous school play. *
Francine dreams of the perfect prom date. She is brought down to earth when a volley ball smacks her right in the face. It puts her on the benches until the end of the game. Katchoo see's Francine with a ruddy cheek a points at who might have done it. Francine isn't sure so Kat pets a boll into the back of  one of the girls. When one of the girls finds it funny Katchoo identifies her as the one who did it and throws a ball full in her face from close up. She runs around impishly. Katchoo gets detention for the rest of the day.  That night Katchoo turns up at Francine's window and finds out that Francine has an older brother Benjamin. they are obviously new friends as Katine tells Fran to call her Katchoo and explains the origin of the nickname.  Night of the play. Backstage Freddie is bored and checking out the girls with a friend. His friend picks Francine, much to Freddie's derision. Katchoo has now been suspended for putting a cherry bomb into a boys locker. Francine gets her curtain call and we see the audiences faces and the round of the ripping material.  Francine is inconsolable at hime when theres a tap on her window again. Fran opens it and a badly beaten Katchoo slides inside.</Summary>
  <Title>Passion Cry</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-14-passion-cry/4000-44874/</Web>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>