<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Disney Masters</Series>
  <Number>18</Number>
  <Title>Walt Disney Uncle Scrooge: Pie in the Sky</Title>
  <Volume>2018</Volume>
  <Genre>Anthropomorphic-funny animals</Genre>
  <Summary>It's Bats, Man!: Donald is a master pest remover, until he meets his match in a bunch of artistic bats.

Snore Losers: Donald has recurring sweet dreams of Scrooge giving him a million dollars. Scrooge has recurring nightmares of giving Donald that same million dollars. A dreamologist has the answer, but will it just make matters worse?

The Bees Have It!: Donald is dead set on having a "proper prideful gentleman's breakfast", consisting of "a spot of tea, a touch of toast, and a dollop of honey". When there is no honey to be found on store shelves, Donald endures great pain and suffering in order to secure some wild honey directly from a hive of many aggressive bees.

Beachhead Bathos: Donald vs. Neighbor Jones in an epic, no-holds-barred sand castle building contest.

Rootin' Tootin' Duck: A myriad of circumstances lead to Donald becoming a hero... as a rodeo clown.

The Amazon Queen: Scrooge has a specific reason for sending Donald (with the boys in tow) to the Amazon to pick up a cursed ancient Amazon necklace, and deliver it to a rich buyer. A reason mysterious enough that the old miser is willing to pay Donald fifty thousand dollars for his services.

Call Off the Wild: Donald tries his hand at Junior Woodchuck animal calls - and wishes he hadn't.

Another Vine Mess: Destitute Donald must contend with a rapidly growing plant, as his house steadily falls apart.

False Economy: Scrooge touts his economic car.

Shooting to the Top: Scrooge takes an unorthodox shortcut to reach the top of a greased flagpole and claim the hundred dollar bill stuck to its top.

Be My Gust: Donald enters a cake-baking contest that is struck by a whirlwind.

Tree's a Crowd: Donald's genteel day with tea and crumpets is continually disturbed by crows and raccoons inhabiting a tree in the duck's yard. The answer? Cut down the tree. But, does anything ever come easy for Donald?

Quick Trim: Scrooge calls a barber for an unusual trim job.

Seafood Blues: Donald hungrily anticipates the food on an ocean cruise, until he boards ship and gets seasick.

The Three B's: Scrooge shows Donald his "Three B" accounting system.

Duel Personalities: Backyard battlers Donald Duck and Neighbor Jones decide to ignore each other - and can't even manage that.

Heavy Duty: A misunderstanding between Daisy and Donald results in Donald putting on a great deal of weight - and suddenly needing to reduce to normal size.

Shaping Up: A run-down Scrooge considers joining a gym but, when he sees the prices, he perks himself up.

The Bright Side: Snowbound in a mountaintop cabin, Donald leads the boys down the steep slopes on a mission for food by using garbage can lids as sleds.

His Money's Worth: Finding himself to be in perfect health, Uncle Scrooge gripes over the amount of medical bills he must pay with no illness or malady to show for it.

Poisoned Palate: Donald briefly entertains the notion of becoming a French chef... VERY briefly.

Lost On a Dog: Uncle Scrooge has the world's only whistling flea, but the flea decides to take a ride on a passing dog.

Tents, Anyone?: Donald and the boys endure many mishaps in their search for the perfect private campsite.

Large Deduction: Uncle Scrooge explains to a tax auditor why he deducts feeding an elephant as an office expense.

Floating Alone: Scrooge tells the story of when he entered the Duckburg hot-air balloon race to Dogalina Island, experiencing a series of slapstick disasters in the process.

Backyard Bet: Donald tries to sucker the boys into mowing the lawn by making a bet, but the boys get to the punchline before Donald does.

Dime Collector: Uncle Scrooge reviews his list of "firsts".

Fly Now---Pay Later: Donald deals with a pesky housefly... in typical Donald fashion.

A Sound Deal: Donald endures much pain and suffering as a door to door salesman for the Blitzkrieg Bugle Works... until he makes one customer very happy.

Tightrope Gag: Donald shows his nephews that "Anybody can walk a tightrope".

A Prickly Relation: Florist Donald finds the perfect office plant for Uncle Scrooge to relate to.

Pie in the Sky: Baron von Strudel, a rival pastry chef from Scrooge's past, schemes to beat Scrooge out of first prize in an antique airplane show.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 22:28:05. [Issue ID 2263422]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>15</Day>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Year>2021</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(september 2021)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Donald Duck,Ms. Snoremore,terrified clown,Roger Lotsagall (famous artist),Huey,Louie,various panicked citizens of Duckburg,Prudence Pettifog,Tasmanian devil ants,bunch of bats,frogs,circus strongman,Titano (the terrible ten foot tall gorilla),ant-besieged homeowner,Dewey</Characters>
  <Writer>John Lustig,William Van Horn,Bill Riling,John Lustig,William Van Horn,Bill Riling</Writer>
  <Penciller>William Van Horn,William Van Horn</Penciller>
  <Inker>William Van Horn,William Van Horn</Inker>
  <Colorist>Susan Daigle-Leach,Digikore,Jo Meugniot,Sanoma,Scott Rockwell,Christos Kentrotis,Katy Llewellyn,Sue Daigle-Leach,Barry Englin Grossman,Hachette,Egmont,David Gerstein,William Van Horn,Susan Daigle-Leach,Digikore,Jo Meugniot,Sanoma,Scott Rockwell,Christos Kentrotis,Katy Llewellyn,Sue Daigle-Leach,Barry Englin Grossman,Hachette,Egmont,David Gerstein,William Van Horn</Colorist>
  <Letterer>William Van Horn,William Van Horn</Letterer>
  <Editor>David Gerstein,Bob Foster,Byron Erickson,Bob Foster,Byron Erickson</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
    <Page Image="67" />
    <Page Image="68" />
    <Page Image="69" />
    <Page Image="70" />
    <Page Image="71" />
    <Page Image="72" />
    <Page Image="73" />
    <Page Image="74" />
    <Page Image="75" />
    <Page Image="76" />
    <Page Image="77" />
    <Page Image="78" />
    <Page Image="79" />
    <Page Image="80" />
    <Page Image="81" />
    <Page Image="82" />
    <Page Image="83" />
    <Page Image="84" />
    <Page Image="85" />
    <Page Image="86" />
    <Page Image="87" />
    <Page Image="88" />
    <Page Image="89" />
    <Page Image="90" />
    <Page Image="91" />
    <Page Image="92" />
    <Page Image="93" />
    <Page Image="94" />
    <Page Image="95" />
    <Page Image="96" />
    <Page Image="97" />
    <Page Image="98" />
    <Page Image="99" />
    <Page Image="100" />
    <Page Image="101" />
    <Page Image="102" />
    <Page Image="103" />
    <Page Image="104" />
    <Page Image="105" />
    <Page Image="106" />
    <Page Image="107" />
    <Page Image="108" />
    <Page Image="109" />
    <Page Image="110" />
    <Page Image="111" />
    <Page Image="112" />
    <Page Image="113" />
    <Page Image="114" />
    <Page Image="115" />
    <Page Image="116" />
    <Page Image="117" />
    <Page Image="118" />
    <Page Image="119" />
    <Page Image="120" />
    <Page Image="121" />
    <Page Image="122" />
    <Page Image="123" />
    <Page Image="124" />
    <Page Image="125" />
    <Page Image="126" />
    <Page Image="127" />
    <Page Image="128" />
    <Page Image="129" />
    <Page Image="130" />
    <Page Image="131" />
    <Page Image="132" />
    <Page Image="133" />
    <Page Image="134" />
    <Page Image="135" />
    <Page Image="136" />
    <Page Image="137" />
    <Page Image="138" />
    <Page Image="139" />
    <Page Image="140" />
    <Page Image="141" />
    <Page Image="142" />
    <Page Image="143" />
    <Page Image="144" />
    <Page Image="145" />
    <Page Image="146" />
    <Page Image="147" />
    <Page Image="148" />
    <Page Image="149" />
    <Page Image="150" />
    <Page Image="151" />
    <Page Image="152" />
    <Page Image="153" />
    <Page Image="154" />
    <Page Image="155" />
    <Page Image="156" />
    <Page Image="157" />
    <Page Image="158" />
    <Page Image="159" />
    <Page Image="160" />
    <Page Image="161" />
    <Page Image="162" />
    <Page Image="163" />
    <Page Image="164" />
    <Page Image="165" />
    <Page Image="166" />
    <Page Image="167" />
    <Page Image="168" />
    <Page Image="169" />
    <Page Image="170" />
    <Page Image="171" />
    <Page Image="172" />
    <Page Image="173" />
    <Page Image="174" />
    <Page Image="175" />
    <Page Image="176" />
    <Page Image="177" />
    <Page Image="178" />
    <Page Image="179" />
    <Page Image="180" />
    <Page Image="181" />
    <Page Image="182" />
    <Page Image="183" />
    <Page Image="184" />
    <Page Image="185" />
    <Page Image="186" />
    <Page Image="187" />
    <Page Image="188" />
    <Page Image="189" />
    <Page Image="190" />
    <Page Image="191" />
    <Page Image="192" />
    <Page Image="193" />
    <Page Image="194" />
    <Page Image="195" />
    <Page Image="196" />
    <Page Image="197" />
    <Page Image="198" />
    <Page Image="199" />
    <Page Image="200" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>