<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Ghost in the Machine Part 2; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;: Down on the Farm</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>24</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Some of Antares' resistance fighters are waiting in the wilderness for a communication from their headquarters. All they know is they're supposed to protect someone against the assassin 9-Jack-9. They finally hear from their contact, but they're in the middle of being attacked by Jack. The team destroys their communicator so Jack can't come through to get them too.

At the base, Zot confronts Jack, who is holding Susan, the daughter of the former president, hostage. Zot manages to use a trick shot to destroy the equipment Jack is using to send his hologram-signal to the base.

Zot grabs Susan and Jenny and flies towards the team in the wilderness. Jack hijacks the electronics on a jet and flies after them. The leader of the team, Sergeant Lucy Chow, shoots the jet down with an explosive arrow.

She welcomes Susan, who is her cousin. Their goal is now to take Suzy to a special room that Jack can't break into. Suzy is important to the rebels as a symbol of the old government, but Suzy remains despondent and doesn't care.

Zot does his best to cheer her up and get her to see the bright side of things. It doesn't fully work but she starts to feel a little more engaged.

On the way to the room, Lucy and Zot argue about whether it is necessary to kill, or feel hatred.

When they get there, Susan sees a strange box outside the room. She opens it and is disintegrated by a massive electric blast. The others, who have worked to hard to help her, don't even see it happen and are in shock.

9-Jack-9 shows up briefly. He explains that the box was connected to an underground cable and he used that to kill her. Then he leaves.

Zot takes Jenny back to Woody's house so she won't be alone. He flies off into the distance and eventually cries on a beach, unable to accept that he failed.

He goes to Max, who says there is a way to beat Jack. He hasn't told Zot until now because he had to be ready. Now Zot is ready to do what needs to be done.

In Down on the Farm, Zot, Jenny, and Peabody crash their aircar. A farmer takes them in while it gets fixed. However, a bank threatens to foreclose on the farm. The farmer hopes to be able to make his payment by putting his cow in a contest. When they wake up, the cow is gone. Zot and Jenny trick their way into the bank headquarters. They find the cow and use their now-fixed aircar to brig it to the contest just in time.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:09.  [CVDB30413]</Notes>
  <Year>1988</Year>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-24-the-ghost-in-the-machine-part-2-the-adventu/4000-30413/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Sgt. Chow, Susan Gallo, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="170975" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="244229" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="233388" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="195140" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="201638" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="193734" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="159253" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="205241" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="196746" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="198394" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="206615" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="191564" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="196378" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="188799" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="198091" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="168942" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="165657" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="135292" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="155944" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="258741" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="244902" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="176076" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="237587" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="187640" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="212914" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="200363" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="172462" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="202357" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="195698" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
