<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Sittin' Around the Kitchen Table; The Heartbreak of the Old Cartoonist; Mr. Wilkins Discusses the Human Condition with Huunruth; Hunting for Old Records; Puzzle Page; Grim Grids; No Way Out; Tootsy Frootsy Funnies; Weirdo Art Section: It's Art for Art's Sake!; Cubist Be Bop Comics; All Meat Comics; Abstract Expressionist Ultra Super Modernistic Comics; Mr. Natural Wants to Talk to You!; Anal Antics; On the Bum Again; Pud; Joe Blow; Freak Out Funnies; They're trying to get me because I bring you the TRUTH!; Morbid Sense of Humor; John Q. Public's Pal Ed Everyman; Sunday Afternoon; The Brat; The Many Faces of R. Crumb; The Adventures of R. Crumb Himself; Let's Eat!; Keep on Truckin'; Why oh why oh why the Hell Am I in Motor City; Help Build a Better America!; Ducks Yas Yas; The Man from Affiganistan; Definetly a Case of Derangement!; It's Cosmic; George Gwaltny; Those Cute Little Bearzy Wearzies; Then on the Other Hand...; Sky-Hi Comics; I'm a Ding Dong Daddy; Head Comix; Whiteman; Ups and Downs; Brombo the Panda; Eggs Ackley- This Kid's a Scream; Adam &amp; Eve - Our First Parents; Just Us Kids!!; Lap O' Luxury; A Short History of America</Title>
  <Series>The R. Crumb Handbook</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-18 00:34:32.  [CVDB412305]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 22:00:04. [Issue ID 943459]</Notes>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Writer>Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb,Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb</Writer>
  <Penciller>Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb,Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb</Penciller>
  <Inker>Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb,Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb</Inker>
  <Letterer>Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb,Robert Crumb,Aline Kominsky-Crumb,R. Crumb</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Robert Crumb</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>MQ Publications</Publisher>
  <Genre>Anthropomorphic-funny animals,Non-fiction,Humor,Biography,Satire-parody</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-r-crumb-handbook-1/4000-412305/</Web>
  <PageCount>12</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Flakey Foont,Mr. Natural</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="34236" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="359918" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="342368" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="676346" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="381400" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="588684" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="428076" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="479120" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="472460" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="443478" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="234328" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="89372" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Doggo and Mode successfully pass off a piece of salvage junk as art.

Random is the word in this series of completely unconnected panels.

Mr. Snoid talks about his residence inside a woman's butt.

Mr. Natural, sick of the city, heads out west. While on the train, a lady who asks him to watch her baby never comes back.

A satirical paranoid rant from Crumb, as he suspects fumes from his ink bottle is actually poison gas planted by a government agent.

Crumb paints himself as being intensely sadistic in this satirical piece.

Crumb draws several different versions of himself.

On a whim, Crumb enrolls in the "National School of Hard Knocks" in order to get some professional training. He winds up getting more than he bargained for.

An H-bomb blows up Mr. Sketchum right after he mails some cartoons to Bertrand Russell.</Summary>
</ComicInfo>