<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Brass Demur,Garrison,Knowlan,Gully,King Vaneer,Maestro,Clavius,Calibretto</Characters>
  <Colorist>Aron Lusen,Chris Lichtner,Liquid!,Christian Lichtner,Joe Chiodo,Liquid!,Christian Lichtner,Aron Lusen,Joe Chiodo</Colorist>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-111950</GTIN>
  <Inker>Adam Warren,Jason Martin,Joe Madureira,Scott Williams,Tim Townsend,Tom Mcweeney,Trevor Scott,Vince Russell,Joe Chiodo,Tom McWeeney,Joe Chiodo</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Richard Starkings,Wes Abbott,Saida Temofonte,Richard Starkings,Comicraft,Wes Abbott,Saida Temofonte</Letterer>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:49:41 [Issue ID 4000-111950] urn:comicvine:4000-111950
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 06:45:49. [Issue ID 95766]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Adam Warren,Joe Madureira,Joe Chiodo,Joe Madureira,Joe Chiodo</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Battle Chasers</Series>
  <Summary>Following the destruction of Skyhold its been reported a number of dangerous criminals have been released. At Outpost Zeta a dark skinned female in scraps of clothing staggers towards into view. the man desert the post despite the warnings that one escapee might be female. She begs them to run... but too late as the squad are rushed but hulking figures and the the outpost destroyed. One guard remains and sees the girl again.. but now shes pale skinned and walking trance like.    In Capital City the king refuses to surrender the city to the escaped criminals of Skyhold as they lay waste to the outer areas, setting fires as they make their point.Gully's reunion with her fathers friend Garrison does not go well as she see him as the one who deserted her family. Reflecting on his past at his wifes grave Garrison is visited by Maestro, who delivers news of Capital city, and they fight over issues in their past. Garrison falls against the monument to his departed wife and the cross stone splits and reveals his sword encased inside.   Knolan and his robot friend have reached Capital City and soon join the battle against the attackers. Gully comes across the pale woman and notices the wide bracelet on her arm. She calls it pretty with its red stones.. as the woman begs her to leave... and within moments she is transformed into a huge demonic creature who refers to the bracelet as Bulgrim's Prison and shes curse for eternity by it.  Meanwhile Garrison cuts his hair.. and prepares to return to his soldiering past as he asks forgiveness of his wife.</Summary>
  <Teams>Golems,Battle Chasers</Teams>
  <Volume>1998</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/battle-chasers-4/4000-111950/</Web>
  <Writer>Joe Madureira,Munier Sharrieff,Joe Madureira,Munier Sharrieff</Writer>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Joe Madureira,Liquid!,Ryan Kinnaird,Tom Mcweeney</CoverArtist>
  <Title>Red Monika</Title>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Editor>Scott Dunbier</Editor>
</ComicInfo>