<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Love and Rockets</Series>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Web>https://www.comics.org/issue/1997682</Web>
  <Summary>This is volume four in the series. Uses the same oversize magazine format as volume one.

Vol. 1- 1982-1996 (50 issues in magazine format)
Vol. 2- 2001-2007 (20 issues in standard US comic book periodical format)
Vol. 3- 2008-2016 (8 issues as Love and Rockets: New Stories in trade paperback format)

Comes with at least one cover variant per issue available exclusively from the publisher. Each variant has its own individual front &amp; back cover.US comic book store release date 2019-07-17.In no Particular Order: The characters namecheck a wide variety of classic tunes as Hector takes pride in the good taste he's imprinted on his daughter. Includes a large playlist for both Hector and Killer.

Animus!: Merlon takes possession of the See Stone now that Lumina has brought it back. Later on however it explodes, setting Animus free.

Fast Bath: Fritz's (as always) debased relationship with Scott continues. Pipo tells him to say he loves her in order to get her to drop him. Now married to her for the third time, he does as asked. She drops him and later he dies of cardiac arrest.

Diva: Part-time music critic Hector writes a negative review of his daughter Killer's live gig without recognizing who she was.

And Another Punk Rock Reunion: Guadalupe and Steve hold a punk rock reunion party as all three iterations of the Love and Rockets band play. Fritz reprises her degrading relationship with Scott.

Tonta: Tonta and friends cosplay at the CalCon comics convention as they prepare to go their separate ways for college. Jolena has invited her family to what one of her daughters calls a "Black Widow" dinner but of them only Tonta shows up.

99°: Maggie and Ray in bed post-coitus in a story narrated from Ray's point of view.</Summary>
  <Notes>Scraped metadata from Comixology [CMXDB757571]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev36 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-03-22 15:07:58. [Issue ID 1997682]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Genre>Drama,Fantasy</Genre>
  <PageCount>35</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (Salem-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Title>In no Particular Order; Animus!; Fast Bath; Diva; And Another Punk Rock Reunion; Tonta; 99°</Title>
  <Volume>2016</Volume>
  <Day>24</Day>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Year>2019</Year>
  <Characters>Jason Sterling</Characters>
  <Writer>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime,Jaime Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>Jason Sterling</Tags>
</ComicInfo>