<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294837</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:07 [Issue ID 4000-294837] urn:comicvine:4000-294837
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:14. [Issue ID 136607]</Notes>
  <Number>19</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Title>The Half-Creatures of the Sargasso Sea; Demon of the Pit; The Fiend from Outer Space; The Skid Row Monster</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-19-demon-of-the-pit/4000-294837/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>The Half-Creatures of the Sargasso Sea: Explorer Paul Raymond has set his mind to proving to his colleagues at the club that there are mysteries to be found in the Sargasso Sea. He travels there, encounters a race of fish men and manages to bring back one of the creatures. But Larpo murders the president of the explorers’ club and swims off. Raymond is apprehended for murder and put away in a mental institution.

Demon of the Pit: Two years ago convicted killer Caesar Renard survived a volcanic eruption which buried the prison he lived in. Now he surfaces from his underground hideout to stalk and murder the commissioner who put him into jail. They wrestle atop the volcanic pit and fall to their deaths.

The Fiend from Outer Space: Scientist Martin develops a test machine for rocket flight capable of accelerating with over 10 Gs of gravity. During a test run pilot Major Blake is overexposed and transformed into a brutish creature from a neighboring dimension. Martin learns of the aliens’ plan to conquer earth and destroys his machine by sacrificing himself.

The Skid Row Monster: A hooded figure calling himself Vengeance calls upon down-and-out lawyer Arthur Drake. He pulls Drake out of the gutter and makes him a member of his criminal gang. Vengeance poses as an all-powerful demon, but has only drugged his underlings to believe so. Drake is able to resist and puts an end to the crime spree.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>