<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Beth Smith,Rick Sanchez,Summer Smith,Morty Smith,Peacock Jones,Bernie,Jerry Smith,Barbarica</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ryan Hill,Ryan Hill</Colorist>
  <Day>27</Day>
  <Editor>Ari Yarwood,Robin Herrera</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-541267</GTIN>
  <Inker>CJ Cannon,Marc Ellerby,Marc Ellerby,CJ Cannon</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!,Crank!</Letterer>
  <Locations>Flarbellon-7</Locations>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:01:44 [Issue ID 4000-541267] urn:comicvine:4000-541267
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 14:48:16. [Issue ID 1608286]</Notes>
  <Number>16</Number>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1037452" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1249664" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1263690" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1081589" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1245426" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1270005" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1014641" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1259068" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1193759" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1219121" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1303403" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1352329" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1274195" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1330470" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1208214" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1124954" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1478363" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1432087" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1328072" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1304905" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1584558" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1645731" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1794480" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1322613" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="860518" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1442947" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="132240" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>CJ Cannon,Marc Ellerby,Marc Ellerby,CJ Cannon</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Oni Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Rick and Morty</Series>
  <Summary>Morty is sick and tired of Rick always being a big selfish jerk, so he convinces Rick to go harvest some "space medicine" on an alien planet. They even bring Summer, even though she won't stop crying about having her heart broken or whatever. But while on the planet, they get interrupted by robobros and some heavy-cologne-wearing dude named Peacock Jones, so Morty might have to resort to some truly unspeakable tactics in order to get the medicine and get home safely.

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                                                                  | Creator(s)               | Sidebar Location |
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover                                                         | CJ Cannon &amp; Ryan Hill    | 1                |
 RI    | Retailer Incentive Cover                                              | Troy Nixey &amp; Dave McCaig | 2                |
 RE    | Exceed Comic: A Divison of Jesse James Comics Exclusive Variant Cover | Mady G                   | Missing          |
 RE    | Convention Exclusive Cover                                            | Mariel Cartwright        | Missing          |
SynopsisAfter a harrowing adventure in which Morty has had to scavenge a birthing canal, Morty is fed up and complains about how Rick is selfish and never does anything for others. The two get into a philosophical debate but are sidetracked when they find Summer sobbing in the corner of the garage. After Morty tricks Rick into doing something nice for others, he also convinces Rick to bring Summer along.

Rick takes his grandkids to Flarbellon-7, a vast, empty planet that Rick uses to routinely sleep off hangovers. Summer, still moping, decides to sit out the adventure when Morty tells her that she might have to stick something up her butt. Rick counters this with the task of clubbing penps, seal-looking creatures that have a fluid in their stomachs that can cure nearly anything. As Morty starts swinging, Summer notices other people.

Rick, Morty, and Summer meet Peacock Jones, a spaceman who travels the cosmos with companions. The lucky lady this time around: Barbarica. Barbarica asks if she can kill Rick's group, but Peacock Jones sends her back to the ship. He then explains that he has arranged for a battle for Barbarica in order to get her "excited" and recommends that Rick's group leave before things get tense. Too late, however, as Robobros show up and Barbarica goes into a violent rage. Barbarica seems to have the upperhand until Morty finally clubs a penp, which falls and lands on Barbarica.

With Barbarica gone, the Robobros turn to square off against the rest of the group. Morty knocks one's head off with his shovel and Rick deactivates it, which then deactivates the rest. One glitch, however, is that the remaining Robobros are then set to self destruct. Peacock Jones flees and invites Summer to explore the cosmos with him. She accepts. Rick convinces Morty to put a device up the penp's butt to collect the cure-all fluids. They escape just before the Robobros explode.

As they fly away, Morty congratulates Rick on procuring something to help others. Rick then admits that the fluid also contains a very powers psychotic, so he will be helping others.

*Don't Look a Gift-Horse in the Rick*
Beth is out for a picnic with her dad in some remote location. The day is ruined, however, when aliens resembling horses show up and attack. Rick starts killing but needs Beth's help. As a horse doctor, Beth naturally feels reluctant to do so. Staring down an alien horse she is trying to kill reminds her of an Earth horse she promised to save, yet fails to do in surgery.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-02 14:01:16.  [Issue ID 541267]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-16-the-ricky-horror-peacock-show/4000-541267/</Summary>
  <Tags>Beth Smith,Penps,Rick Sanchez,Summer Smith,Morty Smith,Peacock Jones,Robobros,Bernie,Flarbellon-7,Jerry Smith,Barbarica</Tags>
  <Teams>Robobros,Penps</Teams>
  <Title>Don't Look a Gift-Horse in the Rick</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-16-the-ricky-horror-peacock-show/4000-541267/</Web>
  <Writer>Kyle Starks,Marc Ellerby,Kyle Starks</Writer>
  <Year>2016</Year>
  <Count>61</Count>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>