<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Beacon,Alex,Savage Dragon,Ultiman</Characters>
  <Count>35</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-152289</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:24:33 [Issue ID 4000-152289] urn:comicvine:4000-152289
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 09:38:03. [Issue ID 244942]</Notes>
  <Number>14</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Big Bang Comics</Series>
  <Teams>Knights of Justice</Teams>
  <Title>National Guardians; Ultiman; Venus; Thunder Girl; The Blitz; Agents of B.A.D.G.E.; The Badge</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/big-bang-comics-14-terror-at-times-end/4000-152289/</Web>
  <Writer>Gary Carlson,Gary Carlson</Writer>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Rich Buckler</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Summary>National Guardians: Still traveling uncontrollably through time, The Dragon finds himself back in Chicago on the day he was kidnapped in 1997; but unknown to him, he's now on Earth-B!

Ultiman: Still on Earth-B, Dragon finds himself knocked 59 years into the past, where Ultiman mistakes him for a man from Mars; their misunderstanding leads to a fight which this Ultiman remembered 59 years later (in the previous chapter).

Venus: Still on Earth-B, Dragon winds up in Korea during the war in 1952 and is caught in a land-mine explosion.  Waking up in a hospital, his nurse turns out to be Venus, who is much more understanding and reasonable than most of the male heroes he's had encounters with. They trade info before he moves on.

Thunder Girl: Still on Earth-B, Dragon lands in 1944, where he rescues Molly Wilson from Dr. Binana. He &amp; Thunder Girl trade greetings before he moves on, but Binana sabotages his dimension-hopping machine by unplugging it.

The Blitz: Because Binana unplugged the dimension machine, Dragon makes it to 1964, but is trapped between the dimensions of Earth-B and Earth-A. Blitz and Cyclone are unable to help, but The Blitz of Earth-B manages to "realign" Dragon's vibrations and send him on his way again.

Agents of B.A.D.G.E.: Dragon finds himself at B.A.D.G.E. HQ in 1965, mistaken for a spy out to steal the "Infinity Orb". But before long, both he and The Badge find themselves pulled into the timestream.

The Badge: Dragon &amp; The Badge find themselves millions of years in the future, where they encounter The Time Being, who stole the Infinity Orb from B.A.D.G.E. HQ.  He also finds a room full of multiple Ultimen.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Penciller>Joe Cooper,John Thompson,Dan Preece,Bill Fugate,David Zimmerman,Mark Lewis,Ken Lester,Joe Kingler,Joe Cooper,John Thompson,Dan Preece,Bill Fugate,David Zimmerman,Mark Lewis,Ken Lester,Joe Kingler</Penciller>
  <Inker>Patrick Tuller,John Thompson,Dan Preece,Bill Fugate,David Zimmerman,Ken Lester,Joe Kingler,Patrick Tuller,John Thompson,Dan Preece,Bill Fugate,David Zimmerman,Ken Lester,Joe Kingler</Inker>
</ComicInfo>