<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Jerry Smith,Morty Smith,Summer Smith,Beth Smith,Rick Sanchez</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ryan Hill,Ryan Hill</Colorist>
  <Day>23</Day>
  <Editor>Ari Yarwood,Robin Herrera</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-508953</GTIN>
  <Inker>Cat Farris,Marc Ellerby,Marc Ellerby,Cat Farris</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!,Crank!</Letterer>
  <Locations>Universe 304-X</Locations>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:01:48 [Issue ID 4000-508953] urn:comicvine:4000-508953
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 14:48:25. [Issue ID 1515038]</Notes>
  <Number>9</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1203549" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1271229" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1220880" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1035597" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="865991" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1343408" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1043329" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1115037" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1053475" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1127073" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1242609" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1035923" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="883938" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="837594" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="961830" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="950664" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="926358" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1068979" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1029689" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1279919" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1078203" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1219139" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="987650" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="695023" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="794928" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>CJ Cannon,Marc Ellerby,Marc Ellerby,CJ Cannon</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Oni Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Rick and Morty</Series>
  <Summary>The adventure continues as Rick, Morty and Summer come face to face with the despotic, evil Morty of the Rickless Dimension! Will he succeed in exterminating all the Ricks in the multiverse, or will our plucky heroes find a way to beat the odds and restore order to the Universe? Probably the latter, but we'll see!

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                                                                  | Creator(s)            | Sidebar Location |
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover                                                         | CJ Cannon             | 1                |
 RI    | Retailer Incentive Cover                                              | Maximus Julius Pauson | 3                |
 RE    | Exceed Comic: A Divison of Jesse James Comics Exclusive Variant Cover | Giahna Pantano        | 2                |
Note: The Gromflomites - and by extension, the Galactic Federation - only appear on the Retailer Incentive Cover.

SynopsisSummer sneaks Rick and Morty through town and introduces them to the Resistance, a cell of individuals determined to overthrow Dictator Morty. Rick has a hard time taking the situation seriously so Summer tells the story of the current situation:

Her Morty was a genius and soon rose to power with his command of technology. But, try as he might, Dictator Morty could not send people between different realities, only objects. As such, Dictator Morty sent a non-human assassin (the goo monster), which flushed Rick out and into the Rickless Universe. The plan: Have Rick develop the tool to send humans into other dimensions so as to kill all the Ricks.

Rick is not impressed.

In Dictator Rick's citadel, Morty hears that Rick has been taken into hiding by the Resistance. He orders Beth to put their sleeper agent into action. The sleeper is Jerry, who is to take Rick at any cost and end the Resistance. Jerry's first order of business is to take Morty hostage and try to blackmail Rick into giving himself up. Jerry does this by holding a gun to Morty's head. Jerry blunders the ploy, however, by accidentally shooting Morty. To cover it all up, Jerry goes ahead and blows the Resistance base up.

*Into the Void*
Morty can't sleep due to an existential crisis over nearly dying earlier in the day. Rick takes Morty to the garage and hands him a box that simply lets him experience death. Morty decides against this and he and Rick fall asleep watching another dimensions version of ALF.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-02 14:02:01.  [Issue ID 508953]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-9-the-rickfinity-crisis-part-tw-ric/4000-508953/</Summary>
  <Tags>The Resistance,Universe 304-X,Jerry Smith,Morty Smith,Galactic Federation,Summer Smith,Beth Smith,Rick Sanchez</Tags>
  <Teams>The Resistance,Galactic Federation</Teams>
  <Title>Into the Void</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-9-the-rickfinity-crisis-part-tw-ric/4000-508953/</Web>
  <Writer>Zac Gorman,Zac Gorman</Writer>
  <Year>2015</Year>
  <Count>61</Count>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>