<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Garbage Pail Kids: Trashin' Through Time</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Volume>2023</Volume>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <Summary>The insane minds of Adam F. Goldberg, Hans Rodionoff and Jeff Zapata have joined forces again to bring you the Garbage Pail Kids as you've never seen them before. Dynamite Entertainment and this incredible trio of creators proudly presents give you the continuing origin of the Garbage Pail Kids!Our heroes have been transported through time to the 1980's - where the Garbage Pail Kids rule the world. That's right, Garbage Pail Kids are the dominant species on earth, and normal humans have been subjugated and are forced to live as outcasts from society. It's Planet of the Garbage Pail Kids we continue "Trashin' Through Time!! Issue #5: It all ends here! Adam Bomb and the Kommandos are cornered by a zombie horde and there's no way out. That is, until they discover that Dead Ted can speak zombie! The GPK zombies form an alliance with our heroes to take down Nasty Nick. Our heroes then learn a shocking twist and you have to see it to believe it! Featuring 4 incredible covers by Jeff Zapata, Tom Bunk, Robert Jimenez and a classic GPK Trading Card image, presented on cardstock! Plus: Each issue is polybagged with a special GPK Trading Card!</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Metron on 2024-07-03 07:26:17. [Issue ID 90783]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <AgeRating>Everyone</AgeRating>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>