<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>New Love</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Title>Drink, Fucker!; Mosquito; Who Cares About Love?; Equinox, Jr.; You Don't Change a Person's Mind, He Just Stops Arguing; Father's Day; Kidney Stoned; Are the Kids All Right?; The Fights; The Love Swine; Roy; Kidney Stoned Again</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Genre>Drama,Superhero,Sports,Humor,Fantasy,Biography,Satire-parody</Genre>
  <Summary>Bar philosophy from two friends drinking together.

A murder in the village- a folk tale about how the mosquito was born.

Assorted misunderstandings- Venus thinks she's in love with Carlos the comic book store clerk, but Petra is having a fling with him. Venus leaves the store crestfallen once she catches Carlos and Kat in an embrace. Petra trashes the store in a rage once Carlos tells her they can't see each other anymore.

Fake old-fashioned gag strip.

A father goes in search of his absent teenage daughter.

Wilson is present at a birth.

Two intellectuals in superhero costumes bemoaning contemporary culture.

Events in the life of John Lester Johnson- a six panel sequence focusing on the Jack Dempsey/John Lester Johnson fight from 1916 and its effects on Dempsey's career.

An attempted child kidnapping at a playground.

Roy keeps his spirit and does good.

Venus recounts to Fritz what she thinks she told her about her model boyfriend and how they met.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 23:34:26. [Issue ID 69231]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <ScanInformation>(june 1997)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Two drinkers</Characters>
  <Writer>Gilbert Hernandez,Seth,Gary Groth,Gilbert Hernandez,Seth,Gary Groth</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gilbert Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gilbert Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Gilbert Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Editor>Seth,Gary Groth,Seth,Gary Groth</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>