<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Abby Holland,Swamp Thing</Characters>
	<Colorist>Tatjana Wood</Colorist>
	<Day>30</Day>
	<Editor>Karen Berger</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-261301</GTIN>
	<Inker>John Totleben,Ron Randall,Steve Bissette</Inker>
	<Letterer>John Costanza</Letterer>
	<Month>11</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:59:09 [Issue ID 4000-261301] urn:comicvine:4000-261301</Notes>
	<Number>42</Number>
	<PageCount>23</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="687113" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="450305"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="817279"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="417893"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="400130"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="445674"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="397615"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="417677"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="479170"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="372489"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="374067"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="408837"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="391563"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="411519"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="431965"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="372230"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="397574"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="377242"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="440339"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="452393"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="405956"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="444182"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="393299"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Steve Bissette</Penciller>
	<Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>The Saga of Swamp Thing</Series>
	<Summary>Comics Legend Alan Moore writes part two of this horrifying tale, as a voodoo ritual release ancient memories and violence on the set of a soap opera set on a real Southern plantation, set in the days of slavery.

 

We are underground viewing a corpse in a coffin, the narrator explains that this person is trying to rest but ultimately can't; and so the body moves to get more comfortable but he still cannot sleep. At the plantation the dead slaves buried in the graveyard begin rising and walk to the manor. Alec and Abby are now at the plantation and he senses a pattern buried in the soil and goes to the manor to investigate.

As the enter they discover the actors are in the basement dungeon. Abby walks in and finds them after Wesley has flayed William's skin. When she approaches them Wesley is outraged by her clothes and comments and he stabs at her with the knife in his hand. Back outside, Alec see Alice, an acquaintance of Abby's from work, meet her father as a corpse. Back in the house Abby finds out the knife is really a prop and neither she nor William have been hurt

Upstairs Wesley goes to face the zombies and realize that all of this happened once before. He had shot a woman, and been beaten to death by the angry slaves. The zombies explain that they have risen to demand their freedom so they can rest. Alec intervenes, but Wesley shoots him through the chest, and he falls into a fire. He rises from the fire and runs through the house and it burn to ashes. He manages to jump into the Green and forms a new body.

With the mansion burned to the ground, every one exits from their trance and in shock leave. Angela has woken from the possession but Billy still believes that he has been skinned. Abby and Alec leave noticing that some of the bodies are missing though they hope they have simply been put to rest.

Elsewhere, it appears that some of the zombies didn't return to the earth. Alice's father steals a truck, a manages to get a job as a ticket-booth attendant at a movie theatre.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-19 10:48:46.  [Issue ID 261301]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-saga-of-swamp-thing-42-strange-fruit/4000-261301/</Summary>
	<Tags>Abby Holland,American Gothic,Swamp Thing</Tags>
	<Title>Strange Fruit</Title>
	<Volume>1982</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-saga-of-swamp-thing-42-strange-fruit/4000-261301/</Web>
	<Writer>Alan Moore</Writer>
	<Year>1985</Year>
</ComicInfo>