<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Part 3 of 3; Pellucidar: Dark of the Sun Part 3 of 3</Title>
  <Series>Carson of Venus: The Eye of Amtor</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Volume>2020</Volume>
  <Summary>Regular SolicitThe official comics prequel to Matt Betts' upcoming Edgar Rice Burroughs Universe novel "Carson of Venus: Edge of All Worlds" concludes! To save the lives of their friends Ero Shan and Nalte, the intrepid Carson Napier and Princess Duare travel to the forbidden Mountains of the Clouds to gather the last piece of the puzzle that will appease an evil ruler. But this might be the brave couple's final mission, because their objective is to collect the mirror-like scales of a huge, dragon-like creature that lurks in the blackness of the mountains' caves! It's an edge-of-your-seat adventure with two of Edgar Rice Burroughs' best-loved characters, written by Matt Betts and Mike Wolfer and gorgeously illustrated by Vincenzo Carratu. Then, the adventure of explorers Jason Gridley and Victory Harben at the Earth's core concludes in Part Three of "Pellucidar: Dark of the Sun," written by novelist Christopher Paul Carey and artist Mike Wolfer! Carson of Venus Eye of Amtor #3 is available with two covers - Main by Vincenzo Carratu and a limited edition 1 in 350 Pulp cover, also by Carratu.

Limited Edition SolicitKeep up with the awesome ERB Universe limited edition pulp line with this rare 350 copy limited edition Pulp Inspired Art cover of Carson of Venus Eye of Amtor #3! Put it under glass with your favorite grading company!

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                                               | Creator(s)                       | Sidebar Location |
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Main Cover                                         | Vincenzo Carratu &amp; Periya Pillai | 1                |
 LE    | Limited Edition Pulp Variant Cover, Limited to 350 | Vincenzo Carratu &amp; Periya Pillai | 2                |
</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-07-06 05:50:33.  [CVDB799914]</Notes>
  <Year>2020</Year>
  <Month>09</Month>
  <Day>17</Day>
  <Writer>Christopher Paul Carey, Matt Betts, Mike Wolfer</Writer>
  <Penciller>Mike Wolfer, Vincenzo Carratu</Penciller>
  <Inker>Mike Wolfer, Vincenzo Carratu</Inker>
  <Colorist>Arthur Hesli, Periya Pillai</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Natalie Jane</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Periya Pillai, Vincenzo Carratu</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>American Mythology Productions</Publisher>
  <Genre>Science Fiction, Action/Adventure, Movies &amp; TV</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/carson-of-venus-the-eye-of-amtor-3-part-3-of-3-pel/4000-799914/</Web>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Carson Napier, Duare, Jason Gridley, Victory Harben</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="985761" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1189924" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1279410" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1330912" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1068530" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1210752" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1285415" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1500373" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1445711" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1218230" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1342662" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1407106" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1452138" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1463620" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1338825" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1395628" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1375895" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1269125" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1204129" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1201813" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1231637" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="989087" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1244349" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1204289" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
