<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Colorist>Chris Blythe,Colin MacNeil,Gary Caldwell</Colorist>
	<Day>24</Day>
	<Editor>Matt Smith</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-164176</GTIN>
	<Genre>Crime,Detective-mystery,Science fiction</Genre>
	<Inker>Carlos Ezquerra,Colin MacNeil,David Roach,Henry Flint,L. Townsend</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Ellie de Ville,Tom Frame</Letterer>
	<Month>7</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:30:45 [Issue ID 4000-164176] urn:comicvine:4000-164176</Notes>
	<Number>1301</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="630048" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="644223"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="550053"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="542122"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="544481"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="518252"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="509871"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="470715"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="486506"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="685210"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="712104"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="724131"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="731875"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="641725"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="646594"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="555531"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="585434"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="493812"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="567131"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="537478"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="596802"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="444702"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="452199"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="478677"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="528574"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="557049"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="759466"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="821958"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="798690"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="759892"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="743810"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="464494"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Carlos Ezquerra,Colin MacNeil,Henry Flint,Laurence Campbell,Staz Johnson</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(july 2002)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Road House Part two: Johnny and Wulf step through a portal at the roadhouse on Portabella into a dimension warp. They fall into a gorge but are caught by giant webs made by arachnivores, which the two fight off before they drop into a body of water. They encounter a range of predators, many of them familiar from Johnny and Wulf's home dimension, in their efforts to return to the portal.

Bison Part One: Chief-of-Police Tozer and Commissioner Hugill arrive at the scene of a shootout with widespread damage at the business premises of Enrique Esposito, an important local businessman and politician. They lead armoured policemen to the office of Esposito's attorney, Edward Cormier, who is being held at gunpoint by police officer, Jack Bison, who had entered the office and searched it without a warrant. Bison believes that Esposito is responsible for his wife's murder. Unhappy with Bison's reckless behavior, Commissioner Hugill fires him but Tozer hopes to turn this into a suspension instead.

Part 2: Vaped!: On the 50th anniversary of the peace agreed between humans and Geeks, Earth was preparing to celebrate the event. However, the Geeks, armed with more advanced technology, reopen the war with a preemptive strike. Corps Command orders ships carrying non-combatants (including retired star-troopers who had fought the Geeks in the last war) to take cover on the surface of the Moon, but they are tracked by the Geeks who land ground units to attack them. When two units of human troops are wiped out, Steve Smith, Jupe and other veterans don combat suits to engage the enemy.

What Lies Beneath Part One: Following a battle, two groups of Souther troops attempt to cross the toxic Khoisin Reservoir in inflatable boats to escape an oncoming Nort force. The reservoir was the scene of an earlier battle where half a million people died - drowned beneath the reservoir's waters. Soon enough, the troops are all picked off one-by-one by water-borne assailants. The remaining group of Southers, which includes a number of wounded, considers its options when no further signal is received from the other groups in the boats. At this point, Rogue Trooper arrives and introduces himself.

Blood &amp; Duty Part Two: After sentencing Gladys Ecks to eighteen months' imprisonment for welfare fraud and shoplifting, Judge Dredd recalls his intention to watch his niece, Vienna Pasternak (whose parents he killed when she was a small child), perform in a play - 'Charles III' - at The Megalopolis theatre. Although he requests three hours of downtime to see the play, he ends up using it to assist two judges pinned down by a rogue citidef (city defense) unit and arrives too late at the theatre to catch up with Vienna. His downtime up, he proceeds to his next case.</Summary>
	<Title>Road House Part two; Bison Part One; Part 2: Vaped!; What Lies Beneath Part One; Blood &amp; Duty Part Two</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-164176/</Web>
	<Writer>Chris Dows,Colin Clayton,Dan Abnett,Gordon Rennie,John Wagner</Writer>
	<Year>2002</Year>
</ComicInfo>