<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Watcher</Characters>
  <Editor>Tom DeFalco</Editor>
  <Format>Digital</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-112838</GTIN>
  <Inker>Al Milgrom,Alan Kupperberg,Bill Sienkiewicz,Bob Budiansky,Bob Camp,Bob Layton,Brent Eric Anderson,Brett Breeding,Dan Crespi,Dave Simons,Eliot Brown,Frank Miller,Frank Springer,Fred Hembeck,Harry Candelario,Jack Abel,Joe Albelo,Joe Sinnott,Marie Severin,Morrie Kuramoto,Rick Parker,Rob Carosella,Ron Zalme,Terry Austin,Tom DeFalco,Brent Anderson,Dave Cockrum,John Romita,Kerry Gammill,Joe Rubinstein,Allen Milgrom,John Morelli,Eliot R. Brown,Danny Crespi,Mark Gruenwald,Jim Salicrup,Larry Hama,Louise Jones,Bob Wiacek,Rick Parker,Fred Hembeck,Dave Simons,Brett Breeding,Al Milgrom,Brent Anderson,Dave Cockrum,John Romita,Kerry Gammill,Joe Rubinstein,Allen Milgrom,Bob Budiansky,Terry Austin,Alan Kupperberg,Jack Abel,Frank Miller,Ron Zalme,Joe Albelo,John Morelli,Bob Camp,Morrie Kuramoto,Eliot R. Brown,Danny Crespi,Mark Gruenwald,Jim Salicrup,Marie Severin,Larry Hama,Louise Jones,Bob Layton,Bill Sienkiewicz,Joe Sinnott,Bob Wiacek</Inker>
  <Letterer>Diana Albers,Fred Hembeck,Rick Parker,Michael Higgins,Terry Austin,Alan Kupperberg,Marie Severin,Diana Albers,Rick Parker,Fred Hembeck,Michael Higgins,Terry Austin,Alan Kupperberg,Marie Severin</Letterer>
  <Locations>Hyboria,Zenn-La,New York City,Savage Land,Space,Ohio,Blue Area of the Moon</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:05:28 [Issue ID 4000-112838] urn:comicvine:4000-112838
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 17:35:19. [Issue ID 36614]</Notes>
  <Number>34</Number>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2444876" ImageWidth="1988" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1941518" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1870031" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1445200" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2029682" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2654146" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1516697" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2106821" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1074844" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1919646" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1966179" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1980766" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1560532" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1984834" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1630594" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1299164" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1920478" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2427516" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1237213" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1674017" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1879263" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1991738" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1928506" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="574952" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2058493" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2285796" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1753836" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1543832" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2004287" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1614719" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1998697" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1988885" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2090388" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1685288" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2220552" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="1560071" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Al Milgrom,Alan Kupperberg,Bill Sienkiewicz,Bob Budiansky,Bob Camp,Bob Hall,Bob Layton,Brent Eric Anderson,Dan Crespi,Dave Simons,Ed Hannigan,Eliot Brown,Frank Miller,Frank Springer,Fred Hembeck,Harry Candelario,Joe Albelo,John Romita Jr.,Marie Severin,Mark Gruenwald,Morrie Kuramoto,Rick Parker,Rob Carosella,Ron Wilson,Ron Zalme,Terry Austin,Tom DeFalco,Brent Anderson,Dave Cockrum,John Romita,Kerry Gammill,Brett Breeding,John Morelli,Eliot R. Brown,Danny Crespi,Jim Salicrup,Larry Hama,Lance Tooks,Mike Carlin,Louise Jones,Ron Wilson,Rick Parker,Fred Hembeck,Dave Simons,Bob Hall,Ron Zalme,Brent Anderson,Dave Cockrum,John Romita,Kerry Gammill,Al Milgrom,Frank Springer,Ed Hannigan,Bob Budiansky,Terry Austin,Alan Kupperberg,Mark Gruenwald,Brett Breeding,Frank Miller,Joe Albelo,John Morelli,Bob Camp,Morrie Kuramoto,Eliot R. Brown,Danny Crespi,Jim Salicrup,Marie Severin,Larry Hama,Lance Tooks,Mike Carlin,Louise Jones,Bob Layton,Bill Sienkiewicz,Eliot Brown,John Romita Jr.</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (AnHeroGold-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>What If?</Series>
  <Summary>Any What If? question you’ve ever had, answered in this jam-packed issue! What If the Invisible Girl dyed her hair? What If Aunt May were Ant-Man? And finally- what If the Watcher were a stand-up comedian? Brace yourselves, True Believers!

All humor issue, featuring wacky alternate realities of the Marvel Universe.

What If the Watcher were a stand-up comedian?

What If the Fantastic Four were bananas?

What If Odin were Peter Parker's uncle?

What If Don Blake and Tony Stark were brothers?

What If Aunt May were Ant Man?

What If Spider-Man married Spider-Woman?

What If Reed Richards took postman Willie Lumpkin up on his offer to join the Fantastic Four?

What If Captain America chose to remain Nomad, the Man Without a Country, instead of taking back the identity of the Star-Spangled Avenger, as he did in the established reality?

What If at some point, Rick Jones decided to leave Captain Marvel in the Negative Zone, never to return to Earth again?

What If Nick Fury had to wear an eyepatch on his right eye instead of his left eye?

What If Ghost Rider had possessed someone else?

What If everyone who'd ever been an Avenger had remained an Avenger?

What If Him married Her?

What If Black Bolt got the hiccups?

What If Galactus ate the Earth?

What If Ka-Zar were a middle-aged accountant instead of a savage?

What If the Hulk were yellow?

What If the Invisible Girl dyed her hair?

What If Power Man were white?

What If the Thing were blue?

What If Captain Marvel hadn't died?

What If Phoenix still lived?

What If Elektra had survived?

What If Dazzler had become a stand-up comedienne instead of a singer?

What If Marvel Comics and the National Endowment for the Art presented Spidey Intellectual Stories?

What If Willie Lumpkin were herald to Galactus?

What If Ghost Rider own a fast food franchise?

What If all the Super-Heroes who now live in New York City moved to Toledo, Ohio?

What If the Watchers in all the realities got together and watched Watchers watching Watchers watching Watchers watching Watchers watching Watchers watching Watchers watching Watchers watching Watchers?

What If Howard the Duck formed his own super-team?

What If Thor had a Swedish accent?

What If Cyclops's energy beams came out of his ears?

What If Wonder Man were a woman -- and Power Man were a girl?

What If Black Bolt were a rock star?

What If Daredevil were deaf instead of blind?

What If the Marvel Production Crew existed in this reality?

What If the Marvel Editorial Crew did, too?

What If Tony Stark had owned an auto plant instead of a weapons factory?

What If Sue Storm had become the Thing?

What If Moon Knight got all his identities mixed up?

What If the Watcher grew hair?

What If Alpha Flight talked like T.V. Canadians?

What If the Silver Surfer, White Tiger, Iceman, and Moon Knight fought Wendigo in a snowstorm?

What If the Black Panther fought the Shroud, Master of Darkness, in a coalmine?

What If Moon Knight had 3 different identities?

What If King Conan were Bing Conan, On the Road to Hyboria?

What If Black Bolt hosted a television show?

What If Bruce Banner's pants didn't stretch when he became the Hulk?

What If you went to the movies and had to sit behind the Leader?

What If Aunt May became a Super-Hero?

What If Reed Richards had not invented unstable molecules?

What If the Hulk married the She-Hulk?

What If Norrin Radd had not volunteered to become the Silver Surfer?

What If Dazzler had decided to become a lawyer?

What If Luke Cage had found the hammer of the Mighty Thor?

What If Doctor Strange were an ordinary magician?

What If Obnoxio the Clown fought crime?

What If Daredevil could see?

What If Thor got a haircut?

What If Spider-Man had married the Black Widow?

What If Iron Man had an eating problem instead of a drinking problem?

What If Dr. Doom had a sense of humor?

What If Galactus needed quick cash?

What If will happen when Stan Lee reads this issue?

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/what-if-34/4000-112838/</Summary>
  <Tags>Wonder Man,Luke Cage,She-Hulk,Ka-Zar,Black Bolt,Black Knight,Thing,Spider-Man,Baron Mordo,Doctor Octopus,Human Torch,Black Widow,Nick Fury,Balder,Recorder,Norman Osborn,Tom DeFalco,Ron Zalme,Redwing,Tigra,Moon Knight,Elektra,Vision,Adam Warlock,Iceman,Watcher,Jean Grey,Moondragon,Blue Area of the Moon,Linda Grant,Iron Man,Doctor Strange,Mike Carlin,Ann Nocenti,Shaman,Fred Mertz,Ohio,Falcon,Stan Lee,S.H.I.E.L.D.,Willie Lumpkin,Jarvis,Silver Surfer,Mantis,Conan,Gladiator (Potter),Wasp,Dormammu,Spider-Woman,Mr. Fantastic,Man-Thing,Beast,Hank Pym,Sasquatch,Shalla Bal,Thor,Guardian,Louise Simonson,Hulk Jr.,Jim Salicrup,Howard the Duck,Asgardian Gods,Wong,Dazzler,Owl,Black Panther,Triton,Scarlet Witch,Hyboria,Zenn-La,New York City,X-Men,Aunt May,Kismet,Aurora,Jocasta,Roger Stern,Rick Jones,White Tiger,Loki,Hercules,Zabu,Space,Quicksilver,Galactus,Aragorn,Kraven the Hunter,Sentinels,John Byrne,Ralph Macchio,The Burglar,Magneto,Shroud,Odin,Terry Austin,Savage Land,Bethany Cabe,Fantastic Four,Sandman,Swordsman,Hulk,Unicorn,Hawkeye,Vulture,Bullseye,Carol Danvers,Dragon Man,Leader,Phoenix Force,Captain Marvel,Ethel Mertz,Invisible Woman,Moon Boy,Northstar,Al Milgrom,Devil Dinosaur,Electro,Phantom Rider,Inhumans,Captain America,Obnoxio the Clown,Medusa,Lockjaw,Daredevil,Avengers,Mark Gruenwald,Marvel Bullpen,Wendigo,Gorgon,Cyclops,Doctor Doom,Mad Thinker,Alpha Flight,Danny Fingeroth,The Watchers,Ancient One</Tags>
  <Teams>Avengers,S.H.I.E.L.D.,X-Men,Alpha Flight,Asgardian Gods,The Watchers,Fantastic Four,Marvel Bullpen,Sentinels,Inhumans</Teams>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/what-if-34/4000-112838/</Web>
  <Writer>Al Milgrom,Bill Sienkiewicz,Bob Budiansky,Bob Layton,Brent Eric Anderson,Danny Fingeroth,Dennis O'Neil,Eliot Brown,Frank Miller,Fred Hembeck,Jim Shooter,Joe Albelo,John Romita Jr.,Mark Gruenwald,Mike Carlin,Roger Stern,Tom DeFalco,Brent Anderson,Mary Jo Duffy,Dan O'Neill,Rick Parker,Michael Carlin,Eliot R. Brown,Alan Kupperberg,Fred Hembeck,Tom DeFalco,Jim Shooter,Mark Gruenwald,Brent Anderson,Al Milgrom,Danny Fingeroth,Roger Stern,Bob Budiansky,Mary Jo Duffy,Dan O'Neill,Frank Miller,Rick Parker,Michael Carlin,Joe Albelo,Bob Layton,Mike Carlin,Eliot R. Brown,Bill Sienkiewicz,Eliot Brown,John Romita Jr.,Alan Kupperberg</Writer>
  <Year>1982</Year>
  <Count>47</Count>
  <Title>What If the Watcher Was a Stand-Up Comedian?; What If the Fantastic Four Were Bananas?; What If Odin Were Peter Parker's Uncle?; What If Don Blake and Tony Stark Were Brothers?; What If Aunt May Were Ant-Man?; What If Spider-Man Married Spider-Woman?; What If Reed Richards Took Postman Willie Lumpkin up on His Offer to Join the Fantastic Four?; What If Captain America Chose to Remain Nomad?; What If, at Some Point, Rick Jones Decided to Leave Captain Marvel in the Negative Zone?; What If Nick Fury Had to Wear an Eyepatch on His Right Eye Instead of His Left Eye?; What If...the Ghost Rider Had Possessed Someone Else?!; What If Everyone Who Ever Had Been an Avenger Had Remained an Avenger?; What If Him Married Her?; What If Black Bolt Got the Hiccups?; What If Galactus Ate the Earth?; What If...Ka-Zar...Were a Middle-Aged Accountant Instead of a Savage?; What If the Hulk Were Yellow?; What If the Invisible Girl Dyed Her Hair?; What If Power Man Were White?; What If the Thing Were Blue?; What If--Captain Marvel Hadn't Died?; What If Phoenix Still Lived?; Elektra Had Survived?; What If Dazzler Had Become a Stand-Up Comedienne Instead of a Singer?; What If Marvel Comics and the National Endowment for the Arts Presented Spidey Intellectual Stories; What If Willie Lumpkin Were Herald to Galactus; What If Ghost Rider Owned a Fast Food Franchise?; What If All the Super Heroes Who Now Lived in New York City Moved to Toledo, Ohio?; What If the Watchers in All the Realities Got Together and Watched Watchers Watching Watchers [repeat "Watching Watchers" to infinity]; What If Howard the Duck Formed His Own Super-Team?; What If Thor Had a Swedish Accent?; What If Cyclops's Energy Beams Came out of His Ears?; What If Wonder Man Were a Woman and Power Man Were a Girl?; What If Black Bolt Were a Rock Star?; What If Daredevil Were Deaf Instead of Blind?; What If the Marvel Production Crew Existed in This Reality?; What If the Marvel Editorial Crew Did, Too?; What If Tony Stark Had Owned an Auto Plant Instead of a Weapons Factory?; What If Sue Storm Had Become the Thing?; What If Moon Knight Got All His Identities Mixed Up?; What If...the Watcher Grew Hair?; What If Alpha Flight Talked Like T.V. Canadians?; What If the Silver Surfer, White Tiger, Night Rider, Iceman, and Moon Knight Fought Wendigo in a Snowstorm?; What If the Black Panther Fought the Shroud in a Coal Mine?; What If Moon Knight Had 3 Different Identities?; What If King Conan Were Bing Conan on the Road to Hyboria; What If Black Bolt Hosted a Television Talk Show?; What If Bruce Banner's Pants Didn't Stretch When He Became the Hulk?; What If You Went to the Movies and Had to Sit Behind the Leader?; What If Aunt May Became a Super Hero?; What If Reed Richards Had Not Invented Unstable Molecules?; What If the Hulk Married the She-Hulk?????; What If Norrin Radd Had Not Volunteered to Become the Silver Surfer?; What If Dazzler Had Decided to Become a Lawyer?; What If Luke Cage Had Found the Hammer of Thor?; What If...Doctor Strange Were an Ordinary Magician?; What If: Obnoxio the Clown Fought Crime?; What If Daredevil Could See?; What If Thor Got a Haircut?; What If Spider-Man Had Married the Black Widow?; What If Iron Man Had an Eating Problem Instead of a Drinking Problem?; What If Dr. Doom Had a Sense of Humor?; What If Galactus Needed Quick Cash?; What Will Happen When Stan Lee Reads This Issue?</Title>
  <Genre>Satire-parody,Jungle,Superhero,Sword and sorcery,Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
</ComicInfo>