<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>David Qin,Katchoo,Emma,Francine</Characters>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-179592</GTIN>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:47:20 [Issue ID 4000-179592] urn:comicvine:4000-179592
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:25:39. [Issue ID 179592]</Notes>
  <Number>25</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>It's a special summer swimsuit issue! Francine and Katchoo hit the beach on the hot white sands of Florida's Emerald Coast. It's summer vacation, and Katchoo is determined to relax and catch a few rays, but between Francine's shrinking bikini, a raging sandcastle war, and an endless stream of love-struck college boys, Katchoo soon finds there is no rest for the weary or diplomatically challenged.

After the heavy and dark issues of late this month Francine, Katchoo and David hit the beach.

Francine bursts into a house in a panic she dashes to the bathroom failing to even notice a small boy sitting on the floor. His mother walks in and asks him what was that noise, he replies it was a wild lady. As Francie exits the bathroom Katchoo comes to the door and tells her this is the wrong house, Francine explains Katchoo wouldn't stop the car on the way there.

Katchoo abandons the others and heads right for the beach as Francine unpacks. later she and David sit on the sand and talk about Darcy and Emma. David recalls how he'd met Katchoo the night she and Emma fled. Francine is coming down to the beach with food when she sees them rolling in the sand and sadly turns and walks back in. They discuss exciting things to do but settle for sitting in the sun all day instead.</Summary>
  <Title>Bikini Beach</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-25-bikini-beach/4000-179592/</Web>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>