<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-56995</GTIN>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:38:08 [Issue ID 4000-56995] urn:comicvine:4000-56995
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 19:01:27. [Issue ID 75642]</Notes>
  <Number>25</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Adventures into Weird Worlds</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-weird-worlds-25/4000-56995/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>30</Count>
  <Title>The Mad Mamba; Two Times Two; A Million Light-Years Away; Nightmare; The Men from Mars</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>The Mad Mamba: Lola schemes to win Jolie's fame. On a trip to Haiti, Lola meets an old woman who offers to show her the voodoo dance. Thinking it's the edge she needs against Jolie, Lola agrees. The woman summons forth zombies who force Lola to dance with them until she dies... then keep dancing.

Two Times Two: The Rroosskkaans refuse to disarm for the United Planets and instead plot to invade their rivals' worlds. Needing more soldiers in order to occupy they invent a duplicator ray which can fashion a double of anyone. Unfortunately they create so many people so quickly the planet falls out of orbit and its inhabitants are flung into space.

A Million Light-Years Away: Ben prepares ships to journey into outer space and it makes him resentful of his life on Earth, imagining the challenges of space. He finally gets to accompany a flight to Uranus, but finds the Uranians have allowed machines to take over their jobs, leaving the species slothful. Ben returns to Earth with newfound love for his life.

Nightmare: A man dreams of creatures holding him prisoner and threatening his life. He awakens in a hospital only to find the same aliens standing over him.

The Men from Mars: Henry sees people around him as Martians. Visiting Dr. Page, he learns Martians invaded Earth by assuming human forms and slowly drove humans to extinction. Page has a mirror which shows his true form. Henry fears he's the only real human left, but when he sees himself in the mirror he realizes he's a Martian. Henry shoots himself in the head.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Characters>Jolie Martin,Lola Britton,Senor Garcia,zombies</Characters>
  <Penciller>Joe Maneely,Paul Reinman,Sam Kweskin,Joe Sinnott,Bill Everett</Penciller>
  <Inker>Joe Maneely,Paul Reinman,Sam Kweskin,Joe Sinnott,Bill Everett</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>