<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Disney Masters</Series>
  <Number>21</Number>
  <Title>Walt Disney Mickey Mouse: The Monster of Sawtooth Mountain</Title>
  <Volume>2018</Volume>
  <Genre>Anthropomorphic-funny animals,Detective-mystery,Adventure</Genre>
  <Summary>The Fantastic Fog [Chapter Three]: The Skipper and Frutch put out to sea with Gyro's fog magnetizer, intending to blind, ground, and plunder shipping. Does Mickey, captive on the pirates' boat with fellow prisoners Goofy and Gyro, have a plan of action?

The Fantastic Fog [Chapter Two]: Mickey, Goofy, and Chief O'Hara find that Gyro Gearloose is mixed-up in a mysterious criminal plot, involving Gyro's invention of a machine that can "magnetize" fog around any metal object. While investigating, Mickey and Goofy are captured by The Skipper and Frutch (who they met in the previous chapter) and are revealed as detectives.

The Fantastic Fog [Chapter One]: Trying to avoid Chief O'Hara, so that they might go on a needed vacation, detectives Mickey and Goofy are mistaken for criminals on the run by two mysterious characters, who lead them into an equally mysterious fog bank where they are invited to join in on a secret crooked plan. Faking an injury, Mickey gets himself and Goofy released from the as of yet unknown caper but with no knowledge of the criminals' identity and location. They quickly deliver the news to Chief O'Hara.

The Threat of the Stone-Eaters [Chapter Three]: Mickey, Goofy, and Dr. Artifact escape from the high mountain on llama-back to warn the authorities of the stone-eating termites and Slunk's evil plans for them. A tense situation ensues as a llama-riding Slunk, with a metal container full of the terror-termites, catches up to our heroes - and an angry group of natives pursues all parties.

The Threat of the Stone-Eaters [Chapter Two]: Mickey and Goofy use a makeshift toboggan, made by mountain water freezing a sleeping bag solid, to slide far enough down the mountain to escape the dangerous freezing temperatures. They find Dr. Artifact to be a prisoner of Slunk and some Andes natives acting as guards. Dr. Artifact has discovered an uncanny species of termite that eat stone instead of wood, and Slunk plans to turn the mites loose on an unsuspecting world, unless his blackmail demands are met.

The Threat of the Stone-Eaters [Chapter One]: Mickey and Goofy are contacted by Professor Cramnoggin to search for Dr. Artifact, a scientist, who has recently become lost in the South American Andes. Once there, they meet up with Slunk who poses as a friend of the missing Dr. Artifact and offers to guide the pair into the mountains. During the night, he abandons Mickey and Goofy in the snows leaving them to freeze to death.

The Monster of Sawtooth Mountain [Chapter Three]: Black Pete uses the excitement and panic over the monster to loot the empty town of Sawtooth Valley. Can Mickey, Goofy, and Frosty O'Hara expose Pete's monstrous hoax?

The Monster of Sawtooth Mountain [Chapter Two]: News of the mysterious monster brings lots of tourists and reporters to the small town of Sawtooth Valley. Frosty O'Hara's handyman Ben spreads the news that the monster is trapped in a box canyon, prompting all the excited, monster-obsessed townspeople to vacate the town to have a look and/or to hunt the monster down.

The Monster of Sawtooth Mountain [Chapter One]: Mickey and Goofy are sent to Sawtooth Valley by Chief O'Hara to investigate a report about a mysterious monster threatening the chief's cousin Frosty O'Hara's winter resort hotel.

Alaskan Adventure [Chapter Three]: Mickey, Goofy, and the chief find that Skulk and Tiny are responsible for the valley's flooding by building a dam on the river just outside the sheer walls of the valley. Tiny is sent through what remains of the tunnel into the valley so that the chief can show him the location of the gold mine. Once Tiny stakes the location and writes down the coordinates, so that Skulk can file a claim, they "promise" to stop the flooding. Mickey has a plan to stop them.

Alaskan Adventure [Chapter Two]: The chief marches Mickey and Goofy (carrying the found totem pole) into a hidden tropical valley heated by volcanic hot springs. Skulk and Tiny follow but are scared off by a crocodile. Mickey and Goofy find they are to be kept as prisoners sentenced to hard labor, so that no outsiders can learn of the tribe's valley and their gold. Mickey tries floating a note out of the valley, but it floats back... because the river is suddenly backing-up with volcanically heated water, which will flood the valley and boil its inhabitants alive.

Alaskan Adventure [Chapter One]: For fishing in Alaska with Mickey, Goofy packs for warmer climes because his great-uncle, Whopper O’Goof, told of a jungle-like area of Alaska with banana trees, crocodiles, and Indians. No-goods Skulk and Tiny, observe Goofy’s odd gear and Skulk recalls Whopper’s oft-told tales of jungles, natives and gold nuggets. They follow stealthily as Mickey and Goofy begin fishing. Goofy’s line snags the carved crocodile head of a totem pole, pulling it out of the river, but, before the villains could move in, a native chief forces the pair to carry the totem pole to an unknown destination.

The Trail to Treasure: Goofy finds a stone with hieroglyphics in his garden. Professor Seezal translates this to be one of a series of buried stones indicating the way to a cache of ancient statues. The trail ends at a barren, rocky island, harboring a fugitive hiding out from the law, who makes things difficult for our heroes.

Pineapple Poachers  [Chapter Three]: The Menehunes of Hawaiian legend help Mickey and Goofy solve the mystery of the pineapple thefts and capture the crooks.

Pineapple Poachers [Chapter Two]: Mickey and Goofy take an outrigger canoe into the Valley of the Lost to determine if the pineapple thefts are the work of the Menehunes of legend, or ordinary crooks. As they paddle into the valley, the plantation foreman George and the taxi driver drop boulders onto the outrigger in an attempt to kill the prying detectives. Mickey and Goofy narrowly avoid death-by-boulder only to find that a torrential storm, combined with the dropped boulders, logs, and brush swept into a sort of dam by the storm, have flooded the valley. As they try to escape the rising tide, they discover... Menehunes!

Pineapple Poachers [Chapter One]: Mickey and Goofy investigate the theft of pineapples on a plantation in Hawaii, where indications point to activity by Menehunes "legendary little men who live and work by night".

Mickey's Strange Mission [Chapter One]: Black Pete's sophisticated cousin Blackstone P. Percival seeks his thuggish relative to inform him of an inheritance of fifty thousand dollars, contingent on his going straight and leading an honest life.

The Moon-Blot Plot [Chapter Three]: Mickey's delaying tactic in the asteroid cluster sufficiently slows The Rover Rogue Boys, allowing our heroes to beat them to the Moon. There, they set a trap for the rapidly approaching villains.

The Moon-Blot Plot [Chapter Two]: The Rover Rogue Boys have a moon rocket built with stolen plans and materials and blast off with the super-spreading black dye to cover the Moon. Gyro builds a makeshift rocket for Mickey, Goofy, and himself to pursue and beat the Rover Rogues to the Moon. When the Rover Rogue's ship moves aggressively against our heroes, Mickey has Gyro head for an asteroid cluster where he plans a delaying tactic to slow the villains' progress.

The Moon-Blot Plot [Chapter One]: Repeatedly foiled when committing their crimes under the shining light of the full moon, The Rover Rogue Boys force Gyro Gearloose to prepare a super-spreading dye with which they intend cover the Moon, blotting out its light.

Mickey's Strange Mission [Chapter Three]: Mickey finally catches up with Pete and prevents him from holding up the miner for his gold, thus preserving Pete's inheritance which would be forfeit unless he reforms for at least a year - and stays reformed to continue getting the money in yearly installments. Once the situation is explained to him, Pete kinda-sorta tries his hand at honest work, but can he walk the straight-and-narrow for the next 366 days? (1960 was a leap year!)

Mickey's Strange Mission [Chapter Two]: While searching for Black Pete, in order to inform him of his pending conditional inheritance, Mickey, Goofy, and Blackstone P. Percival come across a booby-trapped canyon set up to guard a cautious old miner against intruders. Mickey tries warning the miner that Pete is likely lying in wait to rob him of his gold but meets resistance from the unconcerned little miner. For the good of the miner - and Pete, who will lose his inheritance if he commits another crime - Mickey takes matters into his own white-gloved hands.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 22:28:38. [Issue ID 2443125]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>25</Day>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(october 2022)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>police officer,Frutch (henchman),The Skipper,Goofy,Mickey Mouse,Chief O'Hara,Gyro Gearloose</Characters>
  <Writer>Carl Fallberg,Carl Fallberg</Writer>
  <Penciller>Paul Murry,Paul Murry</Penciller>
  <Inker>Paul Murry,Paul Murry</Inker>
  <Colorist>Digikore Studios,Erik Rosengarten,Digikore Studios,Erik Rosengarten</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Paul Murry,Paul Baresh,Paul Murry,Paul Baresh</Letterer>
  <Editor>David Gerstein,Chase Craig,Chase Craig</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
    <Page Image="67" />
    <Page Image="68" />
    <Page Image="69" />
    <Page Image="70" />
    <Page Image="71" />
    <Page Image="72" />
    <Page Image="73" />
    <Page Image="74" />
    <Page Image="75" />
    <Page Image="76" />
    <Page Image="77" />
    <Page Image="78" />
    <Page Image="79" />
    <Page Image="80" />
    <Page Image="81" />
    <Page Image="82" />
    <Page Image="83" />
    <Page Image="84" />
    <Page Image="85" />
    <Page Image="86" />
    <Page Image="87" />
    <Page Image="88" />
    <Page Image="89" />
    <Page Image="90" />
    <Page Image="91" />
    <Page Image="92" />
    <Page Image="93" />
    <Page Image="94" />
    <Page Image="95" />
    <Page Image="96" />
    <Page Image="97" />
    <Page Image="98" />
    <Page Image="99" />
    <Page Image="100" />
    <Page Image="101" />
    <Page Image="102" />
    <Page Image="103" />
    <Page Image="104" />
    <Page Image="105" />
    <Page Image="106" />
    <Page Image="107" />
    <Page Image="108" />
    <Page Image="109" />
    <Page Image="110" />
    <Page Image="111" />
    <Page Image="112" />
    <Page Image="113" />
    <Page Image="114" />
    <Page Image="115" />
    <Page Image="116" />
    <Page Image="117" />
    <Page Image="118" />
    <Page Image="119" />
    <Page Image="120" />
    <Page Image="121" />
    <Page Image="122" />
    <Page Image="123" />
    <Page Image="124" />
    <Page Image="125" />
    <Page Image="126" />
    <Page Image="127" />
    <Page Image="128" />
    <Page Image="129" />
    <Page Image="130" />
    <Page Image="131" />
    <Page Image="132" />
    <Page Image="133" />
    <Page Image="134" />
    <Page Image="135" />
    <Page Image="136" />
    <Page Image="137" />
    <Page Image="138" />
    <Page Image="139" />
    <Page Image="140" />
    <Page Image="141" />
    <Page Image="142" />
    <Page Image="143" />
    <Page Image="144" />
    <Page Image="145" />
    <Page Image="146" />
    <Page Image="147" />
    <Page Image="148" />
    <Page Image="149" />
    <Page Image="150" />
    <Page Image="151" />
    <Page Image="152" />
    <Page Image="153" />
    <Page Image="154" />
    <Page Image="155" />
    <Page Image="156" />
    <Page Image="157" />
    <Page Image="158" />
    <Page Image="159" />
    <Page Image="160" />
    <Page Image="161" />
    <Page Image="162" />
    <Page Image="163" />
    <Page Image="164" />
    <Page Image="165" />
    <Page Image="166" />
    <Page Image="167" />
    <Page Image="168" />
    <Page Image="169" />
    <Page Image="170" />
    <Page Image="171" />
    <Page Image="172" />
    <Page Image="173" />
    <Page Image="174" />
    <Page Image="175" />
    <Page Image="176" />
    <Page Image="177" />
    <Page Image="178" />
    <Page Image="179" />
    <Page Image="180" />
    <Page Image="181" />
    <Page Image="182" />
    <Page Image="183" />
    <Page Image="184" />
    <Page Image="185" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>