<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-327649</GTIN>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T22:01:41 [Issue ID 4000-327649] urn:comicvine:4000-327649
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 02:30:36. [Issue ID 9513]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Stanley Morse</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>03.Key  .Cimmerian32</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Weird Tales of the Future</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/weird-tales-of-the-future-1/4000-327649/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Title>Ten Thousand Years Old!; The Ghouls Who Ruled the World!; The Time Has Come; Survival of the Fittest</Title>
  <Genre>Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>Ten Thousand Years Old!: Jerry Drago and Jill Johnson are abducted by a Venusian Doctor as Earth specimens. The doctor increases their life spans to an indefinite length. Jerry and Jill escape in a stolen rocket and return to Earth. Nobody believes their story, and the rocket disappears. The pair begin to use the Venusian technology they observed to improve the lot of mankind.

The Ghouls Who Ruled the World!: In the year 2042 a group of gangsters are restored to life by a gamma life ray.

The Time Has Come: Alan Moore sets forth on a journey to the Moon in a spaceship designed by Professor Manheim. He is surprised to see another spaceship. It belongs to space pirates led by Jana. Jana has captured Professor Fenrir and his daugher, Desua. Jana tells the High One, ruler of Moon Men, that the prisoners are spies. Fenrir convinces the High One that Jana is lying. The Ruler of Moon Men has Alan Moore fight Jana. The lower gravity of Earth gives him the advantage over Jana. Moore returns to Earth with Jana's ship and Fenrir and Desua in tow, planning to return them to their planet.

Survival of the Fittest: Alpha leads his fellow robots in a peaceful revolt against mankind. Sandy and Doctor Morris's daughter, Arlene, have inadequate records to prove they are human. The general is suspicious of the pair.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Jill Johnson,Jerry Drago</Characters>
</ComicInfo>