<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Sweetie Candy Vigilante</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Volume>2024</Volume>
  <Genre>Comedy,Supernatural,Crime</Genre>
  <Summary>THIS IS FINE... AND DANDY AS CANDY!

Is Pixie questioning a life of candy carnage? Are things all GOOD with Sweetie's resident ninjette? Is she acting BAD in the name of GOOD? What's really on her mind as she gazes into the halo of the Strawberry Ice Moon deep in thought? Moonlight on that and more will be shed....

Sweetie calls a company SWEET MEET to update Candy Wolf, Pixie, Hansel and Gretel, Peter Cottontail, Jack Rabbit, and Honey B. (with Gummee Bear and Tinsel joining on video conference), about the GOOD news that business is growing faster than imagined, and plans for the "Fortress of Sweetness" are nearing completion. That's just Hatchy Milatchy! Soon, the entire world will know the name Sweetie Candy Vigilante!

Also on the agenda, and topping Sweetie's NAUGHTY LIST, is salty nemesis Bart Volgare. Still reeling from the "Sugartown Showdown," he confides to his girlfriend that Sweetie's "fairy tale wash-ups" (as he calls them) wiped out his entire A-Team, leaving him and his now disfigured henchman SUV as the sole survivors. SUV is literally speechless and scarred with a twisted grin on his face, unable to mutter a single word. He's seen some s**t!

Turns out Bart's main squeeze is a high-profile member of the news media, and he's got a scheme to expose Sweetie on live TV for being more than what she may appear to be on her sugary surface. Tales of bullet-eating ice-crystal skulls made from magical snow, exploding jellybeans and grenade easter eggs leave his sanity, or at least his sobriety, in question.

The NYPD learns two mysterious uninhabited islands, long since considered abandoned and dangerous, and within eyeshot of NYC's notorious jail on Rikers Island, have recently been purchased from the city by a "private buyer." Well, well- isn't that NICE!?

THIS ISSUE IS DANDY AS CANDY... DON'T MISS IT!</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-27 10:00:17. [Issue ID 1061054]
Credits from indicia</Notes>
  <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Day>26</Day>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
  </Pages>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/sweetie-candy-vigilante-3/4000-1061054/</Web>
  <Characters>Sweetie</Characters>
  <Writer>Suzanne Cafiero</Writer>
  <Penciller>Thiago Vale</Penciller>
  <Inker>Thiago Vale</Inker>
  <Colorist>Antonio Fabela</Colorist>
  <Letterer>DC Hopkins</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Ivan Tao</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>