<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Meg 470</Title>
  <Series>Judge Dredd Megazine</Series>
  <Number>470</Number>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Summary>We&#8217;re well into the holiday season, so that can only mean it&#8217;s time for Summer Specials to accompany you on your travels. By now I hope you&#8217;ve all picked up the alt-universe 2000 AD Sci-Fi Special, and hitting the shelves right now is the 2024 Misty special, which sees US comics writer Gail Simone craft a trio of chilling tales with artists such as Aly Fell and Carola Borelli. You can take a peak into the creation of this spooktacular issue elsewhere in this typically packed Meg.

We&#8217;ve also got chats with some of the writers and artists behind the new Regened strips, such as Ned Hartley and Mike Walters, and a sneaky peek at the new strips that will be appearing under the all-ages banner. Elsewhere, there&#8217;s a new Dredd thriller courtesy of Ian Edginton and US artist Kevin West, making his debut for the House of Tharg, and another complete Mega-City 2099 tale from Ken Niemand and Tom Foster, joining Armitage, Dreadnoughts and Harrower Squad.

Be here in thirty for the conclusion to all these stories as we wrap up the current roster in time for a special crossover event coming your way in September &#8211; the multiversethreatening Nordland Rising!

*Judge Dredd &#187; Hive (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. This vast urban hell on the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America is home to over 200 million citizens, bordered by the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west and the toxic Black Atlantic to the east. Tensions run a knife-edge and crime is rampant. Stemming the tide of chaos are the Judges. Toughest of them all is Judge Dredd &#8211; he is the Law!

*Armitage &#187; Bullets for an old man (Part 4)*
Brit-Cit, 2146 AD. While the UK equivalent of Mega-City One has its own Judge force, it&#8217;s retained its CID plainclothes division, of which Detective Inspector Armitage was one of its veteran officers. Now a consultant, Armitage hasn&#8217;t lost his surly demeanour and distrust of authority, even when the CID chief is now his long-suffering former partner Treasure Steel...

*Mega-City 2099 &#187; Nu-Yoo (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2099 AD. Before the Judges took complete control of the metropolis, there were two strands of law enforcement &#8211; regular uniformed cops did much of the day-to-day policing, while the helmeted Judges were called upon to pass judgement on certain criminals, vested powers giving them the ability to dispense on-the-spot sentences...

*Judge Dredd &#187; Toxic (Part 3)*
Mega-City One, 2130 AD. This vast urban nightmare on the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America is home to 400 million citizens, every one a potential criminal. With lawlessness rife, only the Judges can prevent total anarchy. These future lawmen are judge, jury and executioner. Toughest of them all is Judge Dredd - he is the law!

*Pandora Perfect &#187; inPerfect Sounds (Part 2)*
Earth, the far future. While the towering starscrapers and flying cars may make this look like some idealised Utopia, crime is still a major problem, and there&#8217;s no felon more wanted than the nefarious Pandora Perez &#8212; burglar, safe-cracker, armed bandit and all-round career criminal. The authorities may think they&#8217;ve finally managed to incarcerate her, but they&#8217;re reckoned without her loyal robot assistant Gort, who&#8217;s succeeded in breaking her out of her cell. With every cop likely to be on their tail, Pandora and Gort are going to have to lie low &#8212; plus there&#8217;s the problem of her ankle shackle, which will explode if she tries to flee...

*Department K &#187; Mecha-City One (Part 2)*
Mega-City One, 2142 AD. Justice Department has many divisions within it tasked with dealing with the various threats that face the metropolis. The psychic personnel of Psi-Division, for example, are at the forefront in the fight against supernatural foes, while TekDiv conducts all manner of experiments and develops advanced weaponry. The mysterious DEPARTMENT K is a branch of the latter, whose brief is to tackle interdimensional enemies that are seeking to break through the walls of reality. Ever since Judge Death&#8217;s appearance, Kirby and her team have been working on ways to keep Mega-City safe from further dimensional incursions...

*Harrower Squad &#187; Urban rotation (Part 3)*
Cal-Hab, 2146 AD. This wild area north of Brit-Cit has become notorious as a dumping ground for the world&#8217;s radioactive waste, and as a consequence much of it outside the major conurbations such as Glascal is an inhospitable wasteland populated by mutant tribes. Patrolling the wilderness are heavy-weapons Judge teams like Harrower Squad...

*DreadNoughts &#187; Nothing to Fear (Part 3)*
USA, 2035 AD. The new Justice Department is still in its early years, with Judges working alongside the police. It&#8217;s proving an explosive transition, with many citizens &#8211; and more than a few cops &#8211; unhappy with these helmeted officers taking to the streets. Boulder, Colorado, has been a recent flashpoint, and now the Judges&#8217; influence is spreading wider...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-09-18 17:50:35.  [CVDB1063396]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>08</Month>
  <Day>20</Day>
  <Writer>David Baillie, Ian Edginton, Kenneth Niemand, Liam Johnson, Michael Carroll, Ned Hartley, Paul Jenkins, Roger Langridge</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gary Welsh, John Higgins, Kevin West, Marco Castiello, Michael Walters, Steve Yeowell, Warren Pleece</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gary Welsh, John Higgins, Kevin West, Marco Castiello, Michael Walters, Steve Yeowell, Warren Pleece</Inker>
  <Colorist>Chris Blythe, Dylan Teague, Jason Millet, John Charles, Sally Hurst</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Jim Campbell, Shawn Lee, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/judge-dredd-megazine-470-meg-470/4000-1063396/</Web>
  <PageCount>132</PageCount>
  <Characters>Detective-Judge Armitage, Judge Dredd, Pandora Perez</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1589329" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1307018" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1220131" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1364754" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1591547" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1491995" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1492614" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1583638" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1311070" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1259527" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1967850" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1588819" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1578236" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1377127" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1323673" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="909737" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1302851" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1184096" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1233044" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1269556" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1138544" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="733592" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="506053" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1078771" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1608874" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="920901" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1236495" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1078248" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1097926" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="732241" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="888955" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="928123" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="800762" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="936488" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="1522201" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="1148683" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="1334205" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="1284586" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="1208457" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="1473218" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="1509005" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="1581753" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="1559474" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="1527376" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="1498721" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="1393800" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="1344534" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="1227400" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="1193326" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="1284339" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="1393050" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="1225420" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="1307068" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="936011" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="1059282" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="750983" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="936307" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="1155361" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="1147422" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="941883" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="873279" />
    <Page Image="61" ImageSize="1432219" />
    <Page Image="62" ImageSize="847704" />
    <Page Image="63" ImageSize="1206435" />
    <Page Image="64" ImageSize="1142836" />
    <Page Image="65" ImageSize="1323955" />
    <Page Image="66" ImageSize="1109263" />
    <Page Image="67" ImageSize="961578" />
    <Page Image="68" ImageSize="1202926" />
    <Page Image="69" ImageSize="1062910" />
    <Page Image="70" ImageSize="1192754" />
    <Page Image="71" ImageSize="1025244" />
    <Page Image="72" ImageSize="1138506" />
    <Page Image="73" ImageSize="1155267" />
    <Page Image="74" ImageSize="1064860" />
    <Page Image="75" ImageSize="1004938" />
    <Page Image="76" ImageSize="926574" />
    <Page Image="77" ImageSize="965194" />
    <Page Image="78" ImageSize="1018154" />
    <Page Image="79" ImageSize="1101826" />
    <Page Image="80" ImageSize="990947" />
    <Page Image="81" ImageSize="946206" />
    <Page Image="82" ImageSize="1042441" />
    <Page Image="83" ImageSize="902986" />
    <Page Image="84" ImageSize="1727742" />
    <Page Image="85" ImageSize="1648741" />
    <Page Image="86" ImageSize="1324009" />
    <Page Image="87" ImageSize="1715639" />
    <Page Image="88" ImageSize="1712627" />
    <Page Image="89" ImageSize="1201083" />
    <Page Image="90" ImageSize="1407387" />
    <Page Image="91" ImageSize="1323018" />
    <Page Image="92" ImageSize="1127031" />
    <Page Image="93" ImageSize="1576882" />
    <Page Image="94" ImageSize="1493914" />
    <Page Image="95" ImageSize="1177830" />
    <Page Image="96" ImageSize="1735614" />
    <Page Image="97" ImageSize="1242733" />
    <Page Image="98" ImageSize="1765398" />
    <Page Image="99" ImageSize="1461600" />
    <Page Image="100" ImageSize="1722631" />
    <Page Image="101" ImageSize="1680377" />
    <Page Image="102" ImageSize="1488348" />
    <Page Image="103" ImageSize="1515401" />
    <Page Image="104" ImageSize="1233556" />
    <Page Image="105" ImageSize="1422605" />
    <Page Image="106" ImageSize="1206703" />
    <Page Image="107" ImageSize="1257948" />
    <Page Image="108" ImageSize="1240816" />
    <Page Image="109" ImageSize="1118721" />
    <Page Image="110" ImageSize="1402342" />
    <Page Image="111" ImageSize="1544492" />
    <Page Image="112" ImageSize="1065377" />
    <Page Image="113" ImageSize="1043880" />
    <Page Image="114" ImageSize="1256900" />
    <Page Image="115" ImageSize="1235421" />
    <Page Image="116" ImageSize="1160141" />
    <Page Image="117" ImageSize="1401798" />
    <Page Image="118" ImageSize="1084142" />
    <Page Image="119" ImageSize="1363620" />
    <Page Image="120" ImageSize="1342020" />
    <Page Image="121" ImageSize="1340515" />
    <Page Image="122" ImageSize="1143336" />
    <Page Image="123" ImageSize="1711832" />
    <Page Image="124" ImageSize="1501331" />
    <Page Image="125" ImageSize="1578046" />
    <Page Image="126" ImageSize="1257553" />
    <Page Image="127" ImageSize="1290767" />
    <Page Image="128" ImageSize="1189923" />
    <Page Image="129" ImageSize="1319769" />
    <Page Image="130" ImageSize="869675" />
    <Page Image="131" ImageSize="1145514" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
