<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Guns Of The Savage Land</Title>
  <Series>Ka-Zar: Guns of the Savage Land</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>1990</Volume>
  <Summary>A naked man wanders out of the Nevada desert, dying of radiation poisoning. Doctor Ronald Franklin calls on Wyatt Wingfoot, an anthropologist, to consult on the case. Wingfoot does his best to learn the man's language, and history, before he dies. Shanna Plunder returns to the Plunder Estate. She is greeted by Zabu, who recognizes her scent. Plunder discovers her husband, Kevin, more colorfully known as "Ka-Zar, The Savage", having difficulty adjusting to the civilized world. Plunder violently fends off her husband, when he tries to rape her. Kevin comes to his senses, and regains his composure, apologizing for his assault.

Wingfoot contacts Plunder. Wingfoot believes the dead man originated from an underground, hidden land, known as "Sibopay". Wingfoot believes Sibopay to be connected to the Savage Land. Wingfoot hires the Plunders, to serve as guides, and consultants, on the journey to Sibopay. Though reluctant, Plunder agrees to take the job. Her husband does not share her reluctance, and very much looks forward to the adventure. Wingfoot uses his contacts, in the Fantastic Four, to secure transportation. Unbeknownst to Wingfoot, the modern world has already found Sibopay. Flying gunships, employed by the Pluto Fuel Corporation, shoot down a flock of Pteranodons.

Returning to Fort Rex, the gunship crew find their commanding officer, LeStrade, viciously punishing one of the men, for alleged criminal conduct. LeStrade has found his place in the strange savage land. Almost immediately upon arriving in Sibopay, Wingfoot crashes the Fantasti-Car, to avoid hitting a dinosaur. Plunder's husband clashes with Wingfoot, over the rightful leadership of their expedition. Plunder is forced to maintain the peace between them. Plunder's husband, and Zabu, fend off an attack by predators. Wingfoot scouts the terrain, while Plunder speaks, privately, with her husband. Plunder agrees to resume calling her husband, "Ka-Zar", providing he consents to respecting Wingfoot.

Plunder fends off Ka-Zar's sexual advances, again, to focus on the expedition. A native tribe from Sibopay surrounds Ka-Zar, Plunder, Wingfoot, and Zabu., Ka-Zar rejoices in seeing tribesmen unsullied by the modern world. Wingfoot is quick to point out the tribesmen's sneakers, and broken English. After recovering the Fantasti-Car, Wingfoot's expedition learns that the tribe is being exploited by the Pluto Fuel Corporation, a company owned by Ka-Zar. Enraged, Ka-Zar usurps leadership of the tribe, to wage war on the corporation. Wingfoot protests. Their argument is tabled when the tribesmen come under attack from the corporation's security forces.

After the security patrol has been dealt with, the tribe rallies around Ka-Zar, Wingfoot is disturbed by how quickly Ka-Zar has brought out the tribesmen's aggression. LeStrade murders several tribesmen, in retaliation for the deaths of his men. Learning of Ka-Zar's presence in Sibopay, LeStrade mobilizes his forces in preparation of an attack. Ka-Zar teaches the tribesmen the ways of war. When Wingfoot protests, Ka-Zar has him beaten, and caged. Plunder again fends off Ka-Zar's sexual advances, this time holding a knife to his throat. Plunder releases Wingfoot. Ka-Zar, leading the tribesmen, storms Fort Rex. A massive firefight breaks out. LeStrade openly challenges Ka-Zar to personal combat.

Wngfoot, and Plunder, stop a sniper from assassinating Ka-Zar. LeStrade is stabbed to death by Ka-Zar. Plunder puts an arrow through the sniper's neck. Wingfoot is dismayed at the tribesmen's possession of guns. Plunder abandons Ka-Zar, refusing to stay with him in Sibopay. Plunder rues the loss of her husband, to the mystique of the newfound Savage Land.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-11-30 18:59:24.  [CVDB122388]</Notes>
  <Year>1990</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Chuck Dixon, Timothy Truman</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gary Kwapisz</Penciller>
  <Inker>Ricardo Villagr&#225;n</Inker>
  <Colorist>Ricardo Villagr&#225;n</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Phil Hugh Felix</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Earl Norem</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Craig Anderson, Tom DeFalco</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ka-zar-guns-of-the-savage-land-1-guns-of-the-savag/4000-122388/</Web>
  <PageCount>61</PageCount>
  <Characters>Ka-Zar, Shanna, Wyatt Wingfoot, Zabu</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>England, London, Nevada, Savage Land</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1126786" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="484925" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="457303" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="575578" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="569318" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="576151" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="590485" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="567277" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="594463" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="682077" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="531958" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="556142" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="561892" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="542536" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="505029" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="566285" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="493294" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="555361" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="516362" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="547717" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="531573" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="637658" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1165930" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="554983" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="568781" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="570660" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="570896" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="567170" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="708154" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="593954" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="644552" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="573472" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="722347" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="1256895" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="610466" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="652343" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="583590" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="589555" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="1166235" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="522872" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="567704" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="614041" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="596840" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="638654" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="666890" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="571313" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="504946" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="458580" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="529715" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="1154577" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="665763" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="579860" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="537044" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="548622" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="581328" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="500550" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="511963" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="501810" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="627550" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="615520" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="633911" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
