<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Captain,Christian Walker,Deena Pilgrim,Retro Girl,Kutter,Flinch</Characters>
  <Count>38</Count>
  <Day>30</Day>
  <Editor>KC McCrory</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-46334</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T19:10:40 [Issue ID 4000-46334] urn:comicvine:4000-46334
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-20 09:01:46. [Issue ID 46334]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Powers</Series>
  <Summary>Heroes glide through the sky on lightning bolts and fire. Flamboyant villains attempt daring daylight robberies. God-like alien creatures clash in epic battle over the nighttime sky. And on the dirty city streets below, Homicide Detective Christian Walker does his job. Detective Christian Walker is a special homicide officer in charge of cases that involve...Powers. What is a cop's job like in a world where Powers are par for the course? And what kind of cop is given the assignment? Find out in the gritty, new crime comic book series Powers from super hot comic writer and EISNER award winner Brian Michael Bendis (Sam And Twitch, Daredevil, Jinx, Batman) and art deco comic artist Mike Avon Oeming (Young Justice, Superman). This on going, hard-boiled crime comic with a mainstream twist is brought to you in startling full color by Pat Garrahy (JLA).

*SPOILERS*
Detective Christian Walker is called in for a domestic dispute. Being a homicide officer, he's not sure why he was called in. It seems a man got in a fight with his girlfriend, threw her out the window, and is locked inside their apartment with her daughter. The woman managed to call the police. When they arrived, the man specifically asked for Detective Walker.

The man inside, Flinch, blames the woman for taking his money and was preventing him from finishing his project. It seems that Walker is getting threw to him. Suddenly there is a loud crash from inside. Walker and other officers bust in and find a huge gaping hole in the ceiling. The girl is safe in another room eating ice cream and watching cartoons.

Flinch had a rocket pack and crash lands outside the building. Walker is not happy. He does not know this man and wants to know why he asked for him. Flinch tells him that another convict, Wolfe, told him that Walker was soft on guys with powers and if he was ever in a bad situation to ask for him. Walker is still pissed. Ready to deliver a blow to Flinch, he is stopped by another detective. He tells him that since it was his collar, he gets to take care of the little girl.

Back at the station, Walker is going around in circles on the phone trying to get a hold of someone from child services to take care of the girl. She responds by asking him what a clitoris is. The girl has quite a mouth on her. She says that her mother's father would smack her around if she spoke out. Her mother gave her freedom to say whatever she wanted.

Popping into his boss' office, he meets his new partner, Deena Pilgrim. It seems she's been reassigned after putting in a request. Walker is told to put the girl in daycare on the third floor.

They get a call to respond to a homicide. Arriving at the scene, they see a costumed female, lying in a pool of blood.</Summary>
  <Title>Who Killed Retro Girl? Part 1</Title>
  <Volume>2000</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/powers-1-who-killed-retro-girl-part-1/4000-46334/</Web>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Writer>Brian Michael Bendis</Writer>
  <Penciller>Michael Avon Oeming,Michael Avon Oeming</Penciller>
  <Inker>Michael Avon Oeming,Michael Avon Oeming</Inker>
  <Colorist>Pat Garrahy</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Brian Michael Bendis,Pat Garrahy</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Michael Avon Oeming</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>