<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Luck of the Irish</Title>
  <Series>Deadpool</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Summary>Banshee recollects the time Deadpool saved his life, then approaches an old teammate to help find the mercenary. Meanwhile, Deadpool's regenerative powers are working... barely. Too bad, because he's not only up against Black Tom's goons, but also the Juggernaut and an old Interpol agent called Danny Peyer.

SynopsisOutside a building belonging to a man named Almadovar, Interpol agents Banshee and Danny Peyer prepare to enter and take Almadovar alive to get intel regarding an Amahl Farouk. Inside they find an infrared security system and Banshee knocks it out with a high screech. Banshee heads out alone and is taken by surprise by Almadovar. Before the criminal can kill Banshee, however, Deadpool charges in and kills Almadovar. Deadpool quickly leaves after telling Banshee that he owes Deadpool a favor for saving his life. Peyer arrives and sees Almadovar dead. Peyer laments the loss, as it will certainly mean a demotion for him.

Years later, Peyer enters his office at Interpol and finds Banshee waiting for him. Banshee asks Peyer for any intel on Black Tom Cassidy's whereabouts and how Deadpool may play into Black Tom's schemes. Peyer promises to help, but only because he sees a chance to get revenge on Deadpool for ruining his career.

In New York, Deadpool wakes up and sees (to his libidinous delight) that Siryn is still with him. He also notes that his hand still has not fully grown back. He focuses on regrowing the hand it is slowly and painfully regenerates. Deadpool remarks that this healing factor is clearly on the fritz. Siryn explains that she is only sticking around so that she can find out what her uncle wants with Deadpool. Unbeknownst to the two, one of Black Tom's soldiers is spying and relaying video to Black Tom.

Elsewhere, Black Tom sees the feed and has a fit, as he was unaware that Siryn was involved. He orders his soldiers to remove her from any battle before taking deadly action against Deadpool. His anger causes his sickness to act up and Dr. Killebrew has to calm Black Tom down. Juggernaut steps in, afraid that Dr. Killebrew is actually hurting Black Tom instead of helping. Black Tom calms his friend down and asks the Juggernaut to collect Deadpool himself.

In New York, Black Tom's soldiers spring into action to capture Deadpool. They are taken by surprise, however, as Deadpool and Siryn were ready for them. Siryn gets her head enveloped by a goo that inhibits her powers and Deadpool has a very large gun put into his face. Deadpool jokes that the Juggernaut is behind the soldiers and uses their confusion to attack and cut Siryn free. Deadpool then hurls himself and Siryn out a window and onto the street below. (Siryn can't fly to save them, as her voice box is a little sore from the goo trap.) Things go from bad to worse when the Juggernaut actually arrives to fight.

Deadpool and Siryn run into a knife shop. The Juggernaut hurls knives and Deadpool shoves Siryn out of the way and, despite his depleted healing factor, takes many knives to his body. Siryn gets her voice back and shatters some knives, but she also shatters the floor and the three fall to the cellar. A large vat of molten metal is just too enticing and Deadpool dumps it all over Juggernaut. This does not stop the Juggernaut. Deadpool and Siryn run outside but are met by Danny Peyer, who orders his backup to shoot Deadpool immediately.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-04 21:45:36.  [CVDB39645]</Notes>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <Month>09</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Mark Waid</Writer>
  <Penciller>Ian Churchill, Lee Weeks</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bob McLeod, Bud LaRosa, Jason Temujin Minor</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dana Moreshead, Mike Thomas</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Richard Starkings</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Ian Churchill</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Bob Harras, Tom DeFalco</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-sins-of-the-past-2-luck-of-the-irish/4000-39645/</Web>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Characters>Almadovar, Banshee, Black Tom Cassidy, Danny Peyer, Deadpool, Dr. Killebrew, Juggernaut, Siryn</Characters>
  <Teams>Interpol</Teams>
  <Locations>Manhattan, New York City, New York State</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="733843" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="669664" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="640046" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="742788" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="756044" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="601156" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="691113" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1001997" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="958338" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="957095" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1038915" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1055739" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1084930" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="969281" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1018800" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1055429" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1068139" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="969912" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1048278" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1090384" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="992486" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1380467" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="841103" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="146604" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
