<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Tales Designed to Thrizzle</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Summary>False advertisement for pubic hair stencils from actor Mickey Rourke.

Bambiffpow Jackson applies for a job.

Snake and Bacon travel back in time to investigate bacon smuggling and meet Cassanova.

Picasso objects to having his life story narrated by a hamburger.

A faux ad for the hair-care product Monk-B-Gone.

A faux ad for the Fabulous Nut Bra.

A brief discussion of Depression Era bordellos located in holes in the ground and on blimps.

Robin Hood and King Arthur write a drinking song.

Kip takes a nap.

A professor explains the origins of Easter as rites honoring Jesus's half-brother, Pagus.

A faux ad for sex blimps.

Uncle Billy narrates brief sketches of raccoons, zebras, warthogs, and polecats.

Two tiny hobos move into Mr. Flopears' ear.

The story of the hottest new boy band.

Tips for kids studying Shakespeare and looking for his lost treasure.

A couple of boys run into Big Top on the street.

Sherlock Holmes uses his magnifying glass to burn the vine that Jungle Boy is swinging on.

Prof. Pumpkin sends Pig Boy, his friend, and their dog into space.

Henry gets a modern sculpture.

Drunk Pirate District Attorney is ejected from court.

Einstein devises a race between dogs and salmon.

A recollection of the city overtaking the country.

A recollection of 1930s entertainment.

King Grampa gets ironic revenge on a bird.

Grampa won't eat a restaurant meal.

Grampa enjoys some nonsensical silhouettes.

Grampa drives an amoeba car.

Buzz Aldrin discovers the body of Ted, the radio operator.

Johnny Jett and the Fat Russian pursue a murderer.

Two cowboys have a fistfight over the literary value of comics.

The Mannister can find no cases in which to use his talents.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-30 22:16:17.  [CVDB146126]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 23:40:03. [Issue ID 277971]</Notes>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Writer>Michael Kupperman,Michael Kupperman</Writer>
  <Penciller>Michael Kupperman,Michael Kupperman</Penciller>
  <Inker>Michael Kupperman,Michael Kupperman</Inker>
  <Colorist>Michael Kupperman</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Michael Kupperman</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Michael Kupperman</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Eric Reynolds</Editor>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/tales-designed-to-thrizzle-1/4000-146126/</Web>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <Characters>Cousin Granpa,Pablo Picasso,Sherlock Holmes,Uncle Sam,William Shakespeare,Pagus,Bacon,Snake,Buzz Aldrin</Characters>
  <Teams>Snake 'n' Bacon</Teams>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="996987" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="427415" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="628106" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="582439" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="595959" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="683502" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="673374" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="692981" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="471036" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="664905" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="630152" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="627713" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="418051" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="677617" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="579246" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="592066" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="561619" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="547582" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="539629" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="516925" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="587900" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="594188" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="635926" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="533761" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="612061" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="478865" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="471193" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="664429" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="609104" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="435399" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="575405" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="565815" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="635039" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="576107" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="654228" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="553806" />
  </Pages>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Title>none; none; Snake 'n' Bacon; Picasso His Astonishing Life Narrated by a Hamburger; Do You Suffer from Hair-Monkeys?; Fabulous Nut Bra; Sex Holes and Sex Blimps; none; none; Holiday Frolics; Uncle Sam Speaks his Mind; none; none; Boybank!; Hey!  Kids!  Shakespeare!; none; Part 47; none; none; none; none; Town and Country; Entertainment; Old King Grampa; Cousin Grampa; Silhouette Nonsense Grampa; Amoeba Car Grampa; Murder on the Moon...Again; Murder Visits the Sex Holes!!; Are Comics Serious Literature?; Feeling Frustrated; none</Title>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>