<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>ECHO</Series>
  <Number>20</Number>
  <Volume>2008</Volume>
  <Summary>Annie lives inside Julie, and she's not happy. Annie is determined to stop the army from activating its top secret super collider, and Julie has been drafted for the job. Fortunately, she has the help of Annie's boyfriend, Dillon, and an insider at HeNRI. That makes four against the army. What are the odds?

Julie can no longer refuse to admit Annie is inside her now and she shares so many memories and experiences that are so real to her but knows they were of another womans.

Ivy takes them on a plane trip back to HENRI to gather more Alloy 618 hoping to get more of Annie back to help the out of this mess.

Jack goes home to Ethan and Todd who are packing to leave. They know too much and he cannot let that happen.

Julie and Ivy land their plane well outside th town and see a flare go up, which quickly becomes obvious that its actually a missile headed right for their landed plane. It strikes and knocks both girls unconscious. Hong steps into view with the lower half of his face missing and an electronic voicebox.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-11-27 14:41:41.  [CVDB204276]</Notes>
  <Year>2010</Year>
  <Month>03</Month>
  <Day>19</Day>
  <CoverArtist>Bryan Q. Miller, Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/echo-20/4000-204276/</Web>
  <PageCount>21</PageCount>
  <Characters>Hong Liu, Ivy M. Raven, Julie Martin</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="2122807" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1967136" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1848964" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1633692" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1621222" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1681468" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1463319" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1682758" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1630379" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2001960" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1947608" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1955457" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1618782" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1098215" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1530448" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1885284" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1373483" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1222379" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="536784" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2275419" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="750766" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
