<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Elaine,Gargoyle [Isaac Christians]</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bob Sharen,Dan Green,Bob Sharen</Colorist>
  <Editor>Carl Potts,Jim Shooter</Editor>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comixology:822163</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Dan Green,Mark Badger,Mark Badger</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Ken Bruzenak,Ken Bruzenak</Letterer>
  <Locations>Virginia</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:28:10 [Issue ID 4000-25786] urn:comicvine:4000-25786 urn:comixology:822163
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 14:45:50. [Issue ID 40330]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1484449" ImageWidth="1988" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1628621" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1800504" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1850943" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1638082" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1555591" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1602405" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1749900" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1963214" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2031034" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2034069" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1882313" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1845116" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1708879" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1604002" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1586601" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1679595" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1884411" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1802239" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1632868" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1278449" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1575862" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1997755" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1661493" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1661017" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Dan Green,Mark Badger,Mark Badger</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Digital) (Shadowcat-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Gargoyle</Series>
  <Summary>Duped by the original Gargoyle, Isaac finds himself powerless in his human body and tormented by Germaine inhabiting Elaine’s body!

A host of gargoyles descends upon Blackston, Virginia. The gargoyles lay siege to the town, and desecrate it's churches. Isaac Christians is tormented by the spirit of Germaine, a Parisian prostitute, inhabiting the form of Christian's lost love, Elaine Willoughby. Christians spurns Germaine, and tries to bring his eldritch powers to bear against her, forgetting that he has lost them. Germaine viciously claws Christians' face. Germaine's tirade against Christians is interrupted by the presence of Derwyddon, an immortal Druid.

Derwyddon cows Germaine, then heals Christian's wounds. Germaine flees, only to be stopped by a floral barrier, conjured up by Derwyddon. Christian's spirit finds strength in Derwddon's presence. The gargoyle continue to run rampant in the small Virginia town. Derwyddon reveals his story, the tale of the last Druid. Derwyddon delves into the history, religion, and culture of the Druids. Against the will of his Gods, Hu and Ceridwen, Derwyddon allowed himself to love a woman.

For this transgression, Derwyddon was judged, and cast into the depths of the sea. There, sprites took pity on Derwyddon, and breathing their magic into him, his life was spared. Derwyddon slept, adrift in the sea, for centuries. When he finally awoke, he found the world had greatly changed. Gone were the old Golds, the faerie folk, the world of magic. Christianity had risen up and usurped their place.

In bitterness and anger, Derwyddon gave life to a host of stone gargoyles, that ringed a church, and set them upon the followers of the new religion. Being near Derwyddon reminds Christians of his relationship with another man, Vishnu Dass. After World War I, Christians had wandered the world, seeking enlightenment. Christians became a diligent follower of Vass. After two years of serving Vass, Christians received a letter calling him home, to Christiansboro. Vass encouraged Christians to return home.

For one brief moment, Christians attained the enlightenment that he sought, but as time drew him more distant from Vass, the memory of that enlightenment faded. Christians turned to the occult to reclaim what he had lost, only to, ultimately, lose himself. Derwyddon impresses on Christian that it is their responsibility to destroy the gargoyles. The leader of the gargoyles plays the PIpes Of Pan, transforming the townsfolk into gnomes, undines, salamanders, and sylphs. The music drives them into a Bacchanalian revelry. Derwyddon, Christians, and Germaine, against her will, journey to Blackston, to confront the gargoyles.</Summary>
  <Title>Lost Souls The Druid's Tale</Title>
  <Volume>1985</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/gargoyle-3-lost-souls-the-druids-tale/4000-25786/</Web>
  <Writer>J.M. DeMatteis,J. M. DeMatteis,J. M. DeMatteis</Writer>
  <Year>1985</Year>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Dan Green</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>