<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Wolf,Brother Jonah,Lady Weeds,Gaurav,Swamp Thing [Alec Holland],Capucine</Characters>
  <Colorist>Matthew Wilson</Colorist>
  <Count>42</Count>
  <Editor>Darren Shan,Matt Idelson</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-458570</GTIN>
  <Inker>Javier Pina</Inker>
  <Letterer>Travis Lanham</Letterer>
  <Locations>Louisiana</Locations>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:13:39 [Issue ID 4000-458570] urn:comicvine:4000-458570
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:17:17. [Issue ID 1225575]</Notes>
  <Number>33</Number>
  <PageCount>22</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="2118465" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1367034" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1122949" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1695878" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1844917" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1102960" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1338581" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1659705" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="3403347" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1413332" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1300202" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1190453" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1550247" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1668930" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1238767" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1453383" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="869981" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="896683" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="882634" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="665368" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="3044728" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1312442" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Javier Pina</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Swamp Thing</Series>
  <Summary>Swamp Thing has more enemies than he ever knew – and one of them is someone he called a friend! But once said friend has put a magical hit on you, and a squadron of occult assassins show up on your doorstep, it gets difficult to smooth things over…

 

After having stabbed Alec, he grabs Lady Weeds and threatens to return her to the Green. The Wolf reasons with Alec that placing her back into that emptiness may well kill her. He says that he will not have to worry about her as Brother Jonah and he will watch over her. He also councils Alec to see for himself the state of the Green by making a connection with it. When he does, he finds the Green is in ruins and out of balance. He decides to go out and deal with the problems in the Green and tells the trio to stay at the house.

When he leaves it is revealed that the Wolf and Lady have been plotting to take the avatar body and retake the Green. After what almost happened Lady Weeds is not content with the Wolf. They comment on their dislike for Capucine and Jonah, and then Wolf give Lady a syringe filled with a liquid to give the user immense power. Wolf then goes into explaining how he managed to orchestrate the Sureen and other problems all around the world to keep Alec preoccupied.

In Louisiana Jonah, Capucine, and Gaurav share stories and admire the miniature avatar body Alec has left behind. Jonah and Capucine step off to one side and talk. Jonah expresses his desire for her subtly and Capucine reciprocates. Out in the world Swamp Thing is suddenly attacked by a flying demon. It is explained that the Wolf has made a deal with a demon to attack Alec wherever he goes. Ultimately the demon appears and tells the Wolf and Lady that they are returning his fee as the Swamp Thing is too powerful. Later that night, the Wolf and Lady are discussing possible step to take Alec out, when a frustrated Lady injects Wolf with the serum in the syringe. Beneath them, in another room, Jonah and Capucine have just awoken from an intimate time together and hear noise upstairs. Jonah goes to investigate when his stomach is suddenly spilt open.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-11-19 06:45:11.  [Issue ID 458570]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-33-the-wolf-and-the-lady-part-one/4000-458570/</Summary>
  <Tags>Louisiana,Brother Jonah,Lady Weeds,Gaurav,Alec Holland,The Sureen,Capucine,The Wolf</Tags>
  <Teams>The Sureen</Teams>
  <Title>The Wolf and the Lady, Part One</Title>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-33-the-wolf-and-the-lady-part-one/4000-458570/</Web>
  <Writer>Charles Soule</Writer>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Rated T+ Teen Plus</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>