<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Palestine</Series>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Count>9</Count>
  <Title>Rewind; Handicapped; The Boys, part four; The Boys, part three; The Boys, part two; The Boys, part one; Jabalia</Title>
  <Volume>1993</Volume>
  <Genre>Biography</Genre>
  <Summary>Rewind: Sameh and Joe get hold of a forbidden video that shows amateur footage of the intifada. They wind up going home past curfew on foot.

Handicapped: Sameh details the serious obstacles in developing programs for the handicapped in Gaza.

The Boys, part four: Sacco interviews a seventeen-year-old who was shot by men in Arabic dress. A YMCA program head wonders how the large number of injured youth in Gaza can be integrated into society.

The Boys, part three: Firas, a fifteen year old, details how he got involved with the “Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine” resistance group, and what he experienced after that.

The Boys, part two: Mohamed and Husein relate what changed for them in the first few days of the intifada.

The Boys, part one: Mohamed and Husein retrace for Joe the route the mourners took that marked the beginning of the first intifada in 1987.

Jabalia: Sameh is the perfect host for Sacco as he gives him an intensive tour of the Jabalia refugee camp.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 22:14:59. [Issue ID 645966]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <AgeRating>Mature Readers</AgeRating>
  <ScanInformation>(september 1994)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Sameh's Brother,Joe Sacco,Sameh,Sameh's Friend</Characters>
  <Writer>Joe Sacco,Joe Sacco</Writer>
  <Penciller>Joe Sacco,Joe Sacco</Penciller>
  <Inker>Joe Sacco,Joe Sacco</Inker>
  <Letterer>Joe Sacco,Joe Sacco</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>