<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd,Proteus Vex,Rogue Trooper</Characters>
	<Colorist>Annie Parkhouse,Chris Blythe,Jim Boswell,Jim Campbell,Michael Spicer,Simon Bowland</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Andy Clarke</CoverArtist>
	<Day>26</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1061068</GTIN>
	<Inker>Dan Cornwell,I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,John McCrea,Sinu Senan</Inker>
	<Month>6</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:40 [Issue ID 4000-1061068] urn:comicvine:4000-1061068</Notes>
	<Number>2388</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1109439" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1311688"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1968079"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="2116438"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="2001440"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1955667"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="2107580"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="2055490"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1200346"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1195581"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1141246"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1521189"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="958362"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1121119"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1935671"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1781475"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1560662"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1566309"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1508605"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1435015"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1345953"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1328364"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="989503"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1288809"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1179093"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1338141"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1319738"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1355071"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1124869"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1527907"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1207157"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="839362"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Dan Cornwell,I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,John McCrea,Sinu Senan</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Gaze upon me, The Mighty Tharg, for I am the bringer of Thrill-power - let it sizzle your optics! 

Welcome once again, my Squaxx, to another weekly circuit-smasher, where the zarjazosity explodes from the page and frazzles your senses. Two new stories join the line-up this prog - there’s a complete Dredd thriller from the Niemand and McCrea droids, and I publish the winning story from Thought Bubble script and portfolio competition victors Ed Whiting and Sinu Chandrasenan, the chilling Terror Tale The Essence of the Piece.

Elsewhere, there’s more unsettling intrigue in Brink, high-octane mayhem in Rogue Trooper, and deep-space drama Proteus Vex reaches its penultimate episode - be here in seven for the scrotnig double-length finale!

If you experienced a rumbling in the galactic firmament recently, it’s no doubt because of the wormhole that opened in your star system the other day. Amongst the objects that tumbled through from a parallel dimension were pages from a version of 2000 AD that exists there. So curious was I about them that I’ve decided to publish them in this year’s Sci-Fi Special. Look out for it on 3 July and prepare to be amazed!

*Judge Dredd » Radicalised (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, with the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west and the toxic Black Atlantic on the eastern side. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*Brink » Consumed (Part 11)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Rogue Trooper » Souther Belle (Part 3)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where use of chemical weapons has rendered the atmosphere poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the planet’s pollutants - G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they’re searching for the traitor that sold them out...

*Tharg's Terror Tales » Essence of the piece(Part 1)*
Experience the terrifying side of Thrill-power with these one-off tales from beyond the veil of sanity. Whether they be ghostly goings-on that send shivers up the spine or splatterfests that sear the retina and paralyse the mind, nothing is what it seems in these glimpses of a realm beyond our own. The artist Anagram’s pieces are struggling to sell at auction and her agent Jacob is becoming dangerously frustrated...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 14)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 2388</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2388-prog-2388/4000-1061068/</Web>
	<Writer>Dan Abnett,Ed Whiting,Geoffrey D. Wessel,Kenneth Niemand,Michael Carroll</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>