<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Freddie Femur,Marie Peters,Katchoo,Francine</Characters>
  <Colorist>Digital Chameleon</Colorist>
  <Count>90</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-44786</GTIN>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:47:32 [Issue ID 4000-44786] urn:comicvine:4000-44786
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-07 19:29:36. [Issue ID 44786]</Notes>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Abstract Studio</Publisher>
  <Series>Terry Moore's Strangers in Paradise</Series>
  <Summary>Francie wakes excited to her alarm clock in her neat and tidy little girls bedroom. Katchoo wakes in her messy room on a mattress on the floor and kicks the clock.   Francine busies herself with getting ready. Katchoo has a cigarette in bed.  Fran has a family breakfast and mom sees her off. Kat plays loud music in her locked bedroom, her mother shouts outside the door, she flicks the cigarette on the floor and jumps out the window leaving the stereo on.  Fran's papers get blown out of her hand by Katina on the back of a boys bike.  Freddie reads a poem in class he wrote entitled "The Breast" in a theatrical manor. Katina is asked for her poem, she asks to go last and the teacher indicates not doing her homework entales being sent to the principal for the third time and that would mean suspension. She produces a a solemn poem called "This Mask I Wear" that takes everyone aback.  The play is in rehearsal and Francine's toga is not coving her ample form. Katina sits n the seats watching. Her boyfriend arrives and says theres a rumor she is gay, he teases her and she elbows him in the face.  Later that night Katina taps on Fran's window and is impressed at all her nice things. She tells her shes beautiful, Fran returns the compliment and Katchoo heads home.</Summary>
  <Title>Prosody</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/strangers-in-paradise-13-prosody/4000-44786/</Web>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Writer>Terry Moore</Writer>
  <Penciller>Terry Moore</Penciller>
  <Inker>Terry Moore</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Terry Moore</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>