<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<Colorist>Chris Blythe,Gary Caldwell</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Jake Lynch</CoverArtist>
	<Day>14</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-482754</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,John Burns,Neil Googe,Patrick Goddard,Simon Coleby</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Ellie De Ville,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>3</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:44:04 [Issue ID 4000-482754] urn:comicvine:4000-482754</Notes>
	<Number>1922</Number>
	<PageCount>31</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1182206" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1440320"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1146051"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1140344"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1083825"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1205685"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1189989"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1240669"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1189553"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1166312"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1225020"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1093900"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1079570"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1046120"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1078866"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="3109896"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1282930"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1592297"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="902020"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1423426"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1481973"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1295506"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1025785"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1453546"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1135587"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1360313"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1130886"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1288139"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1348195"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1344962"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="788454"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,John Burns,Neil Googe,Patrick Goddard,Simon Coleby</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Dredd: 300 Seconds [1]

Mega-City One, 2130 AD. This vast urban nightmare on the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America is home to 400 million citizens, every one a potential criminal. With lawlessness rife, only the Judges can prevent total anarchy. These future lawmen are judge, jury and executioner. Toughest of them all is Judge Dredd - he is the Law!

The Order: The Order [12]

Germany, the thirteenth century. Young Anna Kohl always felt her father was a mystery to her, a distant figure that seemed to be part of a select group of knights. Upon his death, she was determined to learn more about the man, and examining his papers has sent her on a journey of discovery, one in which she will uncover the shocking truth behind the cadre of warriors known as THE ORDER...

Survival Geeks: Steampunk'd [5]

Somewhere in the outer limits of time and space, plunging through the planes of reality, is what looks from the outside like a regular suburban two-up two-down, but it is in fact powered by misfiring transdimensional technology. Inside live sci-fi obsessives Clive, Rufus and Simon, plus new housemate Sam, who hasn’t taken kindly to being trapped inside a malfunctioning craft with a bunch of stoners and action-figure collectors...

Savage: Grinders [12]

In 1999, Britain was invaded by the Volgans. When lorry driver BILL SAVAGE learned his family had been killed by a Volgan shell, he began a one-man war against the aggressors. Currently based in an e-bombed London and living under an alias, Savage continues to lead the resistance...

Tharg's 3rillers Present: 1% [2]

Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story – a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre!

Cover: Jake Lynch

Judge Dredd - 300 Seconds (Ian Edginton - Simon Coleby)Savage Book 9 - Grinders (Part Twelve) (Pat Mills - Patrick Goddard)Survival Geeks - Steampunk'd (Part Five) (Gordon Rennie - Emma Beeby - Neil Googe)Tharg's 3rillers Presents 1% (Part Two) (Eddie Robson - I.N.J. Culbard)The Order (Part Twelve) (Kek-W - John Burns)</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 1922</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-1922-prog-1922/4000-482754/</Web>
	<Writer>Eddie Robson,Emma Beeby,Gordon Rennie,Ian Edginton,Kek-W,Pat Mills</Writer>
	<Year>2015</Year>
</ComicInfo>