<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>zombie),Deadpool [Wade Wilson] (Zombie Universe,The Command [Aquarian [Wundarr],The Conquistador,A.R.M.O.R.,Zombies,Siege],Machine Man [Aaron Stack],Jocasta,Portal [Director Charles Little Sky],Dr. Michael Morbius (Zombie Universe,Jennifer Kale</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jean-Francois Beaulieu</Colorist>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Editor>Bill Rosemann,Joe Quesada,Lauren Henry,Lauren Sankovitch</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-140101</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Rus Wooton</Letterer>
  <Locations>Nexus of All Realities,Florida</Locations>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:11:46 [Issue ID 4000-140101] urn:comicvine:4000-140101
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 17:52:18. [Issue ID 543515]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="512359" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="462628" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="502018" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="505455" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="533160" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="528501" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="464018" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="582840" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="531868" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="533554" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="553268" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="502845" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="478190" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="476706" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="459942" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="559795" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="603418" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="479539" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="582194" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="508878" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="542770" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="417753" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="371959" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="414949" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="247756" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Marvel Zombies 3</Series>
  <Summary>Board up Avengers Tower! Lock down the Baxter Building! The ravenous hordes of Marvel Zombies are invading ... the Marvel Universe! That's right, the next chapter of the MZ saga is a non-stop in-continuity gorefest with major implications for at least one Marvel hero! When the super-undead stumble into the MU from the Man-Thing's Nexus of All Realities, all of Florida is quarantined against the zombie plague. Time is quickly running out for a cure, so the Initiative sends a most unlikely group of heroes into the Zombieverse on a desperate mission to find the one item they need before the whole MU is consumed!

*Summary:*
The Command consisting of Aquarian, Conquistador, Jennifer Kale, and Siege are prowling Citrusville Florida at the Swamp Monster Tour grounds. They got reports of zombies in the area including one in a costume. The Command stumbles at the zombie area and all of a sudden a zombie bits Siege in the face. The other Zombies then tear Conquistador's body apart. All of a sudden the zombie version of Deadpool pops out, injuring Jennifer Kale's arms to prevent her from using magic and bites Aquarian on the neck. Jennifer Kale turns on a giant propeller and signals to Aquarian, whom then blasts Deadpool into it which slices him in many pieces. After that Aquarian shields himself as he puts himself into suspended animation to try to purge the infection. The zombie Siege then tries to eat Jennifer Kale but Siege's mechanical body turns on him and destroys his head.

Elsewhere a zombie leaves the swamp only to be killed by Man-Thing.

At A.R.M.O.R. Morbius has become the head scientist. He gets a message from zombie Deadpool and claims that Deadpool lead the Command to the swamp as a trap and that Deadpool or the virus as entered the real world and wants to spread the zombie virus to super humans in order to spread faster. At this point Morbius is trying to find a cure for the zombie virus that came from the zombie dimension which Deadpool escaped from, but he needs blood from a non-bitten person from that dimension to make the cure work.

A.R.M.O.R. director Charles Little Sky then gets Machine Man and Jocasta(who haven't seen each other since they defeated Ulton with the Thing), and both of them transport to the zombie dimension to get the blood they need.

Morbius then goes into a hidden room in the lab. In the lab is the real Morbius beaten up, bound, and being injected with an anticoagulant. The other Morbius turns out to be the zombie version of Morbius who is undercover.</Summary>
  <Teams>Marvel Zombies,A.R.M.O.R.,The Initiative,The Command</Teams>
  <Title>Part One</Title>
  <Volume>2008</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/marvel-zombies-3-1-part-one/4000-140101/</Web>
  <Writer>Fred Van Lente</Writer>
  <Year>2008</Year>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>