<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Shop Till You Drop Dead Part 3</Title>
  <Series>Army of Darkness: Shop Till You Drop Dead</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Summary>Move over Buck Rogers, there's a new time traveling hero in the future and he's taking the fight straight to the 25th century pansies. Thrust thousands of years into the future by his Necronomicon wielding boss, Ash discovers that he has become the medieval primitive among the sky dwellers of Deca City One. To get back to his own time he must recover the mythical Necronomicon Program by traveling to the ruins of Under City and defeating a digital army of the dead. It's A.I. vs. Wiseguy as Ash is sucked into the Necronomicon and faces off against a twisted computerized version of himself.

Ash finds himself in the year 2501 Ad in Deca City One, and he is being attacked by creature called Deaduns, creature that resemble deadites. He is taken captive by Captian Wren Grey and taken back to Doctor Sagittarius. The Doctor tells Ash that there is legend of the necronomicon program hidden deep under Deca City One.

Ash goes to search for it and finds a Computer mainframe is enter the password and gets sucked in to the program. There he battles Evil Ash. Just when it seems he has the upper hand Evil Ash reveals it had all been a trap and Ash unwittingly released an army of Deadites.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-01 13:27:43.  [CVDB111530]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 09:50:13. [Issue ID 304465]</Notes>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Writer>James Kuhoric</Writer>
  <Penciller>Sanford Greene</Penciller>
  <Colorist>Scott Kester</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Bill Tortolini</Letterer>
  <Publisher>Devil's Due Publishing</Publisher>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Humor</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/army-of-darkness-shop-till-you-drop-dead-3/4000-111530/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Evil Ash,Ash</Characters>
  <Teams>Deadites</Teams>
  <ScanInformation>(2 covers) (Digital-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="394284" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="387214" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="362104" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="351094" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="310816" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="257760" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="339144" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="379678" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="367604" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="396494" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="356304" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="445588" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="427900" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="392220" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="311922" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="289602" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="421602" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="361904" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="398906" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="365326" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="314694" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="343288" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="502514" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="417598" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="806424" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>