<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Army of Darkness</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Count>9</Count>
  <Title>Old School Part I</Title>
  <Volume>2006</Volume>
  <Summary>Army of Darkness #5 Old School follows Ashly J Williams after the events of Army of Darkness vs Re-Animator. Why they didn't start back at #1 is up in the air but they still consider it a new volume.

Ash has discovered that Sheila is still trapped in the Mirror Universe and he can't save her but he might be able to see her one more time. Sugarbaby, explains that she has learned that if Ash goes back to the cabin and severs the Deadite's tie to his world. The hard part is he needs to find what's holding the Deadite spirt to the world and cut it and that will close the portal and then the Necronomicon will grant him one boon. When it howls he needs to state the scared words and his wish.

Once he gets to the cabin he makes Sugarbaby stay in the car so he can go it alone. Once inside Ash is forced to kill Linda's possessed corpse, once again. He feels like he has the upper hand but the last scene is Ash standing over the boby of Linda and does not realize there is a horde of Deadites right behind him.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev55 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-30 18:42:43. [Issue ID 111534]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Year>2006</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/army-of-darkness-5-old-school-part-i/4000-111534/</Web>
  <Characters>Ash,Linda,Sugarbaby</Characters>
  <Teams>Deadites</Teams>
  <Locations>Detroit,S-Mart</Locations>
  <Writer>James Kuhoric</Writer>
  <Colorist>Blond</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Bill Tortolini</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Kevin Sharpe,Nick Bradshaw,Sanford Greene</CoverArtist>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>