<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>The Blood Ship; The Corpse That Wouldn't Stay Dead; The Fatal Note!; The Tunnel of Horror; Vision of the Gods</Title>
  <Series>Nightmare</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-23 10:15:17.  [CVDB373600]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 21:37:46. [Issue ID 262139]</Notes>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Penciller>George Tuska,Syd Shores,Everett Kinstler,George Tuska,Syd Shores,Everett Kinstler</Penciller>
  <Inker>George Tuska,Syd Shores,Everett Kinstler,George Tuska,Syd Shores,Everett Kinstler</Inker>
  <Letterer>Ben Oda,Ben Oda</Letterer>
  <Publisher>Ziff-Davis</Publisher>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/nightmare-1-blood-ship/4000-373600/</Web>
  <PageCount>37</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="417310" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="768512" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1140404" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1201554" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1095786" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1252436" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1230316" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1020814" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1022184" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1144824" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1211926" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1116456" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1135858" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1096976" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1230732" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1048084" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1127230" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1229908" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="743026" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="864766" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="879888" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1156548" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1181464" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1137348" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1134032" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1159784" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1134732" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1017016" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="954682" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1209026" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1150054" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1028346" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="1211442" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="1176446" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="3340754" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="684634" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="793512" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>The Blood Ship: The ship the Gloris Dune is christened but at the launch runs over a drunken sailor who curses it at the loss of his hand. Embittered, he signs aboard the whaler and burns her down. Hoping as the only survivor no one will know, he books passage aboard a mysterious whaler and learns it's the ghost ship, with dire consequences for him!

The Corpse That Wouldn't Stay Dead: Tom hates his brother Jeff. They both get caught in a terrible snow storm and find shelter in a log cabin with no food. In desperation they hunt in the storm and Tom trips, accidentally shooting his disbelieving brother. He buries him in the snow outside the cabin only to have him appear in the cabin the following 2 mornings. Found screaming, Tom is locked up in a hospital and ends his life digging up his brother to prove to him he didn't kill him.

The Fatal Note!: Walt and Eve are shipwrecked in a storm. Walt holds onto a spar to keep afloat and Eve drowns, screaming for help, as Walt claims the spar cannot hold them both. Walt meets Morta, who tells Walt he will die in a year unless he tells someone how he let Eve drown. Walt is rescued and gradually falls in love with Eve's best friend but is haunted by images of Eve's face as she was drowning. He tells no one and a year to the date of her drowning, he flies to Paris and his flight goes down in the ocean, whereupon he jumps in to be with Eve.

The Tunnel of Horror: Two bums are scouring the beach and discover a valuable ring, which leads one to kill the other. He then tries to persuade a former fairground colleague to allow him to rejoin the partnership as he now has money. Refusing, the colleague sees that the bum has indeed got money and is setting himself up in competition, and sends the Police round to frighten him. The bum rushes into the Tunnel of Horror to 'see' his murdered victim and dies in the tunnel.

Vision of the Gods: Two photographers film temples in Ceylon and suddenly see a dancing beauty. On return they find everything fine except she does not appear on their film.

</Summary>
</ComicInfo>