<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Florida Man</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Title>Second Stupefyin' Issue!</Title>
  <Volume>2022</Volume>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <Summary>It's a special Florida Retailers Exclusive cover to Mike Baron's outrageous FLORIDA MAN #2! Issue #1 was such a huge hit, we wanted to give retailers who live in the Sunshine State another special edition they can sell to their proud Floridian comic collectors! But we don't stop there, you can be a Florida Man or Woman no matter where you live. Get this special edition while you can!After Gary gets out of jail, his luck begins to change. His lottery numbers come in and he can finally give his gal Krystal a big wedding. The happy couple buy a mansion, luxury SUV, state of the art flamethrowers, and much, MUCH more. But the honeymoon is interrupted by the po-po, causing Krystal to go berserk. Luckily her friend gets it all on a viral video launching Krystal's wrestling career. The hilarious tales continue in this second stupefying issue of Eisner-winner Mike Baron's Florida Man! Florida Man #2 is available with two covers - Main by Elias Martins and Variant by Barry McClain Jr.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-30 08:58:38. [Issue ID 2428470]</Notes>
  <Publisher>American Mythology Productions</Publisher>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
  <AgeRating>Teen</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Mike Baron</Writer>
  <Penciller>Elias Martins,Val Mayerik,Todd Mulrooney</Penciller>
  <Inker>Marcelo Salaza,Val Mayerik</Inker>
  <Colorist>Ichsan Ansori</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Warren Montgomery</Letterer>
  <Editor>Chris Braly</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>