<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Sugartown Showdown</Title>
  <Series>Sweetie Candy Vigilante</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>2024</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-27 12:54:58.  [CVDB1044990]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Metron on 2024-06-27 12:55:34. [Issue ID 107993]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Writer>Suzanne Cafiero</Writer>
  <Penciller>Thiago Vale,Thiago Vale</Penciller>
  <Inker>Thiago Vale,Thiago Vale</Inker>
  <Colorist>Antonio Fabela</Colorist>
  <Letterer>David C. Hopkins</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Ivan Tao,Jeff Zornow,John John Jesse,Josh Howard,Ned Ivory,Nei Ruffino,Neil Camera,Yonami</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>John Cafiero,Joseph Rybandt,Matt Idelson</Editor>
  <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Genre>Risque,Comedy,Horror</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/sweetie-candy-vigilante-1-sugartown-showdown/4000-1044990/</Web>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="3146967" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2331734" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="3257478" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="3435664" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="3238947" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="3896390" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="4337694" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="3818857" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="3661579" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="3560209" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="3582096" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="3468183" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="3285706" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="3317493" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2683814" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2954023" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2753873" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2902430" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="3167294" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="5585452" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="2779179" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="3427816" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="3457945" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="2213415" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="4729054" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="3956544" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="3697315" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="2551983" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="2192596" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="5474248" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1472421" />
  </Pages>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Summary>Sweetie and her Candy Vigilante squad are back to kick off issue #1, Vol 2 of the SWEET new series with an epic "Sugartown Showdown" not to be missed! Together with her shape shifting, licorice-loving lycanthrope, Candy Wolf, and newly 'minted' ninjette warrior, Pixie Stix, Sweetie faces off with 'salty' arch nemesis Bart Volgare and his gang of thugs in the icy, snowy streets of New York City with a violently delicious fury.

So, you have chosen salt? So be it... Blood is spilled, lives are changed, (many ended), as an army of fabled super-naturals and sugar-fueled allies hop into action to scramble bad eggs. Candy Wolf shows the crime syndicate soldiers first-hand (pun intended), what big teeth he has, while Pixie gives her newly gifted nunchucks a maiden battlefield test-spin reducing criminal weaponry to molten scrap metal! Sweetie's signature Jawbreaker gun resurfaces, armed with delicious new ammo (can't you just smell the gingerbread?), but not before she unleashes some brand new sweetly-sinister confections that wash away the naughty and leave a wicked smile on your face-literally! Isn't that NICE?

What does Bart have to say for himself about the disappearance of Sweetie's parents? Will a certain super-charged monster truck fueled by ice cream make the scene? When the candy-coated carnage ends, will the bodies be bagged before the NYC sanitation dept barrels down the block to do their rounds? Pick up the new issue and find out gum-drop!

Includes a FREE MP3 Download debuting a new, never before released "Hatchy Milatchy" track by Osaka Popstar recorded specifically for this issue!

Accept a little sugar in your life... get Sweetie Candy Vigilante #1 because it's season 2 and Sweetie is the only sugar shot-caller in town!</Summary>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>