<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Savior,Vex,Oblivia,Slaughterhouse,Carcass,Serendipity,Voodoo Childe,Rip,Morgan Gallows,Purgatori</Characters>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <Editor>Brian Pulido</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-748196</GTIN>
  <Inker>Justiniano,Ken Branch</Inker>
  <Letterer>Dave Lanphear</Letterer>
  <Locations>Malibu,Los Angeles,California</Locations>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:40:43 [Issue ID 4000-748196] urn:comicvine:4000-748196 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/748196
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 03:04:00. [Issue ID 748196]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Justiniano</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Chaos! Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Omen</Series>
  <Summary>*16 Months Till the End *
Rip fights his possession but still battles with Carcass and Gallows. Childe uses an invisibility spell to enable her to get past Vex and Savior as they plan an attack on Gallows. She arrives ahead of Vex and starts to battle with Serendipity while also informing Vex that she is being tricked. At the Equinox Counsel there is suspicion of their allegiance with Savior being the correct path.  Blake communes with an angelic being who tells him the chosen one is born of angel and wolf. Oblivia visits her drunken mother asking if the man in th photo that gallows had of her is her father. He mother tells her that he is Lou Garou and they dated but he disappeared. Later his sister Serena came with a baby and money and paid her to raise Oblivia as it was his wish before he died that she should.  Serendipity finds Slaughterhouse unconscious and injured and enters his body to save him. While Carcass enters a burning building to save the occupants.  Vex unleashes her chaos powers and Childe battles it with her good magic until Vex's concentration is broken with a punch from Oblivia.  The Police arrive and seeing the mess of burning buildings and battling monsters charge in.  Oblivia embraces the creature she is inside, more than a creature of the night she is a creature of light too and raises a pillar of flame from earth to sky about her that becomes a blast wave that flattens everyone.  Carcass awakes first and takes his friends to safety and Purgatori comes to claim Saviors body.  Two days later in Malibu. Oblivia questions Gallows and he confirms he is probably her father and Serena was a one-night stand, but also a very special person. the others are gathered there and each confirms they wish to stay and join in Gallows' battle. Vex has reverted to the clueless girl she was but knows she is somehow bound up in this all and has a dangerous part to play and is in too.</Summary>
  <Teams>The Chosen</Teams>
  <Title>Conflict</Title>
  <Volume>1998</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-748196/ https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-omen-5-conflict/4000-124732/</Web>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Jason Jensen,Justiniano</CoverArtist>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>