<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Eileen Martin (Kenneth's sister, death),Madam DuBois (villain, death),Kenneth Martin,Miss Blanchard,The Vault-Keeper (host)</Characters>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Albert B. Feldstein</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-100707</GTIN>
  <Inker>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen</Inker>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:57 [Issue ID 4000-100707] urn:comicvine:4000-100707
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:50:45. [Issue ID 223237]</Notes>
  <Number>22</Number>
  <PageCount>37</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="569" ImageSize="32006" ImageWidth="400" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1472" ImageSize="121393" ImageWidth="967" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1452" ImageSize="153634" ImageWidth="947" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1396" ImageSize="123799" ImageWidth="1017" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1352" ImageSize="129095" ImageWidth="1006" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1374" ImageSize="139782" ImageWidth="1027" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1383" ImageSize="145067" ImageWidth="987" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1357" ImageSize="126365" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1420" ImageSize="135709" ImageWidth="999" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1425" ImageSize="128990" ImageWidth="1004" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1437" ImageSize="134869" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1383" ImageSize="120538" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1413" ImageSize="137797" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1420" ImageSize="147746" ImageWidth="1017" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1423" ImageSize="131449" ImageWidth="1006" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1403" ImageSize="136691" ImageWidth="1024" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1464" ImageSize="133546" ImageWidth="1012" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1383" ImageSize="144681" ImageWidth="1006" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1465" ImageSize="155534" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1475" ImageSize="148664" ImageWidth="990" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1460" ImageSize="136251" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1405" ImageSize="126751" ImageWidth="1002" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1356" ImageSize="139244" ImageWidth="977" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1391" ImageSize="129060" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1395" ImageSize="129060" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="1373" ImageSize="116901" ImageWidth="998" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="1413" ImageSize="127404" ImageWidth="1006" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="1383" ImageSize="105282" ImageWidth="1004" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageHeight="1371" ImageSize="132743" ImageWidth="977" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageHeight="1334" ImageSize="124869" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageHeight="1353" ImageSize="120396" ImageWidth="974" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageHeight="1351" ImageSize="120023" ImageWidth="1002" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageHeight="1371" ImageSize="116897" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageHeight="1361" ImageSize="128340" ImageWidth="1006" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageHeight="1420" ImageSize="104583" ImageWidth="977" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageHeight="1485" ImageSize="159319" ImageWidth="1007" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="119554" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Graham Ingels,Jack Davis,Jack Kamen</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Vault of Horror</Series>
  <Summary>Fountains of Youth!: Eileen responds to a newspaper ad asking for a traveling companion for a heavily veiled Madam DuBois, who is traveling abroad, even though her brother Ken is not too happy with the idea. Then she and Madam DuBois board a cruise ship. Unfortunately, Eileen mysteriously passes away, and Ken investigates. A shipboard doctor informs him that Madam DuBois is similar to a human vampire, who prolongs its life by sapping the youth of their victims. By the time the pair get to DuBois' cabin, her next victim is already withering and dying before their eyes!

The Monster in the Ice!: As Gerald Dawson sits as his desk in a shack in the Arctic, Herbert Campbell enters, telling him that their Eskimo guide refuses to take them any further. Dawson goes to see Lomo in his igloo, and the Eskimo tells him of the monster in the ice, and that no one who sees it comes back in their right mind. Dawson &amp; Campbell rig up a dog-sled and go to the site, spot the monster and dig its ice-encased body out and take it back to their shack. They show the body in ice to Lomo and he freezes in fear, especially when he is ordered to chip the body out of the ice! While that is happening, Dawson and Campbell kick back, telling themselves that this whole thing reminds them of Mary Shelly's book about Frankenstein. Suddenly, they hear a scream and a crash, and enter the adjoining room and see the window broken out and Lomo shaking in fear. Now they know the creature must be put back into the ice, so they go out and dig through the ice to water, and they hope to lure the monster into the trap. The monster shows up....jumps into the hole and drags both men down with him. One year later, the U.S. Air Force decides to build a base near that very spot and two airmen happen to spot the bodies trapped in the ice. So......they start digging out the bodies to see what they can determine what happened to them.....

Gone...Fishing!: Max was a noted sport fisherman, but Steven hated the sport, which he considered cruelty to animals. Max outfitted his reel with the latest gadgets and cast into the water. Soon he got a strike and reeled in his beauty. Steven, sick to his stomach, went back to the car and drove off, taking Max's lunch with it. Spotting a candy bar on the beach, he shoved it in his mouth, never noticing the thin, silky, nearly invisible thread attached to it. When Steven returned, he saw the horrible sight of Max bobbing up out of the water and being drawn farther and farther out to sea!

What the Dog Dragged In!: Blind Betty's dog Jerry is hit by a car but cared for by wealthy Roger Cartwright, who returned her dog to her. Betty was happy to have company and invited him back, which he did and they soon grew quite close. One day, as Roger left her house in his car, he didn't see the truck coming from the other direction. Betty sent Jerry after him and day after day Jerry returned without Roger. Until one day Jerry came in with Roger.

</Summary>
  <Tags>The Crypt-Keeper,Frankenstein's Monster,The Vault-Keeper,The Old Witch</Tags>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/vault-of-horror-22/4000-100707/</Web>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Ray Bradbury,Johnny Craig,Al Feldstein,Bill Gaines,Ray Bradbury</Writer>
  <Year>1951</Year>
  <Count>29</Count>
  <Title>Fountains of Youth!; The Monster in the Ice!; Gone...Fishing!; What the Dog Dragged In!</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A.C.M.P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>