<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Frobisher,Kane,The Doctor,Abel Gantz,Draconian warrior,Peri</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-313144</GTIN>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T01:00:34 [Issue ID 4000-313144] urn:comicvine:4000-313144
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-09 15:43:25. [Issue ID 898507]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="824938" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="509078" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="773178" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="638571" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="551672" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="695968" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="617782" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="535863" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="585756" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="692491" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="532741" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="789915" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="731534" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="679699" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="648077" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="695374" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="703333" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="719298" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="564425" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="641538" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="727789" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="660166" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="648887" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="618633" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="673854" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="613561" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="551861" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>IDW</Publisher>
  <Series>Doctor Who Classics Omnibus</Series>
  <Summary>Frobisher's Story: The Doctor and his allies stop the Skeletoid army from conquering the universe.

The Warrior's Story: The Doctor, his companions, Abel Gantz and a Draconian warrior meet in the Valley of the Gods.

Abel's Story: A fragment of the time vortex crashes into the laboratory of Abel Gantz.

Kane's Story: The Doctor comes to Earth to help stop the Skeletoids.

Funhouse Part 2: The Doctor traps the strange entity that has taken control of the Tardis in the time vortex.

Funhouse Part 1: The Tardis is captured by a strange entity.

War-Game Part 2: The Doctor and Frobisher help Kaon rescue his daughter from Vegar.

War-Game Part 1: While making a quick stop on a random planet The Doctor and Frobisher are captured by Kaon the Draconian.

Once Upon a Time-Lord... Part 2: The Doctor defeats Astrolabus.

Once Upon a Time-Lord...: The Doctor chases Astrolabus to rescue Frobisher.

Polly the Glot Part 3: The Doctor, Frobisher and Asimoff free Polly from the Akkers.

Polly the Glot Part 2: The Doctor, Frobisher and Asimoff meet the Akkers, the dullest alien race in the universe.

Polly the Glot Part 1: Dr. Ivan Asimoff asks The Doctor for help in rescuing Polly who is being used as a side-show attraction.

Voyager Part 5 The Final Chapter: The Doctor and Frobisher escape from the mysterious Lord of Life.

Voyager Part 4 Dreams of Eternity...: The Doctor discovers the origin of Astrolabus.

The Lighthouse... Voyager Part Three: The Doctor meets Astrolabus.

The Light at the Edge of the World... Voyager Part Two: The Doctor and Frobisher chase a strange being across Antarctica and are confronted by a robot.

It Was a Devil Ship.. The Voyager: The Doctor and Frobisher find a sailing ship frozen in the ice of Antarctica.

The Shape Shifter Part Two: The Doctor and Avan Tarklu scam Dogbolter out of the reward he had placed on capturing The Doctor.

The Shape-Shifter Part One: Avan Tarklu, a shape-shifting private eye, tries to collect The Doctor for the reward being offered by an unknown party.

Skywatch-7 Part Two: The U.N.I.T. soldiers use the Zygon's fear of fire to drive it into icy water where it drowns.

Skywatch-7: The troops at U.N.I.T. Skywatch-7 track a possible meteorite landing. When the soldier who goes out to check returns, he is acting strangely. When his colleagues attempt to pursue they discover that he has been replaced by a Zygon.

The Moderator Part Three: The Doctor refuses Dogbolter's offer to buy the TARDIS just before he and Gus escape. Dogbolter then hires the Moderator to track down the TARDIS. He succeeds just as the Doctor returns Gus to his home world and native time. Gus dies in the ensuing shootout, and the Doctor drops the wounded Moderator off in a hospital.

The Moderator Part Two: The Doctor and Gus find themselves in the midst of a labor dispute on a mining planet. When they are taken before the owner of the mining company, Dogbolter, the Doctor reveals that they are time travelers to save Gus's life.

The Moderator Part One: As the Moderator hunts for the Tardis on a mission from Dogbolter, the Doctor and Gus find themselves pursued as curfew-breakers by the Gaunts. Just before they are captured, they fall through the ground into a tunnel.

4-Dimensional Vistas Part VI: The Doctor chases the Time Meddler and the Ice Warriors through time and puts an end to their plans.

4-Dimensional Vistas Part V: The Doctor is rescued from the Ice Warriors but Autex and the Time Meddler escape.

4-Dimensional Vistas Part IV: The Doctor is captured by the Ice Warriors but Angus manages to escape and is rescued by a mysterious group.

4-Dimensional Vistas Part III: The Doctor and Angus enter the Ice Warrior's compound.

4-Dimensional Vistas Part II: The Docotr and Angus discover that one Earth is being shielded from the Tardis.

4-Dimensional Vistas Part I: The Doctor learns that he is lost on a parallel Earth.

Lunar Lagoon [Part 2]: The Doctor attempts to save a Japanese soldier during World War II.

Lunar Lagoon [Part 1]: While relaxing on a south-sea island, The Doctor is taken prisoner by a Japanese soldier.

The Stockbridge Horror [Part 6]: The Doctor is placed on trial by his fellow Time Lords.

The Stockbridge Horror Part 5: The Doctor is arrested by Rassilon.

The Stockbridge Horror [Part 4]: Shayde enters the Tardis computer to confront the entity that has taken over the Tardis.

The Stockbridge Horror [Part 3]: An evil being has invaded the Tardis.

The Stockbridge Horror [Part 2]: While rescuing the Tardis from a forest fire, the Doctor sees a strange monster in the flames.

The Stockbridge Horror: The Doctor discovers that the Tardis has been travelling thru time and space without him.

Stars Fell on Stockbridge Part 2: Maxwell gets lost on a deserted spaceship and must be rescued by the Doctor.

Stars Fell on Stockbridge Part 1: Maxwell mistakes the Doctor for an alien from Venus.

The Tides of Time Part 7: The Doctor and Sir Justin defeat Melanicus.

The Tides of Time Part 6: The Doctor learns the history and origin of Melanicus.

The Tides of Time Part 5: The Doctor, Shayde and Sir Justin meet the Lords of Althrace.

The Tides of Time Part 4: Doctor Who and Sir Justin battle illusions.

The Tides of Time Part 3: Doctor Who and Sir Justin begin their quest.

The Tides of Time Part 2: Doctor Who and Sir Justin travel to Gallifrey.

The Tides of Time: While visiting England to play some cricket, The Doctor witnesses various people from history suddenly appear in the area.

The Neutron Knights: The Doctor is brought to the end of the Earth by Merlin to rescue a few people from destruction.

Junk Yard Demon: Two junk dealers find a Cyberman floating in space.

</Summary>
  <Tags>The Doctor,Time Lords</Tags>
  <Teams>Time Lords</Teams>
  <Volume>2010</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/doctor-who-classics-omnibus-2/4000-313144/</Web>
  <Writer>Alan McKenzie,Steve Parkhouse,Maxwell Stockbridge,Alan McKenzie,Steve Parkhouse</Writer>
  <Year>2011</Year>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Title>Frobisher's Story; The Warrior's Story; Abel's Story; Kane's Story; Funhouse Part 2; Funhouse Part 1; War-Game Part 2; War-Game Part 1; Once Upon a Time-Lord... Part 2; Once Upon a Time-Lord...; Polly the Glot Part 3; Polly the Glot Part 2; Polly the Glot Part 1; Voyager Part 5 The Final Chapter; Voyager Part 4 Dreams of Eternity...; The Lighthouse... Voyager Part Three; The Light at the Edge of the World... Voyager Part Two; It Was a Devil Ship.. The Voyager; The Shape Shifter Part Two; The Shape-Shifter Part One; Skywatch-7 Part Two; Skywatch-7; The Moderator Part Three; The Moderator Part Two; The Moderator Part One; 4-Dimensional Vistas Part VI; 4-Dimensional Vistas Part V; 4-Dimensional Vistas Part IV; 4-Dimensional Vistas Part III; 4-Dimensional Vistas Part II; 4-Dimensional Vistas Part I; Lunar Lagoon [Part 2]; Lunar Lagoon [Part 1]; The Stockbridge Horror [Part 6]; The Stockbridge Horror Part 5; The Stockbridge Horror [Part 4]; The Stockbridge Horror [Part 3]; The Stockbridge Horror [Part 2]; The Stockbridge Horror; Stars Fell on Stockbridge Part 2; Stars Fell on Stockbridge Part 1; The Tides of Time Part 7; The Tides of Time Part 6; The Tides of Time Part 5; The Tides of Time Part 4; The Tides of Time Part 3; The Tides of Time Part 2; The Tides of Time; The Neutron Knights; Junk Yard Demon</Title>
  <Genre>Science fiction</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Penciller>John Ridgway,Mick Austin,Steve Dillon,Steve Parkhouse,Dave Gibbons,Mike McMahon</Penciller>
  <Inker>John Ridgway,Mick Austin,Steve Dillon,Paul Neary,Steve Parkhouse,Dave Gibbons,Adolfo Buylla</Inker>
  <Colorist>Charlie Kirchoff</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Halfacree,Jerry Paris,Steve Craddock</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>