<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Titania,Auberon,Taik,Molly</Characters>
  <Colorist>Nathan Eyring,Nathan Eyring</Colorist>
  <Editor>Julie Rottenberg</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-43552</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Snejbjerg,Peter Snejbjerg</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Richard Starkings,Richard Starkings,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Locations>Faerie</Locations>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:45 [Issue ID 4000-43552] urn:comicvine:4000-43552
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:14:42. [Issue ID 60137]</Notes>
  <Number>35</Number>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="657382" ImageWidth="994" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="527120" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1537" ImageSize="505253" ImageWidth="995" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="528528" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1541" ImageSize="467779" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="510433" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="627037" ImageWidth="982" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="558466" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="542317" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="536037" ImageWidth="982" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="510254" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="487897" ImageWidth="982" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="637243" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1529" ImageSize="646088" ImageWidth="980" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="541141" ImageWidth="970" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="379610" ImageWidth="985" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="363669" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="548052" ImageWidth="973" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="544667" ImageWidth="976" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1536" ImageSize="553740" ImageWidth="979" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1533" ImageSize="525517" ImageWidth="985" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="576679" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1537" ImageSize="493210" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="429100" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="554540" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="1530" ImageSize="512588" ImageWidth="985" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="1531" ImageSize="501139" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="421086" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Snejbjerg,Peter Snejbjerg</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Titania wonders when Faerie began to change, to feel less true.  Selwyn, her maidservant, comes up to comfort her and briefly turns back into his true form as Auberon, before changing back to Selwyn before she notices.  "Selwyn" tries to say that Auberon loves her, but Titania says she wasn't worthy of him.

Titania plans to read the Book of a Single Page for help, but first seduces "Selwyn," to Auberon's surprise.

Yarrow goes to Molly's tree house to find magical wards against her, due to the damage Molly has done since she caught on fire.  Yarrow still feels loyalty to Molly and blames Titania for tricking her.  The Amadan, eavesdropping, drops down behind her.

Molly and Taik walk along in the woods; she is no longer on fire.  He is not a fan of his mother, Titania, and doesn't know why she turned him into a horse.  Molly starts hearing voices; she takes medication to stop this back in the real world, but doesn't have the medication here.  She starts to see Taik in an evil-looking form, but is it just her mental problems?

Amadan says the other fairies blame him for bringing Molly to Faerie in the first place (for their contest of fools, which never happened).  A mob gathers at the bottom of the tree.  Amadan, so brave before, now asks Yarrow to save him.  She says she knows a way.  He swears to do anything she says.

Titania goes to the Book and asks it what she must do.  Stunned at the answer, she runs and asks for the guards.

Molly realizes that her Gran might have packed her medicine when she first sent her off, so long ago.  She and Taik run off to the treehouse to get it.  Taik stops her, and asks if she is really sick--maybe the voices and hallucinations are really just her magical fey nature, giving her insight into reality? As he asks, he looks more demonic again, and then like a horse's skull.  She tells him to get away, and explodes in fire again.

Titania looks out from a tower and sees a black ship flying through the sky, as the Book said would happen.  Three figures with white masks and chains walk out.  They are Hell Lords.  She says the contract was not broken, and it is not the time of the Tiend, so she wants to know why they are here.  They say the contract was broken when someone whose life was given to them escaped from hell and came to Faerie.

This was Taik: they demand the return of him, and seven others, or they will take back that which Hell gave to Faerie.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:20:35.  [CVDB43552]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-35-rites-of-passage-part-nine-a/4000-43552/</Summary>
  <Title>Rites of Passage, Part Nine: Appearances</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-35-rites-of-passage-part-nine-a/4000-43552/</Web>
  <Writer>John Ney Rieber,John Ney Rieber</Writer>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested for Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>