<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<Colorist>Dylan Teague,Giulia Brusco,Jim Boswell</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>I.N.J. Culbard</CoverArtist>
	<Day>24</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1053027</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Lee Carter,Patrick Goddard,R.M. Guera</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>4</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:32 [Issue ID 4000-1053027] urn:comicvine:4000-1053027</Notes>
	<Number>2379</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1501110" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1576479"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1372728"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1228826"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1433049"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1176693"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1097938"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1205035"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1583708"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="2032209"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1362588"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1592680"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1581722"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1897030"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1423497"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1112813"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1682998"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1881139"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1430352"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="2233009"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1623865"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1354838"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1148789"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1305428"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1011737"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1551139"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1500519"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="2014557"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="2089366"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1549169"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1642960"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="1227365"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Lee Carter,Patrick Goddard,R.M. Guera</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>I am The Mighty Tharg, bringer of Thrills to a planet beset by brain-sapping mundanity! 

Yes, it’s that time of the week again, my Squaxx, when you get to escape everyday reality - if just for the time it takes to peruse and absorb these pulse-pounding pages - and be transported to the circuit-shattering worlds of the Galaxy’s Greatest Comic. Inside this ghafflebette prog, you’ll find the latest high-octane instalments of Judge Dredd, Brink, Aquila, Proteus Vex and Indigo Prime, brought to you by the fevered imaginations of my creator droids.

Chained as they are in their work-cubicles, channelling every key-tap and pencil-stroke through my office so I get to oversee the entire process and ensure that it’s all at the necessary level of zarjazosity, the whole Command Module meshes together as a finely tuned machine… staffed by machines! Many of you may be wondering, is this a utopian vision of the future I can get behind - mechanoids programmed to deliver high-intensity entertainment under the direct rule of an alien overlord, who demands nothing less than total subservience?

Well, all I can say is, it works for me - and the end result is pretty damn scrotnig!

*Judge Death » Rend &amp; Tear with Tooth &amp; Claw (Part 4)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, with the toxic Black Atlantic to the east and the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*Aquila » The Rivers of Hades, Book Two: PART 3 (Part 1)*
Following Spartacus’s failed revolt against his Roman masters, his rebel army was crucified. Amongst these was the slave-turned-gladiator AQUILA, who cried out to the gods for vengeance - and was answered by Ammit the Devourer, a deity that gifted him with immortality in return for keeping her fed with evil men’s souls. Now, Aquila has travelled into Hades and retrieved the spirit of Nero, who knows Ammit’s location...

*Brink » Consumed (Part 2)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Indigo Prime » Black Monday (Part 9)*
The multiverse. There is an infinite number of parallel realities, and all need managing in case of dimensional instability. This is where INDIGO PRIME came in, the multiverse’s troubleshooters, whose agents are trained to deal with space/time catastrophes. Now, IP’s HQ has been destroyed in a cataclysmic event, with most of the personnel lost, and its assets acquired by the company ICP...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 5)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 2379</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2379-prog-2379/4000-1053027/</Web>
	<Writer>Dan Abnett,Gordon Rennie,Kek-W,Michael Carroll,Rob Williams</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>