<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Get Lost</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Title>TPB</Title>
  <Volume>2008</Volume>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Satire-parody,Animal,Western-frontier,Science fiction,Detective-mystery,Humor</Genre>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-16 19:53:54. [Issue ID 480175]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Hermes Press</Publisher>
  <Year>2008</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Love Harvey Kurtzman's original MAD? Then you will have to have Ross Andru and Mike Esposito's historic satire and parody magazine, Get Lost. Originally released in 1953, Get Lost delivered three groundbreaking, laugh-filled issues before Bill Gaines sued the magazine's distributor, shutting down production of the magazine. Even though Gaines lost the lawsuit, Andru and Esposito never produced more Get Lost. Hermes Press' historic reprint collects all three issues of the magazine on heavy coated matte paper together with an introductory essay by noted pop-culture historian Ron Goulart, an interview with Mike Esposito, and tons of documentary material in one volume. For this archival edition Hermes Press has painstakingly reconstructed Get Lost's artwork using the original black-and-white line art and recoloring it from scratch. Mike Esposito says it "looks better than the original." MAD's most noteworthy competitor is a treasure to behold for fans of Alfred E. Newman as well as comic book collectors, fans, and anyone looking for a good laugh.</Summary>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/get-lost-1-tpb/4000-480175/</Web>
  <Writer>Mike Esposito,Ross Andru</Writer>
  <Penciller>Mike Esposito,Ross Andru,Mike Esposito,Ross Andru</Penciller>
  <Inker>Mike Esposito,Ross Andru,Mike Esposito,Ross Andru</Inker>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Month>7</Month>
</ComicInfo>