<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Fantastic Comics</Series>
  <Number>16</Number>
  <Count>23</Count>
  <Title>Return of the Serpent Lady</Title>
  <Volume>1939</Volume>
  <Genre>Adventure,Superhero,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>Samson and David investigate a mysterious caravan of trucks headed to Mexico. They find that Herman Husler is smuggling munitions. Our heroes question him, and learn that Sklavor the Dictator is building a military power just over the border to challenge the US. Samson wrecks the whole affair. Infuriated, Sklavor makes an attempt to stop Samson, in vain, and dies in the process.

Serpo, a poisonous dragon, tires of the Fourth Dimension, and visits Earth. Flip observes Serpo taking a woman hostage back to the Fourth Dimension, and pursues him.  Back in the Fourth Dimension, Gogo, master of the Demi-things, sees the girl, and wants her for his bride. Flip must defeat both enemies to save the woman.

Lester Colt, wanted for murder, has just been told by his doctor that he has 3 months to live. He decides to get his revenge on the world for having made him a fugitive. Space Smith and Diana witness Colt murdering a ship full in innocents, and pursue him. They are taken captive by Colt, who imprisons them on a moon of Jupiter. Our heroes get free, and stop Colt's plot, killing him, and capturing his gang.

Hondo, Prussland and Napoli form a political alliance, and seek to commit sabotage to weaken the U.S.'s hold on Hawaii.  Yank advises the Governor to intern all those of Hondo descent, and helps uncover the local Hondoian fishing fleet assisting the Hondo Navy.  Yank is captured, but signals for help, and ends up uncovering the Hondo Navy's battle plans.  The U.S. fleet ends the Hondo Navy threat.

Sir Richard is magically visited in Warwick Castle by a stranger, who announces himself as Mokon, King of the Moon. Mokon has come to claim the hand of Richard's sister, Marion, as foretold by Richard's father.  Later that night, Richard is similarly visited by Mokon's brother, Sukon, King of the Sun. Sukon has come for Richard's sister, Elaine.  Later still, Lucifer comes to claim Richard's sister Jane, but is rebuffed by Richard. Lucifer kidnaps Alice instead.  With the help of Mokon and Sukon's brother, Winkon, Richard pursues Lucifer to Hades and rescues Alice.

Captain Kidd flies Dr. Lake to Kweilin China, to treat a man named Pike, who reveals details of a plot by the Japanese to massacre a Chinese Army division.  Captain Kidd tries to stop the plan, but is captured by the lovely Hi Ling. Kidd is rescued by Pike. The two escape, taking Hi Ling captive.

The Serpent Lady has been plotting her revenge against Sub, and has a new sea monster, Diablo, waiting as a trap for Sub.  Sub arrives, and manages to kill the beast, but the Serpent Lady's assistant, Luco, has plans to usurp power by killing both Sub and the Serpent Lady. Sub saves the Serpent Lady, who reveals her love for Sub.  Sub does not return it, leaving her forlorn.

Stardust detects a plot to rob Fort Knox of its $20 billion gold supply by the villainous Slant-Eye. He fails to arrive in time to stop the villains from invading and demolishing the Fort, but paralyzes the criminals for arrest by authorities. He reserves a terrible end for the mastermind, as Slant-Eye is delivered into the clutches of gigantic, golden sea monster, called the Octopus of Gold.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:11:28. [Issue ID 1305]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fox</Publisher>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Year>1941</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(march 1941)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>David,Samson [Sam],Sklavor (villain, introduction, death),Herman Husler (villain, introduction),Joe Maguire (villain, introduction)</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>Herman Husler (villain,Joe Maguire (villain,death),introduction),David,Samson [Sam],Sklavor (villain,introduction</Tags>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/fantastic-comics-16/4000-255637/</Web>
  <Writer>Fletcher Hanks,Nathaniel Nitkin,Hank Christy,Hank Christy,Fletcher Hanks</Writer>
  <Penciller>Bill Bossert,Don Rico,Fletcher Hanks,Grieg Chapian,H.C. Kiefer,Alex Blum,Hank Christy,Dennis Neville,Henry Kiefer,Alex Blum,Don Rico,Hank Christy,Dennis Neville,Grieg Chapian,Bill Bossert,Henry Kiefer,Fletcher Hanks</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bill Bossert,Don Rico,Fletcher Hanks,Grieg Chapian,H.C. Kiefer,Alex Blum,Hank Christy,Dennis Neville,Henry Kiefer,Alex Blum,Don Rico,Hank Christy,Dennis Neville,Grieg Chapian,Bill Bossert,Henry Kiefer,Fletcher Hanks</Inker>
  <Letterer>Fletcher Hanks,Fletcher Hanks</Letterer>
  <Editor>Victor Fox</Editor>
</ComicInfo>