<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-57100</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:18:30 [Issue ID 4000-57100] urn:comicvine:4000-57100
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 13:49:23. [Issue ID 75890]</Notes>
  <Number>31</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Atlas.1956)  (chums)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Spellbound</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/spellbound-31/4000-57100/</Web>
  <Year>1956</Year>
  <Count>34</Count>
  <Title>Man in a Trance; They Dare Not Come; The Man Who Didn't Belong; He Won't Open the Door; Oh, Perfect Crime!; The Betrayer</Title>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Fantasy</Genre>
  <Summary>Man in a Trance: Ronnie believes the past still exists and invents a formula to enter the 'existing' past so he can find out what became of the Drake Diamond. It works, but he falls in love with Nancy and fears if he takes the diamond in the present she'll be arrested for the theft in the past so he leaves it alone.

They Dare Not Come: The workers in a weather station on Mars become antsy about supplies arriving but the commander maintains control. All of them are human-like robots who need the fuel to keep running.

The Man Who Didn't Belong: Steve rescues Rex from inside the cyclotron but he has no memory of where he came from. Steve starts to resent how perfect Rex seems and how everyone likes him. Eventually Rex steps back into the cyclotron and vanishes. Steve tells his story to Denise then recognizes her as Rex's mother! He realizes Rex was his son from the future and that he can be proud of Rex's achievements.

He Won't Open the Door: Preston believes money can get him anything. Searching for Incan treasure he tries to force a ferryman to lead him across a river, but the ferryman is Charon and he's at the River Styx.

Oh, Perfect Crime!: A sleezy booking agent uses a teleporter to get rich quick.

The Betrayer: When Wilson spies a giant rocket craft headed to Earth which will destroy everything when it lands. Clark builds a hideout on the world's most deserted island, Bimur, so he can be sure to survive. However, that's exactly where the ship is going to land.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Characters>Ken Flynn,Lord Hubert,Oliver Flynn,Nancy Drake,Ronnie Flynn,Dick Flynn</Characters>
  <Writer>Carl Wessler,Carl Wessler</Writer>
  <Penciller>John Forte,Bill Everett,Robert Q. Sale,William Wellman,Howard O'Donnell,George Roussos,John Forte,Bill Everett,Robert Q. Sale,William Wellman,Howard O'Donnell,George Roussos</Penciller>
  <Inker>John Forte,Bill Everett,Robert Q. Sale,Jack Abel,Howard O'Donnell,George Roussos,Jon Small,John Forte,Bill Everett,Robert Q. Sale,Jack Abel,Howard O'Donnell,George Roussos,Jon Small</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bill Everett,Bill Everett</Letterer>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>