<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Raven,Pooka,Intro: Dragon Witch (1st Mor-Meb-Dred),Tarot</Characters>
  <Colorist>Holly K Golightly</Colorist>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-118119</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jim Balent</Inker>
  <Locations>Witch Manor</Locations>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:17:20 [Issue ID 4000-118119] urn:comicvine:4000-118119
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 17:24:40. [Issue ID 134359]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1008161" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="821937" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="847638" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="802761" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="778051" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="813854" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="909463" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="967850" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="898840" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="840890" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="972335" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="808018" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="993386" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1047450" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="926536" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="933852" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="826714" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1009750" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="950525" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="904306" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="894894" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="865841" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="866719" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="595609" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="380684" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="774223" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="629743" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="73007" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jim Balent</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Broadsword</Publisher>
  <Series>Tarot: Witch of the Black Rose</Series>
  <Summary>Tarot's Moon ritual is interrupted by something very huge that her BatCat Pooka has dragged in!

SynopsisTo hopefully lessen the problems her sister, Raven Hex, caused with the second witch's burning, Tarot begins a magical ceremony in her garden in the nude. Just as finishes her initial preparations she notices her cat Pooka flying very quickly. Tarot hardly has time to react when she realizes that a large dragon is chasing Pooka. She springs from her water ritual and snatches up her cat just before the dragon can eat it. She leaps into a pool of water with Pooka (she's still naked) and emerges behind a waterfall in hopes of hiding their scent.

While hiding, Tarot reminisces about finding Pooka as she and Raven snooped around an entrance to the Realm Beyond the Mist. Pooka seemed to be calling out to her. Tarot claimed Pooka as her familiar and the two enjoyed each other, despite Pooka constantly getting into trouble.

This reverie is quickly disturbed when the dragon finds the two. The dragon, which claims to also be a witch, demands Pooka's life as a consequence for breaking dragon law. The dragon chases the still naked Tarot around garden and is finally able to knock her down and corner her. Pooka shows up and the dragon grabs him. Tarot regains her feet and wields her sword menacingly. She convinces the dragon to explain the problem. Pooka, it seems, accidentally ripped of the dragon's son's tail. According to dragon witch law, Pooka must die. Tarot offers to fix the tail if the dragon witch will let Pooka go. The dragon shrinks down to her witch size and agrees to the terms.

An hour later, Tarot enters the Realm Beyond the Mist and heals the young dragon's tail. Despite the dragon witch's warning that she and other dragon witches would join Raven Hex if she ever tried to rebel again, Tarot resumes her ceremony in the garden pools.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-02-15 22:29:28.  [CVDB118119]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/tarot-witch-of-the-black-rose-5-dragon-witch/4000-118119/</Summary>
  <Tags>Tarot's Mother,Raven Hex,Witch Manor,Dragons,Tarot,Son of Mor-Meb-Dred,Pooka,Frost Fairy,Dragon Witch</Tags>
  <Teams>Dragons</Teams>
  <Title>Dragon Witch</Title>
  <Volume>2000</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/tarot-witch-of-the-black-rose-5-dragon-witch/4000-118119/</Web>
  <Writer>Jim Balent</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>