<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Demonslayer,Shmyg</Characters>
	<Colorist>Vyacheslav Doronin</Colorist>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Evgeniy Eronin,Roman Kotkov</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-510632</GTIN>
	<Inker>Andrey Vasin</Inker>
	<Letterer>Anna Sidorova,Irina Smolina,Sviatoslav Kaverin</Letterer>
	<Month>12</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T01:18:43 [Issue ID 4000-510632] urn:comicvine:4000-510632</Notes>
	<Number>2</Number>
	<PageCount>24</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2462953" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="3144975"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1891122"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="3542530"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="3875227"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1926966"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1626666"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1819648"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1740887"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="3384450"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1648962"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1728846"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1713016"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1559285"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1705366"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1521667"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1763397"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1718764"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1816870"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1361299"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="2101469"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1993691"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1614102"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="132240"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Andrey Vasin</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Bubble</Publisher>
	<Series>Demonslayer</Series>
	<Summary>His name is Demonslayer, part 2

We live in a horrible time. A time when the most disgusting dregs are on top of the world and ordinary people are left on their own. Junkies. Gangsters. Killers. Robbers. Rapists. Scums of all kinds have lost their minds in their cruelty. There are no laws for them and no justice for anyone else. They've turned the country into the branch of Hell on Earth. And when the actual creatures from the netherworld found out about all this mayhem, they began to slowly seep into our world to have some fun of their own. Many criminals are giving in to temptation and make deals with these hellspawns, exchanging their freedom for great strength and power. The Evil becomes stronger with every second, and the Hell Gates are slowly opening, and legions of demons are waiting for a moment to strike...

Enter Danila the Demonslayer! The hooded grim avenger is going to bring back the country's former peace. With a help of cynical renegade imp called Sneak he finds and annihilates demons, trying to hold back the infernal invasion. Danila came under fire in Tskhinvali In 2008. Mysterious forces, interested in maintaining the balance between good and evil, chose the bedridden soldier to be their weapon. The new protectors of the Demonslayer gave him the «Hourglass of Life», which appeared to be salvation and a curse at the same time: Danila is alive while the black ash of demons runs in the hourglass. Each grain of ash is obtained with great difficulty, because one can only kill the evil with weapon created in Hell or Heaven and it's not available to mere mortals. Similar deadly force lies within the Demonslayer's glowing tattoos, but they only work together with an old ID tag: if there is an evil nearby, the tag begins to exude terrible cold, ready to liberate the energy for the battle.

Armed to the teeth, Danila the Demonslayer goes hunting: the bloody reaping in the name of good has begun!

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-02-14 18:31:45.  [CVDB510632]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/demonslayer-2-his-name-is-demonslayer-part-2/4000-510632/</Summary>
	<Tags>Demonslayer,His Name Is Demonslayer,Shmyg</Tags>
	<Title>His Name Is Demonslayer Part 2</Title>
	<Volume>2015</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/demonslayer-2-his-name-is-demonslayer-part-2/4000-510632/</Web>
	<Writer>Artyom Gabrelyanov,Evgeny Fedotov</Writer>
	<Year>2015</Year>
</ComicInfo>