<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Garganta,Ghost Rider,Ms. Victory,Nightveil,Rad,She-Cat,Stella Stargaze,Tara</Characters>
	<CoverArtist>Mark Heike</CoverArtist>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<Editor>Mark G. Heike</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-129282</GTIN>
	<Genre>Superhero</Genre>
	<Inker>Antonio Conversano,Drew Gardner,Jeff Austin,Mark G. Heike,Mark Heike,Silvano</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Bill Black,Jeff Austin,Stephanie Heike,Stephanie S. Heike</Letterer>
	<Month>1</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.2.0 on 2024-11-30T20:44:39 [Issue ID 4000-129282] urn:comicvine:4000-129282</Notes>
	<Number>138</Number>
	<PageCount>44</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="310598" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="299306"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="288844"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="291958"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="308614"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="303448"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="302298"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="315000"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="362008"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="292706"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="280798"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="319890"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="272902"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="282844"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="310384"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="292966"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="293826"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="382006"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="353256"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="316910"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="355436"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="297992"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="343100"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="172720"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="192998"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="220576"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="195934"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="424480"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="409774"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="373714"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="400366"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="402014"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="333088"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="373806"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="401828"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="272138"/>
		<Page Image="36" ImageSize="192622"/>
		<Page Image="37" ImageSize="205650"/>
		<Page Image="38" ImageSize="243138"/>
		<Page Image="39" ImageSize="334286"/>
		<Page Image="40" ImageSize="380158"/>
		<Page Image="41" ImageSize="350654"/>
		<Page Image="42" ImageSize="490940"/>
		<Page Image="43" ImageSize="397560"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Antonio Conversano,Drew Gardner,Eric Theriault,Gianluca Cerrutelli,Ken Hunt,Mark G. Heike,Mark Heike,Silvano</Penciller>
	<Publisher>AC</Publisher>
	<Series>FemForce</Series>
	<Summary>Another action-packed issue starring the longest-running female super-team in history!! Start off with that rambunctious RAD, who returns to bedevil her mother, FF head honcho MS. VICTORY in "My Own Worst Enemy". A revenge-seeking madman engineers a battle royale between the two distaff titans that may costs BOTH of their lives- and what might it's conclusion portend? Written by Chris Irving, with art by Gianluca Cerrutelli and Jeff Austin. Then, picking up the thread of last issue's mysterious events, NIGHTVEIL suddenly finds herself at the gravesite of The HAUNTED HORSEMAN, confronted by a new enemy- The BLUE BULLETEER!?! "Shadowhunt" is written by Chris Irving, with art by Ken Hunt (who also drew this issue's stellar front cover) &amp; inks by Mark Heike. Then, TARA FREMONT gets back to her jungle roots in a sequel to a story that appeared in FF #128, as she gets the upper hand on a band of murderous poachers in "Silence Falls on Jungle Island", written by Enrico Teodorani, and drawn by Antonio Conversano. And although we know (based on last issue's events) that SHE-CAT has disappeared, she's in action here in a short feature from another time &amp; place titled "It Was Just Another Night", also written by Enrico Teodorani, with art by Drew Gardner. But that's not all, as the second half of the comic continues with the flip-book mini-feature we debuted last issue with GARGATARAMA-THE COMIC BOOK #2!! Just turn the book over, flip past the great Silvano back/flip cover, and read three more great Good Girl Art stories, all with the GTS theme: GARGANTA herself leads off in "Off To The Races", as a daring robbery at a NASCAR race is foiled single-handedly by Big G in spectacular, size-changing action!! Written and penciled by Mark Heike, with ink finishes by Jeff Austin. Then, one-time giant villainess Marla Allison returns in "Attack Of The 5' 6" Woman", plotted and drawn by Eric Theriault, with inks &amp; dialogue by Mark Heike. Finally, The FEMFORCE themselves come up against their worst nightmare-- a GIANT SIZED STELLA STARGAZE in "Terror On A Tear!!", written by Xizor and drawn by Silvano. More than 40 gages of excitement, over seven different stories!! 48 pages, black &amp; white with color covers, standard comic book size &amp; format, saddle-stitched. Printed in 2007.</Summary>
	<Teams>FemForce</Teams>
	<Title>Stella Stargaze's Ripping Revenge; Attack of the 5' 6" Woman; Off to the Races!!; It Was Just Another Night; Silence Falls on Jungle Island; Shadowhunt; My Own Worst Enemy</Title>
	<Volume>1985</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/femforce-138/4000-129282/</Web>
	<Writer>Chris Irving,Enrico Teodorani,Eric Theriault,Mark G. Heike,Xizor</Writer>
	<Year>2007</Year>
</ComicInfo>