<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd,Judge Giant Jr.,Judge Hernandez,Tee</Characters>
	<Colorist>Eva de la Cruz,Matthew Soffe</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Simon Davis</CoverArtist>
	<Day>7</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1044220</GTIN>
	<Inker>Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Laura Helsby,Luke Horsman,Simon Davis</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Locations>Mega-City One</Locations>
	<Month>2</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:25 [Issue ID 4000-1044220] urn:comicvine:4000-1044220</Notes>
	<Number>2368</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1054530" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1557221"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1557363"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1643395"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1594437"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1794057"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1868842"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1714241"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="879259"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1458421"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1089344"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1036488"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1067384"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1101510"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1036384"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1117303"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="970234"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1287656"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="848979"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1206783"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1429592"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1436181"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1143764"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1286916"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1199976"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1693883"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1534666"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1387536"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1300961"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1677000"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="912413"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="751092"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Laura Helsby,Luke Horsman,Simon Davis</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Welcome, Thrill-seekers, to your latest weekly blast of circuit-scorching excitement, courtesy of my rivet-bustingly busy creator droids. As we surge into February, the tension builds in the scrotnig Dreddstory A Better World, the unease grows on set of folk chiller The Dule Tree in Thistlebone, and the crew of the Full Tilt Boogie regroup. In addition to this, both the 3riller The English Astronaut and eco-actioner Enemy Earth reach their penultimate parts. Be here in seven for the ghafflebette finales!

It means zarjaz new Thrills are thundering towards us, and in two weeks time we’ll be exploring the worlds of a pair. First off, The Fall of Deadworld by Kek-W and Dave Kendall is back for the second half of Retribution after its mid-season break, so you can expect more body-horror madness as Death continues his decimation of an entire civilisation; and secondly we return to the reality-warping universe of Indigo Prime, with Kek-W (yep, it’s that droid again!) and Lee Carter picking up the story from Prog 2270’s one-off!

*Judge Dredd » A better world (Part 5)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law! Now, Accounts Judge Maitland has been conducting an experiment in Sector 304 in a bid to reduce crime...

*Tharg's 3rillers Present » The English Astronaut (Part 2)*
Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story — a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre! Earth, November 1963, and Major Thomas Anderson is about to become the subject of a British Experimental Space Programme project. Locked into the Injection Seat, he’ll take a cocktail of drugs that will dislocate him from the current year and plunge him into 2024...

*Full Tilt Boogie » Full Tilt Boogie: Book two(Part 2)*
Out in the deep reaches of the cosmos, teenager Tee — together with her grandmother and cat — is a bounty hunter/hired help, operating from her spaceship the FULL TILT BOOGIE. Capable and resourceful, Tee was paid to rescue the Luxine Prince Ifan from his debtors’ prison. In the process, she encountered a resurrected Anubite warrior, a member of the enemy race with whom the Luxine Empire was at war...

*Enemy Earth » Enemy Earth: Book Three (Part 9)*
The near future. Mother Nature has turned against the people that live upon the Earth’s surface. Now, the planet’s flora and fauna have mutated and are viciously attacking humanity. As society crumbles, and survivors seek safety, young Zoe, who has lost her own family, has rescued Jules, who’s the prime minister’s son. Now, the pair have been reunited with the PM, and they’re journeying to India...

*Thistlebone » The Dule Tree (Part 5)*
Britain, 2020. It’s been over a year since journalist Seema Chaudry accompanied cult survivor Avril Easton back to the village of Harrowvale, where she suffered at the hands of THISTLEBONE worshippers, a crazed occult group that believed in an ancient woodland deity. One man in the village, Malcolm Kinniburgh, was keeping the Thistlebone legend alive — but now he’s dead, and his house is being cleared...</Summary>
	<Teams>Judges of Mega-City One</Teams>
	<Title>Prog 2368</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2368-prog-2368/4000-1044220/</Web>
	<Writer>Alex de Campi,Arthur Wyatt,Cavan Scott,Paul Cornell,Rob Williams,T.C. Eglington</Writer>
	<Year>2001</Year>
</ComicInfo>