<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-204125</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:04 [Issue ID 4000-204125] urn:comicvine:4000-204125
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:04. [Issue ID 136596]</Notes>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>The Ship of Lost Souls: The gambling ship “Hades” capsizes and dozens of passengers are killed inside the hull. The ship’s owner, Harry Cain, is responsible for this tragedy, because his ship was not ballasted the right way. Two newspaper reporters, who were allegedly killed onboard, have survived and stage a scoop. Posing as ghosts they kidnap Cain, bring him aboard the “Hades” and make him confess his deadly negligence. As Cain whips out a gun, another tidal wave rolls in and takes Cain down to the bottom of the sea.

Hideout in Hell: The Bexer gang robs a bank and goes into hiding. They quarrel over the loot and two of them shoot each other. When the police come searching the woods, Bexer crawls into the compound where the bodies are stored. His phobia of corpses drives him insane.

The Strangling Hands: Collector Noram comes into possession of the severed arms of Jean D’Arst, the infamous French strangler. The arms are rumored to be cursed and to have killed all of their current owners. Noram, however, is strangled by his greedy nephew Don. When the police don’t buy the story of a curse, Don runs – but is strangled by the bodiless arms.

The Man Who Cheated Death: John Blane turns 70 years of age and is obsessed with wanting to live forever. One of the researchers in his laboratories comes up with a liquid which will grant eternal life. Blane drinks down the potion after having murdered his employee who was unwilling to part with it. He is quickly sentenced to die in the electric chair, but can’t be killed. The immortal Blane is locked away, but escapes and commits a bank robbery. During his getaway Blane is horribly mutilated in a car accident and has to spend eternity confined to a hospital bed.

</Summary>
  <Title>The Ship of Lost Souls; Hideout in Hell; The Strangling Hands; The Man Who Cheated Death</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-7-the-strangling-hands/4000-204125/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>