<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Disney Masters</Series>
  <Number>20</Number>
  <Title>Walt Disney Donald Duck: 20,000 Leaks Under the Sea</Title>
  <Volume>2018</Volume>
  <Genre>Anthropomorphic-funny animals</Genre>
  <Summary>Do It Yourself: Fethry convinces Donald to do his own home repairs rather than hire a contractor.

Mountain Magic: To cure Donald's hiccups, Fethry takes him to the mountains to meet bearded hillbilly Hard Haid Moe and suffer through his offbeat hiccup cures.

It's Only Money: Scrooge hires Fethry as an efficiency expert.

Out of the Depths Despair: Donald and Fethry go skindiving. Donald has his eye on treasure, while Fethry is only interested in fish.

The Contest: Scamp and Speedy quarrel over a found bone, until Tramp suggests that a contest decide who gets it. They try competitions of speed, scent-smelling, strength, swimming, and voice quality coming out even every time, until Jock provides a solution.

Water Sports: Fethry wants Donald to go waterskiing... and Donald goes... willingly?

Bah Wilderness: Fethry dragoons Donald into going camping, where they tangle with a mountain lion

Flock Together: Mickey wants to buy Morty and Ferdie a canary, but finds a parrot and dog are also part of the deal.

Matador-To-Door Salesman: Through a series of misunderstandings, Fethry ends up the star attraction in a Mexican bull ring.

The Missing Hair: Agents of the evil organization BLONK hold a movie studio hostage when they steal the trademark toupee of the studio's biggest star.

Suds in Your Eye: Daisy's highly touted garden party caterer turns out to be... Fethry.

Vet Day: When Donald's cat, Tabby, needs to go to the vet, earnest cab driver Fethry unintentionally (but typically) gives them the taxi-ride from... heck!

A Midsummer's Nightmare: A female client of "Fethry's Lonely Hearts Club" (!) sets her sights on Donald as a husband, and Fethry is only too happy to accept the fee for his services. Fethry sends her to Donald's house to charm him, however Donald thinks she is the new housekeeper he hired.

Old Trusty's Scent: Scamp finds a scent for the old bloodhound Trusty to follow, but quickly regrets it.

The Superior Intellect: Fethry disrupts Donald's peaceful life bearing a book on "the care and feeding of the common housecat", turning his unwanted attentions to Donald's cat Tabby. Poor Tabby.

The Case of the Renegade Circus: Agents of the evil organization BLONK put on a sham circus in Duckburg, where the main tent is really a huge iron cage in which to hold Scrooge McDuck and the circus-obsessed citizens as prisoners while they loot the city, starting with Scrooge's Money Bin.

The Piggy Bank: Jiminy Cricket checks to see if Pinocchio is keeping to his promised savings schedule. He is both pleased and displeased for different reasons.

Satisfied Customer: Dale does battle with a pesky woodpecker but chooses the wrong weapon.

20,000 Leaks Under the Sea: Typically over-inspired by an adventure magazine article, Fethry builds a makeshift "diving bell" (actually a two-man mini sub) to go treasure hunting on the ocean floor - with a reluctant Donald as his crew.

The Bouncing Ball: Scamp head-butts a ball, which bounce-butts back.

A Goofy Look at the Newspaper: On his way to cover a flower show, newspaper reporter Goofy inadvertently does good in various wacky situations.

The Pioneer: Fethry drags Donald off to the wilderness to live like their pioneer ancestors.

The Carpet Baggers: The flying carpets of Hakstand are disappearing. Sleuth Fethry and his shanghaied assistant Donald are called to solve the case. The trail leads to a giant moth.

Chased Chaser: A cat-chasing Scamp learns that "there's always someone bigger and badder"... even if it's another dog.

Fall Guy: Fethry is obsessed with going over Niagara Falls in a barrel, but his repeated efforts only succeed in sending Donald and an angry ranger over the falls instead.

There's No Place Like Home: Mountain man Hard Haid Moe and his "Houn' Dawg" drop in to stay with Donald for a month. Can even Fethry dissuade the hard-headed-one?

Law Trouble: Would-be lawyer Fethry defends Donald against a parking ticket.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-10 22:32:01. [Issue ID 2422938]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(june 2022)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Donald Duck,Huey,Fethry Duck,Tabby,Ralph (repairman),two deliverymen</Characters>
  <Writer>Dick Kinney,Dick Kinney</Writer>
  <Penciller>Al Hubbard,Tony Strobl,Al Hubbard,Tony Strobl</Penciller>
  <Inker>Al Hubbard,Larry Mayer,Al Hubbard,Larry Mayer</Inker>
  <Colorist>Disney Italia,Digikore Studios,Nea Aktina A. E.,Mickey Clausen,Hachette,Michael Myers,Pat Keane,Egmont,Scott Rockwell,David Gerstein,Disney Italia,Digikore Studios,Nea Aktina A. E.,Mickey Clausen,Hachette,Michael Myers,Pat Keane,Egmont,Scott Rockwell,David Gerstein</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Tom B. Long,Rome Siemon,David Gerstein,Paul Baresh,Melvin Millar,Willie Schubert,Tom B. Long,Rome Siemon,David Gerstein,Paul Baresh,Melvin Millar,Willie Schubert</Letterer>
  <Editor>David Gerstein,Chase Craig,Alice Nielsen Cobb,Carl Buettner,Chase Craig,Alice Nielsen Cobb,Carl Buettner</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
    <Page Image="67" />
    <Page Image="68" />
    <Page Image="69" />
    <Page Image="70" />
    <Page Image="71" />
    <Page Image="72" />
    <Page Image="73" />
    <Page Image="74" />
    <Page Image="75" />
    <Page Image="76" />
    <Page Image="77" />
    <Page Image="78" />
    <Page Image="79" />
    <Page Image="80" />
    <Page Image="81" />
    <Page Image="82" />
    <Page Image="83" />
    <Page Image="84" />
    <Page Image="85" />
    <Page Image="86" />
    <Page Image="87" />
    <Page Image="88" />
    <Page Image="89" />
    <Page Image="90" />
    <Page Image="91" />
    <Page Image="92" />
    <Page Image="93" />
    <Page Image="94" />
    <Page Image="95" />
    <Page Image="96" />
    <Page Image="97" />
    <Page Image="98" />
    <Page Image="99" />
    <Page Image="100" />
    <Page Image="101" />
    <Page Image="102" />
    <Page Image="103" />
    <Page Image="104" />
    <Page Image="105" />
    <Page Image="106" />
    <Page Image="107" />
    <Page Image="108" />
    <Page Image="109" />
    <Page Image="110" />
    <Page Image="111" />
    <Page Image="112" />
    <Page Image="113" />
    <Page Image="114" />
    <Page Image="115" />
    <Page Image="116" />
    <Page Image="117" />
    <Page Image="118" />
    <Page Image="119" />
    <Page Image="120" />
    <Page Image="121" />
    <Page Image="122" />
    <Page Image="123" />
    <Page Image="124" />
    <Page Image="125" />
    <Page Image="126" />
    <Page Image="127" />
    <Page Image="128" />
    <Page Image="129" />
    <Page Image="130" />
    <Page Image="131" />
    <Page Image="132" />
    <Page Image="133" />
    <Page Image="134" />
    <Page Image="135" />
    <Page Image="136" />
    <Page Image="137" />
    <Page Image="138" />
    <Page Image="139" />
    <Page Image="140" />
    <Page Image="141" />
    <Page Image="142" />
    <Page Image="143" />
    <Page Image="144" />
    <Page Image="145" />
    <Page Image="146" />
    <Page Image="147" />
    <Page Image="148" />
    <Page Image="149" />
    <Page Image="150" />
    <Page Image="151" />
    <Page Image="152" />
    <Page Image="153" />
    <Page Image="154" />
    <Page Image="155" />
    <Page Image="156" />
    <Page Image="157" />
    <Page Image="158" />
    <Page Image="159" />
    <Page Image="160" />
    <Page Image="161" />
    <Page Image="162" />
    <Page Image="163" />
    <Page Image="164" />
    <Page Image="165" />
    <Page Image="166" />
    <Page Image="167" />
    <Page Image="168" />
    <Page Image="169" />
    <Page Image="170" />
    <Page Image="171" />
    <Page Image="172" />
    <Page Image="173" />
    <Page Image="174" />
    <Page Image="175" />
    <Page Image="176" />
    <Page Image="177" />
    <Page Image="178" />
    <Page Image="179" />
    <Page Image="180" />
    <Page Image="181" />
    <Page Image="182" />
    <Page Image="183" />
    <Page Image="184" />
    <Page Image="185" />
    <Page Image="186" />
    <Page Image="187" />
    <Page Image="188" />
    <Page Image="189" />
    <Page Image="190" />
    <Page Image="191" />
    <Page Image="192" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>