<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Captain Clavius,Cranius,Calibretto,Brass Demur,Bulgrim,Knolan,Garrison,King Vaneer,Gully</Characters>
  <Colorist>Aron Lusen,Chris Lichtner,Liquid!,Ryan Kinnaird</Colorist>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-76117</GTIN>
  <Inker>Adam Warren,Jason Martin,Joe Madureira,Scott Williams,Tim Townsend,Tom Mcweeney,Trevor Scott,Vince Russell,Tom McWeeney</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Richard Starkings,Richard Starkings,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:49:43 [Issue ID 4000-76117] urn:comicvine:4000-76117
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 06:46:15. [Issue ID 95767]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Adam Warren,Joe Madureira,Joe Madureira</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Battle Chasers</Series>
  <Summary>Bulgrim reveals that his time is short but that he needs a wielder that is pure of soul and this pale girl is tainted as he faces off against the war golem.

Word reaches the king who orders that both massive creatures should be destroyed. Opening fire Bulgrim is totally unharmed but Calibretto takes heavy damage. Gully begs for mercy but is ignored so once again she dons the gloves and attacks Bulgrim who is unimpressed and unmoved.

Knolan battles the flying Cranius a few streets away. He tricks the green wizard and casts a spell of Banishment on him.. enveloping him in blue light as he is sucked out of this dimension.

Garisson's sword has no effect on Brass Demur's tattooed body and they fight hand to hand. Despite being smaller and weaker than Demur he finds weak point in his magical body armor and scores points against his massive foe. When the battle increases Garrison uses his sword and channels energy though it stunning Demur.

Bulgrim is impressed by Gully's ability to use the gloves and match his power and wants her to be his new vessel. Bretto realizes the bracelet is the source of the curse and smashes it with a final shot, banishing the demon.

The king arrives and congratulates the team on their victory but expresses his suspicion that its strange how many hero's should arrive just in time to save his city from ruin.....</Summary>
  <Teams>Battle Chasers</Teams>
  <Volume>1999</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/battle-chasers-5/4000-76117/</Web>
  <Writer>Joe Madureira,Munier Sharrieff,Joe Madureira,Munier Sharrieff</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Joe Madureira,Liquid!,Tom Mcweeney</CoverArtist>
  <Title>Power</Title>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Editor>Scott Dunbier</Editor>
</ComicInfo>