<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Tales from Wonderland: The Mad Hatter</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Volume>2008</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 12:31:12. [Issue ID 601064]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Zenescope Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Year>2008</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <ScanInformation>(Digital-HD) (Monafekk-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Editor>Raven Gregory,Ralph Tedesco</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
  </Pages>
  <Title>One-Shot</Title>
  <Summary>The origin story of the second Mad Hatter, Drake Liddle. Also contains part two of the three part back-up story 'The Experiment'.

In-depth Summary:

Drake was a fireman, husband, and seemingly loving uncle from Los Angeles. Secretly however, he molests his nephew Johnny on fishing expeditions with the boy. After one of these excursions Johnny confesses his uncle's crime to his grandfather ( Charles Dodgson). That night when Drake went visit his father Charles accuses him of pedophilia and thrusts him through the mirror into Wonderland.

In Wonderland, Drake finds himself trapped between the March Hare and a wall of undead corpses. He is grabbed by the wall and bargains with the hare for his aid. The hare frees him from the wall and in exchange he offers him the 10/6 hat and sends him on a quest to fetch a girl named Lacie. Drake then wanders the jungle for months becoming exhausted and ever more insane. He finds a mirror and there, speaking with his reflection, finally gives up and gives in to Wonderland. In doing so he is able to don the mantle of the Mad Hatter and inherits all of the previous hatter's skin suits. Months later he returns to March Hare and the tea party with Lacie and declares himself leader of the little group.</Summary>
  <StoryArc>Wonderland (Zenescope)</StoryArc>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/tales-from-wonderland-the-mad-hatter-1-one-shot/4000-178515/</Web>
  <Characters>Dormouse,Drake Liddle,Henry Allen,Alice Liddle,Mad Hatter,King of Hearts,Queen of Hearts,Charles Dodgson,March Hare,Jabberwocky</Characters>
  <Locations>Wonderland,Los Angeles</Locations>
  <Writer>Ralph Tedesco</Writer>
  <Penciller>Joseph Dodd</Penciller>
  <Inker>Joseph Dodd</Inker>
  <Colorist>Nei Ruffino</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Jim Reddington</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>David Nakayama,Nei Ruffino,Richard Bonk</CoverArtist>
<Genre>Fantasy,Horror</Genre></ComicInfo>