<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Love and Rockets</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Title>1979; My name is Killer; 12th Street and Vine; Anima; 1979; Since I Don't Have You</Title>
  <Volume>2016</Volume>
  <Genre>Drama,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>This is volume four in the series. Uses the same oversize magazine format as volume one.

Vol. 1- 1982-1996 (50 issues in magazine format)
Vol. 2- 2001-2007 (20 issues in standard US comic book periodical format)
Vol. 3- 2008-2016 (8 issues as Love and Rockets: New Stories in trade paperback format)

Comes with at least one cover variant per issue available exclusively from the publisher. Each variant has its own individual front &amp; back cover.US comic book store release date 2017-12-06.1979: Malo, this time dressed up in "punk" gear, tries to convince Hopey to smuggle drugs across the Mexican border for him.

My name is Killer: Killer tries to come to terms with the less than rapturous response to her newly started singing career.

12th Street and Vine: Maggie finally lets Ray know that it was her brother Calvin who brutally assaulted him. A story told from Ray's point of view, first person perspective.

Anima: The Emperor of Blotos is arrested and condemned to banishment in the Asteroid of Sorrows for unleashing the Hellmets. However, just as his judgement is given, a Hellmet arrives and incinerates his prosecutors after taking over his body. Newly super-powered Isla and her sister Lumina look for a spaceport to get to their home planet, but the Hellmet that Anima had defeated arrives to try to take over Isla's body again.

1979: In Del Chimney's house, Del tries to prevent Doyle from starting a fight, Maggie waits for Hopey, who arrives with Hilary Pute's soon-to-be destroyed lunchbox. Del nixes Malo enlisting Maggie in his scheme to smuggle drugs over the Mexican border.

Since I Don't Have You: Pipo finds out Soledad Marquez has died, then visits her now-officially divorced ex Fritz before taking a flight to Palomar. In a flashback to the time period of the earliest Palomar story, fourteen-year-old Pipo deals with fluctuating interest from Manuel and persistent attention from Soledad. In a teenage pique, she tells Soledad to scare Manuel with an unloaded gun but he winds up killing him. Flash-forward to the mid-to-late nineties post-Palomar period, the now adult and well-off Pipo reconciles with the still-imprisoned Soledad.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev36 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-03-22 15:07:29. [Issue ID 1766201]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Year>2017</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Web>https://www.comics.org/issue/1766201</Web>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (Salem-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Writer>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>