<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-387944</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:35 [Issue ID 4000-387944] urn:comicvine:4000-387944
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:49:16. [Issue ID 9364]</Notes>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Crime SuspenStories</Series>
  <Summary>Out of the Frying Pan...: Old Charlie's efforts to describe the sights outside of the hospital window are really appreciated by two paralyzed patients. But soon, a new patient, Hank Bowers, being held for murder and supposedly blind, is put into the room and he does not appreciate such talk. Until Hank gets an idea for escape.

A Trace of Murder!: The murder-suicide of a husband and wife greatly interests Felix Morley, who wishes to do away with his nagging wife for young and fresh Helen. Felix researches and discovers that some poisons can be administered with no trace of the poison left behind and decides to use it on his wife, Emma, who dies, and all her money is left to Felix. But Felix slips and says that he killed his wife to his girl, so Helen goes to the Police. Unbeknownst to Felix, two cemetery vandals switch the headstones of Emma and Muriel, so when the Police investigate, Felix is in a fix.

The Escaped Maniac!: Bert picks up a hitchhiker alongside the road in a blinding rainstorm and begin a journey together. But when Beeker turns on the radio instead of the car's heater, they hear a broadcast telling of an escaped maniac from the state hospital for the criminally insane and not to pick up any hitchhikers. Naturally, Bert is nervous as they locate an unoccupied home to get out of the rain. Unfortunately, Charles falls victim to the man who picked him up: the real maniac!

Partnership Dissolved!: Doc Merrick displays the effectiveness of his secret chemical solution to tenderize meat: an extract of the papaya fruit, containing an enzyme called Papien which, when mixed with Merrick's secret catalytic agent, creates a solution which acts like Pepsin, a digestive enzyme found in the human body. Together they plan to undercut their competitors in the meat business by dipping cheap cuts into the solution and creating high grade steak. Although Winkler plans a double-cross to get all the profits from this partnership, an unexpected surprise awaits him.....a fatal surprise!

</Summary>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-8/4000-387944/ https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-8-out-of-the-frying-pan/4000-110183/</Web>
  <Year>1951</Year>
  <Count>27</Count>
  <Title>Out of the Frying Pan...; A Trace of Murder!; The Escaped Maniac!; Partnership Dissolved!</Title>
  <Characters>Hank's girlfriend's lover (death),Herb (patient),Hank Bowers (villain),Old Charlie (patient),Hank's girlfriend (cameo)</Characters>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Johnny Craig,Bill Gaines,Al Feldstein</Writer>
  <Penciller>George Roussos,Graham Ingels,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,George Roussos,Graham Ingels</Penciller>
  <Inker>George Roussos,Graham Ingels,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Johnny Craig,Jack Kamen,George Roussos,Graham Ingels</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Johnny Craig</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein</Editor>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>