<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Johnny Alpha,Judge Dredd,Sláine</Characters>
	<Colorist>Carlos Ezquerra,Gary Caldwell,Richard Elson,Simon Davis</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Alex Ronald</CoverArtist>
	<Day>27</Day>
	<Editor>Tharg the Mighty</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-490084</GTIN>
	<Genre>Detective-mystery,Science fiction,Sword and sorcery</Genre>
	<Inker>Carlos Ezquerra,Daniel Dwyer,Mike Collins,Richard Elson,Simon Davis</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Ellie De Ville,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Locations>Mega-City One</Locations>
	<Month>5</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:34:31 [Issue ID 4000-490084] urn:comicvine:4000-490084</Notes>
	<Number>1932</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="763356" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1330305"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1009133"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1198453"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1067168"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1081628"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1003883"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1135407"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1487618"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1129537"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1768507"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1453092"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1084815"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1345563"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1291898"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1097367"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1046987"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="959198"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1153433"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1424730"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1212014"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1206403"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1180484"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1217788"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1115008"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1089057"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1140040"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1220081"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1124564"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1432090"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="976546"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="821462"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Carlos Ezquerra,Daniel Dwyer,Mike Collins,Richard Elson,Simon Davis</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(may 2015)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>*Judge Dredd // Breaking Bud (Part: 4)*
Mega-City One, 2137 AD. Home to 50 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, where crime is rampant. Tensions run a constant knife-edge and only the zero-tolerance Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law! Now, former lab assistant Bud Biggard has stolen a highly powerful bracelet...

*Sláine // Primordial (Part: 9)*
Albion, in a time of myth and legend. Celtic barbarian warrior SLÁINE united the tribes of the Earth Goddess Danu and became the first High King of Ireland. After ruling for seven years, he travelled through time to fight for the Goddess in other eras before returning to save his people from the Fomorian sea devils. He then became a wanderer, serving the Goddess where she directs him, and now he’s battling the Drune Lords...

*Tharg's Future Shocks // The Big Heist (Part: 1)*
Out in the vast reaches of the universe, there are an infinite number of stories waiting to be told. From chronicles of the lowliest swamp denizens in backwater galaxies to the rise and fall of rulers of entire star systems, anything is possible in these twisted tales. Abandon your preconceptions, expect the unexpected and take a trip beyond the edges of the imagination…

*Tharg's 3rillers Present // Commercial Break (Part: 2)*
Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story — a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre! The Lake District, summer 1997. Daisy Chan, Annie Oakley and Leo McKinstry are three friends hanging out in the small town of Osterpool, where nothing very much happens. But when an unusual commercial appears on TV one July evening, they can’t get it out of their heads...

*Strontium Dog // The Stix Fix (Part: 9)*
Late 22nd century. After the Atomic Wars, many survivors were warped by the Strontium 90 fallout. These ‘mutants’ became a victimised underclass, forced into ghettos, and the only career open to them was bounty hunting. One such Search/Destroy agent, or STRONTIUM DOG, is Johnny Alpha, who was thought killed. Now, following a mutant rebellion, he’s been offered a job that will see him released from prison...

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-23 06:28:42.  [CVDB490084]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-1932-prog-1932/4000-490084/</Summary>
	<Tags>Johnny Alpha,Judge Dredd,Mega-City One,Sláine</Tags>
	<Title>The Stix Fix Part Nine; Commercial Break Part Two; The Big Heist; The Brutania Chronicles Book Two: Primordial Part Nine; Breaking Bud Part Four</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-1932-prog-1932/4000-490084/</Web>
	<Writer>Dan Lester,David Baillie,Eddie Robson,John Wagner,Pat Mills</Writer>
	<Year>2015</Year>
</ComicInfo>