<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-204113</GTIN>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:11 [Issue ID 4000-204113] urn:comicvine:4000-204113
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:25. [Issue ID 136592]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>The Killer from Saturn: The city's in panic as an alien-like serial killer stalks the streets at night. Twelve people have to die until clever police lieutenant Jordan comes up with an explanation and confronts the fiend, who turns out to be a mousy city window clerk who wears an imposing monster costume with stilts, who is taking revenge on those who abused him.

Vengeance of the Red Ghost: Susan Maynard fakes her death and plays the avenging ghost coming back from the grave. She starts killing the rest of the family to get her hands on a big inheritance.

Goddess of Murder: Monstrous four-armed goddess Kali demands human sacrifices. When the lovely Caroline is chosen to be the next victim, her lover Kenneth comes to the rescue.

The Beast from Beyond: A hunting company from the city enters the woods and finds no moose, but a dragon-like monster! When all of the campers disappear one by one, the police come investigating. They confront the monster with high-powered rifles and grenades.

</Summary>
  <Title>The Killer from Saturn; Vengeance of the Red Ghost; Goddess of Murder; The Beast from Beyond</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-3-goddess-of-murder/4000-204113/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Jordan,Ed,Oswald Pilcher (villain)</Characters>
  <Penciller>Jack Cole,Leo Morey,Jack Cole,Leo Morey</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jack Cole,Jack Cole</Inker>
  <Letterer>Sam Rosen,Sam Rosen</Letterer>
  <Editor>Alfred Grenet</Editor>
</ComicInfo>