<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-90494</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T13:54:14 [Issue ID 4000-90494] urn:comicvine:4000-90494
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:14:01. [Issue ID 202489]</Notes>
  <Number>30</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Adventures into Terror</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-terror-30/4000-90494/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>31</Count>
  <Title>They Fly by Night; The Dead Don't Sleep; The Man in the Shadows; Don't Nod; A Scream in the Night!</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>They Fly by Night: A boy's parents are killed by a vampire during a trip to Hungary and he survives because the vampire is too sated to drain his blood. He returns to America but continues to have dreams of his parents begging him to return to Hungary so that they can be together forever. When he reaches adulthood he returns to Hungary and prepares to slay the vampire. Instead he encounters his parents who are vampires and offer to turn him into one. He walks towards the two but the story leaves it up to the reader to guess whether he stakes them or submits to their dark embrace.

The Dead Don't Sleep: Have you ever wondered if the dead resent the mediums who disturb their rest? This story answers that question.

The Man in the Shadows: A strange sequence of events turns out to be the disjointed memories of a condemned man.

Don't Nod: The leader of the Chinese secret police enlists an executioner to behead those convicted of crimes.

A Scream in the Night!: All of the people surrounding a writer turn out to be members of a sacrificial cult and since one of them is a psychologist, they have the writer committed to an asylum after he stumbles upon one of their ritual human burnings.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Bob Correa,Al Eadeh,Sol Brodsky,Sy Grudko,Colletta,Bob Correa,Al Eadeh,Sol Brodsky,Sy Grudko,Colletta</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bob Correa,Al Eadeh,Sol Brodsky,Sy Grudko,Colletta,Bob Correa,Al Eadeh,Sol Brodsky,Sy Grudko,Colletta</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jon D'Agostino,Jon D'Agostino</Letterer>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>