<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-204127</GTIN>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:15 [Issue ID 4000-204127] urn:comicvine:4000-204127
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:38. [Issue ID 136606]</Notes>
  <Number>17</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>Return of the Dead: Serge Lamont builds a machine to communicate with the dead. He uses it to learn all the magic secrets of the recently deceased magician Zendali. Zendali, however, comes back to full life and takes Lamont back to his grave.

The Fiend Who Lived Forever: A scientist is able to make himself immortal through experimentation on human victims. He robs banks to gather enough wealth to marry his sweetheart. Nothing can kill him as he is able to survive being burned, drowned, shot at, etc. The problem is while he may be immortal, his body shows the trauma of his wounds and he's oblivious to the fact he looks like a monstrous mangled 'fiend'.

Terror in Chinatown: The collector August Lamont searches frantically for a Chinese “book of the dead” holding great secrets. Lamont murders two book dealers to get his hands on the tome. By opening the book Lamont suffers terrible visions of past crimes – the last one showing his own murder.

The Avenging Ghosts: Gangsters Pete and Joey escape from their prison island in a motorboat and land on the “island of honesty” where no crime ever happens. Anyone who steals something will be imprisoned in a madhouse while his spectral form is doomed to cruise the coastline on a ship of ghosts forever.

</Summary>
  <Title>Return of the Dead; The Fiend Who Lived Forever; Terror in Chinatown; The Avenging Ghosts</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-17-terror-in-chinatown/4000-204127/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>