<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-274711</GTIN>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:08 [Issue ID 4000-274711] urn:comicvine:4000-274711
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:17. [Issue ID 136601]</Notes>
  <Number>12</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>The Shrunken Heads of Dr. Death: In the Amazon jungle, the suit-wearing crackpot Dr. Death lives with his pet monkey Bola and witnesses the crash landing of a passenger plane. The mad doctor kills off all survivors and adds them to his collection of shrunken heads. One day Guy and Marie arrive at the doctor’s jungle home, searching for Marie’s brother Frank who was on the plane that crashed. They detect Death’s secret and have to face the killer chimpanzee Bola in a showdown.

The Phantom Killer: A demolition crew is ordered to tear down an old playhouse of horror. Some of the workers are attacked and killed in the process. Wrecking company executive Weber looks into the matter and manages to detonate the scary location.

The Uninvited Corpse: Alice is married to John Carlton, but her lover, Guy, kills the husband. The evil couple rejoices and starts enjoying life, when dead Carlton drops by. He pesters his murderers and drives a wedge between them.

The Walking Dead: Show promoter Carl Lamont travels to an island in the Caribbean to capture the fabled giant zombie of Zaku, none other than Zog, king zombie. Lamont succeeds in luring Zog into a trap, hauling him to the US and putting him on display in his circus show. But a group of loyal zombies follows him, spreads terror on the mainland and manages to free Zog from his cage.

</Summary>
  <Title>The Shrunken Heads of Dr. Death; The Phantom Killer; The Uninvited Corpse; The Walking Dead</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-12-beware-of-the-uninvited-corpse/4000-274711/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>