<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<Colorist>Jim Boswell</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Nick Percival</CoverArtist>
	<Day>29</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1057120</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Nick Brokenshire,Nick Percival,Simon Parr (PYE)</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>5</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:37 [Issue ID 4000-1057120] urn:comicvine:4000-1057120</Notes>
	<Number>2384</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="839920" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1721295"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="916690"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="883275"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="833270"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="910595"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="921872"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="944286"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="2140640"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1323193"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1591470"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1544952"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1915752"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1214086"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="916498"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1396819"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1066660"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1413828"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1402285"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1059837"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="891530"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1019535"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1032977"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="934810"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1229828"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1107108"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1130314"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1159503"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1078356"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1513307"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1134063"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="909824"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Nick Brokenshire,Nick Percival,Simon Parr (PYE)</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>I am The Mighty Tharg, all-powerful alien editor of this brain-sizzling soup of Thrill-power! 

Indeed, the Galaxy’s Greatest Comic is much like a cauldron into which various ingredients are dropped and stirred, creating a flavoursome mix where the components complement each other and the result is a tasty stew of zarjazness.

Take, for example, the dark, bitter tang of Judge Dredd, smoky with menace as the lawman heads deeper into the Undercity in pursuit of the juves searching for the mythical monster Iron Teeth - its spine-tingling texture works perfectly with the dayglo sweetness of Intestinauts, that sugar underscored with notes of gut-bot. Then there’s the slow-burn unease of Brink, lingering on the palate long after the story is finished, its myriad elements revealing themselves over time, clashing with the oddball sprinkles of alien weirdness that Proteus Vex brings, sharp snaps that blossom in the imagination like synaptic fireworks.

Add to that the caffeine rush of the 3riller, superheated for maximum impact, and you hold in your hands quite the delicacy, carefully put together by this Betelgeusian chef and my minions. Consume with a favourite beverage, and enjoy, Terrans!

*Judge Dredd » Iron Teeth (Part 3)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, where poverty and overcrowding is rife and tensions run a constant knife-edge. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*INTESTINAUTS » Busted Flush (Part 3)*
For stomach upsets, future technology has developed nano-robots called INTESTINAUTS, who fight parasites in the gut. These micro-droids are ingested orally, then once their brave battle against the various horrors that can be found in the stomach is over, they take the Big Flush, ready to be uploaded back to headquarters, where their accrued knowledge of the enemy will help them in future missions...

*Tharg's 3rillers Present » Blue Skies Over deadwick (Part 2)*
Three episodes, one complete, self-contained story - a condensed hit of super-charged Thrill-power beamed to you directly from the Nerve Centre! Earth, the far future. Three climbers have been tasked with an important mission, one that cannot afford to fail. They have heard the rumble, and so must make the arduous, dangerous ascent if they are to save their settlement of Deadwick...

*Brink » Consumed (Part 7)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 10)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 2384</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2384-prog-2384/4000-1057120/</Web>
	<Writer>Arthur Wyatt,Dan Abnett,David Baillie,Kenneth Niemand,Michael Carroll</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>