<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Season of Dreams Pt. 1; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;! (#13)</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Jenny, Terry, and Zot swim at a local pond. Zot talks about how he's going to eventually fix Jenny's Earth. She makes the point that the planet's problems aren't all caused by supervillains.

When they go to a convenience store, Zot notes that some of his small heroics, like saving cats from trees, have started making the paper.

They go to Jenny's house, where Zot finally meets Jenny's mom (who is named in this issue's letter pages). Jenny and Zot go to visit Zot's world, and Butch invites himself along. Zot is nicer to Butch than Jenny.

Butch, however, is frustrated to find out that he becomes a monkey again any time he's in Zot's dimension. He runs up to confront Max, who is playing with his avant-garde jazz group. Max explains that his chimp status just is the way it is.

One member of the band, Ernie, is video-conferencing in from Brazil. He has a super-robot called Zybox who is a part of the whole planet's digital communication; it helps sort and fix all kinds of issues. Ernie noticed that Zybox seems to be thinking for itself.

Zot and Vic have a big public augmented-reality video duel. Butch jumps in to help Zot and Vic pulls in Floyd. They both do well and neither has a big advantage.

Ernie's boss, My. Tyree, is angry with him. He wants Zybox to work with the Air Force but Ernie insists that Zybox stay away from military uses. Tyree threatens to fire him. Ernie asks Zybox to figure out a way out of this problem, even if it means breaking the law, as long as no one is hurt.

The power goes off in the entire region so Zot and Vic's game is canceled. They go back to Max's. Zybox shows up, asking about the portal to Jenny's dimension. They can see that Ernie is stuck inside Zybox. The robot goes through the portal. Zot gets some back-up and then they go after it.

Zybox is waiting in a sports stadium. It sends out giant technological tentacles that wrap around Zot, Vic, and Jenny. Jenny grabs Zot's gun and frees herself, then Zot frees Vic, but Zot is pulled inside Zybox, who is bigger on the inside than the outside. Zybox then goes after the other two kids and pulls them in as well.

Jenny wakes up at home, thinking she had a dream about Zot. But when she mentions it to Butch, he doesn't know who Zot is.

Note: 9-Jack-9 only appears in his human identity as John Sheers.

&#8220;The Adventures of Zot in Dimension 10 &#189;!&#8221;:

Antisocialman annoys Zot and Jenny and hangs out in Zot&#8217;s dimension, where he is annoyed to find that everything is perfect. He then frustrates everyone he runs into. Zot and Jenny confront him but he sprays them with antisocial serum.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:45.  [CVDB28094]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Month>05</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-13-the-season-of-dreams-pt-1-the-adventures-of/4000-28094/</Web>
  <PageCount>31</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Antisocialman, Barbara Weaver, Butch Weaver, Ernie Cortez, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Theresa Maria Veras, Vic Taylor, Zot, Zybox</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="15731" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="280403" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="386569" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="442249" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="388466" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="395548" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="416364" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="478795" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="482812" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="464081" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="471800" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="402800" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="402617" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="455189" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="450658" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="410315" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="394184" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="347461" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="841499" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="360328" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="467211" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="617104" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="538275" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="407390" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="419723" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="470552" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="576679" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="526391" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="455191" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="511631" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="421500" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
