<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Momma Wong,Red Cross</Characters>
  <Colorist>Paul Little,Paul Little</Colorist>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Day>29</Day>
  <Editor>Kristen Simon,Kris Simon</Editor>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-113962</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jimmie Robinson,Jimmie Robinson</Inker>
  <Locations>Smithsonian Institute,T.I.T.,New Port City,The Pentagon,Texas</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:41:58 [Issue ID 4000-113962] urn:comicvine:4000-113962
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 06:13:09. [Issue ID 371780]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jimmie Robinson,Jimmie Robinson</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Digital) (K6-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Bomb Queen IV Suicide Bomber</Series>
  <Summary>'SUICIDE BOMBER' Bomb Queen declares war against the Image Universe! The nuclear aftermath from the Queen's last adventure put the country on high alert and forced government sanctions on her dictatorship. However, unknown to the Queen, there's a deeper, more evil plot forming right under her feet.

With the Shadow Government in ruins and Bomb Queen very much alive and well, which can't be said for her pet cat Ashe, T-Division (housed at the pentagon) is tasked with assessing her latest threat. The Queen is now declaring war on all heroes that pose a threat to New Port City by announcing preemptive strikes on cities that are home to said heroes. T-Division has recruited 2 members of Woods' team from the first attempt to take down Bomb by political means. their analysis of New Port City is that it corrupts the people who live there and is in fact pure Evil.

Meanwhile in New Port work has started on construction of Bomb Queen's new HQ the Tactical Information Turret (or T.I.T. for short). To get the work done in secret she hired teams, promises extra pay and perks and then sends them to Momma Wong's for free food where they are poisoned and disposed of. Momma Wong is very concerned that Bomb is taking the new powers she somehow absorbed from Bomb Teen for granted and reminds her that those powers were supplied by the Shadow Government.

Red Cross is keeping tabs on Bomb after their battle and is reporting back to T-Division on the queens plans. The escalation in threat means they decide to send in a strike team, breaking their bargain with Red Cross to allow her to finish of Bomb Queen once the innocent are rescued.

Meanwhile in Crawford Texas the military arrive at the presidents ranch and seal it of after a report of WMDs are present. They find a rocket in launch position in a barn.

At a rally in the main city square Bomb Queen addressed her public, humorously parodying famous speeches, to unanimous acclaim.

In a final panel a black clawed hand appears as a hidden character claims for a 1000 years of planning it has come to this, that all the puppets are now dancing to his tune, the forces of Earth, Heaven nor Hell will not be able to oppose him.</Summary>
  <Teams>Ku Klux Klan</Teams>
  <Title>Suicide Bomber</Title>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/bomb-queen-iv-suicide-bomber-1-and-now-for-a-word-/4000-113962/</Web>
  <Writer>Jimmie Robinson,Jimmie Robinson</Writer>
  <Year>2007</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Jimmie Robinson</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>