<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Ring in the New Part 2; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189; (#27): Dinosaur Dick</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>27</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>The pie, which Peabody threw at the end of the last issue, and which represents the culmination of a contest in the letters page, goes through 9-Jack-9's immaterial face and hits Zot in the face. (McCloud explains in the letters page that Jack won the contest, but since he doesn't have a material face, he had the pie going through his and then hitting Zot, who was in second place.)

Bellows and the Blotch start getting in an argument. The Blotch is losing physical coherence. He turns into a pile of goo and his eyeballs run away, as does Bellows.

The excitement over, everyone waits outside for the New Year to turn over. Terry has already gone because things were too weird. Instead of watching a ball drop for New Year's, they watch a clock that is projected onto the moon.

Jenny explains to Woody that time in Zot's work is different: the year is 1966, and next year will be 1967, since she first came last year in 1965. However, when Zot comes by, he says next year will be 1966 and they met in 1964. Jenny knows this is not what he said before. However, when the clock hits midnight, everyone cheers the beginning of 1965! When asked, Zot says last year was 1964 and they met in '63. Peabody backs him up. However, even Butch knows that they're getting it wrong.

Max has always thought Jenny's Earth is an imperfect version of Zot's world. Now Woody theorizes that Zot's world was somehow copied off the "real" world and is stuck in a utopian concept of time.

The next day, Zot takes Woody on a tour around his world so they can figure out which world is the original. Woody is amazed by Zot's world but he notices something interesting and later explains it to Jenny.

In Zot's world, there are songs and movies about the Vietnam war and World War II, but there was no actual Vietnam war or World War II. Zot's world seems to be a world without a real sense of time.

Max gets the portal to Jenny's world ready so she and Woody can go home. She talks more about how she plans to move there forever. They realize Vic never came to the party.

Max and Zot explain that they have to be careful with the portals from now on. The government doesn't like the idea of them playing with another dimension, so they have to hide the coordinates of the dimension in a remote device. Just as Woody, Jenny, and Zot step through, the police show up, and Max tells Zot to close the portal.

However, once they do, they realize they can't open it again. Max doesn't have the coordinates, and Zot doesn't have the portal-opening device. They are all stuck in Jenny's Earth. Jenny is distraught at never being able to leave, but Zot is perfectly happy.

In Dimension 10 &#189;, Max goes to a fellow scientist's house. The scientist, Dinosaur Dick, thinks the dinosaurs died from the flu. He goes back in time to cure the dinosaurs. By the time Max shows up, Max and everyone else have turned into dinosaurs because of how history has been rewritten. Max calls Zot, who because he was in Jenny's dimension, is still human. Zot and Jenny go to the past and find Dinosaur Dick. Then some tourists, who come from a future later than Zot's time, show up. They say that Dinosaur Dick's time machine started a tradition of time travel tourism. The future humans now also bring all their radioactive waste to the time of the dinosaurs because it won't affect humans. However, it turns out to be the thing that makes dinosaurs go extinct. They all go back to Zot's time and for some reason they are all humans again. Dick brings a dinosaur with him to study.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:16.  [CVDB31308]</Notes>
  <Year>1989</Year>
  <Month>06</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Ivy Ratafia, Randy Carpenter, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-27-ring-in-the-new-part-2-the-adventures-of-zo/4000-31308/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Bellows, Butch Weaver, Chet Barker, Dekko, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, The Blotch, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Teams>Dreeps, The Pole Police</Teams>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="232658" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="134633" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="219045" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="203039" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="201133" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="168338" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="176607" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="150500" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="226769" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="209232" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="214050" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="229566" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="193617" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="191672" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="224813" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="198431" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="198350" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="218243" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="177141" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="268932" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="236730" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="204817" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="230744" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="205005" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="197261" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="225866" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="184260" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="219671" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="183676" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
