<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Count>18</Count>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein,Albert B. Feldstein</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1396</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Marie Severin,Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:05 [Issue ID 4000-1396] urn:comicvine:4000-1396
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:47:45. [Issue ID 11610]</Notes>
  <Number>17</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>George Evans,Jack Kamen,Joe Orlando,Reed Crandall,Jack Kamen,Reed Crandall,George Evans,Joe Orlando</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Shock SuspenStories</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/shock-suspenstories-17/4000-1396/</Web>
  <Writer>Carl Wessler,Al Feldstein,Carl Wessler,Al Feldstein</Writer>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Inker>George Evans,Jack Kamen,Reed Crandall,Joe Orlando,Jack Kamen,Reed Crandall,George Evans,Joe Orlando</Inker>
  <Title>4-Sided Triangle; In Character; The Assassin; The Operation</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime</Genre>
  <Summary>4-Sided Triangle: A farmer tries to molest a retarded girl he keeps to work on the farm as a servant. She tells him that she's got a boyfriend that she sees in the evening. She goes out into the field to the scarecrow. The farmer gets the idea of disguising himself as the scarecrow so he can get what he wants from the girl. The farmer's wife is awakened by the sound of their love-making and goes out to the field with a pitchfork. When the girl tells the wife about her boyfriend, the wife tries to demonstrate to her that it's only straw by repeatedly stabbing the scarecrow with the pitchfork.

In Character: Bela Kardiff murders all of his Hollywood contacts at a dinner honoring him after he has been typecast in horror pictures and then the company decides to dump him because they are not going to do horror pictures any longer.

The Assassin: An assassin unknowingly pursues his mark to the backstage of a theater and kills the man just before the curtain rises. It turns out that the assassin has walked in on the opening scene of a play about President William McKinley and the man who assassinated him!

The Operation: A diamond thief surgeon cuts open his two goons to smuggle diamonds into the country in their bodies. When he gets a big one worth $250,000 he tells the men he will operate on both of them, but place the diamond in only one so that they will not be tempted to disappear. The doctor sends them a note saying he will be delayed because he knows that this will play on their greed and they will turn on each other. They kill each other, but the doctor did not place the stone in either of them but himself. But the diamond was paste and it quickly caused the doctor's death due to poisoning.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Abner Hester (farmer, death),Annie (retarded servant of the Hesters),Hester Yates (Abner's wife)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
</ComicInfo>