<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Cremator,Death Queen,Lady Death,Lucifer,Purgatori,Vassago</Characters>
	<Colorist>Jason Jensen</Colorist>
	<Count>4</Count>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-119683</GTIN>
	<Locations>Castle Death,Hell</Locations>
	<Month>4</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:40:24 [Issue ID 4000-119683] urn:comicvine:4000-119683</Notes>
	<Number>2</Number>
	<PageCount>21</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="496165" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="504899"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="989042"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="501808"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="506653"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="479328"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="521232"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="601678"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="565202"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1086444"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="513410"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="508483"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="990723"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="489690"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="510497"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="551006"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="485581"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="511340"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="587033"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="990335"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="498478"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Chaos! Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Lady Death: Between Heaven and Hell</Series>
	<Summary>At the last possible moment Lady Death strikes Purgatori, knowing all along that the vision of her mother was fake to draw out her unseen attacker. Purgatori beats a retreat and vanishes.  

*Previously *
On the outskirts of the Endless Graveyard Purgatori uncovers the body of Cremator who was lost to Lady Death in he battle against Lucifer. She tells him he was abandoned there but he claims no malice against his mistress.  *Present Day *
On the shores of the Styx Purgatori corrupts Cremator's mind and she has him create a sword for her like she did for Lady Death. This time he pours all his hatred into its forging. His job done she sends him to Lady Death who assumes he is a yet another phantasm of Purgatori's and she tries to cut him down with the sword he made for her, when it has no effect  she uses her arcane energy instead. She laments that it cannot be him as she hunted for him following their battle with Lucifer and thought his body lost. The attack knocks the sense back into Cremator who manages to warn her of the sword just as Purgatori arrives aback a warhorse. Her nameless wolves rejoin her from their place in waiting and tackle the demoness' own wolves. Purgatori, the more ruthless and experienced combatant overpowers Lady Death and astride her foe impales her stomach as blood bonds strap her to the ground of her own kingdom. Purgatori finally takes what she has lusted for all along and drinks her blood. Her feeding only makes her stronger and now she wishes to free Lucifer's soul that she might feast on him as well. She uses her sword and energy and is shocked to find Lucifer is not within Lady Death!                                                                                                                                            Lady Death takes her enemies confusion and rallies overpowering Purgatori but refusing to believe her. She drags the demoness to the river Styx and shoves her under the waters. Purgatori insists that Lucifer's soul never was inside her.  *Elsewhere *
Lucifer watches over the scene from a hidden place laughing at his control over these naive creatures lives.</Summary>
	<Teams>Nameless Wolves</Teams>
	<Title>The Final Sin</Title>
	<Volume>1995</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/lady-death-between-heaven-and-hell-2-the-final-sin/4000-119683/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Pulido</Writer>
	<Year>1995</Year>
</ComicInfo>