<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Dan,William Clockwell,Omni-Man,Bill,Invincible,Ted,Atom Eve,Deborah Grayson,B.N. Winslow</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bill Crabtree</Colorist>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-105533</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Cory Walker,Cory Walker</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Robert Kirkman</Letterer>
  <Locations>Reginald Vel Johnson High School,Burger Mart,Hawaii,Saudi Arabia</Locations>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:15:42 [Issue ID 4000-105533] urn:comicvine:4000-105533 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/276821
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 07:45:00. [Issue ID 105533]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Cory Walker,Cory Walker</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Invincible</Series>
  <Tags>Invincible [Mark Grayson],Atom Eve,Omni-Man,Mrs. Grayson</Tags>
  <Teams>Flaxans</Teams>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/invincible-3/4000-105533/</Web>
  <Writer>Robert Kirkman</Writer>
  <Year>2003</Year>
  <Summary>While the mysterious bombings continue (see Invincible #1), it's just another day for Mark trying to work out what's normal while still being a superhero - an invincible superhero. First of all he quits his job, after all, what self-respecting superhero flips burgers in his spare time?

Omni Man - aka Mark's father - asks him whether he's interested in teaming up. "Yes, that would be great!" And so they're off, and it's pretty cool, and it's something Mark's always wondered about. Omni Man's pretty good. To be honest, he's really good. Just while they're flying he zips off to take care of a handful of disasters, and pretty much wipes out an alien invasion with only moderate help from Invincible.

Before heading home for the day, father and son take a look at something that's going on in Lakeside Mall: a bomb attached to a stranger. There's no time to save him; no time to decipher its source. The human bomb is thrown up and away. The mall is saved, but a green arm reaches around and grabs Omni Man away into another dimension. It's the one of the Flaxans they had been fighting earlier!

When Mark returns home - alone - he finally understands what it is his mother does: she keeps a home for her husband, believing with just the smallest glimmer of doubt that he'll come home, safe.</Summary>
  <CoverArtist>Cory Walker</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>