<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Aspen Matthews,Judith Banyaski</Characters>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Editor>Frank Mastromauro,Vince Hernandez</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-418856</GTIN>
  <Locations>San Diego,California</Locations>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T22:00:57 [Issue ID 4000-418856] urn:comicvine:4000-418856
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev78 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-09 05:50:21. [Issue ID 418856]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Aspen MLT</Publisher>
  <Series>Michael Turner's Fathom</Series>
  <Summary>A new direction in the FATHOM Universe begins! Michael Turner's best-selling series has reached its milestone 15-year anniversary! However, Aspen Matthews' adventure under the surface has no plans of slowing down! Following the devastating events of 'The Elite Saga', Aspen Matthews finds herself at a decisive crossroads in her life-with the memories of her past no longer weighing her down, she is finally able to set about building a new life in San Diego once more. But, being the daughter of two worlds is no easy feat-and Aspen will quickly discover the winds of change oftentimes lead directly into the perils of fate! The ALL NEW FATHOM starts right here! Writer David Wohl, artist Alex Konat and colorist Beth Sotelo team up once again to bring you the latest adventures of Michael Turner's most beloved creation!

Note: This issue has 10 (A-J) covers and 37 Retailer Exclusive covers.

In alphabetical order:

CoverLtd toArtistSidebar LocationDirect Edition-Alex Konat &amp; Beth Sotelo110th Anniversary Edition-n/a41Blank Sketch Edition-n/a35Special Reserved Edition-Alex Konat &amp; Peter Steigerwald44Archonia750Mark Dos Santos46BlueRainbow Online (day)300?Ale Garza3BlueRainbow Online (night/moonlight)300?Ale Garza2BlueRainbow Online Exclusive Limited Edition (day)300Mike DeBalfo &amp; Nei Ruffino38BlueRainbow Online Exclusive Limited Edition (night)100Mike DeBalfo &amp; Nei Ruffino37Borderlands1,500Ale Garza19Capt. Chuck's Comics400Marcus To29Captain Comics500-28Cleveland Comics-Marcus To12Collectors Ink1,100Paolo Pantalena23Comic City500Paolo Pantalena27Comic Ink1,000Ale Garza9Comic-Kazi500Mark Dos Santos10Comic Kings300Paolo Pantalena26Comic Paradise Plus
WV Pop Con
500-4Creative Comics700Oliver Casteneda22Drawn to Comics700Paolo Pantalena5The Encounter750Paolo Pantalena13Game On! Comics350-25Ghost Ship Comics200?-21Gotham Central Comics &amp; Collectibles300Chris Ehnot7Heroes &amp; Fantasies900Oliver Casteneda45Heroes' Haven750Ale Garza6Islander Comics1,000Paul Pelletier &amp; Tony Kordos33Lone Star Comics750-43Madness Games and Comics1,300Paolo Pantalena24Mile High Comics750Marcus To16Phat Collectibles730Mark Dos Santos47Planet Comics750Marcus To14Reader Copies-Marcus To15RetailerSlayer.com500Paolo Pantalena8Rockin' Rooster Comics and Games1,000Marcus To18Rupp's Comics--42San Diego Comic Con Aspen Century Limited Edition100J. Scott Campbell &amp; Peter Steigerwald39San Diego Comic Con Limited Edition250Alex Konat &amp; Peter Steigerwald40SAME COVER:
Smash It Exclusive Limited Edition
Retailer Exclusive Limited Edition
Big Red Comics
Comic Madness
Dr. Fantasy's Comic Books 'N More
Geeky ___? [scan unreadable]
Pizow
550Tom Hodges36Source Comics &amp; Games1,500Chris Ehnot20Stadium Comics700Marcus To34Texas Toyz750Paolo Pantalena30Uncanny Comics650Paolo Pantalena31Victory Comics750Paolo Pantalena17Wade's Comic Madness700-32Warp 9 Comics300Oliver Casteneda11In order by Sidebar Location:

Covers listed by Sidebar Location:Direct Edition - Alex Konat &amp; Beth Sotelo
Blue Rainbow - Ale Garza (night/moonlight)
Blue Rainbow - Ale Garza (day)
Comic Paradise Plus/ WV Pop Con
Drawn to Comics - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Heroes' Haven - Ale Garza (pencils), Ula Mos (colors)
Gotham Central Comics &amp; Collectibles - Chris Ehnot (pencils/inks), David Delanty (colors)
RetailerSlayer.com - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Comic Ink - Ale Garza (pencils), Ula Mos (colors)
Comic-Kazi - Mark Dos Santos (pencils), Autumn Frederickson (colors)
Warp 9 Comics - Oliver Casteneda (pencils), Paul Limgenco (colors)
Cleveland Comics - Marcus To (pencils), Josh Perez (colors)
The Encounter - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Planet Comics - Marcus To (pencils), Josh Perez (colors)
Reader Copies - Marcus To (pencils), Josh Perez (colors)
Mile High Comics - Marcus To (pencils), Josh Perez (colors)
Victory Comics - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Rockin' Rooster Comics and Games - Marcus To (pencils), Josh Perez (colors)
Borderlands - Ale Garza (pencils), Ula Mos (colors)
Source Comics &amp; Games - Chris Ehnot (pencils/inks), David Delanty (colors)
Ghost Ship Comics
Creative Comics - Oliver Casteneda (pencils), Paul Limgenco (colors)
Collectors Ink - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Madness Games and Comics - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Game On! Comics
Comic Kings - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Comic City - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Captain Comics
Capt. Chuck's Comics - Marcus To (pencils), Josh Perez (colors)
Texas Toyz - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Uncanny Comics - Paolo Pantalena (pencils), Mirka Andolfo (colors)
Wade's Comic Madness
Islander Comics - Paul Pelletier (pencils), Tony Kordos (inker), Will Quintana (colors)
Stadium Comics - Marcus To, Josh Perez
Original Sketch Edition - None
Smash it Exclusive Limited Edition (550) - Tom Hodges/ Retailer Exclusive Edition - Alex Konat &amp; Peter Steigerwald
BlueRainbow Online Exclusive Limited Edition (night) (100) - Mike DeBalfo &amp; Nei Ruffino
BlueRainbow Online Exclusive Limited Edition (day) (300) - Mike DeBalfo &amp; Nei Ruffino
San Diego Comic Con Aspen Century Limited Edition (100) - J. Scott Campbell &amp; Peter Steigerwald
San Diego Comic Con Limited Edition (250) - Alex Konat &amp; Peter Steigerwald
10th Anniversary Edition - None
Rupp's Comics
Lone Star Comics
Special Reserved Edition - Alex Konat &amp; Peter Steigerwald
Heroes &amp; Fantasies - Oliver Casteneda (pencils), Paul Limgenco (colors)
Archonia.com - Mark Dos Santos (pencils), Autumn Frederickson (colors)
Phat Collectibles - Mark Dos Santos (pencils), Autumn Frederickson (colors)</Summary>
  <Title>Awakenings</Title>
  <Volume>2013</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/all-new-fathom-1-awakenings/4000-418856/</Web>
  <Year>2013</Year>
  <Writer>David Wohl</Writer>
  <Penciller>Alé Garza,Alex Konat,Chris B Ehnot,Marcus To,Mark Dos Santos,Oliver Castaneda,Paolo Pantalena,Paul Pelletier</Penciller>
  <Inker>Chris B Ehnot,John Ercek,Mark Roslan,Tony Kordos</Inker>
  <Colorist>Autumn Frederickson,Beth Sotelo,David Delanty,Josh Perez,Mirka Andolfo,Paul Limgenco,Urszula Mos,Wil Quintana</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Dreamer Design,Joshua Reed</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Alé Garza,Alex Konat,Autumn Frederickson,Beth Sotelo,Chris B Ehnot,David Delanty,J. Scott Campbell,Josh Perez,Marcus To,Mark Dos Santos,Mike DeBalfo,Mirka Andolfo,Nei Ruffino,Oliver Castaneda,Paolo Pantalena,Paul Limgenco,Paul Pelletier,Peter Steigerwald,Tom Hodges,Tony Kordos,Urszula Mos,Wil Quintana</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>