<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Joh,Alpanu Lasas,The Wild Hunt,Tim Hunter,Cyril Ransome</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Noelle Giddings,Noelle Giddings,Jamison</Colorist>
  <Editor>Alisa Kwitney,Will Dennis</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-46648</GTIN>
  <Inker>Barbara Schulz,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Barbara Schulz</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:52:00 [Issue ID 4000-46648] urn:comicvine:4000-46648
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:19:51. [Issue ID 63625]</Notes>
  <Number>71</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="351113" ImageWidth="986" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="298514" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="302463" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="263872" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="286331" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="274095" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="256458" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="270023" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="226525" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="226682" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="310711" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="316508" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="353827" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="303710" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="279068" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="297495" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="266187" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="274995" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="230984" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="300344" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="310061" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="308236" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="253157" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Seeking to end the bloodshed and destruction caused by the Wild Hunt, Timothy Hunter takes his destiny into his own hands and challenges the Lord of the Hunt. Back on Earth, Cyril also takes action in a truly ghastly manner, putting his new magic kettle to the test. 

Tim wakes up after sleeping with Joh. He knows the Wild Hunt is after him, and doesn't want her to get caught in his troubles, so he leaves.  He plans to get the glamour stone that made him look like his mom so they don't find him.  He also knows, subconsciously, that sleeping with her was a mistake.  Joh wakes up, and is disappointed to see that he has left.

Cyril, using a glamour stone to pose as a classically-handsome older student, carries a sack with a dead woman--his mother--through the halls of Bardsey, and down into his old haunts in the caves underneath.

Tim has gone back to where he met Barbatos, to find the glamour stone that he had lost.  He sees his mother, then realizes someone else has found the stone and is wearing it. She takes it off--it is Lasas. She asks Tim why his mother would wear a stone that makes her look like herself--the implication being that his mother actually looked different without the stone--but Tim can't accept it, and assumes that it was a gift from Tamlin.  She keeps the stone, and tells Tim to run from the Hunt.  He has until tomorrow morning to escape.

Tim runs for a bit, but realizes there's no escape, so he decides to confront them instead. He uses the Sight to follow the glamour stone's trail.

He comes upon the Hunt's camp, where they are breaking out Drunk's beer.  He runs out to knock the beer away, affronted that they would drink what he spent so long brewing, but they knock him down.  He taunts them that he found them more quickly than they found him, and they agree to give him the challenge: fight a member of the Hunt and take their place if he wins.

Tim gets to choose the challenge, so he picks the Master of the Hunt, and makes the challenge a mini game console trivia contest that he happens to have with him.

Tim wins by a hair, and becomes the new leader; the old Master is banished.  Lasas gives him the glamour stone back.

Cyril puts his mother in the pot he got from Barbatos, which can resurrect people.  She comes out as a zombie, and now has to obey him.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:22:12.  [CVDB46648]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-71-the-hunter/4000-46648/</Summary>
  <Title>The Hunter</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-71-the-hunter/4000-46648/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>