<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Crawfish Cobbs,Rock Zucco,Crawford</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-57083</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:18:26 [Issue ID 4000-57083] urn:comicvine:4000-57083
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 13:49:10. [Issue ID 75873]</Notes>
  <Number>14</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(partial rpt)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Spellbound</Series>
  <Title>Love Story; The Saddest Story Ever Told!; The Revolt of Wilbur Bixby!; The Heat's On!; Close Shave!</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/spellbound-14-love-story/4000-57083/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>34</Count>
  <Tags>Crawfish Cobbs,Rock Zucco,Crawford</Tags>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Fantasy</Genre>
  <Summary>Love Story: The wife of an African guide plots with a doctor to murder her husband.

The Saddest Story Ever Told!: A scientist discovers a cure for baldness which he claims will "grow hair on a billiard ball". When the men who try the formula remain bald, the scientist loses everything and ends up sleeping rough in a park. Telling his story to a policeman, the scientist claims that the cure DOES work, but not on men. To prove it, he produces a handful of billiard balls - all covered in hair!

The Revolt of Wilbur Bixby!: A man becomes free of his shrew wife when they travel to Greece and he drinks from a fountain that transforms him into a centaur so he can eat grass and no longer has to depend upon her favor to buy him meals.

The Heat's On!: A succubus uses a mirror to blind a sea captain on leave as he attempts to push his homely wife out the top story window so that he tumbles out instead and winds up in Hell stoking the flames the way he used to torture his men.

Close Shave!: A shrew wife finds an electric razor annoying so she demands her husband use a straight razor. She demands he kiss her before he leaves for work, but each time he attempts to do so, she complains of beard stubble and sends him back into the bathroom to shave again. Ultimately, he cuts off his face with the straight razor.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Writer>Stan Lee,Stan Lee</Writer>
  <Penciller>Joe Maneely,Ed Winiarski,Carl Burgos,Russ Heath,Fred Kida,Joe Maneely,Ed Winiarski,Carl Burgos,Russ Heath,Fred Kida</Penciller>
  <Inker>Joe Maneely,Ed Winiarski,Carl Burgos,Russ Heath,Fred Kida,Joe Maneely,Ed Winiarski,Carl Burgos,Russ Heath,Fred Kida</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>