<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Ninjas,Ms. Li,Sung Li</Characters>
  <Colorist>Monica Bennett,Bad@$$,Monica Bennett,Bad@$$</Colorist>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Editor>Tom Harrington</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-42826</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Michael Heisler,Mike Heisler,Mike Heisler</Letterer>
  <Locations>San Francisco</Locations>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T19:16:12 [Issue ID 4000-42826] urn:comicvine:4000-42826
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 13:06:59. [Issue ID 59308]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image (Wildstorm); Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Deathblow / Wolverine</Series>
  <Summary>Logan returned to his home in San Francisco where he found his girlfriend Sung Li in tears. She explained that she had called her mother, and the woman told her she didn't have a daughter. When Li then went to her home, her mother threatened to call the police. Logan and Li went back to her mother's home, and she greeted them happily. She claimed not to know what they were talking about concerning the earlier incidents. Sung's mother then attacked her, and a small group of ninjas crashed through the window. They attacked Logan, but Sung's mother was cut and killed by one accidentally . Logan fell out of a window with some of them, and the rest launched a rain of arrows down at him. Michael Cray, aka Deathblow, witnessed the events, and shot one of the ninjas to keep him from killing Logan. Cray then escaped with Logan, taking him to his home to recover. Cray told him that he was in the area because he was following a letter sent to him regarding his old Team 7 teammate Phil Chang. The address on the letter was Logan and Sung's home, but Logan did not know anything about the letter. The group of ninjas arrived, almost destroying Cray's home in the process, and the two made another escape. They returned to Logan's place to find it in shambles and Sung Li missing. However, a mysterious grinning man in a top hat was there.</Summary>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deathblow-wolverine-1/4000-42826/</Web>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Writer>Aron Wiesenfeld,Ivan Zaidman,Aron Wiesenfeld,Ivan Zaidman</Writer>
  <Penciller>Aron Wiesenfeld,Aron Wiesenfeld</Penciller>
  <Inker>Aron Wiesenfeld,Richard Bennett,Richard Bennett</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Aron Wiesenfeld,Richard Bennett</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>