<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Tim Hunter,Mr. Currie</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Jamison</Colorist>
  <Editor>Cliff Chiang,Stuart Moore</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-45887</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Locations>London</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:48 [Issue ID 4000-45887] urn:comicvine:4000-45887
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:15:34. [Issue ID 62777]</Notes>
  <Number>61</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="161948" ImageWidth="975" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="252233" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="272627" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="290491" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="262205" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="293907" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="262176" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="264203" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="270418" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="300501" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="341954" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="282682" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="224246" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="229638" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="318563" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="293875" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="263284" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="274535" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="256514" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="295617" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="261911" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1517" ImageSize="246244" ImageWidth="975" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="301832" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Tim breaks into his apartment, thinking morosely about his father's death and all the others hurt by Tim's problems.  He finds Cyril sitting there, looking like a troll due to the glamour stone.  Cyril is pitying himself over being kicked out of Bardsey, and has taken Tim's Bardsey badge as a way to feel like he is still part of it.

Tim tells Cyril that his dad is dead, and when Cyril doesn't respond, Tim asks if he even cares.  Cyril then accurately asks if Tim cared when Cyril's mom died recently, in the car crash caused by the Other.

Tim grabs a few of his things for when he is on the run from the Other, including his mom's necklace, which he realizes is a glamour stone like the one Cyril is wearing.  He wonders why his mom needed one.

Thomas works with the copy-Tim he has created, who will be a decoy for the Other.  This copy-Tim looks like, and believes himself to be, the same Tim as from Thomas's original world.

The Other feels the copy-Tim's presence.  In-the-Know tells him he has felt the real Tim, but the Other is annoyed with In-the-Know for not finding him faster. In-the-No expands in an attempt to attack the Other, but spreads himself out too thinly.

In the morning, Tim waits where he is supposed to meet Thomas.  Instead he finds a bag with a note.  It says that he lied to Tim, and will not meet him.

Copy-Tim and Thomas wait at the house. Magical rats attack, and Thomas destroys them.  The Other shows up.  The Other kills copy-Tim, but is surprised when the world isn't destroyed. Thomas stabs the Other, and the Other, hurt, fatally wounds Thomas--as he wanted, dying along with "his" copy-Tim.  The Other calls on his creations to heal him.

Thomas, dying, sees the real-world version of himself, an invalid in a wheelchair.  At some point, Tim saw him and, pitying him, made Currie as one of his creations.  He offers his real self a choice--to die for him, and thus escaping his life in the chair.  Currie points out his own hellish life, and asks which is better.  Currie disappears.

The Other celebrates, believing he is now the only remaining Tim.  His Ravenknoll house implodes as he leaves.

Tim watches, thinking of the rest of Currie's letter--that Currie saw Tim as flawed, and uncaring of his creations, and that he must live up to the sacrifices his creations made for him.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:21:44.  [CVDB45887]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-61-all-things-timothy/4000-45887/</Summary>
  <Title>All Things Timothy</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-61-all-things-timothy/4000-45887/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>