<ComicInfo>
    <Series>The Best of Red Sonja</Series>
    <Number>None</Number>
    <Web>https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CBD19DJP</Web>
    <Summary>What better way to celebrate the 50th anniversary of the She-Devil With a Sword than to revisit her greatest tales in an all-new hardcover collection? Brought together for the first time in a single volume, these storied sagas trace the legendary exploits of the Hyboria’s favorite daughter over five skull-smashing, tavern-wrecking decades!

 

From her earliest comic book appearances in Marvel Feature and the very first Red Sonja series — penned by such legendary talents as ROY THOMAS and FRANK THORNE — to her contemporary epics crafted by celebrated scribes like GAIL SIMONE, MICHAEL AVON OEMING, and LUKE LIEBERMAN and artistic titans like WALTER GEOVANNI, MEL RUBI, and LIAM SHARP, The Best of Red Sonja brings readers more than 350 pages of crimson-maned classics — including:

 

• “The Temple of Abomination!” — Roy Thomas &amp; Dick Giordano

• “Red Sonja” — Roy Thomas &amp; Esteban Maroto

• “The Blood of the Unicorn” — Roy Thomas, Ed Summer, Clara Noto &amp; Frank Thorne

• “The Day of the Sword” — Roy Thomas, Doug Moench, Dick Giordano &amp; Terry Austin

• “The Message” — Michael Avon Oeming, Mike Carey&amp; Mel Rubi

• “The Return of Kulan Gath” — Michael Avon Oeming, Mel Rubi &amp; Stephen Sadowski

• “Birth of a She-Devil” — Luke Lieberman &amp; Sergio Davila

• “One More Day” — Jimmy Palmiotti, Justin Grey &amp; Liam Sharp

• “The Cloud Tiger” — Arvid Nelson &amp; Pablo Marcos

• “Wolves on the Road” — Eric Trautmann &amp; Walter Geovani

• “Red Sonja” — Gail Simone &amp; Walter Geovani

• “Queen of the Frozen Wastes” — Frank Cho, Doug Murray &amp; Gregory Homs

• “Worlds Away” — Amy Chu &amp; Carlos Gomez

• “The Coronation” — Mark Russell &amp; Mirko Colak

• “Three Wishes” — Luke Lieberman &amp; Sergio Davila</Summary>
    <Notes>Scraped metadata from Amazon [ASINB0CBD19DJP], [RELDATE:2023-12-20]</Notes>
    <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
    <PageCount>374</PageCount>
    <LanguageISO>EN</LanguageISO>
    <Year>2024</Year>
    <Month>2</Month>
<Genre>Fantasy</Genre></ComicInfo>