<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>The Kid with a Broken Halo</Title>
  <Series>Scud: The Disposable Assassin</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Summary>The issue begins in an office at Marvin's Manikans, where lowly employee Hershel Roundhead is having a meeting with his boss, Mr. Spidergod, regarding a "monster" that's been eating the employees. Mr. Spidergod tells Hershel that if he doesn't get someone to "take care of it", he would send Hershel down to deal with it. We then find Hershel outside on the street, standing in front of a vending machine simply labeled SCUD. He inserts three "Franks", presses a button and out steps Scud, the Disposable Assassin. Hershel gives Scud a disk containing all of the information he will need to complete "the job" on it, and Scud heads off to the Marvin's Manikans building to take out his target.

Once inside, Scud prepares his guns, and begins tracking the "monster", following trails of blood and mutilated bodies of employees. Finally he finds his target, Jeff, a monster with mousetraps for hands, an electrical plug for a head, a squid strapped to his chest and a mouth on each knee that shout pop-culture references as a form of communication. Scud shoots Jeff, and thinks that he is down, when Jeff suddenly gets up and mounts a counter-attack. Attacking with both his head and his hands, Jeff eventually sprays Scud in the face with ink from the squid and runs off.

Frantically searching the building for where Jeff ran off to, Scud stumbles across a startling discovery. Jeff has laid eggs. Scud decides to destroy the eggs, but Jeff ambushes him just as he finishes. Scud manages to shoot off one of Jeff's arms, and just as he is about to deliver the kill-shot, Jeff sprays him in the face again with ink and runs off to another part of the building where construction was going on.

Scud finds his way to a restroom to clean the oil out of his eyes. Upon finishing, he notices a label printed on his back in the mirror. The label states that he would "self-destruct upon termination of target". Not wanting for this to happen, Scud decides to abandon the job and run away. While trying to flee the building, Jeff ambushes him again, only now he has replaced his missing arm with construction equiptment. Deciding that he has no other option, Scud loads four of his fingers into his gun, and proceeds to shoot off both of Jeff's arms and legs. With Jeff now laying bloody and dying on the floor, Scud runs to a nearby pay phone and calls for an ambulance.

At the hospital, doctors have stabilized Jeff's condition and have placed him on life-support. However, as Scud finds out, the state will only pay for life-support for one month. Beyond that, Scud would have to pay for it, or else they'll pull the plug.

Looks like Scud needs a job.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-22 20:39:28.  [CVDB115931]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-13 08:13:41. [Issue ID 89570]</Notes>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Day>15</Day>
  <Writer>Rob Schrab</Writer>
  <Penciller>Rob Schrab</Penciller>
  <Inker>Rob Schrab</Inker>
  <Colorist>Eric Wiese,Jack Gray</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Rob Schrab</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Fireman Press</Publisher>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Adventure</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/scud-the-disposable-assassin-1-the-kid-with-a-brok/4000-115931/</Web>
  <PageCount>35</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Scud,Jeff,Spidergod</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="171134" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="239966" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="351280" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="346198" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="320372" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="265216" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="224670" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="257072" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="280390" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="265616" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="338644" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="343444" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="298720" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="470002" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="293982" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="302784" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="253184" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="386602" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="412960" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="545116" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="450346" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="320198" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="304314" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="412388" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="378968" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="260882" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="312936" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="274608" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="162264" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="491400" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="493110" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="153966" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="276226" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="92398" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="77818" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>