<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Ancient One,Artie,Benjamin Franklin,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Michael Hawthorne,Vetis</Characters>
	<Colorist>Val Staples</Colorist>
	<Count>45</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Axel Alonso,Jordan D. White</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-401205</GTIN>
	<Inker>Mike Hawthorne</Inker>
	<Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
	<Locations>New Jersey,New York City,Ryker's Island</Locations>
	<Month>7</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:04:42 [Issue ID 4000-401205] urn:comicvine:4000-401205</Notes>
	<Number>9</Number>
	<PageCount>22</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1955194" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1347321" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1657228" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="3265178" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="2073456" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1614365" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1731321" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1898378" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1921537" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1921081" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="2224344" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="2075267" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1711986" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1822690" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="2004528" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1681575" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1949152" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1915447" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1824190" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1861137" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1618114" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1586530" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Mike Hawthorne</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Deadpool</Series>
	<Summary>Deadpool targets a MAN with AQUATIC powers!

Then he teams-up with your SUPERIOR Neighborhood SPIDER-MAN!

I PROMISE HE KILLS ONE OF THOSE TWO!

SynopsisDeadpool, having just been harvested for organs by some unknowns, is unconscious. Agent Preston, however, is not. She tries to rouse Deadpool's mind but, being unable to, turns her attention to a door that is now unlocked in Deadpool's brain. She wanders into a museum-like room and marvels at how Deadpool sees himself, as art lines the walls all depicting mysterious opinions. She wonders what a darker part of the room contains and some of the art responds that they don't go down there. She asks who a couple is in a painting that has each face covered and she is scolded for getting too nosy. She promises to keep out for the time being as Deadpool begins waking up.

Deadpool wakes up on the sidewalk with no clue as to what has just happened. He teams back up with Benjamin Franklin and Michael the Necromancer to find out what they've got on the Ancient One's stronghold of magical secrets. Ben has bad news, that a prison has been built on top of the archives. Michael needs a way in so that he can teleport the team. Deadpool has a plan.

Michael approaches a police car and apologizes before lifting his kilt to flash the two officers. Taking the gesture none-too-kindly, one officer tazes Michael in the nads. Michael is booked and placed in a cell on Ryker's Island, the prison directly above the Ancient One's archives. Michael then teleports Deadpool and Ben in and the three descend a mystical rope to the archives. Ben and Michael marvel at the tomes while Deadpool goes off the kill the next victim on Vetis' list. It seems a picture of the Ancient One watches the two men left.

On a beach in New Jersey, a lifeguard named Artie hears cries for help. He springs into action only to find Deadpool faking a drowning. Deadpool then grabs Artie and tries to drown him. This doesn't work and Artie soon calls his underwater friends to come to his aid. Two sharks being gnawing on Deadpool. Artie calls the sharks off before Deadpool can "die" and Artie pulls Deadpool towards shore. Deadpool stabs Artie in the back and lets the lifeguard float to his doom (the two sharks return). Deadpool pulls Artie's mutilated body from the water and rests on the beach. 

Vetis joins Deadpool and proceeds to suck the powers from Artie's body. Vetis explains that each of Deadpool's kills gives him a bit more power so that he can take Mephisto out.

Deadpool leaves disgusted at Vetis and he and Agent Preston discuss the need to approach their dilemma of getting her out of his head differently. Deadpool meets up with Ben and Michael and the two explain that they found the spell they need but they need to learn how to get around certain magical defenses. Deadpool then suggests a new plan: Michael needs to talk to Mephisto personally to barter for his soul in exchange for Vetis. Deadpool then slits Michael's throat.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-10 10:20:43.  [CVDB401205]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-9-the-devil-the-deep-blue-sea/4000-401205/</Summary>
	<Tags>Ancient One,Artie,Benjamin Franklin,Deadpool,Emily Preston,Michael Hawthorne,New Jersey,New York City,New York Police Department,Ryker's Island,Vetis</Tags>
	<Teams>New York Police Department</Teams>
	<Title>The Devil &amp; the Deep Blue Sea</Title>
	<Volume>2012</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-9-the-devil-the-deep-blue-sea/4000-401205/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Posehn,Gerry Duggan</Writer>
	<Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>