<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Dredger,El Mestizo,Judge Dredd,Kurt Hellman,Major Eazy</Characters>
	<Colorist>Dylan Teague,Jim Boswell,John Charles,Matthew Soffe,Quinton Winter</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Cliff Robinson,Dylan Teague</CoverArtist>
	<Day>20</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1015113</GTIN>
	<Inker>Dan Cornwell,Jake Lynch,Nick Dyer,Paul Marshall,Simon Coleby</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>9</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:11 [Issue ID 4000-1015113] urn:comicvine:4000-1015113</Notes>
	<Number>2350</Number>
	<PageCount>52</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1836026" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1528115"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1418456"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1263653"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1439670"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1418879"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1783569"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1179853"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1704297"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1489390"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1405380"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1269156"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1511593"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1395289"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1396004"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1436364"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1483677"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1359824"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1499999"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1403748"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1370889"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1889081"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1837802"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1858339"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1902221"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1791222"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1287631"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1181627"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="986076"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1141930"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1144479"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="1758819"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="1889164"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="1342523"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="1847475"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="1527672"/>
		<Page Image="36" ImageSize="1453945"/>
		<Page Image="37" ImageSize="1523384"/>
		<Page Image="38" ImageSize="1313494"/>
		<Page Image="39" ImageSize="1549208"/>
		<Page Image="40" ImageSize="1893438"/>
		<Page Image="41" ImageSize="1620218"/>
		<Page Image="42" ImageSize="1667314"/>
		<Page Image="43" ImageSize="1610293"/>
		<Page Image="44" ImageSize="1637936"/>
		<Page Image="45" ImageSize="1959340"/>
		<Page Image="46" ImageSize="2492469"/>
		<Page Image="47" ImageSize="2082116"/>
		<Page Image="48" ImageSize="1534480"/>
		<Page Image="49" ImageSize="1237786"/>
		<Page Image="50" ImageSize="1441642"/>
		<Page Image="51" ImageSize="2202348"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Dan Cornwell,Jake Lynch,Nick Dyer,Paul Marshall,Simon Coleby</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(september 2023)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Imagine, if you will, Terrans, another 1982 — that as the Galaxy’s Greatest Comic was surfing a wave of cosmic popularity, it was decided to merge Battle Action into it. 2000 AD had merged with other titles before — namely Starlord and Tornado, which gave the prog Strontium Dog, Ro-Busters, Blackhawk and The Mind of Wolfie Smith — so if Battle became part of my emerald empire, what would become of the characters that joined its pages?

That’s the conceit of this special issue, where the likes of Major Eazy, Dredger, Hellman of Hammer Force and El Mestizo are given SF-fantasy makeovers!

But that’s not all — such is the success of the merger, that a couple of years later in our alternate eighties, it’s decided to create a monthly Judge Dredd title in which Battle properties are reinvented in the Dreddverse. You can read what’s become of Rat Pack, Johnny Red, Darkie’s Mob and more in Meg 460, which is on sale right now! And after all that alt-history excitement, you’ve got a zarjaz brand-new line-up of Thrills coming in Prog 2351 — don’t miss it, my Squaxx!

Cover: Cliff Robinson / Dylan Teague

Judge Dredd -  Juves Rule OK! (Ken Niemand - Simon Coleby)Mega-City One, 2075 AD. Home to over 800 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. A teenage Cadet Dredd is a rising star in Justice Department, but the Judges and the metropolis itself are about to face a terrifying disaster…

Death Game 2049 (Geoffrey D. Wessel - Nick Dyer)In the future, the privatised prisons gave rise to the brutal sport of Spinball, where the Death Row convict teams would play a live-action version of pinball, but on motorcycles and tooled up with all manner of lethal weaponry. These violent games were broadcast to a nation eager for spectacle until it was deemed too dangerous — but fifty years later, it’s back and it’s as bloody as ever…

El Mestizo - Demon with a Six-Gun (Chris Weston)1860s Texas, and the legend of El Mestizo is known throughout the land. Born a slave, he escaped the plantation upon which he was forced to work and made it across the border, re-emerging during the American Civil War as a mercenary, working for both the North and the South. He had no allegiance to either the Union or the Confederacy — he sold his talents to the highest bidder. But El Mestizo now has a terrible secret…

Dredger - Time to Kill (Karl Stock - Paul Marshall)Former Royal Marine turned DI6 agent Dredger is not a man to cross, nor get in the way of — tough, uncompromising and unwilling to negotiate, there isn’t a situation he isn’t prepared to punch, kick, or shoot his way out of. Few can get close to Dredger and though he was in the past partnered with former public schoolboy Simon Breed, who died in a bomb blast, his friendships tend to be short…

Hellman of Hell Force - Fiends of Ungeistwelt Ost (Arthur Wyatt - Jake Lynch)Major Kurt Hellman was a Panzer tank commander, taking part in the 1940 German invasion of Belgium — but he refused to join the Nazi party, setting up ongoing conflicts with the SS. But now, in 1943, German scientists have created a gateway to Hell in a bid to overtake the Allies — and Hellman has found himself stationed there, punishment for his refusal to toe the line…

Major Eazy - The Treasure of Solomon (Gordon Rennie - Dan Cornwell)The African desert, 1942. During the Allied campaign, few officers were as singular as Major Eazy — long-haired and laconic, this scruffy maverick never failed to irritate his superiors. With a cigar hanging from his lips and often found driving his distinctive Bentley, Eazy seemed crazy — but his eccentricities were overlooked because when it came to warfare, he always gets the job done…

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-20 20:15:16.  [CVDB1015113]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2350-prog-2350/4000-1015113/</Summary>
	<Tags>Dredger,El Mestizo,Judge Dredd,Kurt Hellman,Major Eazy</Tags>
	<Title>ad</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2350-prog-2350/4000-1015113/</Web>
	<Writer>Arthur Wyatt,Chris Weston,Geoffrey D. Wessel,Gordon Rennie,Karl Stock,Kenneth Niemand</Writer>
	<Year>2001</Year>
</ComicInfo>