<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Series>Good Boy</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Volume>2021</Volume>
  <Summary>Flint heads to the Hellfire Disco to meet an associate who can help him find the man responsible for Jon's death; Paolo Romano. This issue, everyone dies.

*List of covers and their creators:*
CoverNameCreator(s)Sidebar LocationACover ANick Bradshaw1BCover BFrancesco Francavilla2REBrodog Comics Exclusive Homage Variant Cover (48 Hours Movie Poster)Dayne Henry Jr.14RE

Brodog Comics Exclusive Homage Virgin Variant Cover (48 Hours Movie Poster)Dayne Henry Jr.15REBombardier &amp; Son Exclusive Homage Variant Cover (Terminator Movie Poster)Trey Antley9REBombardier &amp; Son Exclusive Homage Virgin Variant Cover (Terminator Movie Poster)Trey Antley10REFakeMan's Comics Exclusive Homage Variant Cover (Speed Movie Poster)Trish Forstner4REFakeMan's Comics Exclusive Homage Metal Variant Cover (Speed Movie Poster)Trish Forstner5REFour Color Fiends Exclusive Blood Foil Variant CoverNick Bradshaw3REFour Color Fiends Exclusive Wrap-Around Connecting Variant CoverBrayz Art18REFour Color Fiends Exclusive Wrap-Around Connecting Virgin Variant CoverBrayz Art19REFrosty Mug And More Exclusive Homage Variant Cover (Astonishing Spider-Man #14)Martin A Zavala16REFrosty Mug And More Exclusive Homage Variant Cover (Astonishing Spider-Man #14)Martin A Zavala17REHero's Corner Comics Exclusive Homage Variant Cover (Punisher #1)Bryan SilverBax12REHero's Corner Comics Exclusive Homage Distressed Metal Variant Cover (Punisher #1)Bryan SilverBax13REPatreon Exclusive Metal Variant CoverNick Bradshaw8REStray Dogs &amp; Good Boy! Comic Community Exclusive Homage Virgin Variant Cover (Speed Movie Poster)Trish Forstner6REStray Dogs &amp; Good Boy! Comic Community Exclusive Homage Virgin Metal Variant Cover (Speed Movie Poster)Trish Forstner7RETrinity Comics Exclusives Homage Virgin Variant Cover (Matrix Resurrection)Patricio Clarey11</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-13 16:14:43.  [CVDB907581]</Notes>
  <Year>2022</Year>
  <Month>03</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Christina Blanch, Garrett Gunn</Writer>
  <Penciller>Kit Wallis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Kit Wallis</Inker>
  <Colorist>Kit Wallis</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Dave Lentz</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Brayz Art, Bryan Silverbax, Dayne Henry Jr., Francesco Francavilla, Martin A Zavala, Nick Bradshaw, Patricio Clarey, Trey Antley, Trish Forstner</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Travis McIntire</Editor>
  <Publisher>Source Point Press</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/good-boy-3/4000-907581/</Web>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <Characters>Flint Sparks, Ginny, Paolo Vadicci, Rocky, Ruby, Tim, Vinnie Vadicci</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1395215" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1858913" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1376654" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1244596" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1297338" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1763531" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1757889" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1789216" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2000323" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1740240" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1636925" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1350633" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1408885" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1351725" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1250518" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2013822" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1597080" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1598925" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1883727" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1778927" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1344331" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1693501" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1539785" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1941297" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1684124" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1418098" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="2631469" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
