<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2390</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2390</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>I am The Mighty Tharg, galactically revered Betelgeusian editor of this awesome anthology! 

Another week, another circuit-shattering onslaught on the senses courtesy of my Mighty Organ. This prog we welcome a brand-new series to the legion of Thrills that have graced these pulse-pounding pages over the last forty-seven years - script-droid Mike Carroll and art-bot Joe Currie have crafted a hyper-exciting story in Silver, details about which I&#8217;m deliberately keeping&#8230; vague. You&#8217;ll gain the most from this ghafflebette debuting strip, Terrans, going into it knowing as little as possible, so plunge away!

Elsewhere, there&#8217;s a complete Future Shock from Honor Vincent and Mike Walters alongside the latest instalments of Dredd, Brink and Rogue Trooper. As ever, the House of Tharg is a seriously busy site of creativity - make sure you pick up the new Sci-Fi Special that&#8217;s out now, and in a week&#8217;s time Misty returns for an all-new special with stories scripted by Gail Simone and featuring the art of Aly Fell, Carola Borelli and Marianna Ignazzi. Joining it on the shelf will be Meg 470, containing yet another 128 pages of zarjazosity.

So! Much! Stuff! Can your brains handle it, my Squaxx?

*Judge Dredd &#187; The Bam-Hunters (Part 2)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law! Now, a powerful mage has travelled from Cal-Hab to MC-1, hunting down a pair of necromancers...

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 13)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Rogue Trooper &#187; Souther Belle (Part 5)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where use of chemical weapons has rendered the atmosphere poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the planet&#8217;s pollutants - G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they&#8217;re searching for the traitor that sold them out...

*Tharg's Future Shocks &#187; Station Madness(Part 1)*
Out in the vast reaches of the universe, there are an infinite number of stories waiting to be told. These cautionary tales pass from traveller to traveller in the spaceports and around campfires on distant planets, acquiring the status of legend, their shocking ends a salutory lesson in hubris. Anything is possible in these twisted trips into the galaxy&#8217;s dark side. Abandon your preconceptions, and expect the unexpected&#8230;

*Silver &#187; Unearthed: book 1 (Part 1)*
NEW THRILL! Earth, the year 2001. In the middle of the night, somewhere north-east of Bristol, England, a group of armed survivors have arrived at the ruins of a burned-out house, seemingly seeking something. On the back of one of the trucks they've arrived in is a cage. They break out the shovels and start to dig. They've been told what they're hunting for lies here, and it could be the key to saving the human race...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-25 00:31:16.  [CVDB1062859]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Writer>Dan Abnett, Geoffrey D. Wessel, Honor Vincent, Kenneth Niemand, Michael Carroll</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dan Cornwell, I.N.J. Culbard, Joe Robinson Currie, Michael Walters, Richard Elson</Penciller>
  <Inker>Dan Cornwell, I.N.J. Culbard, Joe Robinson Currie, Michael Walters, Richard Elson</Inker>
  <Colorist>Chris Blythe</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Jim Campbell, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Dave Kendall</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2390-prog-2390/4000-1062859/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Judge Dredd, Rogue Trooper</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1763233" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1596081" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1461531" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1459968" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1369902" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1179004" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1161682" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1347789" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1352315" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="977883" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="933392" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1135707" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1115833" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1134327" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1837197" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1927747" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1711538" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1562057" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1459828" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1388747" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1211589" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1331288" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1065048" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1226775" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1085427" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1157218" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1197536" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1123401" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1166893" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1024395" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1005854" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="985975" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
