<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Red Sonja,Bhamothes,Landre,Bregan,Hallister</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ivan Nunes</Colorist>
  <Editor>Luke Lieberman</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-274322</GTIN>
  <Inker>Walter Geovani</Inker>
  <Letterer>Marshall Dillon</Letterer>
  <Locations>Hyboria</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T03:45:35 [Issue ID 4000-274322] urn:comicvine:4000-274322
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 10:00:07. [Issue ID 851146]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>34</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="2587" ImageSize="1610136" ImageWidth="1680" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="2585" ImageSize="1379254" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="2592" ImageSize="1679343" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="2573" ImageSize="1473033" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="2583" ImageSize="1673635" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="2574" ImageSize="1538843" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="2608" ImageSize="1636041" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="2565" ImageSize="1520020" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="2606" ImageSize="1591412" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="2606" ImageSize="1508692" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="2581" ImageSize="1646273" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="2582" ImageSize="1701852" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="2594" ImageSize="1719810" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="2583" ImageSize="1731021" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="2595" ImageSize="1690100" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="2598" ImageSize="1668774" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="2594" ImageSize="1668035" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="2580" ImageSize="1497213" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="2619" ImageSize="1587595" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="2592" ImageSize="1610979" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="2598" ImageSize="1685722" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="2581" ImageSize="1366859" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="2583" ImageSize="1656165" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="2589" ImageSize="1698695" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="2582" ImageSize="1638346" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="2594" ImageSize="1682015" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="2591" ImageSize="1730834" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="2578" ImageSize="1709686" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageHeight="2582" ImageSize="1625101" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageHeight="2589" ImageSize="1582903" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageHeight="2578" ImageSize="1521924" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageHeight="2578" ImageSize="1514085" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageHeight="2585" ImageSize="1663162" ImageWidth="1680" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="632988" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Walter Geovani</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(noads) (2 covers) (Minutemen-Penner)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Red Sonja: Blue</Series>
  <Summary>Peter V. Brett, New York Times bestselling author of the Demon Cycle, takes the reins for this special issue, teaming up with fan favorite artist Walter Geovani to take Red Sonja back to her barbarian roots-and the She-Devil isn't going without a fight! When an unfortunate encounter with a demon deprives her of her trademark chainmail bikini, Sonja is forced to don a familiar blue fur tunic for the remainder of this adventure. Brett brings a mix of deft characterization, wry humor, and hard action to this one-shot homage to the Sonja legacy, honoring longtime fans while offering the perfect stand-alone story for new readers.

Red Sonja has been promised a handsome reward, and asylum for winter by a woman whose son has been captured by a Wizard. So, Sonja goes in search of the wizard, and chances upon a desolate stone tower. She enters with difficulty, only to find that it has an underground chamber.

Sonja reaches the chamber, and find that the boy has been tied up to be sacrificed to a Wolf Demon, whom the wizard is now summoning. Sonja reveals herself, and the wizard is angered by her presence. A brief fight ensues, with Sonja cutting off the wizard's legs. The Demon exclaims that he hasn't seen such courage and agility in a woman. He the commands her to sacrifice the boy. Sonja refuses. The angered Demon tears away her chainmail bikini to pieces. A naked Sonja then cuts off the Demon's head, skins him and shrouds her body.

She then frees the boy from his bonds. Later, Sonja brings him food she has cooked herself. The boy says he knows about Sonja's vow. Sonja modifies the wolfskin into a more suitable attire, and they head out for the boy's village. In the jungle, they are attacked by robbers. Sonja disposes of them quickly, and the boy too lands a lucky killing blow.

After arriving in the village, Sonja claims her reward, and the woman is too happy to reward her. She invited her to her bar. Sonja has her fill of ale, and sings herself to drowsiness. Later, she contacts some blacksmiths to fix her bikini.

Meanwhile, the boy expresses his desire to accompany Sonja on her adventures. Sonja rebukes him, saying that he does not have what it takes to be a truly skilled swordsman. The boy goes away grumbling.

Much later, when Sonja is very tired and sleepy from dancing and drinking, the boy approaches her with a sword. He challenges her to spar. Sonja is reluctant to draw her sword. So the boy, now angry, swishes away at her with swift strokes. A blow hurts Sonja's right arm. Drunken, she swears, brings out her sword, and strikes one blow.

Sonja gasps, only to find that she has decapitated the boy.

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/red-sonja-blue-1/4000-274322/</Summary>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/red-sonja-blue-1/4000-274322/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Brett</Writer>
  <Year>2011</Year>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Title>Blue</Title>
  <Genre>Sword and sorcery</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
</ComicInfo>