<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Jake Brikk,Marren Kane,Peter Elvis Twigs</Characters>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>David Hailwood,John Kirkham</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-461946</GTIN>
	<Inker>Brett Burbridge,Dave Thomson,Graeme Neil Reid,Mats Engesten,Simon Mackie,Tony Suleri</Inker>
	<Letterer>Hard Disk,John Robbins,Ken Reynolds</Letterer>
	<Month>8</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:22:49 [Issue ID 4000-461946] urn:comicvine:4000-461946</Notes>
	<Number>5</Number>
	<PageCount>31</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1254003" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1121267"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1791405"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1855215"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1421159"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1935942"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1714534"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1270151"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1745640"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="2036072"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1553664"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1573742"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1281988"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="807947"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1277944"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1305792"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1779811"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1975506"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1873642"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1815100"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1760968"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1821168"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1808887"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="2312569"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="2361446"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="2485221"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1510512"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1475395"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1511395"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1471795"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="132297"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Brett Burbridge,Dave Thomson,Graeme Neil Reid,Mats Engesten,Simon Mackie,Tony Suleri</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Biomekazoik</Publisher>
	<Series>100% Biodegradable</Series>
	<Summary>Bursting forth from some of the most deranged minds in the comics industry come six self contained sci-fi tales;

The Thing From Another Postcode by Dave Roberts (Futurequake, Something Wicked) and Dave Thomson (Psychedelic Journal Of Time Travel, Dr WTF?)

Peter Elvis Twigs receives a remote control and instruction guide for planet earth from an intergalactic delivery man, and begins to fantasise about all the good things he could do for humanity and, more importantly, himself.

Job For Life by David Hailwood (Toxic, Strip Magazine, SPOD! Oddities From Space) and Brett Burbridge.

Jake Brikk, pizza delivery boy extraordinaire, has 30 seconds to make his pizza delivery; if he fails, the entire delivery business will be handed to the customer and Jake'll be out of a job. Can't have that - Jake loves his job with psychotic devotion.

The Golem Rises by Mister Roberts and Simon Mackie (Hallowscream, Temple Showcase)

Something is pulverising people, defiling corpses...leaving one helluva mess. Fortunately detective Ballard has an outlandish theory that just might make sense of it all.

Marren Kane by David Hailwood and Tony Suleri (Slumdroid, Cosmogenesis, Bulletproof)

Dragged against his will into the cities sewer systems by a deranged cult of partially sighted cyclops worshippers, mutant superfreak Marren Kane must face his deadliest enemy yet; a gigantic amorous squid!

I Married A Creature From Outer Space by Paul H. Birch (Creepy Kofy Movie Time, Bulletproof, Toxic) and Mats Engesten (Brainstorm Comics, Atlantis Studios)

A troubled couple go to a marriage guidance counsellor to sort out their relationship problems. Oh, how Mrs Twinkle rues the day that she married a scrawny little maggot of a man from Mars!

First Impressions by Graeme Neil Reid (Judge Dredd, 2000ad, Meanwhile)

Peaceful alien explorers land on Earth and attempt to make contact with its inhabitance. Just one slight problem...it's 85,000,000 B.C. and dinosaurs rule the planet!

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-02-14 22:10:44.  [CVDB461946]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/100-biodegradable-5/4000-461946/</Summary>
	<Tags>Jake Brikk,Marren Kane,Peter Elvis Twigs</Tags>
	<Volume>2014</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/100-biodegradable-5/4000-461946/</Web>
	<Writer>Dave Roberts,David Hailwood,Graeme Neil Reid,Mister Roberts,Paul H. Birch,Tony Suleri</Writer>
	<Year>2014</Year>
</ComicInfo>