<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Garrison,Gully,Calibretto,Knowlan,Red Monika</Characters>
  <Colorist>Aron Lusen,Chris Lichtner,Liquid!,Ryan Kinnaird</Colorist>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-111947</GTIN>
  <Inker>Adam Warren,Jason Martin,Joe Madureira,Scott Williams,Tim Townsend,Tom Mcweeney,Trevor Scott,Vince Russell,Tom McWeeney</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Richard Starkings,Dave Lanphear,Richard Starkings,Comicraft,Dave Lanphear</Letterer>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:49:47 [Issue ID 4000-111947] urn:comicvine:4000-111947
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 06:45:58. [Issue ID 95763]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Adam Warren,Joe Madureira,Joe Madureira</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Battle Chasers</Series>
  <Summary>Robed figures stand over an open grave, in it rests a condemned man wearing mystic armor and all he feels is searing heat. It is but a dream, the same dream he always dreams but this time something is different, this time the dreamer cannot recognize the faces of the men.

The old man sits up and is seen to sleep on the wood floor, next to the fireplace with naught but a blanket. He calls out to Calibretto to get more wood on the fire but when there is no response he becomes frustrated and asks himself where Calibretto has gone to this time as he's never there when needed.

A small girl runs down a path covered with roots that protrude from the earth. She pants and gasps while she clutches a wooden box, saying, "Won't...let...them...get it!" She ran clutching a box that held something of which she did not know but the fact that those she loved gave their lives to protect it made her willing to do the same.

She turns around for a split second and suddenly her vision is filled with the sight of a giant wolf-like beast and though she does not scream in terror as a young girl might be expected to she shouts, "NO!". With his teeth he grabs her cloak at the back of the neck and as he lifts her up she tells him she will never give it to him so he swings her around like a rag doll.

Throwing the young, blonde-haired girl into a nearby tree she hits it hard with the flat of her back. Falling to the earth below and propped up against the tree she mutters, "I won't give it to you."

More of the man-like wolves appear out of the shadows, given away by their glowing eyes. The leader stands upright, holding a blade and tells her, "THEN. RUN."

And so she does till she reaches the edge of the forest and looking at the base of the plateau she stands upon she sees a city, Granok. It has been abandoned for years after a massive flood destroyed all within it, now she hoped in it she would find refuge.

She huddles into herself as she sits beneath a window ledge and gasps as a wolf-man walks by, his glowing eyes gazing into the window for what seemed to be an eternity. But when he passes she slowly stands up in surprise to look out the pane glass.

Suddenly, the entire wall bursts in as the wolf shreds it to get to her, terrifying the young girl with his tactics. But she stands firm and tells the beast, "Don't make me hurt you!"</Summary>
  <Teams>Battle Chasers,Golems,Werewolves</Teams>
  <Title>The Most Dangerous Game</Title>
  <Volume>1998</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/battle-chasers-1-the-most-dangerous-game/4000-111947/</Web>
  <Writer>Joe Madureira,Munier Sharrieff,Joe Madureira,Munier Sharrieff</Writer>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Joe Madureira,Liquid!,Tom Mcweeney</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Editor>Scott Dunbier</Editor>
</ComicInfo>