<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-109817</GTIN>
  <Inker>Angelo Torres,Johnny Craig,Sid Check,Al Williamson,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Sid Check,Al Williamson,Jack Kamen</Inker>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:33 [Issue ID 4000-109817] urn:comicvine:4000-109817
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:49:19. [Issue ID 9980]</Notes>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <PageCount>30</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="154317" ImageWidth="800" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1274" ImageSize="339377" ImageWidth="940" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1331" ImageSize="369425" ImageWidth="1003" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1125" ImageSize="352087" ImageWidth="842" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1133" ImageSize="363545" ImageWidth="839" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1133" ImageSize="338803" ImageWidth="835" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1122" ImageSize="350538" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1136" ImageSize="356533" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1124" ImageSize="329385" ImageWidth="837" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1095" ImageSize="262060" ImageWidth="834" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1106" ImageSize="293850" ImageWidth="827" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1118" ImageSize="332279" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1127" ImageSize="289521" ImageWidth="839" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1111" ImageSize="339831" ImageWidth="825" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1118" ImageSize="360994" ImageWidth="821" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1110" ImageSize="275219" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1130" ImageSize="343482" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1116" ImageSize="240231" ImageWidth="831" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1143" ImageSize="287085" ImageWidth="828" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1118" ImageSize="302847" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1114" ImageSize="246025" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1118" ImageSize="236854" ImageWidth="833" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1133" ImageSize="303758" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1104" ImageSize="297068" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1115" ImageSize="294487" ImageWidth="842" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageHeight="1111" ImageSize="333903" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageHeight="1107" ImageSize="290382" ImageWidth="831" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageHeight="1118" ImageSize="340817" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageHeight="1140" ImageSize="349370" ImageWidth="836" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="354623" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Al Williamson,Jack Kamen,Johnny Craig,Sid Check,Jack Kamen,Sid Check,Al Williamson</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Crime SuspenStories</Series>
  <Summary>Hear No Evil!: Rita is introduced to Fred Reardon at a party and sets her sights on marrying this rather wealthy man, even though he is stone deaf.....for his money, of course. Soon, she falls in love with Vance Tobin and together they plot to kill Fred. However, Fred is involved in a car accident soon after and regains his hearing, unbeknownst to Vance and Rita, and he overhears the plot to poison him.

First Impulse!: Joan and Helen are at each other's throats, as Helen believes that her sister is making eyes at Bob, her boyfriend. In addition, Helen also overhears the two planning a lunch at a cafe when they will surprise her with some news. So, Helen follows the two, and when she sees the two enter a jewelry store and pick out a ring, she feels her fears are validated. Later, Helen awaits the two coming home and she kills them both....then receives a package from a delivery boy containing a wedding ring engraved to her from Bob!

Second Chance?: Helen is waiting for Bob and Rita to return home and she confronts them both with a gun, accusing Joan of attempting to steal her boyfriend from her. They protest, just as the delivery man from the jewelry store arrives with the package with the wedding ring in it. Helen apologizes to Bob and Joan before Bob is to leaver on a train on business. Joan offers to drive him to the station. Thinking all is well, Helen sits down to relax and notices a letter on her night table from Joan, informing Helen that the pair have left together on the train and she will never see either of them again!

A Question of Time!!: A woman is found murdered and horribly mutilated, in a tourist cabin and the suspicion is that Harry Wismer has murdered his wife. They are wrong......at least for the time being!

Forty Whacks!: Fanny is 22 years old, but her parents will not let her use makeup, choose her own clothing or date boys, and she has had it up to here over it. Running up to the attic, she discovers an old hatchet, and a plan forms in her mind. Later, a detective investigates the murder of both of Fanny's parents and she pleads that she is innocent, that it was the hatchet that killed them. Later, Edith Vance tells her husband that Fanny may be right, as that hatchet was the same one used by Lizzie Borden to kill her father and step mother. Then they noticed their son had the hatchet and was coming for them.

</Summary>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-13/4000-109817/</Web>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Al Feldstein</Writer>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>27</Count>
  <Title>Hear No Evil!; First Impulse!; Second Chance?; A Question of Time!!; Forty Whacks!</Title>
  <Genre>Crime,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Irma (Mrs. Reardon's friend),unnamed detective,Rita Waldon Reardon (villain),Fred Reardon,Vance Tobin (villain, Fred's business associate, death)</Characters>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>