<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>If Looks Could Kill</Title>
  <Series>Deadpool</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Summary>Black Tom is once again broken out of holding by the Juggernaut. This time, however, the boys take a doctor with them. Later, Deadpool is hounded by men who work for Black Tom. Banshee and Siryn drop in the help. All seems well until Deadpool's regeneration abilities stop working.

SynopsisIn a covert facility, Black Tom Cassidy is experimented on by Dr. Killebrew in order to stop the wood-like growth taking over Black Tom's body. Black Tom is in incredible pain, but his torment comes to a close when the Juggernaut barges into the facility and abducts his friend. He takes Dr. Killebrew, who appears to have a cure for Black Tom in a folder marked "Wilson, Wade T.".

In a bar in New York City, Deadpool has an off night in picking up a girl and shows her his face. She flees the bar as armed soldiers enter. The soldiers attack Deadpool, but he makes light work of them - despite having to grow a spleen back. The soldiers get the upper hand, however, when they freeze Deadpool. Before they can remove the frozen mass, Banshee frees Deadpool with a screech. Banshee is surprised to see Deadpool - and vice versa. Siryn then shows up and stops the fleeing soldiers with screeches of her own. Banshee is disappointed that they can't follow the soldiers back to Black Tom. Deadpool is disappointed that the lovely Siryn isn't paying attention to him. The three then figure that Black Tom is not out to kill Deadpool but to capture him. (Deadpool and Black Tom previously tussled in the Circle Chase mini-series.)

Banshee decides to leave and gather intel from Interpol. Siryn wants to stay and keep tabs on Black Tom's target, but Banshee is hesitant, knowing that Deadpool is a loose cannon and not one to be trusted. Deadpool reminds Banshee of something called the Farouk Affair and Banshee decides that Deadpool can be trusted. Banshee leaves.

Deadpool then saves Siryn's life when one of the soldiers attacks with a sword. The soldier claims to be the best swordsman in five continents and manages to cut off Deadpool's hand. Deadpool finishes of the swordsman and then attempts to show off for Siryn by showing off his healing factor. His healing factor, however, does not work as usual. Deadpool ends up passing out from the loss of blood.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-04 21:46:57.  [CVDB39502]</Notes>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <Month>08</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Mark Waid</Writer>
  <Penciller>Ian Churchill</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jason Temujin Minor</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dana Moreshead, Mike Thomas</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Richard Starkings</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Ian Churchill</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Bob Harras, Tom DeFalco</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-sins-of-the-past-1-if-looks-could-kill/4000-39502/</Web>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Characters>Banshee, Bert, Black Tom Cassidy, Deadpool, Dr. Killebrew, Juggernaut, Siryn, Steve</Characters>
  <Locations>New York City, New York State</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="610976" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="904766" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1088070" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="910848" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1070305" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="975524" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1048522" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="877862" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="838694" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="820050" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="901109" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="934567" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="882588" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="898323" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1053207" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="922363" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="835774" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1024519" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1025282" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1060170" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1008383" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="876803" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="827805" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="146604" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
