<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Sometimes a Direction; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;: The Rot Knot</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>34</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Woody decides to write the essay in the school newspaper about homophobia that he thought about in the previous issue. Jenny reads it and congratulates him.

At home, his father is also glad he wrote it. He believes it is important to do the right thing even when it's hard. He had to do that himself in his job. He gives Woody a metaphor from his own father: "Pretty soon, you'll have to decide what direction you want your life to take. Like seeing a lighthouse on the horizon and sailing for it....Memorize where that lighthouse is as soon as you see it, Woody, because there'll be times in your life when you can barely make it out for all the snow and fog and rain."

At school, Woody's friends are all complimentary about the article. Zot welcomes him to the hero business. Woody worries about getting beaten up by the same bullies that hurt Harry, a kid assumed to be gay last issue. Zot says he'll protect him.

The bullies show up and threaten him, saying they'll get him later.

In school, Harry's sister, Pam, says thanks to Woody on behalf of Harry, kissing him on the cheek. Woody gets flustered and asks her out, but she explains that while Harry is not actually gay, she is. She walks away with Terry, who Woody now realizes is gay too.

Woody talks more with his parents, who continue to support him in doing the right thing. He asks his mom what to do about Jenny; he feels like she is never going to commit to him over Zot. His mom advises him to move on.

At school, George says that he thinks Woody's article was good, but it makes him anxious, because he is also gay, but has not yet come out. This is why, as Brandy suspected, he didn't go on a date with her a couple issues ago.

Zot hangs out with Woody after school, waiting invisibly for the bullies. The main bully punches Woody, breaking his glasses, which pushes him to actually hit him back. Still invisible, Zot uses his jet boots to make the bully fly way back into a tree, scaring off the other bullies and making Woody look super-tough.

That night the friends all hang out at Jenny's house. Her parents and brother are away. They watch some movies of Brandy's for her birthday. After everyone else leaves, Woody tells Jenny that it's time for them to stop dating, since it's clear she's going to keep seeing Zot. They can remain friends. She hugs him goodbye.

Woody helps a kid get a stuck baseball hat on the way back. He feels secure in his identity as a person who does the right thing. In a conversation with his dad, his dad says that he never reached his own lighthouse, but "At least I never turned back. Sometimes, a direction is a destination. For some of us, it's enough."

Jenny and Zot clean up the house. Zot says he's glad Jenny chose to be with him. She feels relieved about the decision as well, and feels free. Then Zot asks her if she wants to have sex.

In "The Rot Knot," Zot, Jenny, and Woody sail to Beanworld. Some of the local inhabitants say that it is suffering from Reality Rot. The friends and some of the locals have various adventures that are filled with Beanworld in-jokes and wackiness. They finally make it back home.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:32.  [CVDB94171]</Notes>
  <Year>1990</Year>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Eric Yarber, Ivy Ratafia, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-34-sometimes-a-direction-the-adventures-of-zot/4000-94171/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>Beanish, Brandy, Elizabeth Madison, George Tanaka, Jacob Bernstein, Jenny Weaver, Louise Bernstein, Mr. Spook, Pam Singer, Professor Garbanzo, Ronnie, Spike, Theresa Maria Veras, Woody, Zot</Characters>
  <Locations>Beanworld</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="235312" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="60596" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="162605" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="186654" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="190866" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="182702" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="161981" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="144604" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="162283" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="161934" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="173978" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="179734" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="158974" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="135664" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="202687" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="154985" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="176910" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="170882" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="158268" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="227506" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="249525" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="180572" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="205522" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="211538" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="222338" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="235062" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="227182" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="224076" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="233394" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
