<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Merv,Pa Pickett,Molly,Cole,Alexis,Suzie,Chester,Ethan's Girl,Adam,Alice,Dan,Ted,Pickett Boy,Ethan Daniels,Kenny,Sally,Taylor,Bernard,Nancy,Rob,Wes Wilden,Kenna</Characters>
  <Day>17</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-107255</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna,Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Inker>
  <Locations>Pennystown</Locations>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:08:35 [Issue ID 4000-107255] urn:comicvine:4000-107255
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 05:01:53. [Issue ID 107255]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna,Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Girls</Series>
  <Summary>In a shocking turn of events, the mystery woman will change the lives of Pennystown irrevocably, and raise more questions than answers: Who is this girl? What does she want? Is she a blessing, or a curse?

*Synopsis*
The group outside Ethan's destroyed house are shocked to see naked and identical girls running from the wreckage. They are even more surprised when the girls begin attacking. And then the Pickett boys show up. Ethan is roused by the sounds of gunfire and notes that Merv, Wes, and Taylor are unconscious. He rushes around the house and sees the naked girls viciously attack Suzie and Dan. The girls are chased off by Pa Pickett.

The girl Ethan found in the road emerges from the house and falls into his arms. Pa Pickett and his boy note the wound on her arm and pin her as the girl they are looking for. Pa Pickett points his gun at the girl but Ethan tries to protect, inexplicably stating that she isn't like the others, as she hasn't attacked anyone. Ethan then wrestles with Pa Pickett for the gun and it goes off in the scuffle. The girl dashes away and Pa Pickett throws Ethan down in anger. Wes arrives and knocks the Picketts down. He then restrains the two.

In Adam's house, he, Cole, Kenna, and Alice play video games. They hear commotion outside and Cole raises the shades to see his father kneeling over his mother. Cole approaches and sees that his mom is battered and not breathing. Wes gets her breathing again and Cole's father loads her in the truck and heads to the hospital in Bridgeville.

Wes takes Ethan and Taylor aside and states that they can't tell the townsfolk about the eggs in Ethan's bathroom. Taylor disagrees, but Ethan backs him. Wes then begins to interrogate Pa Pickett in front of the town. The old man claims to know nothing of the girls and Wes punches him. Wes gets further annoyed and seems unhinged until the boy wails that the girl had killed his mom. This sobers the onlookers and Bernard asks why the girls are trying to kill them. Pa Pickett explains that the girls are only trying to kill the women.</Summary>
  <Tags>Merv,Pa Pickett,Molly,Cole,Alexis,Suzie,Pennystown,Chester,Ethan's Girl,Adam,Alice,Dan,Ted,Girl Army,Pickett Boy,Ethan Daniels,Kenny,Sally,Taylor,Bernard,Nancy,Rob,Wes Wilden,Kenna</Tags>
  <Teams>Girl Army</Teams>
  <Title>Part 4</Title>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/girls-4-part-4/4000-107255/</Web>
  <Writer>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Writer>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Count>24</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Jonathan Luna</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>