<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Clive Vista,Judge Dredd,Judge Logan,Mickey Challis,Proteus Vex,Rogue Trooper,Tee,Tyranny Rex</Characters>
	<Colorist>Eva de la Cruz,Giulia Brusco,Jim Boswell,Pippa Bowland</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>John McCrea</CoverArtist>
	<Day>27</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1049538</GTIN>
	<Inker>Eduardo Ocaña,Jake Lynch,Lee Carter,Paul Marshall,R.M. Guera,Simon Davis</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Locations>Mega-City One</Locations>
	<Month>3</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:29 [Issue ID 4000-1049538] urn:comicvine:4000-1049538</Notes>
	<Number>2375</Number>
	<PageCount>52</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2899209" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1623215"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1231754"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1134255"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1468694"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1219705"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1691277"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1623179"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1415192"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="2247658"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="953367"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1170783"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="915582"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="917154"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="884818"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1203626"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1526078"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1698533"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="2146656"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1814832"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1685692"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1845859"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1471358"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1281768"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="975031"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="884888"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1100266"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="925293"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1108727"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1475339"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1325584"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="1259005"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="1480997"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="1289810"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="1389691"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="1156214"/>
		<Page Image="36" ImageSize="1327526"/>
		<Page Image="37" ImageSize="1452366"/>
		<Page Image="38" ImageSize="1308804"/>
		<Page Image="39" ImageSize="1411539"/>
		<Page Image="40" ImageSize="1632283"/>
		<Page Image="41" ImageSize="1560174"/>
		<Page Image="42" ImageSize="991111"/>
		<Page Image="43" ImageSize="1213155"/>
		<Page Image="44" ImageSize="1138333"/>
		<Page Image="45" ImageSize="1478657"/>
		<Page Image="46" ImageSize="1254771"/>
		<Page Image="47" ImageSize="1381432"/>
		<Page Image="48" ImageSize="1212014"/>
		<Page Image="49" ImageSize="1330507"/>
		<Page Image="50" ImageSize="1176759"/>
		<Page Image="51" ImageSize="1117448"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Eduardo Ocaña,Jake Lynch,Lee Carter,Paul Marshall,R.M. Guera,Simon Davis</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>The new issue of 2000 AD has been precision-tooled for those hungry to discover why it’s called the Galaxy’s Greatest Comic – with bitingly good stories from top comics talent!

Acclaimed Scalped and Django Unchained artist R.M. Guera heads the new issue’s stunning creative line-up alongside Suicide Squad and Petrol Head writer Rob Williams, Alex de Campi (Dracula, Motherf**ker!), Eduardo Ocaña (Messiah Complex), Simon Davis (The Royal Society of Portrait Painters), and many more in a special bumper issue.

2000 AD Prog 2375 is a 48-page special on sale from 27 March, with a bold new cover by Hitman artist John McCrea and colourist Jack Davies.

This latest issue is designed to make it easy for new readers to pick up 2000 AD, with a mix of brand new stories and ongoing series that showcase the best the GGC has to offer!

Reunited on Judge Dredd for the first time since 2014’s ‘The Man Comes Around’, Williams and Guera’s new story, ’First Man Up’, is the prelude to their forthcoming thriller ‘Rend &amp; Tear with Tooth &amp; Claw’, which begins in 2000 AD Prog 2376, on sale 3 April.

Supported by colourist Julia Brusco and letterer Annie Parkhouse, ’First Man Up’ sees Dredd plunge into the dangerous streets of Mega-City One to select a Cadet Judge for a new, top secret mission – but what many-fanged horrors await them in the coming weeks?

There is the senses-expanding return of alien space Imperium super-agent Proteus Vex in ‘Devious’ by Michael Carroll (Dreadnoughts) and Jake Lynch (Judge Dredd). As the centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people ends, Vex is now wanted, missing, and presumed dead…

With the announcement of the Rogue Trooper movie in 2025, it’s the perfect time to discover the missions of the lone blue-skinned Genetic Infantryman and, in the complete story ‘War Child’, writer David Barnett (Eve Stranger), artist Paul Marshall (Judge Dredd), colourist Pippa Bowland and letterer Jim Campbell reveal the all-too-harsh realities of life on war-torn Nu Earth.

Meanwhile, Alex de Campi, Eduardo Ocaña, Eva De La Cruz and Annie Parkhouse continue the space opera on Full Tilt Boogie as teenage bounty hunter Tee, her grandmother and cat – as well as their unintended passengers, a prince and a resurrected warrior – seek refuge but find their troubles only multiplying; and Kek-W, Lee Carter and Jim Campbell step into a world where everything really is black-and-white in reality-warping saga Indigo Prime.

Plus there’s the mind-shattering conclusion of the latest series of fully-painted folk horror Thistlebone, ‘The Dule Tree’ by T.C. Eglington and Simon Davies.

*Judge Dredd » Next man up (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, with the toxic Black Atlantic to the east and the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law!

*Full Tilt Boogie » Full Tilt Boogie: Book two(Part 9)*
Out in the deep reaches of the cosmos, teenager Tee — together with her grandmother and cat — is a bounty hunter/hired help, operating from her spaceship the FULL TILT BOOGIE. Capable and resourceful, Tee was paid to rescue the Luxine Prince Ifan from his debtors’ prison. In the process, she encountered a resurrected Anubite warrior, a member of the enemy race with whom the Luxine Empire was at war...

*Thistlebone » The Dule Tree (Part 12)*
Britain, 2020. It’s been over a year since journalist Seema Chaudry accompanied cult survivor Avril Easton back to the village of Harrowvale, where she suffered at the hands of THISTLEBONE worshippers, a crazed occult group that believed in an ancient woodland deity. One man in the village, Malcolm Kinniburgh, was keeping the Thistlebone legend alive — but now he’s dead, and his house is being cleared...

*Indigo Prime » Black Monday (Part 5)*
The multiverse. There is an infinite number of parallel realities, and all need managing in case of dimensional instability. This is where INDIGO PRIME came in, the multiverse’s troubleshooters, whose agents are trained to deal with space/time catastrophes. Now, IP’s HQ has been destroyed in a cataclysmic event, with most of the personnel lost, and its assets acquired by the company ICP...

*Rogue Trooper » War Child (Part 1)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where use of chemical weapons has rendered the atmosphere poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the planet’s pollutants — G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they’re searching for the traitor that sold them out...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 1)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Teams>Judges of Mega-City One</Teams>
	<Title>Prog 2375</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2375-prog-2375/4000-1049538/</Web>
	<Writer>Alex de Campi,Kek-W,Michael Carroll,Rob Williams,T.C. Eglington</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>