<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Doctor,Midnighter,Jenny Sparks,Hawksmoor,Engineer,Swift,Apollo</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ian Hannin,Ian Hannin</Colorist>
  <Editor>John Layman</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-66948</GTIN>
  <Inker>James Hodgkins,John McCrea,James Hodgkins</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bill O'Neil,Bill O'Neil</Letterer>
  <Locations>London,Skywatch</Locations>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:14:55 [Issue ID 4000-66948] urn:comicvine:4000-66948
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:22:04. [Issue ID 86061]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="841380" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="734366" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="824427" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="720539" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="678158" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="636536" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="675724" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="745207" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="631299" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="814590" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="689182" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="576835" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="706304" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="726289" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="552132" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="906718" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="621861" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="796687" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="857597" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="603887" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="865161" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="595325" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="769361" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1140564" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="928586" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>John McCrea,John McCrea</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Jenny Sparks: The Secret History of the Authority</Series>
  <Summary>The relationship of Apollo and the Midnighter takes center stage as the miniseries continues. On the run from Henry Bendix early in their careers, Apollo and The Midnighter are living on the streets, tackling conspiracies which never make it to the papers. What was being air-lifted between the United States and England for the UK's General Election campaign? And what does it all have to do with a drunken, screwed-up Jenny Sparks, shattered from her experiences as a super-hero in New York during the 1980s?  Jenny contemplates how being connected to the era has its pitfalls - for instance, her time during the 1980's. 3rd June 1992. Apollo and Midnighter prepare to launch a covert strike on an air force base. Apollo grabs one of the officers and questions him about the children they have in custody, before dropping him from a great height when the officier reveals the truth about the children. Apollo informs Midnighter of the scale of the abuse, and informs him they are heading for London. In London, Jenny has lunch with Princess Diana. After their lunch, Jenny encounters a man she hasn’t seen for years, Colonel Kirsan Pruzhany. Diana points out that she might have an idea as to why the Colonel is in London, and tips Jenny off to an event that is happening that night in East End. On Skywatch, Bendix speaks directly to Pruzhany about the plans he has in place. Pruzhany confirms the plan and Bendix congratulates him. Bendix asks the Colonel to pass on his well wishes to the Prime Minister. Apollo and Midnighter arrive in London and head straight for the East End. They enter an abandoned warehouse, and it becomes clear that they have walked straight into a trap. Pruxhany and Bendix reveal themselves to the incapacitated Apollo and Midnighter. Bendix address the two, informing them they were foolish to believe they could remain invisible from him. Bendix orders the troops to kill the Apollo and Midnighter.The lights in the room suddenly cut out. Through the use of night vision, the troops see a woman standing in the middle of the room. Jenny addresses Pruzhany, then electrocutes all of his troops. Midnighter takes advantage of the opportunity. He escapes and kills Pruzhany.Jenny briefly chats with Midnighter and Apollo. She then lights one of her trademark cigarettes and leaves.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-10-21 16:34:13.  [CVDB66948]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/jenny-sparks-the-secret-history-of-the-authority-2/4000-66948/</Summary>
  <Tags>London,Midnighter,Jenny Sparks,Henry Bendix,Engineer,The Authority,The Carrier,Skywatch,Lady Diana Spencer,Apollo</Tags>
  <Teams>The Authority</Teams>
  <Title>Rough Trade</Title>
  <Volume>2000</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/jenny-sparks-the-secret-history-of-the-authority-2/4000-66948/</Web>
  <Writer>Mark Millar,Mark Millar</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>