<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Shop Till You Drop Dead Part 1</Title>
  <Series>Army of Darkness: Shop Till You Drop Dead</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Summary>Follows Ashly J Williams after the actions of Army of Darkness: Ashes 2 Ashes

Grab the keys to the Oldsmobile and break out the boomstick, cause Ash is back! The wisecracking everyman with a chin of steel comes face to face with something worse than Deadite possession: Unemployment. Recently returned from his time traveling adventure to Egypt, Ash gets a taste of department store bureaucracy when he is docked for the damages caused to the store and discovers the evil spirit from the woods now inhabits the aisles of S-Mart. As a full-blown Deadite invasion manifests, Ash must fight his way through possessed shoppers and find the Necronomicon before the Army of Darkness is reborn in downtown Detroit.

Ash finds himself trying to explain to his boss at S-mart why he had to "borrow" some guns and ammo and how he personaly stopped a Deadite invasion. Mr.Smart seems to believe him but still charges him for the supplies Ash took. After Ash leaves Mr. Smart reveals himself as a Deadite.

Ash still angry that he need to pay for the supplies he took meets up with Sheila, his princess from 1300AD. She gets jealous that Ash pays attention to Mindy, a co-worker. Shelia storms off and locks herself in the rest rooms.

Ash then vents to Buck and Iggy about dames and how he has this wierd feeling. They are interupted by a girl asking them where Skiwies are, and the three men show her to the unmentionables aisle where she is revealed to be a deadite.

Ash and Buck defeat her with Buck's secret stash of weapons. With Iggy they try to get to the girls but are face to face with an army of Deadites. They decide to try to escape but the exit has become alive and possessed. Buck suggests the basement and the three head there.

Iggy askes them to wait for him and his newly possessed evil hand.

It is also revealed threw out that the Necronomicon that Ash forgot to throw into the time portal at the end of Ashes 2 Ashes had possessed Mr. Smart while he was on vaction in Egypt and used him to get to Ash in USA.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-01 13:28:04.  [CVDB111457]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-12 09:50:11. [Issue ID 304463]</Notes>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Writer>James Kuhoric</Writer>
  <Penciller>Nick Bradshaw</Penciller>
  <Inker>Nick Bradshaw</Inker>
  <Colorist>Étienne St Laurent</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Eric Basaldua</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Devil's Due Publishing</Publisher>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Humor</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/army-of-darkness-shop-till-you-drop-dead-1/4000-111457/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Ash,Sheila</Characters>
  <Teams>Deadites</Teams>
  <Locations>Egypt,Detroit,North America</Locations>
  <ScanInformation>(5 covers) (Digital-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="487168" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="396376" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="422624" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="501194" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="592336" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="567472" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="523242" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="534062" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="365234" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="460280" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="450518" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="414866" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="476908" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="435736" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="470364" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="501608" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="433790" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="389142" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="445296" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="619264" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="645112" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="432852" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="504024" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="758570" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="316370" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="400794" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="850820" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="572564" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>