<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Art and Soul, Part 2</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Zot and the others are attacked in their air-car by some missiles. Some of the local Pole Police's cars are destroyed but everyone is safe. They land and search the area. Butch finds a ventilation shaft that goes down into Dekko's base.

They split up, with some going inside and others waiting above. The ones above are quickly captured by more cone-headed robots. The inside team works their way through the base, amazed at its scale and complexity. Drufus and Vic become more and more frustrated with each other.

Dekko interrogates the group that was captured. Uncle Max realizes Dekko is having delusions and thinks Jenny is his ex-girlfriend Sarah. With Max's prompting, Jenny starts pretending to be Sarah, delving deeper and deeper into Dekko's psychosis--he is afraid of nature, chaos, and emotions, preferring to control. His love for her starts to break him.

Zot's team fights some more robots. Vic separates himself from the rest of the group and finds his way to Dekko. He turns off Dekko, using his technological knowledge, and takes the Key--just what Drufus thought he would do.

The Pole Police take Dekko into custody and Zot and his friends watch a video Vic left for them, explaining why he took the Key. He shows a recording he made of the leaders of Sirius IV, conspiring to attack Earth as a way to create unity on Sirius, thus driving up their profits.

Prince Drufus of Sirius is stunned but accepts the tape's truth. He, Zot, Jenny, Butch, Max, and Peabody travel to Sirius to intervene.

We learn that Max and Zot's family's came from Sirius as well. Jenny finally gets Zot to explain about his parents. They were perfect parents when he was very young, but at a certain point they argued and then left on what was supposed to be a short trip. It got longer and longer, and eventually they seemed to disappear. Zot sublimated his hurt into training to be the best at many activities. Eventually he became a hero. Jenny is thankful he opened up to her and believes that his parents must have had a reason to leave.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:31.  [CVDB24487]</Notes>
  <Year>1984</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Colorist>Adam Philips, Scott McCloud</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode, Dean Mullaney</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-4-art-and-soul-part-2/4000-24487/</Web>
  <PageCount>33</PageCount>
  <Characters>Butch Weaver, Dekko, Drufus, Floyd, General Harcort Schrapp, Jenny Weaver, Luthor Von Clokmann , Max, Peabody, Sam Twik, Sarah Melpignano, Vic Taylor, Weevis Swimbler, Zot, Zot's Dad, Zot's Mom</Characters>
  <Teams>The Pole Police</Teams>
  <Locations>Sirius IV</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="158548" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="196285" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="192239" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="178910" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="197066" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="181433" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="185381" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="203487" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="198860" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="185846" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="190812" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="193675" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="188040" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="208921" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="217822" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="201906" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="212374" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="204692" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="179062" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="184595" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="165915" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="189071" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="183697" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="178956" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="168845" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="174408" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="167202" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="179396" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="339617" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="115858" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="180352" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="181199" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="213600" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
