<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-139781</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:32:46 [Issue ID 4000-139781] urn:comicvine:4000-139781
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:59:40. [Issue ID 234810]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Avon</Publisher>
  <Series>Diary of Horror</Series>
  <Title>The Phantom of Philip Hawks; The Ghost's Curse!; The Mirror of Death!; Beware of the Undead!</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/diary-of-horror-1-beware-of-the-undead/4000-139781/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>The Phantom of Philip Hawks: Young lovers John Allen and Mary Kane set sail for their honeymoon voyage on their own ship, but they have been cursed by John’s rival, Philip. The jealous man wanted to have fair Mary for himself. Philip Hawks’ ghost commandeers the boat and they all perish at sea.

The Ghost's Curse!: Jarod Parks is secretary to successful classic dancer Mona Travis. Since Parks has gambling debts, he murders Mona and forges her last will. The dancer’s ghost, however, pesters Parks with haunting threats of his punishment after death. When Parks finally dies, he rots away in his grave fully conscious.

The Mirror of Death!: When on shore-leave sailor Steve Lajos changes into dapper businessman Robert Martin and robs unsuspecting ladies of their jewelry. The vain and arrogant Lajos meets his fate when entering the temple of mirrors, house of seven-armed god Struga. Lajos breaks the mirror which reveals his ugly inner self and is damned to live in the presence of vengeful Struga.

Beware of the Undead!: Trinidad tourist Nat Grear learns of the native lore of the Obeah man, a devil incarnate. There was a man named Tamiko who killed out of pure lust, until he fell to his death in a waterfall. Grear plans to shove his wealthy uncle into the cursed waters, but ends up drowning there himself. He now has all of eternity to spend and suffer along with the original Obeah man.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
  <Penciller>A. C. Hollingsworth,Norman Nodel,A. C. Hollingsworth,Norman Nodel</Penciller>
  <Inker>A. C. Hollingsworth,Vince Alascia,A. C. Hollingsworth,Vince Alascia</Inker>
</ComicInfo>