<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Colorist>Eva de la Cruz</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>Alex Ronald</CoverArtist>
	<Day>6</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1047419</GTIN>
	<Inker>Dave Kendall,Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Lee Carter,Simon Davis</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>3</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:28 [Issue ID 4000-1047419] urn:comicvine:4000-1047419</Notes>
	<Number>2372</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1460632" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1493488"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1747000"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1733462"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1600292"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1825430"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1740017"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1667327"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1627005"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1807133"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1176149"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1287839"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1124046"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1374457"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1257729"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1487252"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1570302"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1488879"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1435111"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1410394"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1162487"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1392357"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1359960"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1578176"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1189604"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1316656"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1009245"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1220628"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1102421"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="825237"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1107040"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="1218901"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Dave Kendall,Eduardo Ocaña,Henry Flint,Lee Carter,Simon Davis</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<ScanInformation>(march 2024)</ScanInformation>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Bow before my Mightiness, for I am Tharg, Betelgeusian being of immense zarjazness! 

We reach the nerve-jangling finale to the current Dredd thriller A Better World this prog, and indeed the whole issue is so stuffed with galactic goodness that it’s spilled out onto the back page. What other comic can give you this kind of uninterrupted cosmic magnificence — Indigo Prime, Thistlebone, The Fall of Deadworld and Full Tilt Boogie, bang after bang after bang!

Well, I can think of another title that’s equally scrotnig, and it’s of course the Judge Dredd Megazine— anything released from the House of Tharg is never less than one hundred per cent ghafflebette — and if you haven’t yet picked up Meg 465, I highly recommend you do so, for within you’ll find the start of a new Devlin Waugh series by Ales Kot and Steven Austin, as well as a complete Mega-City 2099 story from Ken Niemand and Conor Boyle, alongside Dredd, DeMarco, P.I., and Harrower Squad.

Add to that tributes to the much-missed artists Ian Gibson and John Burns, an interview with Wireheads writer Mark Eyles, and much more, it’s another packed 128 pages you can’t afford to miss, Terrans!

*Judge Dredd » A better world (Part 9)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges — empowered to dispense instant justice — can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD — he is the Law! Now, Accounts Judge Maitland has been conducting an experiment in Sector 304 in a bid to reduce crime...

*Indigo Prime » Black Monday (Part 2)*
The multiverse. There is an infinite number of parallel realities, and all need managing in case of dimensional instability. This is where INDIGO PRIME came in, the multiverse’s troubleshooters, whose agents are trained to deal with space/time catastrophes. Now, IP’s HQ has been destroyed in a cataclysmic event, with most of the personnel lost, and its assets acquired by the company ICP...

*Thistlebone » The Dule Tree (Part 9)*
Britain, 2020. It’s been over a year since journalist Seema Chaudry accompanied cult survivor Avril Easton back to the village of Harrowvale, where she suffered at the hands of THISTLEBONE worshippers, a crazed occult group that believed in an ancient woodland deity. One man in the village, Malcolm Kinniburgh, was keeping the Thistlebone legend alive — but now he’s dead, and his house is being cleared...

*The Fall of Deadworld » Retribution (Part 10)*
The planet that became known as DEADWORLD was once a regular civilisation existing in a parallel dimension. But the end of days is coming, and creatures called the Dark Judges are spreading their contagion, exterminating all life. While Sov forces have take advantage of the chaos and invaded, Jess Childs and co have been trying to save Judge Fairfax — but in the process Jess has been sucked through a portal...

*Full Tilt Boogie » Full Tilt Boogie: Book two(Part 6)*
Out in the deep reaches of the cosmos, teenager Tee — together with her grandmother and cat — is a bounty hunter/hired help, operating from her spaceship the FULL TILT BOOGIE. Capable and resourceful, Tee was paid to rescue the Luxine Prince Ifan from his debtors’ prison. In the process, she encountered a resurrected Anubite warrior, a member of the enemy race with whom the Luxine Empire was at war...

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-14 12:19:41.  [CVDB1047419]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2372-prog-2372/4000-1047419/</Summary>
	<Title>ad</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2372-prog-2372/4000-1047419/</Web>
	<Writer>Alex de Campi,Arthur Wyatt,Kek-W,Rob Williams,T.C. Eglington</Writer>
	<Year>2001</Year>
</ComicInfo>