<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Owl,Mal Donalbain (flashback),Zabo (flashback),Broussard [also as Arthur Tumolo] (introduction),Ben Richards,Bill Nelson (flashback),The Cat [Greer Nelson],Dr. Joanne Tumolo,The Cat [Shirlee Bryant] (flashback)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <Editor>Roy Thomas</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-12826</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jim Mooney,Marie Severin,Jim Mooney</Inker>
  <Letterer>Charlotte Jetter,Charlotte Jetter</Letterer>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:39:19 [Issue ID 4000-12826] urn:comicvine:4000-12826
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 15:53:26. [Issue ID 25826]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <PageCount>22</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="559870" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="562445" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="500423" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="567101" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="593008" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="535868" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="547353" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="573946" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="551038" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="603856" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="582902" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="533761" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="575497" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="615937" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="589090" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="514564" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="549188" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="585212" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="475549" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="600400" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="588170" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="574441" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>The Cat</Series>
  <Summary>Greer Grant stars as The Cat! It's a Chicago skyline battle as the Cat goes claw-to-talon with The Owl, Daredevil's enemy!

When we last saw the Cat, she was fleeing Malcolm Donalbain's burning building. Later that same night, we found her puzzling over some strange sensations that had led her to the roof of a hospital. She'd been certain her mentor, Dr. Joanne Tumulo, had died, but she seemed to hear the professor's voice in her head. Climbing down a wall, she clung outside the doctor's window and was relieved to overhear a doctor state that she would recover. The woman in the Cat uniform, Greer Nelson, went home to rest until the next day.

In an extended flashback, Greer recalled how she and Shirlee Bryant had participated in an experimental conditioning program designed by Dr. Tumulo and funded by Shirlee's patron, Mal Donalbain. The doctor discovered Donalbain was going to use her discoveries to create an army of enhanced women who would use his chain of health spas as a front to take over the nation. Dressed in a yellow-and-blue Cat uniform, Shirlee was to be their prototype. Dr. Tumulo was horrified to see Shirlee follow Donalbain's orders, without regard to her own safety, and fall to her death while demonstrating her new acrobatic abilities. She fled, taking one of the uniforms as evidence for the police. Donalbain ordered his henchmen to set off an explosion at her lab to destroy the evidence and get rid of her interference. Greer had taken the Cat uniform and used it to stop Donalbain and avenge her mentor. She was relieved that Dr. Tumulo needed her now, not the Cat.

The next morning, Greer drove to the hospital. There, she met Dr. Tumulo's attorney, Ben Richards, and Arthur Tumulo. While Tumulo excused himself, the attorney told Greer he'd never heard the doctor mention a nephew. In fact, she'd named Greer as her sole beneficiary in her will. While they were speaking, someone hijacked an ambulance and abducted Dr. Tumulo. Greer jumped in her convertible and followed them, but lost them in the warehouse district. Inside one of the buildings one of the kidnappers asked the man who had posed as Arthur Tumulo, calling him Mr. Broussard, what they should do about their pursuer? He ordered them to bring Greer along. At gunpoint, they brought her into an elevator and took her and the doctor to the next floor. There they met one of Daredevil's rogues gallery, the Owl. When the Owl berated Brousard, the henchman reminded him he'd gotten the others for him, and Tumulo was ready for the transfer. Greer demanded to know what was going on. The Owl responded by explaining he was gathering the wisdom of businessmen, artists, and scientists on tape for his own use. Dr. Tumulo's mind was about to join the others. One of the Owl's henchmen escorted Greer out. He knocked her unconscious, then locked her in a closet.

When Greer awoke, she put on the Cat uniform (which she'd luckily brought along in her purse). She used her super sensitivity to pick the lock and escape. She located the doctor being wheeled back onto the elevator, knocked out the goon with her, and took her back to the ambulance. As the Cat attempted to drive away, the Owl and his henchmen emerged from the building to stop her. She pulled a fire alarm manual station to bring help, then battled the villains. When the fire engine arrived, with a police car in support, the Owl retreated to his building. He found Broussard attempting to feed the contents of the tapes into his own brain. The attempt to download all the information at once overloaded Broussard's mind, leaving him comatose. The Owl fled to his rooftop heliport, but the Cat was waiting for him there. He escaped by leaping over the edge. The Cat was surprised to see him fly away, leaving her to deal with Dr. Tumulo and the police.</Summary>
  <Tags>Mal Donalbain,Shirlee Bryant,Tigra,Owl,Dr. Joanne Tumolo,Zabo,Bill Nelson</Tags>
  <Title>The Owl and the Pussycat!!</Title>
  <Volume>1972</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-cat-2-the-owl-and-the-pussycat/4000-12826/</Web>
  <Writer>Linda Fite,Linda Fite</Writer>
  <Year>1973</Year>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>