<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-907</GTIN>
  <Inker>Bernard Baily,S. Finocchiaro,Tony Mortellaro,Eugene Hughes,S. Finocchiaro,Tony Mortellaro,Eugene Hughes</Inker>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T22:01:34 [Issue ID 4000-907] urn:comicvine:4000-907
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-17 02:30:15. [Issue ID 11052]</Notes>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Bernard Baily,Sal Trapani,Tony Mortellaro,Eugene Hughes,Sal Trapani,Tony Mortellaro,Eugene Hughes</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Stanley Morse</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(19pages)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Weird Mysteries</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/weird-mysteries-8/4000-907/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>12</Count>
  <Title>I Killed Mary; Premonition; The Witche's Curse [sic]; Bum Ticker; The One That Got Away</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>I Killed Mary: Bland weakling Robby is ignored and ridiculed by his family and peers for being nondescript and dull. When he decides to kill the local pretty girl Mary to prove he can be dangerous and exciting, no-one believes he did it. Distraught at not getting any respect or credit for being bold and daring, Robby then hangs himself out of depression.

Premonition: A college student has a premonition that his home town was destroyed by devils from hell. When he gets home, he's relieved to see his parents are OK and that it was all a dream. He doesn't notice they have devil tails...

The Witche's Curse [sic]: A broken man who's tired of being bullied by his brutish wife goes for a walk one night and encounters a witch. She offers to change him into anything he wants and warns him not to tell anyone about her. He asks to be turned into a powerful black knight so he can kill his wife. After the deed is done, he's upset about not getting credit for the murder and tells the police what happened. They don't believe him, but since he ratted on the witch, she turns him into a rat before their eyes. The rat is then hung for the murder of the wife.

Bum Ticker: A young go-getter man is upset that he has a weak heart and is told by his doctor to give up his lifestyle. Depressed, he finds out about a strange doctor that can help him using unorthodox methods. He agrees to get surgery by this doctor and everything turns out fine. That is until he finds himself speeding up or slowing down at unnatural levels. Finally his heart breaks apart and it's revealed that the doctor had replaced his heart with a mechanical one.

The One That Got Away: A prize fisherman and his friend go fishing in a stream. When the fisherman gets killed by hundreds of fish looking for revenge, his friend who managed to escape, realizes that he was "The One That Got Away".

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Editor>Stanley Morse</Editor>
</ComicInfo>