<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Witchblade,Jackie Estacado,Butcher Joyce</Characters>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Day>20</Day>
  <Editor>Marc Silvestri,Rob Levin</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-110758</GTIN>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:58:42 [Issue ID 4000-110758] urn:comicvine:4000-110758
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 12:25:00. [Issue ID 361017]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>15</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="677971" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="310019" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="586952" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="585279" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="633813" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="520773" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="555083" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="554790" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="544524" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="846909" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="506494" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="571006" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="445426" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="665193" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="428819" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>First Born First Look</Series>
  <Summary>Overview

The Summer Event of 2007 begins here! Top Cow Productions is proud to present a sneak preview of First Born, the highly anticipated three issue limited series debuting in July. Buzz has been steadily building for Top Cow's first comic event in years since it was first announced in Wizard Magazine's 2007 Preview Issue in January.

This First Look introduces new fans to the story leading into First Born as well as an exclusive early look at the event itself. 

Witchblade Recap

Sara Pezzini was the daughter of a New York City police officer. She followed in her father's footsteps and during an undercover investigation one night, stumbled upon the Witchblade and became its latest bearer. The artifact with enormous destructive potential and Sara has had to wrestle against it time and again. The Witchblade is the male offspring of two forces of the universe, The Angelus and The Darkness. After learning about the Witchblade, Sara remained a cop and started taking on the cases that were too weird or were deemed unsolvable. That all ended when she became pregnant. The pregnancy was unexpected and impossible because Sara hadn't had sex in more than a year. Nevertheless she decided to keep the child. To assure its safety she passed on the Witchblade to Danielle Baptiste and took time off work. Some of her allies include Detective Patrick Gleason (her lover), Patience (the current Magdalena), and Jackie Estacado (current wielder of The Darkness). Their common enemy is the Angelus. Though currently without a host, the agents of the Angelus are still completing their masters work. 

The Darkness (partial story)

The Butcher is torturing a member of an Armenian gang that has been moving into Franchetti territory. Butch tries to get something out of him but even removing teeth fails to provide any information. Jackie comes from the shadows and starts his own interrogation. He first talks kindly with the man, but when he receives nothing but insults in return, it's time to stop being gentle. Jackie turns out the lights and starts to terrify the man with his creatures. The man screams in fear and seems ready to talk, but before he can, the roof of the building is torn open and Angelus pour in. 

Sketchbook

The last couple pages are filled with sketches and art made by Stjepan Sejic.</Summary>
  <Teams>Angelus Warriors</Teams>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/first-born-first-look-1/4000-110758/</Web>
  <Writer>Ron Marz</Writer>
  <Year>2007</Year>
  <StoryArc>First Born</StoryArc>
  <Penciller>Stjepan Šejić</Penciller>
  <Inker>Stjepan Šejić</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Stjepan Šejić</CoverArtist>
  <Title>First Born</Title>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
</ComicInfo>