<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Fantastic Comics</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Count>23</Count>
  <Title>The Power of the Slave-Giant's Goddess; Out to Lunch; The Treasure of Coralla; The Secrets of Magic</Title>
  <Volume>1939</Volume>
  <Genre>War,Spy,Superhero,Fantasy,Jungle,Science fiction,Sword and sorcery,Humor,Adventure</Genre>
  <Summary>Jean Dorne is secretary for J.B. Reegan, owner of Black Star Line shipping. Jean goes to the police when she has overheard that Reegan is employing underworld figure Mr. Jackson to pirate his own ships for the insurance money.  The police pay Jean no heed, and when she is captured, it is Samson who must rescue her and bring the villains to justice.

The Three-armed tyrants keep the Dwarf-Men of Mars under their power with the aid of their minions, the Slave-Giants. Flick and Adele have promised to help them become free, and the Dwarf-Men hatch a plan whereby Adele will impersonate the idol of the Slave-Giants, and break them free from the Three-armed invaders.

Sir Richard sets off once again for the Holy Land with a new company of crusaders. He meets the wizard Kara on the way, who enlists him on a mission to recover the Golden Chalice. He arms Richard with a magic ring, and sets him on his way. Richard must overcome many magic beasts on the way to his ultimate battle with the giant guardian of the chalice, Gotha. He brings Kara the chalice, and is rewarded for his work with a cloak of invulnerability.

The US Government is aware that information on their defenses has been smuggled out of the country into the hands of our enemies, but cannot find how. Yank Wilson, Agent Q-4, enlists the aid of fellow agent X-16. They troll for clues, and find themselves on the trail of a foreign artist, Count Jorgka, who paints landscapes in America, and sells them abroad. Yank has a hunch, but will they stop the Count before he wiggles out of their grasp?

Diverted from their mission to Mars, Space Smith and Dianna are captured by the robot scientists of Venus who wish to turn Dianna into one of their Leopard Women by brain transplant.

Captain Kidd seeks the lost explorer, Arndt Barrows and his company, who had fallen captive of the jungle magician, Negus.  All of Barrows party are now dead, with the exception of Colonel Bennet, who is being tortured by Negus.  Kidd's exploration party are magically killed from a distance, one by one, as Kidd closes in on Negus' lair, in the bowl of a great jungle tree.

The neighborhood brat plays with the Professor's inventions, uninvited, and, in the process of shooing him away, the Professor unwittingly causes an accident which propels him to the wrong side of a mirror.  The brat tries to help him break free, but when these efforts fail, the brat gloats over the Professor's misfortune.  The Professor gets his revenge.

A criminal scientist, dubbed the "Demon", creates a device which can destroy a coastal city with a tidal wave.  He tests in on a cruise ship, killing 2,000 innocents, before training it on New York City. Stardust arrives, and makes the "Demon" a victim of his own device before stopping the wave and saving the City.

Sub goes on a mission to salvage treasure from shipwrecks near Atlantis, and Peg stows away to join him. Poseida, King of the mermen from nearby Coralla, has been busy gathering the treasure for himself, and captures Sub and Peg.  Poseida offers Sub treasure to allow him to keep Peg as his queen.  When Sub refuses, he must face a monstrous crab in a pit fight. Sub escapes and radios Lantida for help, and the Atlantean mermen come to Sub's aid.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:10:27. [Issue ID 656]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fox</Publisher>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Year>1940</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>(february 1940)</ScanInformation>
  <Characters>Mr. Jackson,Jean Dorne,J. B. Reegan (villain, introduction),Samson</Characters>
  <Writer>Audrey Blum,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Jack Farr,Waldo Harrison,Will Eisner,Orville Wells,Hank Christy,Toni Blum,Boris Plaster,Will Eisner,Orville Wells,Jack Farr,Hank Christy,Toni Blum,Boris Plaster,Fletcher Hanks</Writer>
  <Penciller>Alex Anthony Blum,Bill Bossert,Don Rico,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Grieg Chapian,H.C. Kiefer,Jack Farr,Lou Fine,Alex Blum,Hank Christy,George Tuska,Boris Plaster,Karl Kief,Alex Blum,Don Rico,Grieg Chapian,Jack Farr,Hank Christy,George Tuska,Boris Plaster,Fletcher Hanks,Karl Kief</Penciller>
  <Inker>Alex Anthony Blum,Bill Bossert,Don Rico,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Grieg Chapian,H.C. Kiefer,Jack Farr,Lou Fine,Alex Blum,Hank Christy,George Tuska,Boris Plaster,Henry Kiefer,Alex Blum,Don Rico,Grieg Chapian,Jack Farr,Hank Christy,George Tuska,Boris Plaster,Fletcher Hanks,Henry Kiefer</Inker>
  <Colorist>Mike Okamoto,Mike Okamoto</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab,Jack Farr,Jack Farr,Fletcher Hanks,Fred Schwab</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
    <Page Image="67" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>J. B. Reegan (villain,introduction),Mr. Jackson,Jean Dorne,Samson</Tags>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/fantastic-comics-3-the-giant-mystery-plane/4000-197116/</Web>
  <Teams>Leopard Women of Venus,Frogmen,Martian Slave Giants,Saurian Lizards,Robot Scientists,Mermen of Coralla,Martians,Three Armed Martians</Teams>
  <Locations>Space,Venus,Mars of the Fouth Dimension,Atlantis,Coralla,New York City,Fourth Dimension,Africa,Mars</Locations>
  <CoverArtist>Lou Fine</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Victor Fox</Editor>
</ComicInfo>