<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Werewolf By Night,Luther Kane,Mr. Evans,Lissa Russell,Judson Hemp,Joshua Kane,Desmond</Characters>
  <Colorist>Glynis Oliver Wein</Colorist>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Editor>Roy Thomas</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-13197</GTIN>
  <Inker>Mike Ploog,Mike Ploog</Inker>
  <Letterer>John Costanza</Letterer>
  <Locations>Los Angeles,California</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:02:27 [Issue ID 4000-13197] urn:comicvine:4000-13197
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-20 19:29:21. [Issue ID 13197]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <PageCount>21</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="6046929" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="3559382" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="4003879" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="3490144" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="3447364" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="3169869" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="3523806" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="3929965" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="4269422" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="3776249" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="3820176" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="3317609" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="4206851" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="4360893" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="3577780" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="3775135" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="3582137" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="3414919" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="3720661" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="4398819" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="4166437" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Mike Ploog,Mike Ploog</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Werewolf by Night</Series>
  <Summary>When the hermit-millionaire Luthor Kane holds Jack's sister hostage, the hairy horror storms the millionaire's mansion!

Having survived Joshua Kane's hunt, but with a gunshot wound in his shoulder, Jack Russell returns to Kane's ranch to rescue his sister, Lissa. After tending to his injury, however, he is confronted by the hunter's brother, Luther Kane, and Kane's hired muscle, Desmond. Luther offers Jack a deal: he can cure Lissa before she ever falls to the family curse, but only if Jack, as the Werewolf, kills a business rival named Judson Hemp. The desperate Jack reluctantly agrees.

That evening, Luther drops Jack off outside Hemp's heavily guarded compound. After moonrise, the Werewolf makes his way through armed guards and attack dogs, finally entering the house through a skylight, where Hemp adjusts a telescope. The senile old man looks upon the Werewolf as if he were a puppy, when the beast unexpectedly reverts to Jack, thanks to a lunar eclipse.

Refusing to harm the gentle old man, Jack fights his way outside, steals a motorcycle, and escapes the compund. He reaches Kane's ranch where he accosts Luther, demanding Lissa's cure, but is restrained by Desmond. As the thug holds Jack in a bear hug, the eclipse ends, and the Werewolf re-emerges. Desmond flings a stiletto at the beast, who ducks and then kills his opponent. Behind him, Luther collapses, the stiletto sticking out of his chest. The Werewolf frees Lissa from her cell.</Summary>
  <Tags>California,Werewolf By Night,Los Angeles,Luther Kane,Mr. Evans,Werewolves,Lissa Russell,Judson Hemp,Joshua Kane,Desmond</Tags>
  <Teams>Werewolves</Teams>
  <Title>A Life For A Death!</Title>
  <Volume>1972</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/werewolf-by-night-5-a-life-for-a-death/4000-13197/</Web>
  <Writer>Len Wein</Writer>
  <Year>1973</Year>
  <Count>43</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Mike Ploog</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>