<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Death Queen,Evil Ernie,Lady Death,Lucifer,Matthias,Purgatori,Smiley,Vassago</Characters>
	<Count>4</Count>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-119600</GTIN>
	<Locations>Egypt,Europe,Hell,Pennsylvania,Pittsburgh,Styx</Locations>
	<Month>1</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:40:24 [Issue ID 4000-119600] urn:comicvine:4000-119600</Notes>
	<Number>1</Number>
	<PageCount>25</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="389924" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="427611"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="545816"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="565310"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="505778"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="499886"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="488211"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="499296"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="614006"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="567473"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="599928"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="596097"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="588969"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="593498"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="419456"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="523785"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="513831"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="508963"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="537136"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="630493"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="519636"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="590274"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="575250"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="563565"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="412956"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Chaos! Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Lady Death: Between Heaven and Hell</Series>
	<Summary>*Present Day.*
Lady Death stands in her Endless Graveyard and while the undisputed master of Hell she is plagued with nightmares of losing her control of the realm. She surveys all she owns, the Graveyard, the River Styx where you can drown enemies making them reveal truths. 

 

*3371 Years Prior.*
In Egypt Sakkara stands before a bonfire and calls out to Lucifer as her followers dance in a frenzy, the blood of scarifies flows from her mouth. Lucifer answers her call and is impressed by her darkness and drags her willingly to hell. In the city of Dis Sakkara lies on Lucifer's bed has been transformed into a demoness with red skin and wings. She bites Lucifer's throat and takes his blood, he strikes her for the impertinence but she has now tasted power and lusts for it insatiably. As much as he desires her she is far to unpredictable and calculating to be left lose and he banishes her to the Necropolis via the Nexus. 

 

*Medieval Europe 1485AD.*
Hope is a happy girl and he mother protects her from increasingly unstable father until one day he slays her mother for not siring him a son. He damns her soul as a bridge from earth to hell that it might not rest. 

 

*Present Day.*
Lady Death recounts her journey into hell and wonders at a storm gathering in the sky that she did not will into beings. A voice in her head claims to be her conscience and that it is shaping her world. It raises up the land and traps her, taking her sword, and tells her to remember how she campaigned with her father as a willing participant in his murder of the townsfolk and fed their souls into the pit. She refuses this twisted version of th truth but the voice reminds her that she is no longer innocent and with Evil Ernie she has slaughtered millions. 

On earth Ernie has not been able to communicate with Lady Death for a long time due to the meddling of Purgatori. The Demoness, having tastes god blood has tastes only for the blood of the powerful and Lady Death is the most powerful available. It is she that is twisting her memories and breaking her down and enraging her, making her blood all the more angry and tasty to Purgatori.

Purgatori has her in a mental prison of the void but the anger she has inspired enables Lady Death to break free. But Purgatori wont be denied so easily and conjures a vision of Hope's mother. Even though Lady Death knows its a vision she is seduced by the accurate story the vision gives of that she was released to heaven but was captured but a demoness. They embrace and Purgatori drops the disguise so close to her goal.</Summary>
	<Title>Between Heaven and Hell</Title>
	<Volume>1995</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/lady-death-between-heaven-and-hell-1/4000-119600/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Pulido</Writer>
	<Year>1995</Year>
</ComicInfo>