<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Melody,Melody's Sister,Morty Smith,The Ghost of Christmas Present,Spirit of Some Guy You Once Saw at the Bus Stop and Made Eye Contact With,Mr. Chimney,The Ghost of Christmas Past,Sal,Melody's Mother,Melody's Father,Proselyte,Rick Sanchez,The Ghost of Christmas Future</Characters>
  <Colorist>Ryan Hill,Ryan Hill</Colorist>
  <Day>25</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-506725</GTIN>
  <Inker>Marc Ellerby,Zac Gorman,Marc Ellerby,Zac Gorman</Inker>
  <Letterer>Crank!,Crank!</Letterer>
  <Locations>Blumbus Dimension</Locations>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:01:29 [Issue ID 4000-506725] urn:comicvine:4000-506725
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 14:47:46. [Issue ID 1504122]</Notes>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="1104072" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1284398" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1814098" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1358058" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1475957" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1279318" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1216606" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1391354" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1410244" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1668738" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1459340" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1365790" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1286649" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1496304" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1584752" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1505321" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1370551" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1598872" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1507305" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1142656" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1321665" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1137553" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1068515" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1211843" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="879907" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Marc Ellerby,Zac Gorman,Marc Ellerby,Zac Gorman</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Oni Press</Publisher>
  <Series>Rick and Morty</Series>
  <Summary>In this holiday special issue illustrated by series writer Zac Gorman, Rick and Morty celebrate Blumbus, a strange, alternate reality version of Christmas…with a shocking twist! If Morty can survive the night, he may just learn the true meaning of Blumbus after all!

*List of covers and their creators:*
 Cover | Name                                                                  | Creator(s)            | Sidebar Location |
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Reg   | Regular Cover                                                         | CJ Cannon &amp; Ryan Hill | 1                |
 Var   | Variant Cover                                                         | George Bletsis        | 2                |
 RE    | Exceed Comic: A Divison of Jesse James Comics Exclusive Variant Cover | Giahna Pantano        | 3                |
SynopsisRick and Morty are in the Blumbus Dimension. Rick hates the idea while Morty enjoys the nuanced differences between Blumbus and Christmas. The two part: Rick is off to find a bar while Morty hangs around the town to enjoy the holiday.

Morty tries to convince himself that Mr. Chimney is not a creepy replacement for Santa Claus but freaks out when what he thought was a stature winks at him. Morty runs headlong into a girl, Melody, that invites him home for Blumbus. Morty feels incredibly awkward about this, especially when he learns that Melody's family thought she was killed at war, but eventually buys in to being in their home.

Rick has found a bar and watches the dimensions version of "A Christmas Carol", in which Mini Mike goes to the store for Mr. Frooge to get a blumberflarg, which ends up being a lost teenage boy. Rick realizes that Morty is dumb enough to be picked up as a family's potential blumberflarg and runs out of the bar.

At Melody's house, Melody begins the blumberflarg ritual by trying to seduce Morty, who is becoming increasingly wary of the situation. Melody's mom interrupts and drops that Morty will soon be cooked, which freaks him out. Morty tries to escape but is held back by the family. Mr. Chimney shows up with Rick and blasts Melody's family into dust and explains that Morty has been a good boy and does not deserve to die. Mr. Chimney then describes in detail things in Morty's room. This shocks Rick, as Mr. Chimney is apparently a god that can see inter-dimensionally, and Rick tries to knock out Mr. Chimney as the two run away.

Later that night, Rick and Morty watch the Blumbus version of "It's a Wonderful Life". Morty leaves when the blumberflarg is shown. Rick berates him but is then approached by a ghost of some guy who warns him of a visit by three ghosts. Rick has a quick Scroogeian trip and begs to go back - which is granted - so he can watch the rest of the show.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-01-02 14:01:24.  [Issue ID 506725]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-8-a-very-special-blumbus/4000-506725/</Summary>
  <Tags>Melody,Melody's Sister,Morty Smith,The Ghost of Christmas Present,Spirit of Some Guy You Once Saw at the Bus Stop and Made Eye Contact With,Mr. Chimney,The Ghost of Christmas Past,Three Spirits,Sal,Melody's Mother,Melody's Father,Proselyte,Rick Sanchez,The Ghost of Christmas Future,Blumbus Dimension</Tags>
  <Teams>Three Spirits</Teams>
  <Title>A Very Special Blumbus</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/rick-and-morty-8-a-very-special-blumbus/4000-506725/</Web>
  <Writer>Zac Gorman,Zac Gorman</Writer>
  <Year>2015</Year>
  <Count>61</Count>
  <Genre>Humor</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Editor>Robin Herrera,Ari Yarwood</Editor>
</ComicInfo>