<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Fear</Characters>
  <Colorist>Nick Filardi,Nick Filardi</Colorist>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <Day>7</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-117006</GTIN>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:28:25 [Issue ID 4000-117006] urn:comicvine:4000-117006
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 05:12:42. [Issue ID 391373]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Fearless</Series>
  <Summary>From the creator of GROUNDED comes the story of a literal man without fear. To the criminals he terrorizes and the citizens he protects, Fear is a bold, even reckless superhero. To those who know his secret, he's a man paralyzed by a crippling anxiety disorder, who needs an anti-fear drug to fight his war on crime. But what happens when his supply runs out? 

*SPOILERS*
From the creator of GROUNDED comes the story of a literal man without fear. To the criminals he terrorizes and the citizens he protects, Fear is a bold, even reckless superhero. To those who know his secret, he’s a man paralyzed by a crippling anxiety disorder, who needs an anti-fear drug to fight his war on crime. But what happens when his supply runs out?   The story begins with Adam Rygert standing atop a building, trying to convince himself he is not afraid. He has a momentary flashback to a childhood birthday partner where he was mortified for being too afraid to jump from the diving board. He overcomes the flash back, puts his helmet on, and lets the mysterious gas run through his helmet and into his breathing area. The gas brings on a change in Adam and he easily dives off the building and flies off. HE comes to the docks and find criminal activity. During the tussle one of the villains cracks his helmet, releasing the gas. He dives out the window and uses an inhaler to get another hit of the gas then enters the battle again. When he succeeds he flies away but one of the nearby homeless people obtain a small portion of his drug and starts to use it.

 During the news coverage we meet Becky Edwards, a reporter and childhood friend of Adam. She talks highly of Adam's alter-ego Fear; however, she is quickly cut off by a police officer. Adam has another flashback to his childhood with Becky and how he had such a huge crush on her that he missed three days of school after talking to her. Now, however, they are going out and she knows he is secretly Fear. She does seem to question why he thinks it's his responsibility though. He starts to have an asthma-attack and then explains that the town was once safe and he feels he can make it again.

 He has a final flashback to the day he met Lionel, his tutor that would go on to make the drug he uses as fear. Lionel scolds him for being so careless the day prior. They head into a secret lair where he keeps the drug. He reveals a concern that his time is limited and someday Ryan will need to learn to make the drug. Ryan argues that he should go public with it, but Lionel disagrees saying it may fall into the wrong hands.

 In another house Victor, the head of the criminal activity in the area, is angered by Fear's action and exclaims he'll need to deal with him personally. A man arrives and says he could help and that he knows Fear's weakness.

 Back at Adam's mansion, we see that Adam was thrown out of his own restaurant. It is also revealed that his father is deceases and, according to his butler, he is not doing a very good job of living up to his legacy. Becky calls him to give him a tip about some activity. Adam heads out as Fear but this time the villains are actually a distraction. He deals with them very easy. Prior to the battle he had tried to contact Lionel with no luck, so afterward he went to his house to see what had happened. When he arrived, he found the house trashed and a message that said "I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE."</Summary>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/fearless-1/4000-117006/</Web>
  <Writer>David Roth,Mark Sable,Mark Sable,David Roth</Writer>
  <Year>2007</Year>
  <Penciller>Paul J Holden,PJ Holden,PJ Holden</Penciller>
  <Inker>Paul J Holden,PJ Holden,PJ Holden</Inker>
  <Letterer>Kristyn Ferretti,Kristyn Ferretti</Letterer>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>