<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Cavewoman: Rain</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Title>Chapter Three</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>The storms have begun and even the animals are scared. Professor Cook, Capt. Lavery, Sgt. Higgins and Bruce Kabbit are stuck in the mud. They're trying to get Prof. Cook's vehicle out when Meriem show up with the baby. She gives it to Bruce to hold and easily frees the thing from the mud. She tells them she was just at the electric plant and Klyde is the reason the power is out. They are radioed about cyclone activity and try to avoid one.

Sgt. Marstone rallies up some of the locals and makes them gun crazy. He supplies them with weapons and proposes a dinosaur hunt. All of the kids in the comic shop are safe in the storage room when they hear movement on the other side of the door. It turns out to be the owner and he's ok. There is one more dinosaur and he crashes through the door. The owner kills it. The twisters have frightened a herd of Triceratops and they stampede through the town. Corporal Mack stumbles in on Marstone's speech and she tries to talk him out of it citing several examples of why it's a bad idea. He ignores her.

Meriem and them, all crammed into the Professor's vehicle drive through the hole the Triceratops herd made. Meriem jumps out and wants to help. She saves a little girl and her injured father. Sgt. Marstone and crew rescue a group of people stuck on a balcony but almost kills them in the process. Capt. Lavery sees the whole thing and yells at him. He tells her you can't just take a Triceratops by the nose and lead it out of town. Back at the comic shop, Klyde crashes in and grabs Lumpy. Lumpy tries to sign to him that he's OK but Klyde takes him anyways.

Meriem is struggling with the stampeding Triceratops that is in front of the herd. She's steering it using it's horn. The herd rumbles right past Sgt. Marstone and Capt. Lavery. Bruce takes the opportunity to point out you CAN lead one out of town by the nose. Meriem sees Klyde with Lumpy a short while later and stands right in the way. Her Grandfather appears and tells her she's foolish and that she should find a way to trick him instead. Klyde grabs her by the head and she kicks him but he manages to fling her away. She knocks over a steel post and then uses it as a weapon smacking Klyde on the head. He's doesn't seem hurt and grabs her. Just as his teeth are about to dig into her torso we see her scream off panel.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 03:29:44. [Issue ID 59685]</Notes>
  <StoryArc>"Cavewoman: Rain" Rain</StoryArc>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Day>4</Day>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cavewoman-rain-4-chapter-three/4000-43151/</Web>
  <Characters>Timothy Higgins,Klyde,Patricia Lavery,Bob Cook,Francis Reicher II,Meriem Cooper,Lieutenant Mack,Francis Peacock Reicher,Bruce Kabbit,John Marstone</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>Prehistoric Jungle</Locations>
  <Writer>Budd Root,Budd Root</Writer>
  <Penciller>Budd Root,Bradley Walton,Cara Walton,Budd Root,Bradley Walton,Cara Walton</Penciller>
  <Inker>Budd Root,Bradley Walton,Cara Walton,Budd Root,Bradley Walton,Cara Walton</Inker>
  <Colorist>Looptan Garou</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Budd Root,Looptan Garou</CoverArtist>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
  <Letterer>Bradley Walton,Cara Walton,Bradley Walton,Cara Walton</Letterer>
  <Editor>Joe Pruett</Editor>
</ComicInfo>