<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Abraham Lincoln,Benjamin Franklin,Deadpool,Doctor Strange,Emily Preston,George Washington,Gerald Ford,Michael Hawthorne,Richard Nixon,Wong</Characters>
	<Colorist>Val Staples</Colorist>
	<Count>45</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Axel Alonso,Jordan D. White</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-371106</GTIN>
	<Inker>Tony Moore</Inker>
	<Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
	<Locations>Washington D.C.</Locations>
	<Month>3</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:04:37 [Issue ID 4000-371106] urn:comicvine:4000-371106</Notes>
	<Number>3</Number>
	<PageCount>23</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2018102" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1266470" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="2132550" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="2278500" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1873311" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="2035113" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="2166268" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="2350922" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="2144911" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="2424282" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1999783" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1967569" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="2170681" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="2291051" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="2090139" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="2030398" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="2039694" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="2070861" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="2209848" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1992765" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1900169" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="2044770" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1799893" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Tony Moore</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Deadpool</Series>
	<Summary>Deadpool vs. Dead Presidents…this time, TRICKY DICK NIXON! Can even Doctor Strange help the M w/the M? This is the Deadpool series you will marry someday!

Deadpool finishes telling Dr. Strange about the recent events with the dead presidents coming back to life via a necromancer. Dr. Strange, however, is unimpressed and is about to show Deadpool, Agent Preston, and the ghost of Benjamin Franklin to the door but first takes a peak into the story to give the trio a real look at what is going on. Opening his third eye, Dr. Strange is surprised to find Richard Nixon raising from the dead. Dr. Strange explains that the necromancer is working with powers he knows little about and is bringing the presidents back to life without their humanity. He leaves to meditate. Wong instructs the visitors to be ready to depart at a moment's notice.

Some presidents meet in a family dentistry to try and resolve a dispute concerning the course of action to take. A spaceship has been proposed and Ford has to remind everyone that the nation doesn't even have a space program anymore. The necromancer, shackled, tries to spout some sorcery to help him escape but Ford knocks the wind out of him. This little bit of incantations is enough for Dr. Strange to locate the men and he teleports the group to the dentistry (minus Ben Franklin because he is still mad about a past indiscretion). Deadpool begins shooting presidents while Dr. Strange vanishes with the necromancer. The spell book the necromancer uses is dropped, however, and Washington claims it to aid in future destruction.

On the astral plane, Dr. Strange banishes the necromancy from Michael the necromancer. Michael then explains that he learned of his skills when he was in fifth grade and had wished life back into his dead hamster. He was later recruited out of college and trained by S.H.I.E.L.D. to hone his powers.

Outside the dentistry, Deadpool takes on Washington, Ford, and Lincoln. He tells Agent Preston to leave and she does so with the promise to return with more help. Deadpool is smashed inside a car, receives a sword in the back, and then kicked into a building. He thinks help has arrived when a helicopter touches down but it is only more dead presidents. Nixon hops off and recognizes that he's at Watergate. Ford trips and gets sliced to bits by the helicopter's rotor blade. Dr. Strange returns as the helicopter departs. He pulls Washington's sword from Deadpool's back and begins another round of meditation. Deadpool turns his attention to Nixon who is bent on destroying Watergate. Deadpool attacks but is quickly thrown into an elderly woman's apartment. Nixon follows and starts whooping Deadpool until the merc can kick Nixon in the Little Nixon. Dr. Strange then appears and gives Deadpool the Washington sword and explains that it is now enchanted to fell the undead. Deadpool wastes no time in sticking it in Nixon's chest. The president explodes in a flash of pink light.

Outside, Dr. Strange explains that the sword should help Deadpool defeat the rest of the undead presidents. He then whispers a seemingly dire observation to Deadpool and departs. Agent Preston states that Michael the necromancer is cooperating and they'll have to see what comes next.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-10 10:20:08.  [CVDB371106]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-3-dr-strange-lives-or-how-i-learned-deadp/4000-371106/</Summary>
	<Tags>Abraham Lincoln,Benjamin Franklin,Deadpool,Doctor Strange,Emily Preston,George Washington,Gerald Ford,Michael Hawthorne,Richard Nixon,S.H.I.E.L.D.,Washington D.C.,Wong,Zombies</Tags>
	<Teams>S.H.I.E.L.D.,Zombies</Teams>
	<Title>Dr. Strange Lives (Or How I Learned Deadpool Was Da Bomb)</Title>
	<Volume>2012</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-3-dr-strange-lives-or-how-i-learned-deadp/4000-371106/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Posehn,Gerry Duggan</Writer>
	<Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>