<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Black Hole (villain),Dr. Angst (villain),the Critic,The Terror (last app. in MYSTIC COMICS #10),Tillie the Hun (villain),Sitting Bullseye (villain),Howard the Duck,the Spanker (villain)</Characters>
  <Colorist>Glynis Oliver Wein,Glynis Oliver,Glynis Oliver</Colorist>
  <Count>60</Count>
  <Editor>Bobbie Chase,Tom DeFalco</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-32737</GTIN>
  <Inker>Dale Keown,Joe Rubinstein,Jim Sanders III,Jim Sanders III</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jim Novak,Jim Novak</Letterer>
  <Locations>New York City,New Mexico,Space,Connecticut</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T13:58:59 [Issue ID 4000-32737] urn:comicvine:4000-32737
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:37:48. [Issue ID 47941]</Notes>
  <Number>15</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="4830515" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2144503" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="2287570" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="2163754" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="2299814" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2188645" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1840474" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2108739" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2353040" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2208760" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2220376" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1974414" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1739080" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="2057032" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2278292" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2276524" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2351929" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2216494" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1942582" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2092227" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1883011" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1603045" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1663308" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Dale Keown,Bryan Hitch,Bryan Hitch</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>The Sensational She-Hulk</Series>
  <Summary>*Synopsis*
She-Hulk and Howard the Duck's adventure in the Baloney-verse continues! But when bitten by a horde of angry demons, Shulkie becomes a mindless, smashing killing machine — just like her cousin, the Hulk!

*Plot Summary*
In the baloney-verse, a de-hulked Jennifer Walters and Howard the Duck are chased by some hungry demons. The demons manage to get a hold of Jennifer, but at the same time, she undergoes a transformation into a savage, muscular and grey She-Hulk. After getting rid of the demons, she begins to threaten Howard and when Brent finds them and mentions Jennifer's name, she gets mad and begins to approach him.

The Critic has had enough of this and transport the three of them back to Brent's office where She-Hulk reverts back to Jennifer Walters, unaware of what she turned into back at the baloney-verse. The trio decide to head back to Jennifer's apartment.

Meanwhile, an old man transforms into a creature in a dark cloak and kills a doctor and a business man.

Jennifer, Howard and Brent arrive at Jennifer's apartment where she tells a very surprised Weezi to get Howard some coffee before taking a hot shower. While she's having her shower, Brent and Howard discuss telling Jennifer what she turned into back at the baloney-verse.

At the Wormwall, New York State Correctional facility, a power drill creates a hole for Mangles to escape through.

Back at Jennifer's apartment, Brent tells Jennifer about what happened back at the baloney-verse and they realise that her transformations are triggered due to nightfall. As the sun is beginning to set, they decide to leave to find a safe place where Jennifer can undergo her transformation without hurting anyone.

Mangles arrives in his old neighborhood and assembles a group called ,'Band of the Bland'.

Jennifer and her friends arrive at the 'Gamma Ray Dude Ranch and Spa' where they find Bruce’s lab. Jennifer seals herself inside of it, hoping that it will be able to contain her when she transforms. There she is surprised by two kids who have hidden in the vault due to their warts.

The Critic and Dr. Angst watch as failed universes start raining down on the Earth.</Summary>
  <Tags>Doctor Angst,She-Hulk,Connecticut,Sitting Bullseye,Black Hole,Brent Wilcox,Terror,Band of the Bland,Tillie the Hun,New York City,The Critic,New Mexico,The Spanker,Howard the Duck,Blonde Phantom,Space</Tags>
  <Teams>Band of the Bland</Teams>
  <Title>Secret Warts</Title>
  <Volume>1989</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-sensational-she-hulk-15-secret-warts/4000-32737/</Web>
  <Writer>Steve Gerber,Steve Gerber</Writer>
  <Year>1990</Year>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>