<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Blob [Fred Dukes],The Owl [Leland Owlsley] (dies),Power Man [Luke Cage] (zombie),Avengers [Black Widow [Natasha Romanova] (zombie),Dr. Octopus [Otto Octavius] (zombie),Dazzler [Alison Blaire],Howard the Duck (zombie),Spider-Man [Peter Parker],Ms. Marvel [Carol Danvers] (zombie),Wrecker [Dirk Garthwaite] (zombie),Iron Fist [Danny Rand] (zombie),Dagger [Tandy Bowen] (zombie),Rhino [Aleksei Sytsevich] (zombie),Cloak [Tyrone Johnson](zombie),Thunderball [Dr. Eliot Franklin],Punisher [Frank Castle] (zombie),Ash [Ashley G. Willaims],Kingpin [Wilson Fisk] (dies),The Leader (zombie),Elektra [Elektra Natchios] (zombie),Captain America [Steve Rogers] (zombie),Wasp [Janet Van Dyne] (zombie)],Hammerhead (dies),Winter Soldier [Bucky Barnes] (zombie),Ash [Ashley Williams],Hawkeye [Clint Barton] (zombie),Black Cat [Felicia Hardy] (zombie)</Characters>
  <Colorist>June Chung,June Chung</Colorist>
  <Count>5</Count>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <Editor>Ralph Macchio</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-107997</GTIN>
  <Inker>Fabiano Neves,Arthur Suydam,Fabiano Neves</Inker>
  <Letterer>Rus Wooton,VC,VC,Rus Wooton</Letterer>
  <Locations>New York City,Sanctum Sanctorum,Fisk Tower</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:08:11 [Issue ID 4000-107997] urn:comicvine:4000-107997
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 13:12:19. [Issue ID 345211]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <PageCount>23</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="594529" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="798549" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="562259" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="706732" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="771254" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="718897" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="771687" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="718152" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1534206" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="718996" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="653818" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="730890" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="656383" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="753508" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="639621" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="703283" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="666144" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="707830" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="707283" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="686640" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="566795" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="745986" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="615140" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Fabiano Neves,Arthur Suydam,Fabiano Neves</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel / Dynamite Entertainment</Publisher>
  <Series>Marvel Zombies / Army of Darkness</Series>
  <Summary>Spider-Man hops on Hawkeye and threatens to eat his brains if they don't give the webbed-up Ash to him. He is cautioned against that mainly because once they are zombified, they don't taste good. Spider-Man argues that he had to lug Ash around and listen to him talk nonstop. Ash tries to crawl away as they discuss this. Finally Cap says they may need Hawkeye later and allows Spider-Man to have Ash.

They swing away and once they reach a roof top and Spidey lets Ash down, Ash tries attacking him. Spider-Man quickly points out that he is still human. It seems his powers are working to keep off the affects of Colonel America's bite.

Spider-Man soon takes off when he's reminded of Aunt May and Mary Jane. Ash calls after him as the Punisher comes up behind him. As the Punisher admires Ash's chainsaw, he discovers that he's trying to save this world from the deadites. Frank tells Ash that if he helps him first, then he'll help Ash find the Necronomicon.

Frank busts in on a meeting between the Kingpin, Hammerhead and the Owl. Kingpin insists that they are now on the same side, humans versus zombie. Frank disagrees as he doesn't think Kingpin was ever human and shoots them.

As they are about to leave Fisk Tower, they see that the zombie infection is spreading. Ash sees Thunderball cornered by a bunch of super zombies. He tells Frank that he's not infected. Frank doesn't care because he's a criminal too. He goes out shooting at all of them. The bullets aren't having too much of an effect as they overcome and do away with the Punisher.

Ash decides that he works best alone. He says he doesn't need a partner until he sees Winter Soldier trying to take a bite out of Dazzler. As Winter Soldier tells Dazzler to give him "some sugar," Ash informs him that that is his line and shoots his head off. Dazzler thanks Ash as he checks out her...assets. He claims he's checking her for zombie bites.

As they walk away, Ash tells Dazzler his situation and about the Necronomicon. When she realizes they're in Greenwich Village, she takes Ash to Stephen Strange's sanctum sanctorium. Dazzler fills Ash in on who Dr. Strange is has he's grabbed from behind.

Hearing a big "crunch!" behind her, Dazzler turns to see where Ash is. She sees Ash apparently with the top of his head missing lying in the lap of a zombified Howard the Duck.

To be continued?</Summary>
  <Teams>Zombies,Wrecking Crew,Avengers,Marvel Zombies</Teams>
  <Title>Part 2 of 5: Marvel Team-Ups</Title>
  <Volume>2007</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/marvel-zombies-vs-army-of-darkness-2-marvel-team-u/4000-107997/</Web>
  <Writer>John Layman,John Layman</Writer>
  <Year>2007</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Arthur Suydam</CoverArtist>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Humor,Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>