<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
	<Colorist>Dylan Teague,Giulia Brusco,Jim Boswell</Colorist>
	<CoverArtist>R.M. Guera</CoverArtist>
	<Day>8</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1054487</GTIN>
	<Inker>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Lee Carter,Patrick Goddard,R.M. Guera</Inker>
	<Letterer>Annie Parkhouse,Jim Campbell,Simon Bowland</Letterer>
	<Month>5</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.9 on 2024-07-27T21:39:34 [Issue ID 4000-1054487] urn:comicvine:4000-1054487</Notes>
	<Number>2381</Number>
	<PageCount>32</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1389180" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1367014"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="998483"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1416014"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1471467"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1447845"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1472434"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1397780"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1378722"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1256353"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1487476"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1466465"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1482885"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1684410"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1670585"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1154838"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1173769"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1061671"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1115128"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1548065"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1177343"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1207041"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1003681"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1143858"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="1094875"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="1498316"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="1741659"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="1378040"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="1200480"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="1444916"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="1939973"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="1730141"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard,Jake Lynch,Lee Carter,Patrick Goddard,R.M. Guera</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
	<Series>2000 AD</Series>
	<Summary>Call me The Mighty Tharg, Betelgeusian overlord at the helm of this awesome anthology!

Two Thrills come to their scrotnig finales this prog, Terrans - Indigo Prime blows the roof off with its mind-expanding conclusion to Black Monday, while Dredd’s life-or-death struggle in the frozen wastes reaches its climax as the lawman goes head-to-head with the rampaging grizzly bear that’s stalked him for the last five episodes. Will he prevail? Or will he end up as so much ursine dung on the side of a mountain? There’s only one way to find out, and, believe me, I’m not stopping you, my Squaxx - tear your eyes from my verdant verbiage and go find out for yourselves!

That means joining Aquila, Brink and Proteus Vex next week we’ve go two new zarjaz stories - Ken Niemand and Nick Percival collaborate on seriously scary Dredd chiller Iron Teeth; and Arthur Wyatt and Pye Parr reunite for the latest Intestinauts saga Busted Flush. It’s high-octane action at the micro-level!

Just enough space for the hard sell from Quaxxann - if you don’t already have it on your shelf, get the Essential Psi-Judge Anderson: Satan. Right. Now. You won’t regret it, humes!

*Judge Death » Rend &amp; Tear with Tooth &amp; Claw (Part 6)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, with the toxic Black Atlantic to the east and the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*Aquila » The Rivers of Hades, Book Two: PART 1 (Part 5)*
Following Spartacus’s failed revolt against his Roman masters, his rebel army was crucified. Amongst these was the slave-turned-gladiator AQUILA, who cried out to the gods for vengeance - and was answered by Ammit the Devourer, a deity that gifted him with immortality in return for keeping her fed with evil men’s souls. Now, Aquila has travelled into Hades and retrieved the spirit of Nero, who knows Ammit’s location...

*Indigo Prime » Black Monday (Part 11)*
The multiverse. There is an infinite number of parallel realities, and all need managing in case of dimensional instability. This is where INDIGO PRIME came in, the multiverse’s troubleshooters, whose agents are trained to deal with space/time catastrophes. Now, IP’s HQ has been destroyed in a cataclysmic event, with most of the personnel lost, and its assets acquired by the company ICP...

*Brink » Consumed (Part 4)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*PROTEUS VEX » Devious (Part 7)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
	<Title>Prog 2381</Title>
	<Volume>1977</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2381-prog-2381/4000-1054487/</Web>
	<Writer>Dan Abnett,Gordon Rennie,Kek-W,Michael Carroll,Rob Williams</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>