<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-221545</GTIN>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:14 [Issue ID 4000-221545] urn:comicvine:4000-221545
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:36. [Issue ID 136600]</Notes>
  <Number>11</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Title>The Moulder of Doom; Buried Alive; The Monster They Couldn't Kill; The Face from Hell</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-11-the-moulder-of-doom/4000-221545/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>The Moulder of Doom: Sculptor Guy Morzat creates the most life-like portraits, because his works are not sculptures, but corpses covered with plaster of Paris. When Morzat tries to flee the town the statues come alive and take revenge.

Buried Alive: Hugo, a stage magician, is always second in line to the “Great Carvel”. So he plans to murder his rival and take his place of fame. Hugo fakes his own death, sneaks out of the morgue, kills Carvel and goes back into a state of suspended animation. His assistant Pepe, however, fouls up the plan for his rescue from the grave.

The Monster They Couldn't Kill: Dr. Fry has been feeding on atomic energy and turned into a superhuman on the rampage. Every attempt to restrain him fails. Fry perishes in the end as he’s overfed himself on a pile of atomic garbage.

The Face from Hell: Playboy and gambler Arthur Wells loses everything at the casino. The devil guarantees him his money back – if they switch faces! Wells enters into this weird pact and now bears a satanic likeness which scares people away instantly. A desperate Wells bargains again with the devil to change faces back. If his girlfriend June still loves him, Wells will be realeased from the pact.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>