<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Lillian Ashby,John Ashby</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-56986</GTIN>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:38:06 [Issue ID 4000-56986] urn:comicvine:4000-56986
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 19:01:18. [Issue ID 75633]</Notes>
  <Number>16</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Adventures into Weird Worlds</Series>
  <Tags>Gordon Langley</Tags>
  <Title>Kiss of Death; Surprise!; Mind over Matter; Flying Saucer; The Old Man's Secret!</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-weird-worlds-16-the-kiss-of-death/4000-56986/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>30</Count>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>A woman plans to get rid of her writer husband by taking him to a house supposedly haunted by vampires and shocking his bad heart. She dresses as a vampire, but he recognizes her and thinks it is part of her attempt to add atmosphere for his horror writing, and he isn't scared. A real vampire bites him later in the evening, and when his wife tries again the following night, the man, now a vampire, bites her.

An old man in love with a Gypsy girl murders his rival. The girl continues to moon over the dead man so a Gypsy woman offers to make the old man resemble the man he killed. He goes to the gravesite at night with a picture and the sorceress summons the ghost and commands it to exchange faces with the old man. He rushes off to see the girl, but she screams at his approach, as he now has the face of a corpse several months dead.

A man receives Yogi training to make objects disappear, and when his friend introduces him to Cartesian skeptical doubt, they both disappear.</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Tony DiPreta,Jack Keller,Bill Benulis,Ross Andru,Joe Orlando,Jay Scott Pike</Penciller>
  <Inker>Tony DiPreta,Jack Keller,Jack Abel,Jay Scott Pike</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>