<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Day>10</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-204420</GTIN>
  <Inker>Everett Raymond Kinstler,George Roussos,Gerald McCann,Harry Lazarus,Mort Meskin</Inker>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:32:48 [Issue ID 4000-204420] urn:comicvine:4000-204420
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:59:47. [Issue ID 9891]</Notes>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Everett Raymond Kinstler,George Roussos,Gerald McCann,Harry Lazarus,Mort Meskin</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Avon</Publisher>
  <Series>Witchcraft</Series>
  <Summary>The Man Who Bribed Death: Newspaper correspondent Robert Avery has a heart condition and only one more day to live. He strikes a bargain with death himself: Avery kills people before their time and gets to stay alive longer. He travels to dangerous spots like war-torn Korea and Red China where life is cheap and death sudden. His luck runs out as he tries to be smuggled out of a disease-stricken city in a coffin.

The Terrible Face: Plastic surgeon Emil Toller is jealous of the handsome Jack Parks. Parks is engaged to lovely Nanette whom Toller plans to marry. When Parks is hurt in a car crash, Toller disfigures his face, driving the man to suicide. The dead man’s misshapen face haunts the surgeon who ends up inheriting his terrible features.

Claws of the Cat: Grace and Walter Brock murder his rich aunt Annie for her money. They kill her pet cat, too. After burying the old woman, they find the cat’s body gone. Months later, strange things start to happen: Walter is scratched by an invisible animal, and Grace transforms into a murderous feline.

Diary of the Monster: John Stark is a firebug. He causes a lot of fires until he is caught red-handed. Stark claims his innocence on behalf of being possessed by a monster inside of him. When Stark commits suicide in his cell, the fire monster indeed breaks loose.

</Summary>
  <Title>The Man Who Bribed Death; The Terrible Face; Claws of the Cat; Diary of the Monster</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/witchcraft-4-the-man-who-bribed-death/4000-204420/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>6</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>