<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Part IV: Punisher Punished!</Title>
  <Series>Deadpool Kills the Marvel Universe</Series>
  <Number>4</Number>
  <Volume>2012</Volume>
  <Summary>SynopsisThe shocking conclusion to Deadpool's murderous rampage hacking and slashing through the Marvel Heroes!

PlotDeadpool is on a mission to kill all the superheroes and supervillains of the Marvel Universe, so when people start jumping off buildings, Punisher quickly assumes Wade has something to do with it. Frank is correct but he walks right into Deadpool's trap and uses the Puppet Master's puppet to force Punisher to punish himself, with a bullet to the head.

Later, Taskmaster has tracked Deadpool to a swamp, where Taskmaster attempts to put the insane Deadpool down for good. Taskmaster learns that Deadpool might not be as crazy as everyone thinks but before Taskmaster can finish the job, Man-Thing shows up and destroys Taskmaster.

Man-Thing then opens a doorway for Deadpool to leave his universe and travel through time and space to the Marvel Offices of our world. There Deadpool sees Cullen and the other Marvel writers and artists. Deadpool then nods to the reader and lets them know "You are next."</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-04 15:15:09.  [CVDB352696]</Notes>
  <Year>2012</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Writer>Cullen Bunn</Writer>
  <Penciller>Dalibor Talaji&#263;</Penciller>
  <Inker>Dalibor Talaji&#263;</Inker>
  <Colorist>Lee Loughridge</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Kaare Kyle Andrews</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso, Jordan D. White, Nick Lowe</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-kills-the-marvel-universe-4-part-iv-punis/4000-352696/</Web>
  <PageCount>21</PageCount>
  <Characters>Betsy Braddock, Black Knight, Black Widow, Blade, Bullseye, Cyclops, Daredevil, Deadpool, Death Adder, Doctor Bong, Doctor Octopus, Dogpool, Dragon Man, Dum Dum Dugan, Elvis Presley, Galactus, Gladiator, Hit-Monkey, Iceman, Invisible Woman, Iron Fist, Jigsaw, Kidpool, Kingpin, Lady Bullseye, Madame Masque, Man-Thing, Nick Fury, Nova, Phoenix Force, Puck, Punisher, Puppet Master, Sam Wilson, Shang-Chi, Shocker, Silver Surfer, Tarantula (Rodr&#237;guez), Taskmaster, Texas Twister, Thanos, Valkyrie</Characters>
  <Teams>Avengers, Fantastic Four, Marvel Bullpen, X-Force, X-Men</Teams>
  <Locations>Everglades, Florida, New York City, New York State, Nexus of All Realities, Space</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="554159" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="491208" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="660849" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="435989" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="391294" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="453090" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="402433" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="453555" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="487405" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="544312" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="415324" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="446656" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="492534" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="361512" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="400557" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="444793" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="528110" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="438298" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="975094" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="518774" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="509100" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
