<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<AgeRating>Mature 17+</AgeRating>
	<Colorist>Paulo Esper</Colorist>
	<Count>11</Count>
	<CoverArtist>Stéphane Degardin</CoverArtist>
	<Editor>Eric Peyron</Editor>
	<Format>Series</Format>
	<Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
	<Inker>Paulo Teles,Stéphane Degardin</Inker>
	<Letterer>Eric Peyron</Letterer>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.2.0 on 2024-11-01T01:47:29</Notes>
	<Number>11</Number>
	<Penciller>Paulo Teles,Stéphane Degardin,Walmir Archanjo</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Glyphs Productions</Publisher>
	<Series>Worlds of Rage</Series>
	<Summary>A lot is happening behind the scenes in the Rage Universe, and many stories are still left to be told. Most of these stories will be told in Worlds of Rage.

• Serena: Serena, priestess of Axliom has been tasked to bring very coveted relics to a faraway temple in the Gonthor mountains, but who is really Serena, and what is the true nature of the relics? The truth continues to unfold in this new chapter! Meet different kinds of heroes from the Rage Universein the series Serena,written by Eric Peyron and penciled by Stéphane Degardin!

• Arcana: What really happened in the Fortress of Kahel? How did it end up a nest of demons, with a Hell's Pit in the dungeons? How did Master Demon Torg become its new lord and master? Well, as in this issue’s chapter of Serena, it's Answers Time in Arcana too! While Brann is looking for Aelwen, Torg is slaughtering the soldiers of Kahel. Will Brann arrive on time, or is it too late for Aelwen and her suite? Discover the past of the Rage Universe in the series Arcana, written by Eric Peyron and penciled by Walmir Archanjo!

• The Rage Universe isn’t limited to the European Kingdom of Arthkan. Events are beginning to unfold in Kusha, the African continent of the Rage Universe, which will ultimately have an impact on the Rage Series. Discover the secrets of the Continent of Kusha, the African part of the Rage Universe in Curse of the Panthermen, a Comic Strip written by Eric Peyron and penciled by Stéphane Degardin!

• Discover more Black and White and Color pages of Rage Bane of Demons, the original Rage Graphic Novel, in the Bonus Pages section!</Summary>
	<Volume>2017</Volume>
	<Writer>Eric Peyron</Writer>
	<Year>2024</Year>
</ComicInfo>
