<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Celia,DJ Amun (death of),Dem,Doktor Sleepless,Doktor Sleepless [John Reinhardt],Mars,Nurse (Doktor Sleepless' assistant),Sing Watson,Tag</Characters>
	<Colorist>Andrew Dalhouse</Colorist>
	<Count>13</Count>
	<Country>US</Country>
	<Day>10</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-368906</GTIN>
	<Genre>Science fiction</Genre>
	<Inker>Ivan Rodriguez</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Letterer>Mark Seifert</Letterer>
	<Month>7</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:25:46 [Issue ID 4000-368906] urn:comicvine:4000-368906 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/368906</Notes>
	<Number>1</Number>
	<PageCount>24</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="1765969" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1208771"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1185687"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1559443"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1032959"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1302947"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1629563"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1287343"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1549656"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1707550"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1593556"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1659190"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="1785949"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1743493"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1605558"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1557995"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1957212"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1590923"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1829524"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1289780"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1585069"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1542075"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1722096"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="1321348"/>
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Ivan Rodriguez</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
	<Series>Doktor Sleepless</Series>
	<Summary>It's the near future. No-one has their flying car. Everyone feels cheated. What America needs now is a Mad Scientist. A city with a secret is shocked out of its apathy by the return of a young technological genius who has reinvented himself as Doktor Sleepless. But perhaps he never left and perhaps his planned new future doesn't include the city. For fans of Ellis' fantastic sci-fi tales and have missed the absence of Transmetropolitan, this series is what the Doktor ordered!

A city with a secret is shocked out of its apathy by the return of a young technological genius who has reinvented himself as Doktor Sleepless.

But perhaps he never left and perhaps his planned new future doesn’t include the city.

For fans of Ellis’ fantastic sci-fi tales and have missed the absence of Transmetropolitan, this series is what the Doktor ordered!

The issue is available with a regular cover by series artist Ivan Rodriguez, or wraparound cover by Raulo Caceres, a signed poster edition which features a Doktor Sleepless poster signed by Warren Ellis himself, and also a rare 1-in-15 Future Warning Sign cover.

John Reinhardt has returned to Heavenside ... a bit different. He hasn't slept in a year and his angst has reached a peak. He has become the "character" Doktor Sleepless and he wishes to bring salvation to those he feel jipped of a future.

At a local dance club, DJ Amun is confronted by a former lover who has kept his aborted child/fetus with her in a vial around her neck. He freaks out, Sleepless takes his Pronoia, and he ends up killing himself. His friend, Sing, finds out the next morning that Amun is dead, thanks to her contact lens with advanced technology. Sleepless now begins to size up Heavenside with his nurse for his upcoming unveiling.

At Sing's bookstore, a shipment shows up unsolicited from John Reinhardt and Sing wonders it Johnny is back in town when she sees his address. Accompanying the address, though, is the name Doktor Sleepless and not Johnny's. Sleepless pays visit to a local grinder bar where he revives a man everyone thinks is gone for good. Doing so, he proclaims himself the "Future Science Jesus".

Back at Sing's bookstore, she and her friends enjoy a drink in DJ Amun's honor, putting on his radio show hoping a pre-taped show would be playing. Instead, Sleepless has taken over the airwaves, proclaiming what is on everyone's minds: "Where is our future? The one we deserve?" He turns on a signal in the air which shows the number 666 in gears before putting the music back on the air.</Summary>
	<Tags>Celia,DJ Amun (death of),Dem,Doktor Sleepless [John Reinhardt],Mars,Nurse (Doktor Sleepless' assistant),Sing Watson,Tag</Tags>
	<Title>The Return to Scartop Mountain</Title>
	<Volume>2007</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-368906/</Web>
	<Writer>Warren Ellis</Writer>
	<Year>2007</Year>
</ComicInfo>