<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Raymond Knowby,Ash</Characters>
  <Colorist>Davi Comodo</Colorist>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-499115</GTIN>
  <Inker>Eduardo Garcia,Gabriel Rearte,Pericles Junior</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jacob Bascle</Letterer>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:30:59 [Issue ID 4000-499115] urn:comicvine:4000-499115
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:52:19. [Issue ID 1496155]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>53</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="2559004" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1610787" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="2889040" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1923976" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="2949931" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2923400" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="2630493" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2808647" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2738521" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2948593" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2847042" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="2764403" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="2889316" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="3015190" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2059198" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2200784" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2933446" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2261849" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="2839292" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2954421" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="2857139" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="2682120" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="2834232" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="2702053" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="2564893" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="2633921" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1857533" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1874518" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="2557536" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="2614405" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="2302036" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="2475671" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="2607648" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="2621544" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="2456480" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="2401730" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="2590891" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="2303256" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="2003606" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="1938603" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="2657803" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="2645022" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="2725780" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="2624161" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="2758854" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="2525832" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="2755608" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="2688948" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="2829913" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="2391429" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="693734" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="624104" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="44226" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Eduardo Garcia,Enza Fontana,Gabriel Rearte,Pericles Junior</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Space Goat Productions</Publisher>
  <Series>Evil Dead 2: Tales of the Ex-Mortis</Series>
  <Summary>*Soul Power, Part 1*
College Student Don Simmons wants to use the power of the Ex-Mortis to win the heart of Brittney, a girl in his class that hasn't noticed him all school year.  When Professor Knowby sends Simmon to see his mentor Professor Lucy Milton, Simmon learns Milton has been infected by the Ex-Mortis and demands Simmon get her the Ex-Mortis or else she will kill Brittney.

*The Lottery, Part 1*
4000 BC, the Sumerian City of Akhsa.  A lottery has been going of fro generations where the winner is sacrificed to the Gods.  The sacrifices are suppose to bring prosperity but they have been failing the last 5 years.  This year Ishme Ahr name was drawn and unlike his parents he has excepted the rite.  He throws himself into the pit with the Dagan, and "that's where his real story begans"

*Deadite Walking*
Professor Jarvin has been crippled for the last 2 years due to drinking and driving, he uses the Ex-Mortis and a sacrifice to gain the power to walk.  He then kills one of his students and while trying to escape the police losses control of his new legs.  This causes him to impale himself on his old wheelchair in an act that looks like suicide.

*Camp Deserted Part 1*
Watchee-Waki Camp, new counciler arrive to find the head leader murdered.  They are soon attacked by deadites. Kino Nam uses the Ex-Mortis to open a portal to banish the Deadites but instead it sucks her back in time where she comes face to face with a cowboy version of herself.

 

Groovy Ash-approved first issue! The new Evil Dead "Ash-thology," kicks it into Kandarian high gear by expanding the Evil Dead Universe. The companion series to our own Evil Dead 2: Beyond Dead By Dawn calls forth four Ash-centric stories of Deadites, ghouls, monsters, and more. Featuring stories by writers Frank Hannah, Justin Peniston, and Georgia Ball with art by Enza Fontana, Gabriel Rearte, Alan Quah, and Eduardo Garcia.

WHAT IS IT: This is the companion series for the OFFICIAL EVIL DEAD 2 SEQUEL before the other sequel, EVIL DEAD 2: BEYOND DEAD BY DAWN! Certified Groovy!

FOR FANS OF: Evil Dead 2, Walking Dead, and Buffy the Vampire Slayer.

WHAT HAPPENS: Four separate stories, “Soul Power” by Justin Peniston and Enza Fontana; “Camp Deserted” by Georgia Ball and Eduardo Garcia; “The Lottery” by regular Evil Dead 2 writer Frank Hannah and Gabriel Rearte; “Deadite Man Walking” by Ivan Cohen and Pericles “PJ” Junior. All tie into the Evil Dead 2 Universe and expand what we know about Deadites, Kandarians, and the Ex-Mortis.</Summary>
  <Teams>Deadites</Teams>
  <Title>Camp Deserted; Deadite Man Walking; The Lottery; Soul Power</Title>
  <Volume>2015</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/evil-dead-2-tales-of-the-ex-mortis-1-soul-power-ca/4000-499115/</Web>
  <Writer>Frank Hannah,Georgia Ball,Ivan Cohen,Justin Peniston</Writer>
  <Year>2015</Year>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
</ComicInfo>