<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2401</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2401</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>Call me The Mighty Tharg, ebullient emerald editor of this award-winning SF anthology! 

I trust you&#8217;ve fully recovered from the galaxyshaking events of last week&#8217;s Nordland Rising crossover, Terrans, and your circuits are prepped for another level of Thrill-power - because I&#8217;m about to pummel your diodes with yet more zarjazness in the shape of the all-new line-up starting this prog!

Well, Brink continues (I know you Squaxx wouldn&#8217;t forgive me if you didn&#8217;t find out what happens next&#8230;) but elsewhere we&#8217;ve got the start of Book Four of the ever-popular The Out by the Abnett and Harrison droids, Garth Ennis and Patrick Goddard reunite following last year&#8217;s acclaimed Blighty Valley story for a new Rogue Trooper thriller When a G.I. Dies, the Williams, Wyatt and Lynch droids pick up some plot threads from A Better World in Judge Dredd: Silence, and The Ordercreators Kek-W and John Burns collaborate on a brand-new historical horror Nightmare New York.

This would prove to be John&#8217;s final work as ill health led him to retire, and he sadly died at the end of 2023. So it adds an extra potency to view the last pages of a comics master and appreciate his extraordinary talent&#8230;

*Judge Dredd &#187; Silence (Part 1)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law! Now, notorious criminal fixer and assassin Major Domo is wanted for the murder of Judge Maitland...

*The Out &#187; The Out: Book 4 (Part 1)*
The furthest edge of the universe. Cyd Finlea was a photo-journalist working for the publishers Global Neographic, travelling deep into outer space - otherwise known as THE OUT - and cataloguing the alien societies that she encounters. She left Earth ten years ago and has been seeking other ex-pat humans - but now, having lost her old pal Cheerio and said goodbye to her daughter Joey, she&#8217;s going further...

*Nightmare New York (Part 1)*
NEW THRILL! Lower Manhattan, 1845. Paradise Square is at the centre of Five Points in Old New York, where five street corners meet. The early days of the North American metropolis are marked by a mix of poverty, organised crime and hardscrabble lives, where ragpickers rub shoulders with Christian missionaries. Young Lil, living rough on these dank streets, has just turned eighteen...

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 23)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Rogue Trooper &#187; When A G.I Dies (Part 1)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where the atmosphere has been rendered poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the pollutants - G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they&#8217;re searching for the traitor that sold them out...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-10-01 08:20:36.  [CVDB1071729]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>09</Month>
  <Day>25</Day>
  <Writer>Arthur Wyatt, Cat Sullivan, Dan Abnett, Garth Ennis, Kek-W, Rob Williams</Writer>
  <Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard, Jake Lynch, John Burns, Mark Harrison, Patrick Goddard</Penciller>
  <Inker>I.N.J. Culbard, Jake Lynch, John Burns, Mark Harrison, Patrick Goddard</Inker>
  <Colorist>Jim Boswell</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Rob Steen, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Mark Harrison</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2401-prog-2401/4000-1071729/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Bagman, Bridget Kurtis, Cyd Finlea, Gunnar, Helm, Judge Dredd, Rogue Trooper</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1455849" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1604289" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1068273" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1485808" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1184362" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1122698" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1230789" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1115979" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1388264" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1431771" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1570798" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1227926" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1385302" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1471955" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1214888" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1418643" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1470828" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1483325" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1413774" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1101720" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1104649" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1113512" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1049800" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1451073" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1673030" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1131844" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1101119" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1263286" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1220415" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1344195" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1632688" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1136961" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
