<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Eightball</Series>
  <Number>23</Number>
  <Count>23</Count>
  <Title>Andy 2004; The Origin of Andy; What Do You Think of Andy?; Louie at Home; Andy's World; Dear Dusty; Cigarette?; Incredible; The Next Day; The Origin of the Death Ray; Baf!; Baseball; The Adventures of the Death-Ray; Andy; The Further Adventures of the Death-Ray; On Patrol; Target Practice; Sonny; Andy's Dream; Sonny and Theresa; The Death-Ray and Louie; Andy Again; Stoob in "The Test"; Sonny's Lament; The Unthinkable; Dear Dusty (again); Louie in Love; Andy, Louie; The Last Straw; 26 Years Later; The United States of Andy; Why Did Andy Destroy You?; What Do You Think of Andy (Again)?; Choose Your Own Adventure</Title>
  <Volume>1989</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 15:10:22. [Issue ID 240171]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>7</Day>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Year>2004</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <ScanInformation>[Counterpaul-Dcp]</ScanInformation>
  <Writer>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Writer>
  <Penciller>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Penciller>
  <Inker>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Inker>
  <Colorist>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Daniel Clowes,Daniel Clowes</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>The most popular alternative comic in the world is back, and it's bigger and better than ever! Presenting the first new issue of Eightball in over two years, and it's another self-contained, full-color, oversized masterpiece like the award-winning previous issue! "The Death Ray" is an astonishing new graphic novelette by Daniel Clowes. Set mostly in the '70s, it's the story of a teenage superhero — part bildungsroman, part horror story, part superhero comic (yes), it takes the experimentation in terms of story structure, coloring, etc from "Ice Haven" (Eightball #22) to the next level. It's sure to set mouths agape and tongues a-waggin'!

The Death Ray is divided into 34 parts.</Summary>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/eightball-23-the-death-ray/4000-110385/</Web>
  <CoverArtist>Daniel Clowes</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>