<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Rainulf the Wraith-Stalker,Alien</Characters>
  <Day>24</Day>
  <Editor>Phil Amara</Editor>
  <Format>One-Shot</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-128580</GTIN>
  <Inker>David Wenzel,David Wenzel</Inker>
  <Letterer>Tracy Hampton-Munsey,Tracey Munsey</Letterer>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T00:19:41 [Issue ID 4000-128580] urn:comicvine:4000-128580
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-09 21:17:35. [Issue ID 337166]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <PageCount>22</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1088468" ImageWidth="1365" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="364582" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1508350" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1203310" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1537900" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1492043" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1443217" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1400961" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1605760" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1486081" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1489608" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1417384" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1415358" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1355597" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1536410" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1430343" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1635387" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1496457" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1649518" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1486449" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="2048" ImageSize="1380194" ImageWidth="1365" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1453979" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>David Wenzel,David Wenzel</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Dark Horse</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Digital) (Bean-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Aliens: Stalker</Series>
  <Summary>In a time of myth, when Vikings ruled the land, when their berserker rage went unmatched by anyone who opposed them. In this fierce and merciless time, the legendary warrior Rainulf the Wraith-Stalker is summoned by the granddaughter of a dead king to best a deadly enemy. But this enemy is unlike anything Rainulf has ever faced. In the dense, cold mists of this ancient land hides an invincible creature born of the Underworld -- with iron skin, dagger teeth, and blood that burns stone -- known in the far-flung future as an Alien.

Torfinn, the leader of a band of Vikings has taken the offer of Lady Alwin and her brother Odo to rid their homeland of the Stalker, a demon their ancestors awaken and has since cursed their bloodline by attacking their village every fifty years. Torfinn, acquires the aid of Rainulf the Wraith-Stalker, a seer who has been trained his whole life to fight the Stalker. Now ready to fight the Stalker, Torfinn and his band of warriors go to Lady Alwin and Odo's homeland where they see the carnage the Stalker leaves behind.

Before they are prepared the Stalker attacks and it's revealed to be a Alien solider, and the Viking's weapons have little to no effect against it. Torfinn is blinded and many of his men are slaughtered. The Stalker is runs away when Rainulf makes a giant bonfire, and Torfinn's advance and corner the Stalker in its cave.

Rainulf volunteers to go into the cave, as long as Odo and his men guard the entrance, but once in the cave Odo betrays Rainulf and Torfinn. He backstabs Torfinn, kills his men and leaves Rainulf to die, but not before he takes any treasure, he can get his hands on. Rainulf, unaware of what's happening outside the cave fights the Stalker with fire and his mentor's special sword. He seems to be winning when the Stalker runs away, back above ground.

Meanwhile, Lady Alwin protests her brother's actions, but he and his men force her to leave the island, assuming the Stalker will be coming for them next. Out on the water, Odo and his men are ambushed by the Stalker, who kills everyone but Lady Alwin. Seeing her brother dead, Lady Alwin goes into a blood frenzy and with Rainulf help they are able to kill the Stalker, but not before it melts Rainulf's sword down to the hilt and sinks the boat.  

Years Later, Rainulf's ancestor is now a Colonial Marine, and is telling his fellow solders the legend behind his strange, shaped dagger and how it has brought him luck killing Aliens, the future versions of Stalkers.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 15:04:26.  [CVDB128580]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/aliens-stalker-1/4000-128580/</Summary>
  <Teams>Colonial Marines,Aliens (Xenomorphs),Vikings</Teams>
  <Volume>1998</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/aliens-stalker-1/4000-128580/</Web>
  <Writer>David Wenzel,David Wenzel</Writer>
  <Year>1998</Year>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Title>Aliens: Stalker</Title>
  <Genre>Science fiction,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Colorist>David Wenzel</Colorist>
</ComicInfo>