<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Conversation; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;: Revenge of the Black &amp; White Villains or: "Fill in the Blank!"</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>35</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Jenny and Zot have an extended discussion about whether to have sex. Zot asked Jenny if she wanted to have sex at the end of the last issue, and Jenny is uncomfortable with the idea.

They tell each other they love each other. They both say they are virgins. (At one point, Zot says he is 16, and McCloud says in a later commentary that Jenny is also "a couple years older" than before, so presumably also 16.) Zot is a little confused about why Jenny is so embarrassed; this seems to partly be because of how sex is treated on his world and partly because he is so optimistic and naive about Jenny's world.

Jenny talks about her stuff animal bear, Marvin. She has had him since the first time her family moved; he is her one constant friend in life. Now Zot fills that space.

Jenny admits she has feelings about him too, and turns the tables by playfully asking what about her turns him on. He is embarrassed to admit that he finds her breasts sexy.

They clasp together on the bed and for a moment seem like they are going to sleep together, but then Jenny says she's not ready. Zot gets up to go sleep in his interdimensional portal, but Jenny finally agrees to see what it's like in there. The issue has an intentionally ambiguous ending that does not say whether they sleep together or not.

In "Revenge of the Black and White Villains," The Blotch and Doctor Pweent talk in prison. They use Dimension 10 1/2's non-continuity powers to escape, along with Bellows. Pweent finds out that they're all in a black and white comic and determines to change that. Meanwhile Zot and Jenny go to aa TV station where they see a computer that can colorize old comics and movies, and also make other changes, like switching the actors. The villains come in and take over the computer, transporting Zot and Jenny into old books and movies. At home, Jenny's mom and Butch see that everything on their TV has been changed. The villains argue among themselves and chaos happens. Zot and Jenny return to normal and everything is fixed--except for D. Pweent, who is now stuck in an old show.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:34.  [CVDB94172]</Notes>
  <Year>1991</Year>
  <Month>03</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Eric Yarber, Ivy Ratafia, Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-35-the-conversation-the-adventures-of-zot-in-d/4000-94172/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>Doctor Pweent, Jenny Weaver, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="94089" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="180078" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="168122" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="172176" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="149927" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="153385" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="161620" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="173072" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="166703" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="174329" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="173123" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="185917" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="184316" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="179616" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="165355" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="145991" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="150457" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="151077" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="176384" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="193421" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="269432" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="298133" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="212519" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="150241" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="192897" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="202398" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="204437" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="203130" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="204727" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
