<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Robot,Bulletproof,The Immortal,Black Samson,Invincible,William Clockwell,Deborah Grayson,Atom Eve,Dupli-Kate,Derek Sanders,Shrinking Ray,Art,Donald Ferguson,Amber Bennett,Monster Girl,B.N. Winslow,Chad Anderson,Cecil Stedman,Rex-Splode,Dan</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bill Crabtree</Colorist>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-125184</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Frank Cho,Ryan Ottley,Frank Cho</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Rus Wooton</Letterer>
  <Locations>Reginald Vel Johnson High School,Burger Mart,Saudi Arabia,Utah</Locations>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:14:43 [Issue ID 4000-125184] urn:comicvine:4000-125184 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/276832
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 07:20:32. [Issue ID 125184]</Notes>
  <Number>14</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Frank Cho,Ryan Ottley,Frank Cho,Ryan Ottley</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Invincible</Series>
  <Teams>Flaxans,Guardians of the Globe</Teams>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/invincible-14/4000-125184/</Web>
  <Writer>Robert Kirkman</Writer>
  <Year>2004</Year>
  <Summary>Mark Grayson is just like most everyone else his age, except that his father is the most powerful superhero on the planet. And now he's begun to inherit his father's powers. It all sounds okay at first, but how do you follow in your father's footsteps when you know you will never live up to his standards? They're back! The dreaded alien invaders from another dimension have returned seeking revenge! Invincible and Atom Eve are the front line against an all-out invasion of EPIC proportions. The end of the world is at hand, and our best defense is a couple of 18-year old superheroes. Let's hope they've got their hormones in check!

This issue begins with Invincible,and the Guardian of the Globe fighting the alien race of the Flaxans. Somehow they are not aging until one of their wristbands falls off and Invincible discovers their weakness. Invincible returns home to find the Immortal waiting outside his window, telling him that he doesn't trust him. When he actually gets inside, Cecil is in his house and explains to him that the recording from his fight with Omni Man has been released to the media. When Invincible asks him how he got into his house he tells him that he has the technology to teleport. In the meantime Derek, one of the kids who was abducted and almost turned into a living bomb causes trouble at school. Mark runs into Amber who immediately embraces him and they agree to talk later. Bulletproof is added to the Guardians of the Globe, and the Immortal is put in charge. Mark returns home to find his mom drunk on the floor and she tells him, "Why did you have to fight him Mark? Why did you have to drive him away?"</Summary>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <CoverArtist>Bill Crabtree,Frank Cho</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>