<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Kenny,Molly,Ethan's Girl,Ruby,Taylor,Nancy,Alexis,Chester,Pa Pickett,Nina,Pickett Boy,Antwan,Ethan Daniels,Junior,Wes Wilden,Ted,Sally,Merv</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jonathan Luna</Colorist>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-107254</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna,Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Inker>
  <Letterer>Jonathan Luna</Letterer>
  <Locations>Pennystown</Locations>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:08:40 [Issue ID 4000-107254] urn:comicvine:4000-107254
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 05:02:39. [Issue ID 107254]</Notes>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna,Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Girls</Series>
  <Summary>The ultimate battle of the sexes begins.

*Synopsis*
Naked girls, identical to the one Ethan found in the road, hatch from eggs in Ethan's bathroom. Ethan, Taylor, and Wes stare in disbelief. 

Outside Ethan's house, the town folk gather and fill Ted and Ruby in on what occurred the night before. Ted is shocked at how terrible Ethan acted and hopes that Wes can straighten Ethan out.

Inside Ethan's house, Wes demands that Ethan give some answers as to why naked girls are hatching from eggs. Ethan doesn't know, and the conversation gets the girls' attention. The girls attack the trio in the kitchen. The people outside hear the scuffling and assume that Wes is beating Ethan up. Inside, the girls continue to pound on the trio, Wes and Ethan are somewhat between the girls and Taylor and Taylor is able to escape with the men into a closet.

Trapped in the closet, Ethan picks up a walkie-talkie and contacts Merv. Once he hears that Ethan is in trouble, Merv packs up his dynamite and heads to Ethan's house. He storms in with a flare and begins waiving it at the girls, even burning one in the side. The burned girl knocks the flare to the ground and the others gather around Merv, who is now also on the ground (some dynamite has fallen from his pack). A fire starts, however, and the girls run out the door scared. The trio and Merv run out the back as the dynamite catch fire and explode. The girls had gone out the front and headed for the pack of townspeople. Ethan comes to to hear screaming.</Summary>
  <Tags>Kenny,Ethan's Girl,Pennystown,Alexis,Junior,Nancy,Pickett Boy,Antwan,Sally,Merv,Molly,Chester,Girl Army,Nina,Ruby,Taylor,Pa Pickett,Ethan Daniels,Wes Wilden,Ted</Tags>
  <Teams>Girl Army</Teams>
  <Title>Part 3</Title>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/girls-3-part-3/4000-107254/</Web>
  <Writer>Jonathan Luna,Joshua Luna</Writer>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Count>24</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Jonathan Luna</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>