<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Alpanu Lasas,Barbatos,Tim Hunter,Molly,The Wild Hunt,Tim Hunter II,Lord Auberon</Characters>
  <Colorist>Jamison,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Jamison</Colorist>
  <Editor>Alisa Kwitney,Heidi MacDonald,Will Dennis</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-46651</GTIN>
  <Inker>Barbara Schulz,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Peter Gross,Ryan Kelly,Barbara Schulz</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:51:36 [Issue ID 4000-46651] urn:comicvine:4000-46651
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:14:55. [Issue ID 63628]</Notes>
  <Number>74</Number>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="352258" ImageWidth="986" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="309780" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="260272" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="253030" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="272618" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="268300" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="256748" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="233219" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="247882" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="270986" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="264402" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="303242" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="337716" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="267510" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="298397" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="283635" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="255878" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="323266" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="234358" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="244941" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="218020" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="271505" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1511" ImageSize="269744" ImageWidth="986" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="275874" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Timothy Hunter makes a fateful choice, and makes the ultimate sacrifice in his final confrontation with his evil Other self. And the one who survives the battle will forfeit his soul to the demon Barbatos. 

Barbatos and Hauptman watch over the Other's mansion. Tim wants to meet the Other before he reclaims his magic, and Barbatos insists that Tim get his magic before he takes his memory.  However, they don't see Tim sneaking in--they see Molly.

Tim had written a letter to Molly, explaining that he was going to sell his memory to Barbatos despite her warning, but not because he wanted power--because he was willing to sacrifice himself to get rid of the Other.

Molly comes after him, despite his warning, passing through the Other's creepy statues of everyone he has defeated.  A Wobbly finds her and brings her in.

The Other tries to beat off versions of Leah; he's tired of all these variants.  He is very happy, however, to see Molly.  She pretends to want to help him, but the Other realizes Molly would never say that.  He tears off her glamor stone to reveal that it is really Tim.

Tim lies, saying that he is a duplicate made by Thomas Curry, and explains that he has the bottle of his magic.  He gives it to the Other.  The Other makes Tim test it to make sure it's not poison, then he drinks it down.

The Other overloads, but isn't dead. Barbatos comes in and thinks Tim is reneging on the deal. Tim tries to kill the Other but fails. The Other pathetically says it only wanted to not be alone.  Tim realizes he's no better than the Other and is responsible for him. He absorbs part of his magic to close the gates between worlds.

Tim gives Barbatos his memory of how he created the Other, which makes the Other disappear.  When he disappears, all the memories Tim gave up, piece by piece, to create the other Tims in other dimensions come back to him.  He is now able to feel.

Tim collapses and seems to have broken under the strain.  Barbatos comes over to "help."

The real Alpanu Lasas talks with Auberon. He says his plan was to make sure the Wild Hunt remained free, since their role is important. The real Lasas will take his place in the Hunt.  Auberon says Tim made the right sacrifice and he respects that.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:22:19.  [CVDB46651]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-74-the-closing-part-two-being-m/4000-46651/</Summary>
  <Title>The Closing Part Two - Being Mr. Wrong</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-74-the-closing-part-two-being-m/4000-46651/</Web>
  <Writer>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>