<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1935</GTIN>
  <Inker>Ogden Whitney,Harry Lazarus,Art Gates,Ken Landau,Harry Lazarus,Art Gates,Ken Landau,Ogden Whitney</Inker>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:34:38 [Issue ID 4000-1935] urn:comicvine:4000-1935
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 02:50:46. [Issue ID 12223]</Notes>
  <Number>35</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Ogden Whitney,Harry Lazarus,Art Gates,Sam Citron,Ken Landau,Harry Lazarus,Art Gates,Sam Citron,Ken Landau,Ogden Whitney</Penciller>
  <Publisher>American Comics Group</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>ACG Aug  Ontology</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Forbidden Worlds</Series>
  <Volume>1951</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/forbidden-worlds-35/4000-1935/</Web>
  <Year>1955</Year>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Title>The Night Nothing Happened; The Tiny War!; Calculated Risk!; The Dreamer!</Title>
  <Summary>The Night Nothing Happened: Collins, a young scientist, discovers through his instruments that an alien invasion is coming. The aliens cause a fog that renders humanity in a trance. Collins is spared because he was in his lead shielded lab at the time. After the fog is dispersed, Collins tries to explain what happened to the other scientists including the respected Professor Dobson. No one believes him and he is institutionalized.

The Tiny War!: Jim and Sally come across a war in the forest between the benevolent Forest Goblins and the malevolent Water Goblins.

Calculated Risk!: Scouts from the planet Volarnus go to Earth to size it up for invasion. They try to land on a patch of uninhabited territory that their ships echo detector confirms. They land only to realize that this uninhabited territory is the Ocean and they sink. When they don't radio back to their home planet, the other Volarnians believe that Earth is too dangerous and call off the planned invasion.

The Dreamer!: Claire Adams has dreams of the future that come true including winning the lottery. When she begins to have troubling dreams of disasters that come true, she can't bare to sleep anymore. In one of her dreams a shadowy figure assures her she won't have bad dreams anymore. Claire is relieved, and the next day out with her husband she is hit and killed by a car. The shadowy figure was right. She won't have bad dreams anymore because she is now dead!

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <Characters>Collins,Professor Dobson</Characters>
  <Letterer>Ed Hamilton,Ed Hamilton</Letterer>
  <Editor>Richard E. Hughes</Editor>
</ComicInfo>