<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-56975</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:38:13 [Issue ID 4000-56975] urn:comicvine:4000-56975
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 19:01:10. [Issue ID 75622]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Adventures into Weird Worlds</Series>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-weird-worlds-5/4000-56975/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>30</Count>
  <Title>I Crawl Through Graves; You're Going to Die Yesterday; Where?; The Terrible Trunk; Don't Bury Me Deep!</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Science fiction</Genre>
  <Summary>I Crawl Through Graves: A ghoul digs underground tunnels throughout a nearby cemetery in order to rob the dead until one of the corpses returns for her jewelry.

You're Going to Die Yesterday: A man uses a time machine in order to murder the father of his rival before he was ever born, but ends up making a mistake and killing his own father.

Where?: A story of an amnesic old vampire that feeds only once a year at midnight.

The Terrible Trunk: A criminal buys a trunk at auction that makes anything put inside disappear. He figures he can use it in order to eliminate murder evidence, but as he is lugging it down the stairs, he stumbles and falls into it.

Don't Bury Me Deep!: An undertaker desperate to sell an expensive coffin, panics when the corpse turns out not to be dead, and kills the man again, which accidentally leads to his own death.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Dick Ayers,Gerald Altman,Joe Maneely,Joe Sinnott,Bill Everett</Penciller>
  <Inker>Ernie Bache,Gerald Altman,Joe Maneely,Joe Sinnott,Bill Everett</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>