<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Pix</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Title>One Weirdest Weekend</Title>
  <Volume>2017</Volume>
  <Genre>Teen,Superhero</Genre>
  <Summary>Pix is babysitting for Noah, and assumes that his conversations with Bonus are only in his imagination.

Pix, Bonus, and the bear free Noah, and Pix agrees to kiss the frog, so that everyone can resume their true forms.  She's stunned to discover that he is a tall and handsome young man, but appalled that he assumes they will immediately get married.  She explains the whole day's events to her parents and her girl friends, while Lorne and his Uncle Ellis establish themselves locally so that he may pursue his wooing.

Pix refuses to kiss the frog, but reluctantly agrees to accept his help... and that of his uncle, transformed into an owl... when she learns that Noah has disappeared from his bed next door. Bonus the dog reveals that he can speak with all other creatures, and coordinates the search after Pix is turned into a winged rabbit, so as not to attract attention. They find that Noah has been taken prisoner by the missing escaped monkey, who demands the secret of Noah's ability to talk with his dog and other animals... not recognizing that the power actually lies with the dog, not Noah.

Accustomed to being the center of attention, Luke becomes enraged when people at the restaurant are more interested in Pix than in him. Losing control, he transforms into a red dragon and attacks. Once she defeats him, the lady from the shoe store reveals herself as a white dragon, and describes an ongoing war between her kind and the evil reds. An exhausted Pix wants nothing more than to go to bed, but her sleep is interrupted by a frog demanding that she kiss him.

Pix fights off nemeses in the sink drain, but regains her size in time to get ready for her date with Luke. This discombobulates Seth, who arrives on the scene too late, planning to proclaim his love for Pix.

Pix explains to the national TV audience that her father is King of the Fairies, making her a fairy princess. When the studio technology goes wild and attacks, Pix protects the audience, the host, and the other guest, teen heartthrob Luke. Luke asks her out to dinner, and she goes shoe shopping. A mysterious saleswoman gives her a pair of new shoes. But when Pix returns home she discovers that she has been shrunk to be only a few inches tall. Meanwhile the community is obsessed with news of a monkey escaped from the zoo.

Pix's friends help her with her superhero debut.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 06:49:19. [Issue ID 1822937]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Month>2</Month>
  <Year>2017</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>E/Everyone</AgeRating>
  <Characters>Norah,Pix,Noah,Bonus,Rich (Noah's father)</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
    <Page Image="52" />
    <Page Image="53" />
    <Page Image="54" />
    <Page Image="55" />
    <Page Image="56" />
    <Page Image="57" />
    <Page Image="58" />
    <Page Image="59" />
    <Page Image="60" />
    <Page Image="61" />
    <Page Image="62" />
    <Page Image="63" />
    <Page Image="64" />
    <Page Image="65" />
    <Page Image="66" />
    <Page Image="67" />
    <Page Image="68" />
    <Page Image="69" />
    <Page Image="70" />
    <Page Image="71" />
    <Page Image="72" />
    <Page Image="73" />
    <Page Image="74" />
    <Page Image="75" />
    <Page Image="76" />
    <Page Image="77" />
    <Page Image="78" />
    <Page Image="79" />
    <Page Image="80" />
    <Page Image="81" />
    <Page Image="82" />
    <Page Image="83" />
    <Page Image="84" />
    <Page Image="85" />
    <Page Image="86" />
    <Page Image="87" />
    <Page Image="88" />
    <Page Image="89" />
    <Page Image="90" />
    <Page Image="91" />
    <Page Image="92" />
    <Page Image="93" />
    <Page Image="94" />
    <Page Image="95" />
    <Page Image="96" />
    <Page Image="97" />
    <Page Image="98" />
    <Page Image="99" />
    <Page Image="100" />
    <Page Image="101" />
    <Page Image="102" />
    <Page Image="103" />
    <Page Image="104" />
    <Page Image="105" />
    <Page Image="106" />
    <Page Image="107" />
    <Page Image="108" />
    <Page Image="109" />
    <Page Image="110" />
    <Page Image="111" />
    <Page Image="112" />
    <Page Image="113" />
    <Page Image="114" />
    <Page Image="115" />
    <Page Image="116" />
    <Page Image="117" />
    <Page Image="118" />
    <Page Image="119" />
    <Page Image="120" />
    <Page Image="121" />
    <Page Image="122" />
    <Page Image="123" />
    <Page Image="124" />
    <Page Image="125" />
    <Page Image="126" />
    <Page Image="127" />
    <Page Image="128" />
    <Page Image="129" />
    <Page Image="130" />
    <Page Image="131" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>