<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Cavewoman: Rain</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>8</Count>
  <Title>Chapter Two</Title>
  <Volume>1996</Volume>
  <Summary>The storms are finally coming. Meriem has rescued the baby and is washing it near a waterfall. She's having a lot of fun with the child and really enjoys making it laugh. Her grandfather appears to her and tells her they re being hunted. With the baby secure in a backpack she plans to climb a high tree and knock the Bird Claws off. They are smart though and try to get ahead of her on adjacent trees. She manages to elude most of them and even punches one in the face. She makes it to the electric plant and finds body parts and Klyde's foot prints. He's still there. She uses sign language to tell him that lizards are coming to hurt little Gramp and that she is weak. He roars and surprises the Bird Claws when they show up.

Prof. Cook is driving his armored speedster along with passengers Cap. Lavery, Sgt. Higgins and Bruce Kabbit. On their way to the electrical plant they try to rescue a man who left the safety of the Compound (what the towns people are calling the mall) to retrieve his beloved truck. A T-Rex and Triceratops fight has broken out and the Professor is loving it. It looks as though the Triceratops is killed but just as the Rex is going to eat the man the Triceratops pierces it's torso with it's horns and kills it. They collect the man whose truck is now destroyed and continue to the power plant.

Lumpy and some guys are trying to get some comics to read. The owner of the shop agrees to give them each $40 in comics and promises to keep the kids' club a secret if they help him move them to the compound. They agree and move everything over. Lumpy sees a dinosaur attack a policeman and the owner orders everyone into the storage room. One of the dinosaurs crashes through the window and attacks him.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 03:31:56. [Issue ID 59681]</Notes>
  <StoryArc>"Cavewoman: Rain" Rain</StoryArc>
  <Publisher>Caliber Press</Publisher>
  <Year>1996</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cavewoman-rain-2-chapter-two/4000-43149/</Web>
  <Characters>Meriem Cooper,Francis Reicher II,Timothy Higgins,Patricia Lavery,Bob Cook,Bruce Kabbit,Francis Peacock Reicher,Klyde</Characters>
  <Teams>Dinosaurs</Teams>
  <Locations>Marshville,Prehistoric Jungle</Locations>
  <Writer>Budd Root</Writer>
  <Penciller>Budd Root,Richard Pollard</Penciller>
  <Inker>Bradley Walton,Budd Root,Richard Pollard</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bradley Walton</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Budd Root</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Joe Pruett</Editor>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
  </Pages>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
</ComicInfo>