<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Dr. Tucker,Retro Girl,Kutter,Zora,Christian Walker,Johnny Royalle,Deena Pilgrim,Captain</Characters>
  <Count>38</Count>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Editor>KC McCrory</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-46350</GTIN>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T19:10:29 [Issue ID 4000-46350] urn:comicvine:4000-46350
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-20 08:57:13. [Issue ID 46350]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Powers</Series>
  <Summary>Detectives Christian Walker and Deena Pilgrim work out of the special homicide officers in charge of cases that involve...Powers. And now they are involved in the most important case of their careers. Retro girl, America's darling, has been murdered. It's cops and superheroes like you have NEVER seen them in the gritty, crime comic book series Powers from super hot comic writer and EISNER award winner Brian Michael Bendis (Sam And Twitch, Daredevil, Jinx, Batman) and art deco comic artist Mike Avon Oeming (Young Justice, Superman). This on going, hard-boiled crime comic with a mainstream twist is brought to you in startling full color by Pat Garrehy (JLA).

SPOILERS

News of Retro Girl's death is all over the news. An autopsy is about to be attempted. It is uncertain how to actually pierce her skin and what to compare the findings with. Kutter meets Deena and manages to insult her right away. She shuts him down with little effort. In the Captain's office, Walker and Pilgrim are told that there is a visitor on the rooftop.

The hero known as Zora has arrived to talk to Walker. She wants to know if they found out who killed Janis. She also asks Walker if he's spoken to Johnny Royalle yet. He's filed a restraining order on everyone. Walker tells her that they haven't spoken to anyone yet. Zora tells Walker that even though things are different, he can still call her, just to talk. He says maybe he will. Deena is surprised and asks if he knows her. Walker just shushes her.

In the child care room, Calista is entertaining the other kids by telling them of the exploits against space monkeys. Walker is glad she's doing okay after everything she's been through. They make their way to Johnny Royalle's nightclub. Johnny is not there. He's already been picked up. Johnny's men won't tell them who. Deena hands Walker her gun and beats the crap out of them. One is about to tell her who took Johnny in when a news report comes on answering their question. Kutter brought him in even though it's not his case.</Summary>
  <Title>Who Killed Retro Girl? Part 2</Title>
  <Volume>2000</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/powers-2-who-killed-retro-girl-part-2/4000-46350/</Web>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <Writer>Brian Michael Bendis</Writer>
  <Penciller>Michael Avon Oeming,Michael Avon Oeming</Penciller>
  <Inker>Michael Avon Oeming,Michael Avon Oeming</Inker>
  <Colorist>Pat Garrahy</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Brian Michael Bendis,Pat Garrahy</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Michael Avon Oeming</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>