<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Little Orphan Annie,Elvis Presley,The Spirit,Alfred E. Neuman,Ed Sullivan,Batman,Moby Dick,Walt Disney,Officer Pupp,Mickey Mouse,Ming The Merciless,Robert E. Lee,Captain Ahab,Buster Brown,Barney Baxter,Mad Hatter,Pogo Possum,Mary Worth,Smilin' Jack,Ignatz Mouse,Charlie Chan,Mickey Mantle,Krazy Kat,Dick Tracy,Jerry Lewis,Liberace,Ishmael,Dean Martin,Steve Allen,Lone Ranger,Queequeg,Starbuck,Dick Grayson,The Yellow Kid,Groucho Marx,Popeye,Casper,Dickie Dare</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-129539</GTIN>
  <Inker>Don Martin,Harvey Kurtzman,Jack Davis,Norman Mingo,Reed Crandall,Jack Davis,Don Martin,Phil Interlandi,Bob Clarke,Rice,Bill Davis,Parks,Ilnicki,Jerry Lee,Kent,Thomas,Wally Wood,Bill Elder</Inker>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:17:15 [Issue ID 4000-129539] urn:comicvine:4000-129539
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:34:36. [Issue ID 93830]</Notes>
  <Number>30</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
    <Page Image="51" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Don Martin,Harvey Kurtzman,Jack Davis,Norman Mingo,Reed Crandall,Jack Davis,Don Martin,Phil Interlandi,Bob Clarke,Rice,Bill Davis,Parks,Ilnicki,Jerry Lee,Kent,Thomas,Wally Wood,Bill Elder</Penciller>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Mad</Series>
  <Tags>Little Orphan Annie,Elvis Presley,The Spirit,Alfred E. Neuman,Ed Sullivan,Batman,Moby Dick,Walt Disney,Officer Pupp,Mickey Mouse,Ming The Merciless,Robert E. Lee,Captain Ahab,Buster Brown,Barney Baxter,Mad Hatter,Pogo Possum,Mary Worth,Smilin' Jack,Ignatz Mouse,Charlie Chan,Mickey Mantle,Krazy Kat,Dick Tracy,Jerry Lewis,Liberace,Ishmael,Dean Martin,Steve Allen,Lone Ranger,Queequeg,Starbuck,Dick Grayson,The Yellow Kid,Groucho Marx,Popeye,Casper,Dickie Dare</Tags>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/mad-30/4000-129539/</Web>
  <Year>1956</Year>
  <Count>550</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Harvey Kurtzman,Norman Mingo</CoverArtist>
  <Title>B. F. Goodnrich Autoless - Because You Don't Need a Car, Just Tires; Elvis Pelvis; Gunsmoked; Alfred E. Neuman Answers Your Questions; The Manly Art of Self Defense; Scenes We'd Like To See: The Gladiator and the Empress; MAD Builds a More Civilized Mouse Trap; Motorist Beware!; Bowling; Collegiate Whimsey; Morbid Dick; Alfred E. Neuman Answers Your Questions; What's Happened to the... Pulp Magazines?; A Saw Screams at Midnight; MAD Merit Badges; Walt Dizzy Presents Dizzyland; Alfred E. Neuman Answers Your Questions</Title>
  <Genre>Satire-parody,Humor</Genre>
  <Summary>B. F. Goodnrich Autoless - Because You Don't Need a Car, Just Tires: Phony ad for tires from B. F. Goodnrich that don't need a car.

Elvis Pelvis: Satirical look at various facets of Elvis Presley's style.

Gunsmoked: Quick recap of typical plots from the show.

Alfred E. Neuman Answers Your Questions: Advice for a man who loves both his wife and taxidermy, but whose wife hates his taxidermy.

The Manly Art of Self Defense: Excerpts from a treatise on The Manly Art of Self Defense by Edmund E. Price, published 1867, with illustrations and new captions.

Scenes We'd Like To See: The Gladiator and the Empress: A man is thrown into the gladiatorial ring and defeats a better armed opponent...but loses to a lion.

MAD Builds a More Civilized Mouse Trap: Several supposedly civilized ways to trap and kill mice.

Motorist Beware!: Describes the escalating efforts of police to patrol highways unnoticed, including several of the latest unmarked vehicles.

Bowling: Shows the scoring, style tips, psychological underpinnings, and problems of bowling.

Collegiate Whimsey: Gag cartoons from the following college publications: Iowa State Green Gander; Harvard Lampoon; Stanford Chaparral; Florida Smoke Signals; Cornell Widow; Minnesota Daily; Michigan Gargoyle; California Pelican; U.C.L.A. Scop

Morbid Dick: Tells the tale of the ill-fated voyage of the Peckwad in a vain attempt to kill the white whale.

Alfred E. Neuman Answers Your Questions: Advice to a man whose girlfriend's father threatens that the man will only marry his daughter over his dead body.

What's Happened to the... Pulp Magazines?: Various genres of pulp stories are all given the same treatment, showing underlying similarity.

A Saw Screams at Midnight: Techniques for using a band saw.

MAD Merit Badges: Scout-type merit badges for everyday lazy, loutish clods.

Walt Dizzy Presents Dizzyland: Behind the scenes look at the 5 worlds of Dizzyland: Tomorrowsland, Frontrearland, Adventuresland, Fantasticland, Moneyland.

Alfred E. Neuman Answers Your Questions: Advice for a girl who's being stalked by a boy.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Edmund E. Price,Phil Interlandi,Nick Meglin,Rice,Bill Davis,Parks,Ilnicki,Jerry Lee,Kent,Thomas,James Blish,Carl Reiner</Writer>
  <Editor>Albert B. Feldstein,Harvey Kurtzman</Editor>
</ComicInfo>