<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Day>10</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-221876</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:32:15 [Issue ID 4000-221876] urn:comicvine:4000-221876
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 15:10:22. [Issue ID 273959]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Series>Ted McKeever's Metropōl</Series>
  <Summary>Notochord is being taken down town by two officers, one decides to take a shortcut but runs over a dog. He gets out to check on it, it's dead but is infested with fleas and he gets bitten. A rather large long haired character gets off a bus but is confronted by a mugger, the mugger see's that It's a woman and says he's going to have a "good time" but the big lady grabs his hand, disarming him and then murdering him. she walks off bumping into the man who hung the other man in the last issue. He stumbles over the body of the mugger and runs away into a diner where there is a rather peaky looking character who is ordering vomits and then dies. The man who saw the muggers body then leaves and is accosted in the street by two prostitutes he declines but a man named Humphrey takes one back to his room.

We then see a man buying a paper but he doesn't manage to get that far as he vomits and dies before paying.

Notochord is being questioned by the two detectives but he doesn't know what they want him to say, the officer who ran over the dog says he is feeling ill and would like to go home, they throw Notochord into a rather disgusting holding cell for the night telling him to have "pleasant dreams". Notochord then calls out to Enoch.</Summary>
  <Title>My Bones, My Pulse</Title>
  <Volume>1991</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/ted-mckeever-s-metropol-2-my-bones-my-pulse/4000-221876/</Web>
  <Year>1991</Year>
  <Count>12</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Writer>Ted McKeever,Ted McKeever</Writer>
  <Penciller>Ted McKeever,Ted McKeever</Penciller>
  <Inker>Ted McKeever,Ted McKeever</Inker>
  <Colorist>Ted McKeever,Ted McKeever</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Phil Felix,Phil Felix</Letterer>
  <Editor>Marc McLaurin</Editor>
</ComicInfo>