<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Kids Are (Mostly) All Right</Title>
  <Series>Prelude to Deadpool Corps</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Volume>2010</Volume>
  <Summary>Witness the birth of the most important super hero team ever in a universe-spanning event that will rock the month of March! Wade Wilson has been tapped to save the Universe, and to do that he's going to need help. Enter: The sexy-but-insecure Lady Deadpool! The devious-but-lovable Headpool (a.k.a. the Zombie Deadpool Head)! The bratty-but-brilliant Kidpool! And the irascible mutt known as Dogpool! Individually, they're, well, kind of messed up, but together, they're the unstoppable force know as DPC.Summary

In this universe most marvel heroes are kids. Professor X wants to tap Emma Frost by having a dance social between Professor X's male students, and Emma Frost's female students. Storm warns the professor about Kidpool so the professor made a plan. Meanwhile Kidpool is seen giving a wedgie to kid Cyclops which caused them both to see Storm. Storm used the professors plan by putting both of them in detention for the whole day. So Kidpool and Cyclops are in the danger room for detention, Cyclops says he has the codes for the danger room. So Kidpool took 2 lightsabers and fought Cyclops until he figured out Cyclops could just unlock the door and leave. So Kidpool and Cyclops are at the dance, Cyclops sees Jean dancing with Wolverine. Cyclolps said he will give Kidpool 20 dollars if he can distract them long enough for him to get to Jean. So Kidpool distracted the students until Wolverine attacked Kidpool along with Angel and Colossus. Storm then broke up the fight and everyone was saying how much they don't like Kidpool until Earth 616 Deadpool came in and said he needed Kidpool. So Kidpool went with Deadpool and Earth 616 Deadpool called Kidpool Tito.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-04 18:19:39.  [CVDB199993]</Notes>
  <Year>2010</Year>
  <Month>05</Month>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <Writer>Victor Gischler</Writer>
  <Penciller>Whilce Portacio</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jaime Mendoza</Inker>
  <Colorist>Thomas Mason</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Clayton Cowles</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Dave Johnson, Rico Renzi</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Axel Alonso, Joe Quesada, Sebastian Girner</Editor>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/prelude-to-deadpool-corps-2-the-kids-are-mostly-al/4000-199993/</Web>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Characters>Angel, Beast, Colossus, Cyclops, Deadpool, Emma Frost, Jean Grey, Kidpool, Professor X, Rogue, Storm, Wolverine</Characters>
  <Teams>X-Men</Teams>
  <Locations>Xavier Institute</Locations>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="798393" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1224844" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1255565" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1016413" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1143152" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1150046" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1281204" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1146467" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1386104" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1257414" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1188668" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1238690" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1396256" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1132918" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1207236" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1392282" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1017416" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1127556" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1060233" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1106673" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1349153" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1250632" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1130349" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="741086" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="924222" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
