<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Asteroth,Brahma,Ganesha,Kali,Lady Death,Shiva,Vandala,Vishnu</Characters>
	<Colorist>Jason Jensen</Colorist>
	<Count>5</Count>
	<Day>1</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-124505</GTIN>
	<Month>6</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:37:46 [Issue ID 4000-124505] urn:comicvine:4000-124505</Notes>
	<Number>3</Number>
	<PageCount>25</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="394640" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="267593"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="616081"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1247266"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="698628"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="677453"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="685824"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="589732"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="585167"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="649070"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="626709"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="703702"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="666688"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="522007"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1383048"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="683996"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="671608"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="716459"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="671898"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="725282"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="622947"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="662193"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="676222"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="616958"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="191021"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Chaos! Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Lady Death: The Odyssey</Series>
	<Summary>Kali is the ruler of the Cremation Grounds, a realm of Hindu gods and she senses the impending approach of Lady Death as the herald of the Judgement Era. She start to devour her very willing followers

Transported again Lady Death arrives in the cremation grounds and is set upon by Kai's winged servants who try to net her. This time she is more powerful when she arrives and defeats the winged messengers, one of whom flies back and tells Kali of her arrival.

Inside the Trinity temple Lady Death witnesses the other gods discussing Kali's eating of her followers and decide that she is doing what she was created to do. Kali finds her in the temple and touches her shoulder Lady Death takes exception to being touched and against the instructions of the other gods Kali draws her swords and attacks.

Kali accidentally slays one of the other gods in her frenzy but reveals that judgement is coming to all the realms. The other gods discuss her as the pair battle. They come to the conclusion that Kali is out of control and send a flood to cleanse her. The Flood sweeps her into the abyss.

Vandala watches over the mess and wonders if she has made the right choice in forcing Lady Death's hand who now declares she has learned nothing and that all her efforts are still purely self serving. Vandala is dismayed even if she has given Lady Death back her fighting spirit, but none of the nobility or insight. Only for her to shout that she just wants peace and renounces the warrior in her.

She decides enough is enough and starts the spell to bring Lady Death back to the void to talk with her directly when Asteroth appears, he tracked her down as the one hiding his target from him.

Lady Death tumbles through the realms the spell drawing her to the void broken she falls until she appears in a beautiful medieval world and she utters one word. Peace.</Summary>
	<Teams>Daevas</Teams>
	<Title>Sacrificed</Title>
	<Volume>1996</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/lady-death-the-odyssey-3-sacrificed/4000-124505/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Pulido</Writer>
	<Year>1996</Year>
</ComicInfo>