<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Season of Dreams Pt. 2; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;! Number 14</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>14</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>This issue was nominated for best single issue for the Eisners.

Jenny seemingly woke up from a dream at the end of last issue. Now she looks outside and sees that it's snowing, when it was June before. Her mom brings her back in and Butch makes a comment about this being the third time this week.

Jenny tells her mom the truth about Zot, but her mom insists that was all a dream. Butch backs up her mom, who then tells Jenny that she has an appointment with a psychologist. They leave Jenny alone to rest for the day. She desperately looks around for proof about what's been happening but can't find anything. She finds her diary, but it has no clues, and in fact references a divorce for her parents, which has not happened in real life.

She runs down to school and pulls out Terry, asking her to corroborate her experiences with Zot. Terry says Zot is a TV character that Jenny has been obsessed with.

Jenny goes home and watches the show, now unsure what is real.

They visit the psychologist. Jenny thinks she can see Zot, but no one else can. She freaks out, ripping the illusion to shreds, and has a psychotic break.

She wakes up in the hospital, almost ready to believe it has all been her imagination. She notices the lightning bolt necklace Zot gave her, which is the proof she needs that Zot is real. Once again, she shreds the illusion around her, this time waking up naked alongside Zot, who is in a coma. Vic is also there, also in a coma.

They are inside Zybox. She finds her clothes in a pile and puts them on. Ernie Cortez, the inventor of Zybox, comes in and explains that he saved their clothes after Zybox was going to destroy them. He is also a prisoner.

Meanwhile, Butch, Max, and Peabody race across the country in an air-car, along with some police from Max's world. Everyone they pass has been hypnotized into standing still, due to a signal coming through their radios or TVs. Peabody jams that signal for them, but can't help everyone.

They finally get to New York and fin Zybox at the top of the Twin Towers. He has grown to enormous size. Zybox warns them not to come near or he will harm the kids. He refuses to say what he wants.

Back in Rio de Janeiro, Ernie's son is hypnotized into continuously playing a video game.

In the Adventures of Dimension 10 1/2, Antisocialman has made Zot annoying, and Cynicalman joins in.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:47.  [CVDB28317]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Month>07</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-14-the-season-of-dreams-pt-2-the-adventures-of/4000-28317/</Web>
  <PageCount>31</PageCount>
  <Characters>Antisocialman, Barbara Weaver, Bellows, Butch Weaver, Cynicalman, Dekko, Digger, Drufus, Ernie Cortez, Floyd, Grand Poo-Bah, Hacker, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Theresa Maria Veras, Vic Taylor, Zot, Zybox</Characters>
  <Teams>The Devoes</Teams>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="15731" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="386572" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="456534" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="433526" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="426997" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="436384" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="488311" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="434362" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="454129" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="512239" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="522090" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="414715" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="496274" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="456486" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="514876" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="567444" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="481828" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="468543" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="455685" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="381590" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="375858" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="367316" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="418536" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="455887" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="400635" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="483066" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="376434" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="545751" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="456397" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="461464" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="444078" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
