<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-361159</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:40:20 [Issue ID 4000-361159] urn:comicvine:4000-361159
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 01:38:44. [Issue ID 306541]</Notes>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Pines</Publisher>
  <Series>The Unseen</Series>
  <Summary>The Phantom Bus: Lawyer Keggler comes to the lonely town of Coultonville and gets drawn into an old tragedy. After a ride on a phantom bus and a dance in the cemetery, Keggler is haunted by the ghost of a dead girl.

Bayou Vengeance: The not-too-bright handyman Louis robs the dead Miss Caroline of her diamond ring to give it to his sweetheart Nanette. Miss Caroline returns from the grave and demands back her precious ring. In a bayou quicksand showdown Louis loses his life.

Dr. Death: After a car accident, a man drags himself into a doctor's house and passes out on the floor. He awakens and finds his wounds treated well, but has to learn from the neighbors that the doctor died the previous night.

Mirror of Hate: The evil and disfigured Lucia kills her half-sister Diane so she won't marry Ted, the man she loves herself. The desperate Lucia commits suicide and her soul is trapped in a mirror. The evil soul in the mirror takes possession of the next woman Ted loves - and a struggle for life and death ensues.

Peg Powler: A man encounters Peg Powler, "the green-haired haunt" of English rivers.

The Eerie Glen: A young man feels sick and goes to bed with a fever. In the night, his dead father comes for him and shows him his new home, the eerie glen. When the young man returns into town, he finds that everybody is ignoring him. Reaching the house, he discovers a society of mourners around a coffin. The young man has obviously died during the night.

</Summary>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-unseen-6/4000-361159/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Title>The Phantom Bus; Bayou Vengeance; Dr. Death; Mirror of Hate; Peg Powler; The Eerie Glen</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Theodore L. Keggler,Lucy Cummings,Dr. Dalton</Characters>
  <Penciller>George Roussos,Jack Katz,Art Saaf,Ross Andru,Alex Toth,George Roussos,Jack Katz,Art Saaf,Ross Andru,Alex Toth</Penciller>
  <Inker>George Roussos,Jack Katz,Art Saaf,Ross Andru,Mike Peppe,George Roussos,Jack Katz,Art Saaf,Ross Andru,Mike Peppe</Inker>
</ComicInfo>