<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>The Sureen [Knot,Swamp Thing [Alec Holland],Capucine,Wolf,Lady Weeds,Brother Jonah,Pistil]</Characters>
  <Colorist>Matthew Wilson,Matthew Wilson</Colorist>
  <Count>42</Count>
  <Editor>Chris Conroy,Matt Idelson</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-446953</GTIN>
  <Inker>Jesus Saiz,Jesús Saiz</Inker>
  <Letterer>Travis Lanham,Travis Lanham</Letterer>
  <Locations>Louisiana</Locations>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:13:08 [Issue ID 4000-446953] urn:comicvine:4000-446953
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:14:11. [Issue ID 1185872]</Notes>
  <Number>29</Number>
  <PageCount>22</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="2357333" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1406166" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1762347" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1684395" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1880771" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1426778" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1978406" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1875667" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="4476526" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1416934" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1183668" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1679545" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1812526" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1651708" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1872279" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1682468" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1578501" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1256975" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1488193" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1720733" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="3212605" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1304869" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Jesus Saiz,Jesús Saiz</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Swamp Thing</Series>
  <Summary>The three-part “Gift of the Sureen” arrives to usher in major changes to The Green! Alec Holland begins his journey across the globe in search of the truth behind an incredible offer from the mysterious cult known as the Sureen!

 

 

The issue opens with the Wolf and Lady Weeds discussing how weak they feel inside of Abigail's old house. The Wolf calms Lady Weeds by telling her that he has a number of connections that he left running in the world during his tenure as avatar that they could look into. Outside Knot of the Sureen begins to explain who he and his group is to Alec. Brother Jonah and Capucine have a heartfelt reunion. Unconvinced by Knot's words he asks Jonah about them. They are a cult who worship the Green and it's avatars.

In New Orleans the Wolf and Lady Weeds are exploring; the Wolf comes across a woman and asks her a question with uncommon phrasing and word usage and is swiftly smacked across the face. Back in the swamp, Knot interjects in Alec and Jonah's conversation, he says that they offer a service but in return would like a sacrament. That sacrament is in the form of a fruit that the group of Sureen eat and they form a deep connection with the Green. Back in New Orleans the Wolf and Lady are meeting with a lawyer to access some funds, when he is denied Lady Weeds threatens him until they are allowed.

In the swamp Alec takes notice that the Wolf and Lady are missing. He wakes Capucine and Brother Jonah and sends them to go look for the missing pair while Alec is left alone to deal with the Sureen. He wakes Knot up and asks about the service they can provide. He replies by explaining that they allow themselves to take in the avatar's spirit and within their bodies that avatars can wrap up any worldly issues. The ritual called the "Locum" is prepared and by nightfall they are ready to perform it. A young man named Pistil is to be the host and he is given a liquid, then Alec extends his consciousness into a seed and presses it into Pistil's forehead.

Once the ritual is finished Alec is still dormant inside Pistil and the Sureen suddenly remove their cloaks and Knot takes off his disguise. They place the avatar body in a body bag and prepare to leave. In New Orleans Lady Weeds and the Wolf are in a tattoo parlor where she is getting a full body tattoo. In the swamp Alec wakes with human senses intact, but his heart begins beating quickly as he rises, too quickly and he vomits blood. When he fall back down in the background we see he is alone and Abigail's house is ablaze.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-11-19 06:45:59.  [Issue ID 446953]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-29-the-gift-of-the-sureen-part-1-of-3/4000-446953/</Summary>
  <Tags>The Sureen,Knot,The Wolf,Capucine,Lady Weeds,Brother Jonah,Louisiana,Alec Holland,Sureen</Tags>
  <Teams>The Sureen,Sureen</Teams>
  <Title>The Gift of the Sureen Part 1 of 3</Title>
  <Volume>2011</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/swamp-thing-29-the-gift-of-the-sureen-part-1-of-3/4000-446953/</Web>
  <Writer>Charles Soule,Charles Soule</Writer>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Rated T+ Teen Plus</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>