<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-294537</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T16:54:05 [Issue ID 4000-294537] urn:comicvine:4000-294537
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 02:52:08. [Issue ID 136602]</Notes>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Quality Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>Web of Evil</Series>
  <Summary>Demon Inferno: Raymond Stevens discovers the abode of inner-earth demons Hate, Violence and Betrayal. They brand him with the devil’s sign and send him back home. Stevens is now ruled by his demons and starts killing people in a satanic rage.

Timepiece of Terror: Horror writer Ward Blake searches for a fabled “bronze clock of Tibet”. When chiming the artifact is revealing projections of terrifying events of history. Blake finally finds the clock in Cairo and kills the owner to get his hands on the timepiece. Ward then uses the clock as inspiration for countless bestselling horror novels. But success comes with a price. The clock begins to drive Blake insane.

Prehistoric Beast: Museum curator Edmond Manard unfreezes a prehistoric man from an iceberg and brings him back to life by transfusing him his blood. From now on the ice age man goes on a rampage – and Manard experiences the same pain as the creature.

The Ghoul of Ghost Swamp: “Ghost Swamp” in the Florida everglades is said to host a supernatural ghoulish creature killing all who dare enter. An oil surveying expedition penetrates the swamp and gets wiped out by a swift-acting being in a weird mask. One of the company men donnig a costume is behind the murders, but gets strangled by the real swamp ghoul.

</Summary>
  <Title>Demon Inferno; Timepiece of Terror; Prehistoric Beast; The Ghoul of Ghost Swamp</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/web-of-evil-13-the-ghoul-of-ghost-swamp/4000-294537/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Penciller>Charles Nicholas,Louis Ravielli,Charles Nicholas,Louis Ravielli</Penciller>
  <Editor>Alfred Grenet</Editor>
</ComicInfo>