<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-389912</GTIN>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:42:39 [Issue ID 4000-389912] urn:comicvine:4000-389912
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:49:05. [Issue ID 10822]</Notes>
  <Number>19</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Crime SuspenStories</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-19/4000-389912/ https://comicvine.gamespot.com/crime-suspenstories-19/4000-731/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>27</Count>
  <Writer>Al Feldstein,Johnny Craig,Harvey Kurtzman,Bill Gaines,Harvey Kurtzman,Bill Gaines,Al Feldstein,Johnny Craig</Writer>
  <Penciller>Al Feldstein,George Evans,Johnny Craig,Marie Severin,Reed Crandall,Reed Crandall,George Evans,Johnny Craig</Penciller>
  <Inker>Al Feldstein,George Evans,Johnny Craig,Marie Severin,Reed Crandall,Reed Crandall,George Evans,Johnny Craig</Inker>
  <Colorist>Marie Severin,Marie Severin</Colorist>
  <CoverArtist>Al Feldstein</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein</Editor>
  <Title>The Killer; Wined-Up!; Murder May Boomerang; About Phase</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense,Crime</Genre>
  <Summary>Jonathan worked hard at his work, never wanting to follow in the footsteps of his father. Then he met Elsie, whom he intended to marry after he had established himself. However, because Jonathan's father was not a member of a guild, Jonathan was denied his opportunity to make a living, and reluctantly accepted doing his father's line of work. On the side, Jonathan practiced his own trade, which kept him away from home for days at a time. One day, he returned home to find that his wife had been fooling around with another man and had killed him. Now, Jonathan must ply his own trade: on Elsie!

Charles, in a wheelchair since an auto accident, learns that the accident was no accident at all, and that his wife Laura wanted to kill him because she was sick and tired of living with him. She now informs him that is going to try again by wheeling him out on a pier, attaching a wire to it so that she can pull the chair into the lake as she goes swimming. But she is in for a great surprise!

Wilbur always enjoyed recounting the gory murder details found in his column in The London News to his wife, who promptly told him to shut up in a very loud voice. But he touted to her that all the murders occurred under a full moon and that a werewolf had to be responsible. He planned to kill his wife, as he had done to three other women, then claim he was lycanthropic, a victim of the full moon. Unfortunately for him, January 29, 1953, had a full eclipse of the moon at the time of the murder, so poor Wilbur was sentenced to death for pre-meditated murder.</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Elsie (Jonathan's wife),Jonathan's father (in flashback),Jonathan (a hangman)</Characters>
  <Letterer>Jim Wroten,Jim Wroten</Letterer>
</ComicInfo>