<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Yeah, Yeah! The Clang Twang</Title>
  <Series>Tales of the Beanworld</Series>
  <Number>6</Number>
  <Count>21</Count>
  <Volume>1985</Volume>
  <Summary>Mr. Spook is attempting to open a pod, but it resists all attempts.  The Boom'r Band attempts to explain the problem, but their odd lingo only confuses him further.  Even though the tools he tried to use were damaged, Mr. Spook is undeterred.  On the way to figure out a way to open the mystery pod Mr. Spook runs into Beanish who is busy creating his latest Look-See Show titled Proffy.  Beanish locates a powerful being that won't tell Beanish its name, floating in the sky.  Beanish is ordered not to tell anyone about how to find this individual.  Because Beanish promises to keep its existence secret they can be friends. 

The mystery pods create two distinct sounds so an attempt is made to use the Boom'r Bands methods and powers to determine what is inside.  They create music with it, but because it's from a mystery pod Mr. Spook orders the Boom'r Band to stop playing.  They continue playing despite Mr. Spook's concerns.  Their new sound is named The Clang Twang!

Beanish' audience is missing because they're discovering The Clang Twang.  The action moves to the center of Beanlife -- great Gan'Ma'Pa.  The beans dance themselves into a long sleep.  To wake them up a bean falls from the Gan'Ma'Pa (which is a large tree) and the new bean tells Mr. Spook to make him angry so he can wake up the beans.  They need to be up to collect some Chow from dazed Hoi-Polloi.  This does not happen because the beans are still out cold.  Mr. Spook and the rest of the beans learn their lesson and vow to never play the Clang Twang again.

The dancing also caused Beanish to sleep through his appointment.  He makes it late, and falls in love with his floating unnamed being.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-15 11:25:04.  [CVDB449958]</Notes>
  <Year>1987</Year>
  <Writer>Larry Marder</Writer>
  <Penciller>Larry Marder</Penciller>
  <Inker>Larry Marder</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Larry Marder</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/tales-of-the-beanworld-6-yeah-yeah-the-clang-twang/4000-449958/</Web>
  <PageCount>36</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Beanish, Mr. Spook</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="871506" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="319986" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="251450" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="191666" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="211356" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="398714" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="466846" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="478568" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="552664" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="401836" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="441662" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="460238" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="499550" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="452944" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="427346" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="489002" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="410372" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="391020" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="335914" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="321268" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="416542" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="318358" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="287810" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="204364" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="231210" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="436134" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="327008" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="336988" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="400904" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="267602" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="370448" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="421162" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="306288" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="245596" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="586502" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="423610" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>