<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>True Grunge; A Poem; A Poem; It's The Story of Fluffy, The Cat Who Was A Rock Star!; "Isn't It Wonderful To Be Loved!"; What's Been Going On; Hey, Amy!  What Do You Want To Be When You ... Grow Up???; Reservoir; Action Girl Gears Up For Winter; "Ding Dong"; Damn Crow; "Bilingue"; All Girls Together; River Baby Dream Child; Action Girl: Cakes &amp; Dresses; Soundtrack</Title>
  <Series>Action Girl Comics</Series>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Count>19</Count>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-11 13:41:07.  [CVDB142007]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 11:59:35. [Issue ID 304890]</Notes>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>18</Day>
  <CoverArtist>Sarah Dyer</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Sarah Dyer</Editor>
  <Publisher>Slave Labor</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/action-girl-comics-1/4000-142007/</Web>
  <PageCount>27</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <Characters>Action Girl</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="375462" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="475644" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="614926" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="263438" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="801662" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="825632" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="276456" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="230866" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="357220" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="475064" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="438058" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="436610" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="465244" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="437714" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="621448" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="481674" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="337166" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="370418" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="181894" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="459362" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="484466" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="270674" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="579172" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="484336" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="460968" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="589276" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="267230" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>A man and a woman are sitting on a couch reading newspapers.  The woman scratches her head and comments that her head itches.  The man asks when she last showered, the woman says 7-10 days ago.  Both resume reading their newspapers for several more panels without speaking.  In the last panel the woman reaches up and scratches her head again.

A 4-panel illustrated poem about a girl getting her first bra.

A 4-panel illustrated poem about a girl getting her first bra.

An overview of the rise and fall of Fluffy.  The cat is discovered, becomes an overnight success rock star, then succumbs to a hedonistic lifestyle and loses everything.  Fluffy then realeases a comeback album that bombs, and finally finds a career doing TV commercials for cat food.

A woman is drawing, her cat tries to interrupt to get attention.  Eventually the cat curls up on top of the paper, preventing the woman from doing anything except rubbing the cat.

Spot illos of various activities engaged in over the last few days - New Year's Eve party, drinking Coke Classic, palying with a cat, shopping.

Single panel answers to the title question at ages 3 (apple tree), 6 (first lady astronaut), 9 (a leper), 12 (Mark Tawin), 15 (happy), 18 (left alone), and Now (not going to happen).

A girl sneaks over a fence at night to go swimming in a reservoir.  While swimming a possum steals her clothes and shoes.  After she gets out she gets stuck climbing back over the fence, some geese fly down and help her get off the fence, then fly away.

A young single woman visits a girl friend who has recently had a baby and sees how drastically her friend's life has changed.

Unseen narrator talks about a crow that keeps hanging around, only to later be revealed that the narrator is dead and the crow is pulling scraps of flesh from the narrator's skull.

Girl wearing a Bi-Pride T-shirt is asked by various people what it means, she tells one it means bilingual and tells another it means bicycle.

Young man floats down a river in a canoe, while singing songs and dreaming.

Action Girl paper doll, with three outfits (New Wave Action Girl; Little Action Girl; 1990s Action Girl) and accessories (sheet cake; devil's food cake; key lime pie).  Also a 5-panel comic strip titled Kimi &amp; Kitty.</Summary>
</ComicInfo>