<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Cecil Stedman,Monster Girl,Shapesmith,Atom Eve,Robot,Invincible,Black Samson,Universa,Rus Livingston,Bulletproof,Deborah Grayson,Brit</Characters>
  <Colorist>FCO Plascencia,FCO Plascencia</Colorist>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>23</Day>
  <Editor>Aubrey Sitterson</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-189593</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Cliff Rathburn,Cliff Rathburn</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Rus Wooton,Rus Wooton</Letterer>
  <Locations>Earth,Texas,Space,Houston</Locations>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:14:16 [Issue ID 4000-189593] urn:comicvine:4000-189593 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/691794
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 04:15:26. [Issue ID 691794]</Notes>
  <Number>69</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Ryan Ottley,Ryan Ottley</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Invincible</Series>
  <Teams>Guardians of the Globe,Sequids</Teams>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/invincible-69/4000-189593/</Web>
  <Writer>Robert Kirkman,Robert Kirkman</Writer>
  <Year>2009</Year>
  <Summary>EVERYTHING IS DIFFERENT NOW! Who is Universa?! Why did she come to this planet in search of the one called Invincible? What does it have to do with the impending Viltrumite Invasion?! And why did she decide to come NOW, on the eve of an attack from the SEQUIDS?! The answers to all these questions and even more questions piled on top of them – in this issue of Invincible.   SPOILERS The story begins with a new character Universa making her way to Earth. Kirkman describes her as a warrior queen who has traveled countless miles to the planet earth, and will not stop until she gets what she has come for as her planet is in grave danger. Next, we see Rus Livingston fully possessed by Sequids reeking havoc. The Sequid invasion has begun. Mark &amp; Eve are discussing what happened last issue (It’s a major spoiler, I won’t spoil it for people just beginning the series) just then Eve receives a call that they are needed. When Mark, and Eve arrive on the scene Universa is attacking a Nucear power plant. She has a special kind of staff that wields the power of two light spectrums and turns them into one blast thus creating an unstoppable power. Invincible commences the battle with her, and later is partly defeated evidently leaving Eve to help fight Universa while he recovers. Unfortunately Eve is still having trouble with her powers. The Guardians of the Globe led by Brit go to stop the Sequid threat. They create a type of barrier, and appear to have everything handled. Off panel we return to Invincible’s battle with Universa. Mark steals her staff, only to be electrocuted by its fail safe Invincible appears to be defeated until Eve now powerless (per-say) leaves her unconscious with a left hook. Seconds later Cecil arrives and asks for Mark’s help against the Sequid Invasion. Mark assumes that they have the situation handled. The issue ends with a splash page in which Rus Livingston has defeated the Guardian of the Globe.</Summary>
  <CoverArtist>FCO Plascencia,Ryan Ottley</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>