<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Tom Malverne [Jack the Ripper],vampires</Characters>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-90493</GTIN>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T13:54:02 [Issue ID 4000-90493] urn:comicvine:4000-90493
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:15:05. [Issue ID 202488]</Notes>
  <Number>29</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Atlas.1954)  (Pmack)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Adventures into Terror</Series>
  <Tags>Jack the Ripper</Tags>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-terror-29/4000-90493/</Web>
  <Year>1954</Year>
  <Count>31</Count>
  <Title>The Vampire Man; From Out of the…Grave; The Man Who Walked the Plank; The Faceless Ones; The Horrible House</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>The Vampire Man: This story postulates the Jack the Ripper killings were done by a hateful hunchback who wanted to become a vampire so he could kill mortals, but was repulsed by the sight of blood, so vampires killed him when he could not fulfill their condition that he partake of human blood before new year's eve.

From Out of the…Grave: In old England, a hunch backed grave robber named Grimm makes his living digging up corpses and selling them to doctors to experiment on illegally. When the doctors are finished they have Grimm dispose of the bodies. In stead of putting them back in their graves Grimm simply tosses them in the river. One night however, the offended dead rise from their watery graves to get revenge against him, frightening him to death. When a new grave robber beings working for their doctors, his first dig is ironically Grimm himself.

The Man Who Walked the Plank: After a pirate captain's ship is sunk, he finds himself surrounded by sharks, floating on the plank he has forced many to walk off of. His undead victims from Davey Jone's locker jostle the plank, forcing him to walk it, until he tires and falls prey to the sharks.

The Faceless Ones: The first space flight from Earth finds the astronauts landing in Hell.

The Horrible House: A wealthy man dreams of an atom bomb wrecking his house and burying him alive, so he goes into the country where he thinks he is safe and has a house built. The construction men warn him that the ground is soft, but he disregards their warning, and the entire house sinks beneath the earth with him inside.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Larry Woromay,Gene Colan,Werner Roth,Myron Fass,Al Eadeh,Larry Woromay,Gene Colan,Werner Roth,Myron Fass,Al Eadeh</Penciller>
  <Inker>Larry Woromay,Gene Colan,Werner Roth,Myron Fass,Al Eadeh,Larry Woromay,Gene Colan,Werner Roth,Myron Fass,Al Eadeh</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>