<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Invincible,Omni-Man</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bill Crabtree</Colorist>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-125148</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Cory Walker,Ryan Ottley,Cory Walker,Ryan Ottley</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Robert Kirkman,Rus Wooton</Letterer>
  <Locations>Space,Earth</Locations>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:14:33 [Issue ID 4000-125148] urn:comicvine:4000-125148 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/276830
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 07:15:49. [Issue ID 125148]</Notes>
  <Number>12</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Cory Walker,Ryan Ottley,Cory Walker,Ryan Ottley</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Invincible</Series>
  <Volume>2003</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/invincible-12-perfect-strangers-part-4/4000-125148/</Web>
  <Writer>Robert Kirkman</Writer>
  <Year>2004</Year>
  <Title>Perfect Strangers, Part 4</Title>
  <Summary>Mark Grayson is just like most everyone else his age, except that his father is the most powerful superhero on the planet. And now he's begun to inherit his father's powers. It all sounds okay at first, but how do you follow in your father's footsteps when you know you will never live up to his standards? "Perfect Strangers," Conclusion, Mark's world comes crashing down around him. After the events of last issue, Mark is left wondering how he'll survive. You have front row seats as Mark comes face to face with the most deadly foe of his short- lived superhero career. It's all been leading up to this, and you do not want to miss this issue!

Omni-Man attempts to convince his son to join him in conquering the Earth as the two do battle. He asserts that humans are too short-lived and fragile to really be treated as equals, and seeks to demonstrate this by remorselessly killing thousands indirectly as he fights with Mark.

Invincible refuses to accept his father's point of view, and continues to fight on despite being completely outclassed. Frustrated and enraged by his son's defiance, Omni-Man beats him near to the point of death, and asks what he thinks he would still have on Earth in five-hundred years time if he remained there. Invincible reponds that he would still have his father, and Omni-Man leaves the planet with tears in his eyes.</Summary>
  <StoryArc>Perfect Strangers</StoryArc>
  <CoverArtist>Bill Crabtree,Cory Walker</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>