<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Day>10</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-334</GTIN>
  <Inker>Lee Elias</Inker>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:26:37 [Issue ID 4000-334] urn:comicvine:4000-334
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 18:08:51. [Issue ID 10373]</Notes>
  <Number>8</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Lee Elias</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Harvey</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>2 stories</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Tomb of Terror</Series>
  <Title>Hive!; The Search; The Eyes of March!; Vision in Bronze</Title>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/tomb-of-terror-8/4000-334/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>16</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>Hive!: When landowner Carol Leighton starts paying too much attention to one of her farm hands, the other workers decide he has gotten too big for his britches and take action.

The Search: Ricky Slate, in prison for a double murder, has an emergency brain surgery.  While under anesthesia he meets several strange figures who try to prevent him from finding his soul.

The Eyes of March!: When Laura Duncan leaves her creepy husband Nicholas March for the young Johnny Franklin, March gets revenge by using the hypnotic stare of his large uncanny eyes to force Laura to commit suicide. The angered Johnny kills March, but his eerie eyes haunt Johnny from the grave and forces him to commit suicide as well.

Vision in Bronze: Two antique collectors buy a castle.  Inside they find a suit of armor, and one collector traps the other in the armor and leaves him to die.  Soon the remaining collector is haunted by the armor.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Carol Leighton,Joe,Rufe,Charlie Patch</Characters>
</ComicInfo>