<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <AgeRating>Rated M / Mature</AgeRating>
  <Count>11</Count>
  <Country>US</Country>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-1256171</GTIN>
  <Genre>Crime,Historical,Drama</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T18:37:53 [Issue ID 4000-1256171] urn:comicvine:4000-1256171 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/1256171
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 10:50:56. [Issue ID 1256171]</Notes>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>C.O.W.L.</Series>
  <Title>Principles of Power - Chapter 5: Sacrifice</Title>
  <Volume>2014</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c-o-w-l-5-principles-of-power-chapter-5-sacrifice/4000-466285/</Web>
  <Year>2014</Year>
  <Summary>The end of the first arc and a huge turning point for the series! John Pierce and Geoffrey Warner square off over C.O.W.L.'s big secret, Radia faces public outcry, and Arclight resorts to lethal force...against one of his own.

Some members of C.O.W.L. are arrested in the aftermath of the fire blast against a city building during the union's strike. It looks like this will create huge problems for Geoffrey Warner as he tries to negotiate a new contract with the city.  Their other union allies walk away from them.

John Pierce and Arclight talk about John's evidence that the evil Chicago Six had access to C.O.W.L.'s technology designs due to a mole.  They think Warner will block them from making it public so John wants to go to the regular police.  Arclight isn't so sure, and is having a hard time imagining leaving the celebrity of his current lifestyle. But, he also feels like the union is throwing him under a bus over his scandal over beating up a pimp, so he agrees to go along.

However, when he goes to clean out his locker, he finds Warner, who talks him out of it, telling him how the city needs heroes.  John, meanwhile, finds even more incriminating evidence in Warner's office.

John sets up a time to meet with an unknown police contact, so he can drop off the materials.  On the way, he sees some thieves running into an alley, and stops them. However, Arclight shows up, and kills Pierce.

Warner meets with Camden Stone, the crime boss, and makes a deal with the devil: in order to get a new union contract, he needs the city to believe that C.O.W.L. still has a reason to exist, so he asks Stone to put together a team of costumed criminals to attack the city.

Features a bio on John Pierce.</Summary>
  <Characters>Geoffrey Warner,John Pierce,Camden Stone,Arclight</Characters>
  <Teams>C.O.W.L.</Teams>
  <Locations>Indiana,Chicago</Locations>
  <Writer>Alec Siegel,Kyle Higgins</Writer>
  <Penciller>Rod Reis</Penciller>
  <Inker>Rod Reis</Inker>
  <Letterer>Troy Peteri</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Trevor McCarthy</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Andy Schmidt</Editor>
</ComicInfo>