<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Crimple,Vuall,Gwendolyn,Nikki,Molly O'Reilly,Tim Hunter,Sir Timothy Hunter,Araquel,Barbatos,Tanger,Khara</Characters>
  <Colorist>Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh,Sherilyn Van Valkenburgh</Colorist>
  <Editor>Julie Rottenberg</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-41728</GTIN>
  <Inker>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Inker>
  <Letterer>Comicraft,Richard Starkings,Richard Starkings,Comicraft</Letterer>
  <Locations>Hell,London</Locations>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T20:52:01 [Issue ID 4000-41728] urn:comicvine:4000-41728
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 21:18:15. [Issue ID 58051]</Notes>
  <Number>19</Number>
  <PageCount>26</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="1548" ImageSize="421235" ImageWidth="1000" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="1551" ImageSize="622152" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="1548" ImageSize="548696" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="1548" ImageSize="587838" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="491386" ImageWidth="982" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="437977" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="533722" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="500539" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="1544" ImageSize="536066" ImageWidth="991" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="1544" ImageSize="566105" ImageWidth="980" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="1540" ImageSize="548800" ImageWidth="980" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="1545" ImageSize="564682" ImageWidth="979" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="580895" ImageWidth="985" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="1544" ImageSize="662980" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="1540" ImageSize="550320" ImageWidth="983" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="1542" ImageSize="563336" ImageWidth="982" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="1543" ImageSize="621641" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="1538" ImageSize="507767" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="1545" ImageSize="443913" ImageWidth="988" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="1541" ImageSize="609465" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="1548" ImageSize="575880" ImageWidth="994" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="1538" ImageSize="472872" ImageWidth="967" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="1544" ImageSize="490819" ImageWidth="987" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageHeight="1539" ImageSize="548648" ImageWidth="997" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageHeight="1541" ImageSize="573096" ImageWidth="989" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="474536" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Peter Gross,Peter Gross</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Books of Magic</Series>
  <Summary>Part 5 of the 5-part 'Playgrounds.' Tim, Molly and Crimple work their way through Hell to find Tanger and Happy the Golem, who have become the subjects of Barbatos's plot to take over the world. Plus, Hell will never be the same when Tim and his twisted future self, Mr. Wrong, come face-to-face for the first time. 

Sir Timothy, now transformed into a dragon, plays Go Fish with some other dragons.  He finally seems at peace.  Nikki and Khara show up, asking for his help in defeating Barbatos and helping Araquel.

Araquel, meanwhile, shows up at young Tim's house and talks with Gwendolyn, who is helping keep house. He wants to warn Tim about Barbatos, but Gwendolyn tells him he's already missing, and the police are looking for him.  She tells him to save Tim himself.

Tim and Molly, meanwhile, are still kissing and cheering up hell. Tim wants to take Molly home, but they have to get Tanger and Happy first.  Crimple has been sprouting wings from being near Tim and Molly's love.  They threaten Vuall, but she won't help, so Tim and Molly kiss some more.

Barbatos has brought Tanger and Happy on stage at his Happy Crisps demonstration, but neither of them eat, so he can't show the assembled demons how they work.  Tanger makes a speech to convince the demons that humans won't be taken in by the snacks.  One of the pink T. rexes breaks in to warn the demons that love is spreading through hell, and Tanger says that Openers, like Tim, can create very powerful effects when they fall in love.

Tim and Molly's love has brought the withered Vuall back into the state of a beautiful, if unconscious, maiden.

Barbatos's demonstration, now nearly empty after the demons flee, is further interrupted by a flamingly-mad Araquel.  He slashes off Barbatos's magic sand-clock.  He hasn't been able to find Khara and Nikki (who are in the future), so he assumes Barbatos killed them.  Tanger persuades Araquel not to kill Barbatos, since that would turn Araquel into a demon.

Sir Timothy, as dragon, shows up and tells Araquel that Nikki and Khara are safe, and he rushes off to join them.  Barbatos recognizes him, and tries to convince him to free him, but Sir Timothy is now self-aware to realize that he was Barbatos's slave, not his master.

Tim, Molly, and Crimple show up.  Tanger and Crimple have a happy reunion.  Sir Timothy is filled with wonder at seeing the original Molly, who he has tried to copy for so long.  However, Barbatos stops them from reuniting in peace, and sucks himself, Tim, Molly, and Sir Timothy into one of the magical storybooks.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-07-22 16:19:12.  [CVDB41728]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-19-playgrounds-part-v-really-pr/4000-41728/</Summary>
  <Teams>Retarded Lizards</Teams>
  <Title>Playgrounds, Part Five: Really-Pretend</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-books-of-magic-19-playgrounds-part-v-really-pr/4000-41728/</Web>
  <Writer>John Ney Rieber,John Ney Rieber</Writer>
  <Year>1995</Year>
  <Count>75</Count>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Suggested For Mature Readers</AgeRating>
</ComicInfo>