<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Shreddercon!</Title>
  <Series>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Saturday Morning Adventures</Series>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <Volume>2023</Volume>
  <Summary>SynopsisSeason's greetings from Saturday Morning Adventures! There's nothing more magical than winter in New York. Only this year, City Hall's banned St. Nick look-alikes outright. To the surprise of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles and the rest of New York, the usual crew of Kris Kringles have been replaced by an army of... Shredder cosplayers! To fill the Santa-shaped hole in New Yorkers' hearts, Shredder is hosting a convention celebrating... himself?! Is this really an altruistic act to lift spirits, or is something more nefarious afoot? Move over, Santa. ShredderCon is coming to town!

PlotIn a penthouse of New York City, Mr. Oroku, better known as the Shredder, meets with Kai Eddiku, a artist and descendant of Eddiku Yuri, the great feudal Japan artisan who created a sword that could cut through time and space. Kai agrees to make a replica of the sword for Oroku for a fee, but he will need the Hand Guard from one of Eddiku Yuri's creations. One such Hand Guard is on display at the Mid-Manhattan Muesum of Asian Art, for one week only.

Later at Shedder and Krang's Evil Lair, Shredder relays his plan to use the St. Nick-Con as cover to break into the museum, but he is informed that the event is canceled. Instead, Shredder has another idea and needs Krangs Duplication Ray.

A few days later, Shredder announces, Shredder Con and hand out free Shredder costumes to the citizens of New York City, then as predicted the Shredders start getting drunk and disorderly. This causes a distraction for the police and the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, who need to deal with the crowd instead of finding the real Shedder. 

Meanwhile at the Mid-Manhattan Museum of Asian Art, Bebop and Rocksteady, dressed as Shredder have broken into the museum and tied up the guards. Then when the real Shredder joins them the trio replace a real Yuri hand guard with a fake and get away.

Outside all the Shredder customes disappear leaving the crowd naked and cold. This turn of events confuses the Turtles who have no idea what Shredder was up to.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-26 16:48:33.  [CVDB1032490]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-saturday-morning-adve/4000-1032490/</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-26 16:48:33.  [CVDB1032490]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-18 11:30:34. [Issue ID 2586258]</Notes>
  <Year>2023</Year>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Day>29</Day>
  <Writer>Erik Burnham</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jack Lawrence,Sarah Myer</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jack Lawrence,Sarah Myer</Inker>
  <Colorist>Luis Antonio Delgado,Raúl Angulo</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Ed Dukeshire</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Jack Lawrence,Raúl Angulo</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Thea Cheuk,Nicolas Niño</Editor>
  <Publisher>IDW</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-saturday-morning-adve/4000-1032490/</Web>
  <PageCount>30</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Miniseries</Format>
  <Characters>Kai Eddiku,Michelangelo,Rocksteady,Bebop,Shredder,Krang,Leonardo,Donatello,Raphael,April O'Neil</Characters>
  <Teams>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</Teams>
  <Locations>New York City</Locations>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (Li'l-Empire) (HD-Upscaled)</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="3139473" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="2492645" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1722703" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1818140" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1531375" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="2445574" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="3499603" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="2391272" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="2578635" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="2536760" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="2983850" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="2332060" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="2268755" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="2368830" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="2456305" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="2409086" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="2504779" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="2774020" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="2824638" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="2590468" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="2247970" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="2439499" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="2555281" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="2265024" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="2493456" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="2048275" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="2407468" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="2096734" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="2636643" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="3879084" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>