<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Batroc,Benjamin Franklin,Chance,Daniel Gump,Deadpool,Doctor Octopus,Emily Preston,Lady Stilt-Man,Michael Hawthorne,Taskmaster,Trapster,Vetis</Characters>
	<Colorist>Val Staples</Colorist>
	<Count>45</Count>
	<Day>31</Day>
	<Editor>Jordan D. White</Editor>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-404695</GTIN>
	<Inker>Mike Hawthorne</Inker>
	<Letterer>Joe Sabino</Letterer>
	<Locations>Hell,Manhattan,New Jersey,New York City</Locations>
	<Month>7</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:05:09 [Issue ID 4000-404695] urn:comicvine:4000-404695</Notes>
	<Number>10</Number>
	<PageCount>24</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2155646" Type="FrontCover" />
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="1387111" />
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="1834384" />
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="1727223" />
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1643489" />
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1654264" />
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1682683" />
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1877809" />
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="2155476" />
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1681988" />
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1758636" />
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1769066" />
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="2111130" />
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1777932" />
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1708244" />
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1600422" />
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1829734" />
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="2011261" />
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1580548" />
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1859137" />
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1309746" />
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="1763561" />
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1559575" />
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="805240" />
	</Pages>
	<Penciller>Mike Hawthorne</Penciller>
	<Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
	<Series>Deadpool</Series>
	<Summary>Deadpool targets a MAN with AQUATIC powers!

Then he teams-up with your SUPERIOR Neighborhood SPIDER-MAN!

I PROMISE HE KILLS ONE OF THOSE TWO!

SynopsisDeadpool and Benjamin Franklin travel down a road in a stolen ice cream truck. Benjamin is appalled and furious that Deadpool just killed their friend Michael the Necromancer. Deadpool explains that he was thinking outside the box and Benjamin leaves and floats into a strip club.

In Hell, Michael awaits his turn in a very long line. Too impatient, Michael calls to a demon in charge and asks to see Mephisto. The demon refuses but Michael insists that he has a secret Mephisto will certainly want to know. Michael gets eaten by the demon.

Back in Manhattan, Deadpool scales a building to get to his next target, a clairvoyant named Daniel Gump. Agent Preston tries to get Deadpool to rethink his actions but he explains that he knows what he is doing. He calmly walks into Gump's floor but gets immediately ejected. He is saved by Spider-Man (Doctor Octopus) and the two ascend the building. They meet Gump's troupe of protection and begin fighting.

Gump himself arrives with explosives strapped to his chest and a horde of mercenaries. Spider-Man webs Gump's hand and the two combat the mercs: Batroc, Chance, Lady Stilt Man, and Paste Pot Pete (er, the Trapster). Deadpool gets the upperhand by flooding the rooftop with the Trapster's paste, sticking most of the combatants to the roof (including Spider-Man). Deadpool steals Spider-Man's webshooters and pursues Lady Stilt Man, who has made off with Gump.

Gump sees Deadpool coming and gets a premonition as to what is about to happen. Before he can tell Deadpool's plan to Lady Stilt Man, however, Deadpool uses a webshooter to seal Gump's mouth. Deadpool then dispatches Lady Stilt Man by using explosives on her legs. He then kills Gump. Spider-Man shows up and knocks Deadpool out for being a murderer. Spider-Man hangs Deadpool up with the other mercs to await the arrival of the police. Deadpool finds a blowtorch, however, and is soon free.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-10 10:20:48.  [CVDB404695]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-10-eight-legs-to-kick-you/4000-404695/</Summary>
	<Tags>Batroc,Benjamin Franklin,Chance,Daniel Gump,Deadpool,Doctor Octopus,Emily Preston,Hell,Lady Stilt-Man,Manhattan,Michael Hawthorne,New Jersey,New York City,Taskmaster,Trapster,Vetis</Tags>
	<Title>Eight Legs to Kick You</Title>
	<Volume>2012</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deadpool-10-eight-legs-to-kick-you/4000-404695/</Web>
	<Writer>Brian Posehn,Gerry Duggan</Writer>
	<Year>2013</Year>
</ComicInfo>