<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Prince Valiant</Series>
  <Number>5</Number>
  <Count>24</Count>
  <Title>Vol. 5: 1945-1946</Title>
  <Volume>2009</Volume>
  <Summary>Fully half of this latest volume of Hal Foster’s epic masterpiece — again scanned from superb syndicate proofs — is devoted to the remaining chapters of “The Winning of Aleta,” a 20-month (!) epic in which Valiant obsessively pursues his bride to be. Not surprisingly this is followed by a sequence called “Matrimony,” which ends with a newly wed queen adjusting to the luxurious, exciting court life at Camelot.

But Val’s marriage does not signal an end to his adventures, quite the contrary. In “War in the Forest” Val is sent out to spy on encroaching Saxons — unknowingly aided by Aleta, who, disguised as a small knight (and dubbed “Sir Puny”) helps prevent disaster. But the 1946 strips end with Val and Aleta unable to return to Camelot and the displaced couple journeying to Thule…

Half the strips in this volume also include the delightful “The Medieval Castle,” Foster’s chronicle of two young boys growing up during the time of the First Crusade — but by the end of the 1945 strips this series has ended and the Valiant portion resume its full-page glory.

This volume also features a Foreword by P. Craig Russell, a gallery of Hal Foster's commercial illustration work and an essay titled "Aleta: Water Nymph of the Misty Isles" by Brian M. Kane.

With stunning art reproduced directly from pristine printer’s proofs, Fantagraphics has introduced a new generation to Foster’s masterpiece, while providing long-time fans with the ultimate, definitive version of the strip.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev110 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-06-01 09:59:02. [Issue ID 382870]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Day>13</Day>
  <Month>6</Month>
  <Year>2012</Year>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/prince-valiant-5-vol-5-1945-1946/4000-382870/</Web>
  <Characters>Sir Lancelot,King Arthur,Queen Guinevere,Prince Valiant,Aleta</Characters>
  <Locations>Thule,Camelot</Locations>
  <Writer>Hal Foster</Writer>
  <Penciller>Hal Foster,Hal Foster</Penciller>
  <Inker>Hal Foster,Hal Foster</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>Hal Foster</CoverArtist>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>