<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Forbidden Worlds</Series>
  <Number>72</Number>
  <Count>145</Count>
  <Title>Dr. Martin's Marvelous Museum; Call in the Night; The Strange Ones!; The Ironclad Will!</Title>
  <Volume>1951</Volume>
  <Genre>Fantasy</Genre>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 19:07:28. [Issue ID 14693]</Notes>
  <Publisher>American Comics Group</Publisher>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Year>1958</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Approved by the Comics Code Authority</AgeRating>
  <ScanInformation>(november 1958)</ScanInformation>
  <Penciller>Ogden Whitney,John Forte,Emil Gershwin,John Forte,Emil Gershwin</Penciller>
  <Inker>Ogden Whitney,John Forte,Emil Gershwin,John Forte,Emil Gershwin</Inker>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Tags>Dr. Martin,Brenda Trent,Jed Hoffstra,Eddy Brewster</Tags>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/forbidden-worlds-72/4000-4059/</Web>
  <Summary>Dr. Martin's Marvelous Museum: Eddy and Brenda have grown up as neighbours and friends. But Brenda wants someone courageous as a boyfriend and all-state quarterback Jeff takes her out as well. Brenda confuses her dates and all three go out together to the private closed house of Dr Martin. The Dr shows them his museum exhibits and, after Jed and Brenda have left, challenges Eddy to track down the Georgio tiara. Eddy visits the eras of the exhibits and finds the tiara defeating obstacles on the way. Eddy meets Jed and Brenda, Jed challenges Eddy but he now has courage and defeats Jed. Brenda is happy with her real man.

Call in the Night: Chief Crane receives a phone call advising of a fire at 346 Elm. When the fire equipment arrives they find that someone is inside, old man Parkins. The firemen save Mr Parkins. Later, when they are making out the fire report, Crane asks Parkins if he knows anyone called Danny, as he made the call. Parkins tells Crane that Danny is his son and that he always looks after him. Crane wonders why Danny is not present and Crane says that his son died in 1942. Further attempts to trace the phone caller are unsuccessful.

The Strange Ones!: Glenn Parker is driving home when two strange lights cause him to crash his car. The two lights are concerned that Glenn does not die. When Glenn wakes up he drives home. Over the following weeks Glenn is obsessed with building a strange machine. Olga is concerned about Glenn and calls the doctor who hypnotises Glenn. Glenn reveals that the machine is to give physical form to the lights who want to invade Earth. The doctor and Olga rush to the machine just as two aliens emerge. There is a brief fight and the aliens accidentally destroy the machine and disappear. The invasion is over.

The Ironclad Will!: Jude Tyndal's heirs get exactly what they deserved, even if it is impossible to explain how he accomplished it.

</Summary>
  <Characters>Dr. Martin,Brenda Trent,Jed Hoffstra,Eddy Brewster</Characters>
  <Editor>Richard E. Hughes</Editor>
</ComicInfo>