<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Ghost in the Machine Part 3; The Adventures of Zot! in Dimension 10 &#189;: The Stupidity Plague</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>25</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>Harry, the new dictator of Antares, hires 9-Jack-9 to kill Zot.

Jenny shows up at Max's. It's dark, so Jack can't appear using any electric objects. Max tells her Zot has gone after Jack. Zot joined the rebellion on Antares in order to force the enemy to hire Jack to kill him, thinking there was no other way to defeat Zot.

Zot is very effective, destroying a lot of the enemy military's weapons without killing anyone. However, Lucy Chow and others in the resistance have no such compunctions and readily kill the soldiers.

Zot finds Jack waiting for him in the dictator's headquarters. Zot uses a portal to teleport back to Earth and Jack follows him. Zot uses special goggles to see the energy trail that Jack uses to send his energy-self around the universe. Now he can follow it to its source.

He follows him to a house in England. Max explains that he knows who 9-Jack-9 is--he inhabits the body of a dead man, Sir John Sheers. In fact, Sheers plays fiddle in Max's band. Max says he's "actually a fairly nice fellow...all things considered." Jenny is shocked that Max never tried to stop him, but Max says that only Zot could do it, and only now that he's ready.

Zot makes it to Jack's house where he is attacked by electric coils. Jack speaks through his hologram but his host body of Sheers is there as well. He taunts Zot about his parents. Zot tosses a cable onto Sheers so Jack has to turn them off to avoid being electrocuted. Jack starts blasting at Zot, who flies around. Jack accidentally blasts Sheers, who dies. Zot is saddened even by Jack's death.

Back on Antares, the rebellion has won. The general, Harry, is in jail. He's afraid Jack will get him since he can't pay anymore. Jack does show up on his TV. It turns out that he can survive without a body now.

In "The Stupidity Plague," Doctor Pweent hires Stupid Boy, who is stupid. Zot and Jenny realize Butch has just become even more stupid than usual and bring him in to get checked out. It turns out that many people are now stupid. Cynicalman helps figure out how to solve the problem. They go to another doctor, Professor Quidley, who realizes it came from Pweent's video games. They go to stop Pweent, but then they find out Quidley now has a cure. He essentially solves it all, including for Stupid Boy, through placebos.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:18:11.  [CVDB30874]</Notes>
  <Year>1989</Year>
  <Month>02</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Matt Feazell, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Letterer>Bob Lappan</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-25-the-ghost-in-the-machine-part-3-the-adventu/4000-30874/</Web>
  <PageCount>29</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Butch Weaver, Cynicalman, Doctor Pweent, Jenny Weaver, Max, Sgt. Chow, Zot</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="247882" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="174895" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="142216" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="222961" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="236987" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="214101" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="203926" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="178119" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="160223" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="175311" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="190867" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="194378" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="209460" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="204256" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="163175" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="119453" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="156157" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="178178" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="184842" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="246241" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="243107" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="156060" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="214424" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="175482" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="178689" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="237081" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="225207" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="218318" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="206390" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
