<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Elaine,Gargoyle [Isaac Christians]</Characters>
  <Colorist>Bill Sienkiewicz,Bob Sharen,Bob Sharen</Colorist>
  <Editor>Carl Potts,Jim Shooter</Editor>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <GTIN>urn:comixology:822158</GTIN>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <Inker>Bill Sienkiewicz,Mark Badger,Mark Badger</Inker>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Letterer>Ken Bruzenak,Ken Bruzenak</Letterer>
  <Locations>Virginia</Locations>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:28:11 [Issue ID 4000-25685] urn:comicvine:4000-25685 urn:comixology:822158
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 14:46:01. [Issue ID 40223]</Notes>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <PageCount>24</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1621165" ImageWidth="1988" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1579274" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1716858" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1966473" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1708518" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1640846" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1785565" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1596407" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1645853" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1973332" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1897528" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2069217" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1868213" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1917765" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1984719" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2217128" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1673033" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1832413" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2093985" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1824161" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1526792" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="1052377" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageHeight="3056" ImageSize="2029668" ImageWidth="1988" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1479730" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Bill Sienkiewicz,Mark Badger,Mark Badger</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Digital) (Shadowcat-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Gargoyle</Series>
  <Summary>Christians finds his human body occupied by the original mind of Gargoyle!

At the Christians family manor, in Christiansboro, Virginia, the Gargoyle comes face-to-face with the impossible. The Gargoyle confronts himself, or rather his human self, Isaac Christians, along with the love of his life, the long dead Elaine Willoughby. The Gargoyle curbs his violent nature, upon seeing how much it frightens Willoughby. Christians taunts the Gargoyle by cavorting with a host of lustful harlots, reminding the Gargoyle of his own wanton past. Christians reveals the nature of the harlots, as well as the unspeakable pleasures he has experienced, since inhabiting the Gargoyle's human form. Christians reveals his own nature. Christians speaks of a more mythological world, before the rise of Christianity.

The old Gods died. The spirits of the Earth and Air became stone. Churches were built on the places that once served as worship for the old Gods. One such church was built over a hot spot for mystic energy, which permeated the entire structure, reawakening the spirits within the church's multitude of gargoyles. These sprits would have remained aware, but unmoving, as lifeless stone, had it not been for the coming of a powerful sorcerer. In retribution for the loss of the old world, the sorcerer returned motion to the gargoyles, and set them upon the land. Their wanton assault upon the innocent, however, instilled feelings of remorse in the sorcerer, who returned the gargoyles to unmoving stone. Some of the gargoyles, had become too powerful, and thus could not be restrained anew

They wandered the world, becoming the stuff of legends. One gargoyle, in particular, became the slave of an insane magician, spending years in servitude, until finally rising up to slay it's master. For centuries after, it lived in the shadows, preying upon the innocent. This gargoyle burned with the desires of the flesh, but, as a creature of stone, could never truly experience those pleasures. It became a creature worshipped by man, bringing it to the attention of the demonic cabal, the Six-Fingered Hand. Enslaved again, this gargoyle rebelled, and was punished for it's transgressions, just as the demons also punished Christians The Gargoyle realizes that the spirit inhabiting his human body, is the same one that was expunged from the Gargoyle body now inhabited by Christians' spirit.

"Christians" reveals the further horrors he has committed in the old man's body. Sharing Christians memories, the spirit of the gargoyle is privy to all of the Gargoyle's secret sins. The Gargoyle reflects on a time, shortly after Word War I, when he, as Christians, lived in Paris. Christians sought to fill the emptiness in his heart in the arms of prostitutes. Christians fell madly in love with one such prostitute, Germaine. Christians became more debauched, desperate to hold onto Germaine's fleeting affections. Ultimately, it was all for naught. Germaine abandoned Christians. The Gargoyle flees the memories of how far he had fallen as a man. The Gargoyle is attacked by the other living gargoyles. The Gargoyle is defeated. Willoughby begs the Gargoyle to protect her.

"Christians" offers to switch spirits with the Gargoyle, returning their spirits to their rightful bodies. Willoughby pleads with the Gargoyle to consent to "Christians" proposal, so that they can be together again. Against his better judgment the Gargoyle consents to the transference of souls. The spirit of the gargoyle returns to the Gargoyle's body, as Christians spirit regains his humanity. Leading the other gargoyles, the Gargoyle takes flight, and vanishes into the night sky. "Willoughby" strikes Christians, berating him for being a fool. Though the body is that of Willoughby, the spirit animating it is Germaine. Germane laughs at Christian's plight. Unbeknownst to them, the sorcerer, the very one who originally gave life to the gargoyles, draws near.</Summary>
  <Teams>Six-Fingered Hand</Teams>
  <Title>Burning Bright: The Gargoyle's Tale</Title>
  <Volume>1985</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/gargoyle-2-burning-bright-the-gargoyles-tale/4000-25685/</Web>
  <Writer>J.M. DeMatteis,J. M. DeMatteis,J. M. DeMatteis</Writer>
  <Year>1985</Year>
  <Count>4</Count>
  <CoverArtist>Bill Sienkiewicz</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>