<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2378</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2378</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>Call me The Mighty Tharg, universally renowned purveyor of Thrills - the future is now!

One of the most popular of modern 2000 AD series returns this prog as the sixth book of Brinkcommences within these pages, courtesy as ever of the Abnett and Culbard droids. While 2022&#8217;s previous arc, Mercury Retrograde, took a deviation and followed journalist Nolan Maslow&#8217;s parallel investigation into sect activity, in Consumed we&#8217;re back with HSD officer Bridget Kurtis, stopping over at Belleholme Habitat and about to become embroiled in a spate of murders&#8230;

With Brink joining the scrotnig likes of Dredd, Aquila, Proteus Vex and Indigo Prime, once again it&#8217;s a line-up thrumming with so much Thrill-power that it threatens the very fabric of your reality. What can be done? Why, pour more on, of course, with the release this week of Meg 467, featuring a complete Dredd story from Mike Carroll and Paul Marshall, more DeMarco, P.I., Devlin Waugh and Harrower Squad, and the return of Brit-Cit Detective Judge Armitage courtesy of Liam Johnson and Warren Pleece.

Add to that chats with Chris Weston, Igor Goldkind and more, it&#8217;s a ghafflebette package you mustn&#8217;t miss, Terrans!

*Judge Death &#187; Rend &amp; Tear with Tooth &amp; Claw (Part 3)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America, with the toxic Black Atlantic to the east and the irradiated Cursed Earth to the west. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law!

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 1)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Aquila &#187; The Rivers of Hades, Book Two: PART 1 (Part 2)*
Following Spartacus&#8217;s failed revolt against his Roman masters, his rebel army was crucified. Amongst these was the slave-turned-gladiator AQUILA, who cried out to the gods for vengeance - and was answered by Ammit the Devourer, a deity that gifted him with immortality in return for keeping her fed with evil men&#8217;s souls. Now, Aquila has travelled into Hades and retrieved the spirit of Nero, who knows Ammit&#8217;s location...

*Indigo Prime &#187; Black Monday (Part 8)*
The multiverse. There is an infinite number of parallel realities, and all need managing in case of dimensional instability. This is where INDIGO PRIME came in, the multiverse&#8217;s troubleshooters, whose agents are trained to deal with space/time catastrophes. Now, IP&#8217;s HQ has been destroyed in a cataclysmic event, with most of the personnel lost, and its assets acquired by the company ICP...

*PROTEUS VEX &#187; Devious (Part 4)*
The far future. The centuries-long war between the Alliance and the Obdurate people is over, a conflict ended when the Alliance teleported a dying white dwarf star into the Obdurate system. Imperium agent PROTEUS VEX - who is operated by a flesh-pilot - became an enemy of the Alliance when he released info about past war crimes. In the wake of the war with the Scorchers, Vex is missing, presumed dead...</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-07-14 22:52:38.  [CVDB1051843]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>04</Month>
  <Day>17</Day>
  <Writer>Dan Abnett, Gordon Rennie, Kek-W, Michael Carroll, Rob Williams</Writer>
  <Penciller>I.N.J. Culbard, Jake Lynch, Lee Carter, Patrick Goddard, R.M. Guera</Penciller>
  <Inker>I.N.J. Culbard, Jake Lynch, Lee Carter, Patrick Goddard, R.M. Guera</Inker>
  <Colorist>Dylan Teague, Giulia Brusco, Jim Boswell</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Jim Campbell, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Patrick Goddard</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2378-prog-2378/4000-1051843/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Judge Dredd</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="1020690" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1292359" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1285898" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="1250284" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1350843" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1261677" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1533989" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1094188" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1101145" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1008045" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1035556" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1173308" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1191536" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1589372" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1532521" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1744193" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1896022" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1846031" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="937618" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1003447" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="858702" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1191829" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1225783" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1236471" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1377512" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1131864" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1388701" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1331970" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1354655" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1469200" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1408594" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1778952" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
