<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-177278</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T15:49:52 [Issue ID 4000-177278] urn:comicvine:4000-177278
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 19:35:03. [Issue ID 342861]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>AC</Publisher>
  <Series>Deep Dimension Horror</Series>
  <Summary>Stake Out!: Barbara Irons is an actress playing a vampire who is actually killed and turned into a real vampire in Transylvania. Years later, she decides to move to America and go back into acting. She never looks older so she continues to get starring roles. She signs on with a producer who insists on realism so he only films at nights. Because she feeds on people in the surrounding area, her films always get good publicity. Unfortunately for her, her producer replaces Peter Cushing with a real vampire hunter from Europe. When he kills her, he asks the camera, "There! Was that real enough for you?"

Ship of Ghouls: Two men take a rich man out on their boat fishing. He insists that they sail into heavy fog looking for a good fishing spot and while inside, they come upon a strange old boat. He is convinced that there is gold on board so he climbs aboard. They follow him to bring him back, unfortunately the ship is alive and eats all of them. In the end, another boat approaches and the people plan on boarding her.

Lover, Come Back... from the Grave!: Ethan's wife Fay dies when the local doctor can't save her. Old Liza (a magic healer) comes and says she can bring her back to life if Ethan will pay enough. Ethan does and Old Liza lets a demon enter her body. Ethan thinks it is Fay brought back to life but when there are many killings around them the local people come looking for Fay. She attacks them and Jeb shoots her. When she dies the demon spirit leaves her body and Ethan says goodbye to her.

Hong Kong Horror: Taking Norma Stanhope home, Chris sees a vampire fly out of a house. He discovers a dying man in the house who becomes a vampire. Chris kills the vampire, and then he and Norma go to Norma's father, the head of military intelligence with their story. At Maj. Stanhope's house, they see a vampire; they shoot and kill it. It turns out to be Maj. Stanhope in disguise. Norma tells Chris about a secret investigation of the major's: the Reds have moved an ancient Mandarin vampire tomb to Hong Kong and are using it to produce vampires. Chris and Norma then figure out how to stop the Red plot.

</Summary>
  <Title>Stake Out!; Ship of Ghouls; Lover, Come Back... from the Grave!; Hong Kong Horror</Title>
  <Volume>1994</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/deep-dimension-horror-1-stake-out/4000-177278/</Web>
  <Year>1994</Year>
  <Count>1</Count>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Barbara Irons,Gorman</Characters>
  <Writer>Bill Black,Bill Black</Writer>
  <Penciller>Bill Black,Chris Allen,Harry Lazarus,Bill Black,Chris Allen,Harry Lazarus</Penciller>
  <Inker>Mark Heike,Harry Lazarus,Mark Heike,Harry Lazarus</Inker>
  <Editor>Bill Black,Richard Hughes,Richard Hughes</Editor>
</ComicInfo>