<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-90475</GTIN>
  <Month>8</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T13:54:10 [Issue ID 4000-90475] urn:comicvine:4000-90475
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:15:11. [Issue ID 202470]</Notes>
  <Number>11</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(remix)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>Adventures into Terror</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/adventures-into-terror-11/4000-90475/</Web>
  <Year>1952</Year>
  <Count>31</Count>
  <Title>Dead Man's Escape!; Under the Knife!; He Who Laughs Last, Gets...the Horselaugh; Ed's Young Wife!; Island of Horror</Title>
  <Genre>Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Summary>Dead Man's Escape!: A convict from an island prison tries to escape by being dumped in the bay inside of a corpse bag. Instead of dumping him in the bay, a large well has been dug which they are now using to dispose of bodies, inhabited by a large octopus.

Under the Knife!: During an operation a man dies briefly and experiences a boatride with a beautiful woman named Zoe who is trying to outdistance Death. After passing dead man on the shore who died in battle as cowards and later on down the line, sirens, they are overtaken by Death. The man looks Death in the face and screams. He regains consciousness and the doctor congratulates him on his yell calling him a miracle since he was dead for seventeen minutes. He is taken to another doctor and he screams in his mind after anesthesia is administered because he had seen the man's face and it was that of...Death.

He Who Laughs Last, Gets...the Horselaugh: A man who plays the rear end in a dummy horse act is jealous of the man who plays the head, so he kills him and when he returns to the stage that night, is trampled by the front part of the costume.

Ed's Young Wife!: A man tries to get his lover's husband out of the way by sawing through the steering column of his car so it will give way on the mountain road, but is surprised to see him when he goes to his lover's abode. The husband tells him he wasn't feeling well that morning so he sent his wife in his place.

Island of Horror: A "ghoulish" reporter finds more than he bargained for when he meets with a mysterious stranger on a boat to talk about some local disappearances.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Joe Maneely,Tony DiPreta,Bill Benulis,Ben Brown,Joe Sinnott,Joe Maneely,Tony DiPreta,Bill Benulis,Ben Brown,Joe Sinnott</Penciller>
  <Inker>Joe Maneely,Tony DiPreta,Jack Abel,David Gantz,Joe Sinnott,Joe Maneely,Tony DiPreta,Jack Abel,David Gantz,Joe Sinnott</Inker>
  <Letterer>Sam Rosen,Sam Rosen</Letterer>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>