<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Cogliostro,Malebolgia,Guy DuBlanc,Spawn (Covenant),Vandalizer</Characters>
  <Colorist>Mark Nicholas</Colorist>
  <Count>28</Count>
  <Day>31</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-166351</GTIN>
  <Inker>Chance Wolf,Kevin Conrad Hanna</Inker>
  <Letterer>Oscar Gongora,Richard Starkings</Letterer>
  <Month>5</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:59:50 [Issue ID 4000-166351] urn:comicvine:4000-166351
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-19 03:38:56. [Issue ID 166351]</Notes>
  <Number>15</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Nat Jones,Nat Jones</Penciller>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Spawn: The Dark Ages</Series>
  <Summary>It is 901 AD. The Dark Ages. The darkest of times. Centuries after the Romans retreated and faded, yet many centuries before reason and order would take hold. The Dark Ages were times marked by sweat and blood and lives cut short by famine and disease. Desperate days. These were the times the lands known today as Great Britain were fought over like raw meat in a dog's teeth. The world was up for grabs. New religions were sweeping the continent like a plague of hope in a hopeless time. These are the days that a Hellspawn named Covenant walked the earth in search of the truth, understanding and solution to the curse that bound him. These are his Dark Ages. These are his adventures... In his effort to once again become a man, Covenant is complacent in the town of Rhyll where he is revered by the town's residents as their protector. One night, Covenant has a tortured sleep filled with nightmares of savage death and destruction. When he awakes, he finds that his nightmare has become real. The townspeople have been mercilessly slaughtered, and those few who have survived the carnage point to Covenant as the murderer. Cog tells the Hellspawn that by trying to recapture his humanity, he has fallen into a trap set by Malebolgia, but Covenant doesn't trust or believe the old man.</Summary>
  <Tags>Cogliostro,Malebolgia,The Phlebiac Brothers,Guy DuBlanc,Spawn (Covenant),Vandalizer</Tags>
  <Teams>The Phlebiac Brothers</Teams>
  <Title>Dark Days Coming</Title>
  <Volume>1999</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/spawn-the-dark-ages-15-dark-days-coming/4000-166351/</Web>
  <Writer>Steve Niles</Writer>
  <Year>2000</Year>
  <CoverArtist>Simon Davis</CoverArtist>
</ComicInfo>