<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-91056</GTIN>
  <Month>9</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T14:05:31 [Issue ID 4000-91056] urn:comicvine:4000-91056
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 12:59:48. [Issue ID 203202]</Notes>
  <Number>21</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Marvel</Publisher>
  <ScanInformation>(Atlas.1953)  (chums)</ScanInformation>
  <Series>War Comics</Series>
  <Volume>1950</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/war-comics-21/4000-91056/</Web>
  <Year>1953</Year>
  <Count>49</Count>
  <Title>The Heroes!; The Flag!; The Bandit; Formosa!</Title>
  <Genre>War</Genre>
  <Summary>The Heroes!: War correspondent Marone visits Korea to see what real heroism is; he witnesses how exhausted the soldiers are and yet keep fighting on, caring for their wounded and never looking back; he decides this is real heroism.

The Flag!: The Korean schoolteacher Ki Li tries to befriend US soldiers by speaking English, explaining how he wants to move to the USA, but the soldiers are suspicious of him. When the Chinese move in, Ki Li flies a US flag over his town and the Chinese retaliate by killing him; at the sight of this, the US forces attack the Chinese and crush them in honor of Ki Li.

The Bandit: Captain Devers is supplying black market items to the Chinese, but when a US pilot is shot down he picks him up in his boat. The Chinese demand Devers turn him over and he refuses, finally battling the Chinese and deciding from now on he'll be on the side of his own country.

Formosa!: Freedom fighters on Formosa strike back against the Chinese army. Formosan Yu Yi-Huen recalls how the communists slew his family and he wants to make them pay. Fellow freedom fighter Kuo takes Yu to see his grandmother and she relates the complete history of Formosa and the many powers which have fought over it; Yu dies in battle with the Chinese, pleased to at least have been a martyr. In the USA, President Eisenhower encourages support for Formosa.

</Summary>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <AgeRating>Authorized A. C. M. P. Conforms to the Comics Code</AgeRating>
  <Penciller>Vern Henkel,Gil Evans,Bill Benulis,Joe Maneely,Vern Henkel,Gil Evans,Bill Benulis,Joe Maneely</Penciller>
  <Inker>Vern Henkel,Gil Evans,Jack Abel,Joe Maneely,Vern Henkel,Gil Evans,Jack Abel,Joe Maneely</Inker>
  <Editor>Stan Lee</Editor>
</ComicInfo>