<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Pandora Boxley,Death Jr.</Characters>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Day>1</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-128149</GTIN>
  <Month>4</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T17:41:12 [Issue ID 4000-128149] urn:comicvine:4000-128149
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev43 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-04-18 18:56:05. [Issue ID 128149]</Notes>
  <Number>1</Number>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
    <Page Image="40" />
    <Page Image="41" />
    <Page Image="42" />
    <Page Image="43" />
    <Page Image="44" />
    <Page Image="45" />
    <Page Image="46" />
    <Page Image="47" />
    <Page Image="48" />
    <Page Image="49" />
    <Page Image="50" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>Image</Publisher>
  <Series>Death Jr.</Series>
  <Summary>Middle school is never easy, but it's even harder when you're dead. "DJ" tries to live the life of a typical teenager, but the fact that his dad is the Grim Reaper makes things tough. Luckily, he finds his niche with some of the weird kids: Pandora, a little goth girl, Smith &amp; Weston, conjoined twins, Stigmartha, a girl who bleeds when she gets nervous, and The Seep, an armless, legless, foreign exchange student in a jar. So when a trip to the Museum of Supernatural History gives him an opportunity to impress his new friends, he unwittingly puts himself and the whole town in danger.

Issue one follows Death Jr (aka DJ) on his first day to school! which is not the easiest thing when your a walking skeleton and every animal you come in contact with usually ends up dying! when he gets dropped off at school by his mom (who surprisingly is human) all the kids are a bit hesitant about going near DJ and some down right mean right off the bat. The Teacher then begins the day by introducing everyone to there new class pet which unfortunate for DJ does not win him any new friends. At lunch he meets Pandora (a girl with a compulsion with opening things) who becomes DJ's best friend! Pandora then later introduces DJ to her friends Stigmartha(who bleeds at her palms when she gets nervous), Weston and Smith (the conjoined at the head twins), and Seep(a legless, armless, very angry boy who lives in a giant test tube with wheels!)who all basically make up the outcast group at school! This issue is mostly a building of the characters being that its the first issue, with lots of little jokes and puns (which continue through the whole series) but towards the end of this 48 page comic! Death Jr. and Pandora wonder off on there class field trip to the museum, when they come across this skull shaped box on a pillar! I wont go into details as to not spoil the ending, but lets just say DJ's dad, Death! does not have many friends!</Summary>
  <Title>Death Jr.</Title>
  <Volume>2005</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/death-jr-1-death-jr/4000-128149/</Web>
  <Writer>Gary Whitta</Writer>
  <Year>2005</Year>
  <Penciller>Ted Naifeh,Ted Naifeh</Penciller>
  <Inker>Ted Naifeh</Inker>
</ComicInfo>