<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo>
  <Series>Love and Rockets</Series>
  <Number>3</Number>
  <Title>You Can't Get a False Positive 2.0; I Come From Above to Avoid a Double Chin (part 3); Professor Enigma and Missy; 1979; Animus; 1979</Title>
  <Volume>2016</Volume>
  <Genre>Drama,Superhero</Genre>
  <Summary>This is volume four in the series. Uses the same oversize magazine format as volume one.

Vol. 1- 1982-1996 (50 issues in magazine format)
Vol. 2- 2001-2007 (20 issues in standard US comic book periodical format)
Vol. 3- 2008-2016 (8 issues as Love and Rockets: New Stories in trade paperback format)

Comes with at least one cover variant per issue available exclusively from the publisher. Each variant has its own individual front &amp; back cover.US comic book store release date 2017-08-02.You Can't Get a False Positive 2.0: The women get a new perspective on their past then meet Luba for the first time.

I Come From Above to Avoid a Double Chin (part 3): Now that the punk reunion show is over, the old gang meets up for coffee and chat. Afterwards, Eugene menaces Hopey and Maggie.

Professor Enigma and Missy: Killer and Baby reminisce about working on the Professor Enigma children's show which featured all the ladies playing the same character but at different ages.

1979: A post gang, pre-goth Isabel prevents Hopey from getting in trouble at the Belson Rec Center.

Animus: Super-powered wrestlers fight giants. Isla picks herself and Lumina out of rubble. Giant-sized Animus disposes of a Hellmet and the adversary it was controlling only to have it come back and seemingly squeeze the life out of her, leading them both to be consumed by flames.

1979: A flashback story taking place before the series 1981 debut. Maggie meets Del in his Hoppers house which is the neighborhood punk hangout, and Isabel makes sure Del treats Maggie with respect.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev36 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-03-22 15:07:45. [Issue ID 1725593]</Notes>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Month>7</Month>
  <Year>2017</Year>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Web>https://www.comics.org/issue/1725593</Web>
  <ScanInformation>(digital) (Salem-Empire)</ScanInformation>
  <Writer>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Writer>
  <Penciller>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Penciller>
  <Inker>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Inker>
  <Letterer>Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez,Gilbert Hernandez,Jaime Hernandez</Letterer>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" />
    <Page Image="2" />
    <Page Image="3" />
    <Page Image="4" />
    <Page Image="5" />
    <Page Image="6" />
    <Page Image="7" />
    <Page Image="8" />
    <Page Image="9" />
    <Page Image="10" />
    <Page Image="11" />
    <Page Image="12" />
    <Page Image="13" />
    <Page Image="14" />
    <Page Image="15" />
    <Page Image="16" />
    <Page Image="17" />
    <Page Image="18" />
    <Page Image="19" />
    <Page Image="20" />
    <Page Image="21" />
    <Page Image="22" />
    <Page Image="23" />
    <Page Image="24" />
    <Page Image="25" />
    <Page Image="26" />
    <Page Image="27" />
    <Page Image="28" />
    <Page Image="29" />
    <Page Image="30" />
    <Page Image="31" />
    <Page Image="32" />
    <Page Image="33" />
    <Page Image="34" />
    <Page Image="35" />
    <Page Image="36" />
    <Page Image="37" />
    <Page Image="38" />
    <Page Image="39" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>