<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Prog 2395</Title>
  <Series>2000 AD</Series>
  <Number>2395</Number>
  <Volume>1977</Volume>
  <Summary>Call me The Mighty Tharg, all-powerful alien editor of this eye-popping Thrilltopia! 

Another Wednesday, another blast to your cranial circuits courtesy of the Galaxy&#8217;s Greatest Comic, Terrans - the August line-up continues to set alight to readers&#8217; diodes the planet over as Judge Dredd, Brink, Silver, Rogue Trooper and Herne &amp; Shuck all plough ahead at maximum excitement levels.

In fact, you better make sure your Thrill-buffers are operating efficiently because next week will see the publication of the third bumper prog of 2024, with extra pages and additional stories. So don&#8217;t say I didn&#8217;t warn you, my Squaxx - stock up on those lead-lined reading mitts today and protect yourselves from the shattering effect of Thrill-exposure!

What else is new in the House of Tharg? Well, those of you collecting Hachette&#8217;s 2000 AD Ultimate Collection will be able to pick up this week #181, the first book in the fourth extension - the Abnett and Harrison droids&#8217; The Out, which contains the first three series (and with the fourth about to hit the prog in the autumn, it&#8217;s the ideal primer for those that missed it). We&#8217;re on the final stretch to a ghafflebette two hundred volumes!

*Judge Dredd &#187; Machine Rule (Part 4)*
Mega-City One, 2146 AD. Home to over 200 million citizens, this urban hell is situated along the east coast of post-apocalyptic North America. Crime is rampant, and only future cops the Judges - empowered to dispense instant justice - can stop total anarchy. Toughest of them all is JUDGE DREDD - he is the Law! The Mark 8 Mechanismo robot Judges have been on the streets for several years now...

*Rogue Trooper &#187; Recon (Part 3)*
Nu Earth, site of a galactic war between the Norts and the Southers, where the atmosphere has been rendered poisonous. So the Southers created the Genetic Infantrymen, bred to be immune to the pollutants - G.I.s like ROGUE TROOPER, the last of his kind. Together with biochip buddies Helm, Gunnar and Bagman, they&#8217;re searching for the traitor that sold them out...

*Herne &amp; Shuck &#187; Suffer The Children (Part 4)*
The UK, 2024. Herne is a troubleshooter and hired help for many different magical factions in the country. Accompanied by Shuck, a demon in dog form, he travels the country picking up work where he can, whether it be exorcism or a rescue. Recently, he was tasked with saving a young girl called Carys, only to find out she was scheduled for ritual sacrifice. The pair are now trying to get the child to safety...

*Brink &#187; Consumed (Part 18)*
The late 21st century, and through environmental catastrophe and industrial overload Earth has been reduced to a wasteland. Mankind finally evacuated the planet in 2072 and millions were housed in a number of deep-space Habitats. But life on these cramped, overcrowded stations is tense, often spilling over into madness. Sects are rife, and Bridget Kurtis of the Habitat Security Division is investigating their reach...

*Silver &#187; Unearthed: book 1 (Part 6)*
Earth, the year 2001. A group of armed survivors sought out the resting place of a five hundred-year-old vampire, who may just help them against the alien Sepsis, who invaded the planet a few decades earlier. The vamp, called Baroness DeSilva, has proved powerful in battling the extra-terrestrials, and now she has been tasked by the resistance to help capture a Harvester&#8230;</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-08-24 23:53:37.  [CVDB1066809]</Notes>
  <Year>2024</Year>
  <Month>08</Month>
  <Day>14</Day>
  <Writer>Dan Abnett, David Barnett, Geoffrey D. Wessel, John Wagner, Michael Carroll</Writer>
  <Penciller>Colin MacNeil, I.N.J. Culbard, Joe Robinson Currie, Lee Milmore, Paul Marshall</Penciller>
  <Inker>Colin MacNeil, I.N.J. Culbard, Joe Robinson Currie, Lee Milmore, Paul Marshall</Inker>
  <Colorist>Chris Blythe, Pippa Bowland, Quinton Winter</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Annie Parkhouse, Jim Campbell, Simon Bowland</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Frazer Irving</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Rebellion</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/2000-ad-2395-prog-2395/4000-1066809/</Web>
  <PageCount>32</PageCount>
  <Characters>Bridget Kurtis, Judge Dredd, Rogue Trooper</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="942331" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1409833" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1168700" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="926858" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="1203573" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="1053538" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="1295824" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1310346" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1447895" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="1188127" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="1360632" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="1090192" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="1313869" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="1183333" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="1578061" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="1538635" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="1353816" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="1503705" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="1604125" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="1248407" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="1058028" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="1067397" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="1115294" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="1147976" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="1016819" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="1167042" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="1214366" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="1127764" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="1301093" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="1252752" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="1256813" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="1086453" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
