<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Bronco,Gayle Ransom,Lightning Bowman,Lionel "Buster" Crabb,Lionel Crabb,Mary Raven,Piet Vanderkirk,Rock Raven,Yuri</Characters>
	<Colorist>Digikore Studios</Colorist>
	<Count>5</Count>
	<Country>US</Country>
	<Format>Limited Series</Format>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-612794</GTIN>
	<Genre>Science fiction</Genre>
	<Inker>Chris Dreier</Inker>
	<LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
	<Locations>Berlin,Ignition City</Locations>
	<Month>4</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T02:22:40 [Issue ID 4000-612794] urn:comicvine:4000-612794 urn:grandcomicsdatabase:issue/612794</Notes>
	<Number>1</Number>
	<PageCount>24</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="2203053" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="618801"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="843131"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="3657857"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="1796679"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="1629932"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="1528575"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="1583709"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="1760318"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="1761861"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="1282744"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="1399274"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="2927365"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="1936561"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="1760887"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="1856332"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="1831057"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="1930847"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="1701417"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="1965182"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="1835718"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="2011682"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="1799220"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="974213"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Avatar Press</Publisher>
	<Series>Warren Ellis' Ignition City</Series>
	<Summary>Warren Ellis uses mature language and imagery to bring readers the science fiction story of Mary Raven. The series has a pulp adventure feel with airships and phaser pistols in the normal everyday life of the 1950s.

Mary Raven, a pilot in her own right, learns that her father has been killed in Ignition City. The city is the last space port open. Mary heads there to collect her father's effects and figure out what happened.

Where did the space heroes go to die? A major new series by Warren Ellis, the writer who reinvented science fiction in comics, in the alternate-world style of the award-winning Ministry Of Space and Aetheric Mechanics - a retro-punk 'future of the past' where spaceships still belched smoke and arguments were still settled with laser pistols. 1956. Personal space flight is becoming illegal all over the world. Grounded space pilot Mary Raven has to journey to Earth's last spaceport, the island of Ignition City, to recover her dead father's effects - and discovers, there in the lawless interzone of the ramshackle settlement raised inside the ring of launch pads, that her father died on the wrong end of a ray-gun. She's not going to leave until she finds out who killed Rock Raven, but there's a lot of people who'd rather feed her to the recycling chipper first! Ignition City is an on-going color epic told in five issue series featuring the art of Aetheric Mechanics' Gianluca Pagliarani and launching with a Regular and Wraparound cover by Pagliarani, a painted cover by Felipe Massafera, and a rare Design Sketch cover by Pagliarani!</Summary>
	<Tags>Bronco,Gayle Ransom,Lionel "Buster" Crabb,Mary Raven,Piet Vanderkirk,Rock Raven,Yuri</Tags>
	<Volume>2009</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/c/4000-612794/</Web>
	<Writer>Warren Ellis</Writer>
	<Year>2009</Year>
</ComicInfo>