<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Alfred E. Neuman</Characters>
  <Day>10</Day>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-129545</GTIN>
  <Month>12</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:20:54 [Issue ID 4000-129545] urn:comicvine:4000-129545
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 23:54:22. [Issue ID 93836]</Notes>
  <Number>36</Number>
  <PageCount>52</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="149572" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="148762" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="166003" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="133681" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="100925" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="168906" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="160096" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="241930" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="229855" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="271745" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="253277" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="150550" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="134827" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="179710" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="181612" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="206492" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="167529" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="229747" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="182548" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="188484" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="199153" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="193576" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="195794" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="300689" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="305482" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="187357" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="175290" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="164053" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="177764" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="185569" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="147238" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="177992" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="119924" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="168246" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="140080" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="214429" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="246723" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="159883" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="185932" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="202821" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="189624" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="179900" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="128355" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="137969" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="278609" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="300588" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="204497" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="187554" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="203598" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="206604" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="129338" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="133945" />
  </Pages>
  <Publisher>EC</Publisher>
  <Series>Mad</Series>
  <Summary>New Morris Philip Gives You a Natural Smoke with an Un-natural Light!: Parody of ad for Phillip Morris cigarettes.

Personalized TV Antennas: Customized tv antennas to show your profession or hobby.

TV Movies With Built-In Commercials: What tv dramas might look like if they embedded commercials directly within movies.

MAD Hats: Everyday household containers used as women's hats.

My Fren' Dufo: Story of Wally Cox's incredibly stupid boyhood friend.

Scenes We'd Like to See: The Duel: At a gun duel, the seconds and other spectators shoot each other and the man in charge of the weapons finishes off the crowd.

Blind Date: A story of a blind date, as told differently by the boy and girl involved.

Parking Meters: Parking meters for all types of waiting activities, and a solution to the problem.

The Nursery News: Nursery rhymes reported as realistic news stories.  Fake photos credited to Ozgood Z'Beard and Melvin Coznowfski.

Paul Sturdley's Secret File: Interview with a notorious kitten dumper.

Cowboys 'n Indians: Story of how the handbook of real Indian lore that came with a kid's Indian outfit saved the day.

Raw Guts: Parody of men's magazines, with beginnings of several adventure stories.

Home Movies: Comparing the improved photographic opportunities presented by movies versus still cameras.

Bomb Song Hits: Parodies to songs are written for the post-nuclear war days.

OK! Gunfight at the Corral!: Parody of movie "Gunfight At The OK Corral."

The Children's Hour: Humorous drawings to illustrate the famous poem, with a macabre ending.

Mr. Morgan Tells the Story of the 12 Bottles: Henry empties his 12 bottles of whiskey down the sink, except for one glass per bottle...which he drinks.

A Martian Field Guide to U.S. Wild Life - 1957 Edition: Details of pop culture stereotypes presented as a field guide to wildlife from a Martian point of view.

Scenes We'd Like to See: The Human Shield: A bank robber takes a hostage to enable his getaway, but she turns out to be in on the scheme.

</Summary>
  <Tags>Alfred E. Neuman</Tags>
  <Volume>1952</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/mad-36/4000-129545/</Web>
  <Year>1957</Year>
  <Count>550</Count>
  <Title>New Morris Philip Gives You a Natural Smoke with an Un-natural Light!; Personalized TV Antennas; TV Movies With Built-In Commercials; MAD Hats; My Fren' Dufo; Scenes We'd Like to See: The Duel; Blind Date; Parking Meters; The Nursery News; Paul Sturdley's Secret File; Cowboys 'n Indians; Raw Guts; Home Movies; Bomb Song Hits; OK! Gunfight at the Corral!; The Children's Hour; Mr. Morgan Tells the Story of the 12 Bottles; A Martian Field Guide to U.S. Wild Life - 1957 Edition; Scenes We'd Like to See: The Human Shield</Title>
  <Genre>Humor,Satire-parody</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Writer>Frank Jacobs,Dave Berg,Bob Elliott,Ray Goulding,Don Martin,Paul Laikin,Al Feldstein,Jerry De Fuccio,Nick Meglin,Albert B. Feldstein,Henry Wadsworth Longfellow,Henry Morgan</Writer>
  <Penciller>Kelly Freas,Bob Clarke,Wally Wood,Basil Wolverton,George Woodbridge,Joe Orlando,Dave Berg,Mort Drucker,Don Martin,Albert B. Feldstein</Penciller>
  <Inker>Kelly Freas,Bob Clarke,Wally Wood,Basil Wolverton,George Woodbridge,Joe Orlando,Dave Berg,Mort Drucker,Don Martin,Albert B. Feldstein</Inker>
  <Editor>Al Feldstein</Editor>
</ComicInfo>