<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>Games</Title>
  <Series>Zot!</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Volume>1984</Volume>
  <Summary>In the chaotic aftermath of the brief ruckus caused by the Church of De-Evolution, Jenny and Zot try to figure out how to help Butch, who has been turned into a chimp. Unfortunately, the gun that make him go ape was destroyed.

Peabody the robot butler announces that the Golden Key that everyone wants gives off a unique radiation signature, which will help them search for it.

Zot decides to bring the remains of the de-evolution gun to his uncle Max, a genius. As he and Jenny fly to Max's house, she continues to be amazed at Zot's Earth. Zot mentions that she can stay as long as she wants, since no time will go by on her Earth. Unknown to them, 9-Jack-9 is surveilling their activities for a mysterious other figure.

Uncle Max's house is a sprawling wonderland of science, architecture, and gardens. He gives Butch a translator so they can understand him and agrees to work on reversing his condition. He also talks with Zot about Zot's parents; something happened with them, but Zot doesn't want to talk about it.

Zot, Jenny, Butch, and Peabody decide to go sightseeing in town while Max works on the chimp cure. There is a giant game arcade, with all sorts of screen games, virtual reality games, and hologram-enhanced rides. Butch finally enjoys Zot's world when he sees a player break a record in a VR battle game. Zot and Jenny go on a hologram ride as he reminisces about his parents. Peabody, who stayed with Butch, picks up the key's energy signature inside the VR game. Zot goes inside to find it, and is followed both by Drufus, the incompetent young prince of Sirius IV (who Peabody told about the key's location), and 9-Jack-9.

Inside, Zot recognizes the voice of the record-breaking player, who has the key, but he can't quite place him. They fight and get in a chase, which Drufus manages to screw up. Drufus goes off after the escaping player while Zot finds the key which he dropped. 9-Jack-9 is about to grab it when the game is shut off, along with the electronic signal that Jack (a digital being) was riding on.

Zot, Jenny, Peabody, and Butch return to Max's while 9-Jack-9 reports in to his contact, who is revealed to be Dekko. Dekko will now take a more direct hand in the attempt to gain possession of the key.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-12-07 14:17:27.  [CVDB24289]</Notes>
  <Year>1984</Year>
  <Month>05</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Scott McCloud</Writer>
  <Penciller>Scott McCloud, Scott McCloud</Penciller>
  <Inker>Scott McCloud, Scott McCloud</Inker>
  <Colorist>Tom Ziuko</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Carrie McCarthy, Todd Klein</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Scott McCloud</CoverArtist>
  <Editor>Cat Yronwode, Dean Mullaney</Editor>
  <Publisher>Eclipse</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/zot-2-games/4000-24289/</Web>
  <PageCount>30</PageCount>
  <Characters>9-Jack-9, Butch Weaver, Dekko, Drufus, Floyd, James Goodman, Jenny Weaver, Max, Peabody, Vic Taylor, Zarbim Borlock, Zot</Characters>
  <Teams>The Devoes</Teams>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="153397" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="192055" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="220497" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="162828" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="178766" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="190907" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="212991" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="198983" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="172873" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="179893" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="188120" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="172054" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="194035" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="186875" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="185181" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="153813" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="179464" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="171831" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="164180" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="168263" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="206878" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="194402" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="201893" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="202240" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="182360" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="173348" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="182821" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="189489" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="195390" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="186561" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
