<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Blind Man's Bluff; The Dreamer; The Smiling Cavalier; The Island; The Devil's Armchair; Find the Traitor; The Black Pit; A Very Strange Burial; The Amazing Peter Hurkos</Title>
  <Series>Boris Karloff Thriller</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <Volume>1962</Volume>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-15 21:42:09.  [CVDB6321]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 10:43:32. [Issue ID 512223]</Notes>
  <Year>1963</Year>
  <Month>1</Month>
  <Writer>Paul S. Newman,Paul S. Newman</Writer>
  <Penciller>George Evans,Mike Sekowsky,Tom Gill,Dan Spiegle,Bob Fujitani,Jack Sparling,Giovanni Ticci,Jerry Robinson,George Evans,Mike Sekowsky,Tom Gill,Dan Spiegle,Bob Fujitani,Jack Sparling,Giovanni Ticci</Penciller>
  <Inker>George Evans,Mike Peppe,Herb Trimpe,Dan Spiegle,Bob Fujitani,Jack Sparling,Alberto Giolitti,Tom Gill,Jerry Robinson,George Evans,Mike Peppe,Herb Trimpe,Dan Spiegle,Bob Fujitani,Jack Sparling,Alberto Giolitti,Tom Gill</Inker>
  <Letterer>Ben Oda,Tom Gill,Ben Oda,Tom Gill</Letterer>
  <Publisher>Western</Publisher>
  <Genre>Non-fiction,Detective-mystery,Fantasy,Biography,History,Horror-suspense</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/boris-karloff-thriller-2/4000-6321/</Web>
  <PageCount>84</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Buzz Murphy (death),Jim Blake (death),Judy Davis,Boris Karloff (host)</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="478944" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="522176" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="680756" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="622078" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="593024" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="649350" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="586818" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="568952" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="610316" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="577240" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="808358" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="483936" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="565576" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="602504" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="824290" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="594556" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="675790" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="592606" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="701770" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="613506" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="701100" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="677942" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="734114" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="661526" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="562392" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="531178" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="538382" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="527046" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="571502" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="547260" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="637736" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="551028" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="536766" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="497354" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="517918" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="494636" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="595870" />
    <Page Image="37" ImageSize="637040" />
    <Page Image="38" ImageSize="537328" />
    <Page Image="39" ImageSize="738132" />
    <Page Image="40" ImageSize="686762" />
    <Page Image="41" ImageSize="564398" />
    <Page Image="42" ImageSize="600182" />
    <Page Image="43" ImageSize="825462" />
    <Page Image="44" ImageSize="645078" />
    <Page Image="45" ImageSize="625270" />
    <Page Image="46" ImageSize="624318" />
    <Page Image="47" ImageSize="557866" />
    <Page Image="48" ImageSize="748298" />
    <Page Image="49" ImageSize="749202" />
    <Page Image="50" ImageSize="648514" />
    <Page Image="51" ImageSize="676322" />
    <Page Image="52" ImageSize="484696" />
    <Page Image="53" ImageSize="814726" />
    <Page Image="54" ImageSize="668564" />
    <Page Image="55" ImageSize="600090" />
    <Page Image="56" ImageSize="564746" />
    <Page Image="57" ImageSize="563712" />
    <Page Image="58" ImageSize="685488" />
    <Page Image="59" ImageSize="505084" />
    <Page Image="60" ImageSize="637834" />
    <Page Image="61" ImageSize="742676" />
    <Page Image="62" ImageSize="647006" />
    <Page Image="63" ImageSize="659610" />
    <Page Image="64" ImageSize="555974" />
    <Page Image="65" ImageSize="644236" />
    <Page Image="66" ImageSize="443806" />
    <Page Image="67" ImageSize="482680" />
    <Page Image="68" ImageSize="555984" />
    <Page Image="69" ImageSize="610030" />
    <Page Image="70" ImageSize="617532" />
    <Page Image="71" ImageSize="453074" />
    <Page Image="72" ImageSize="472154" />
    <Page Image="73" ImageSize="491502" />
    <Page Image="74" ImageSize="685418" />
    <Page Image="75" ImageSize="577734" />
    <Page Image="76" ImageSize="621578" />
    <Page Image="77" ImageSize="634026" />
    <Page Image="78" ImageSize="572694" />
    <Page Image="79" ImageSize="624978" />
    <Page Image="80" ImageSize="579910" />
    <Page Image="81" ImageSize="584290" />
    <Page Image="82" ImageSize="224948" />
    <Page Image="83" ImageSize="445418" />
  </Pages>
  <Summary>Blind Man's Bluff: During a race, Buzz Murphy, driving very recklessly because Jim is in the lead, causes Jim to crash. Afterwards, Buzz asks Jim's fiancée out for a drink while he is in the hospital. The next day while Buzz is driving on the racetrack Jim suddenly shows up behind him and causes him to die in a crash. The people at the wreckage comment that Jim had died in the hospital just before the crash.

The Dreamer: Mark Pearson shows up at Dr. Korvo's (a psychiatrist) office after hours begging him to help him.  He has a recurring dream about being on a ship when it sinks.  Dr. Korvo agrees to try to help him and hypnotizes him because he has amnesia.

The Smiling Cavalier: Laurie Callan loves to visit the museum and try to sketch the 17th century masterpiece "The Smiling Cavalier" but she never seems to be able to get it right. One night when she accidentally remains in the museum after it closes the paintings come to life. The "Smiling Cavalier" (Don Juan) and the other two "Smiling Cavalier" paintings come out and chase Laurie until she can escape. The night guard that lets her out looks just like the Don Juan "Smiling Cavalier".

The Island: Cecil Matthews is a bank employee who is sick of his job. He steals $30,000 and flies to Hawaii where he plans to charter a plane to Papinee, an island he found in an old "Islands of Paradise" book. The bank notices the theft before he can get to Papinee so he hijacks a mail plane to fly him there. Once there he kills the pilot and settles in at the deserted village. What Cecil doesn't know is that the reason the village is deserted is that the Island of Papinee was chosen by the Government to use in a missile test. The next day he is destroyed when the bomb is detonated on the island.

The Devil's Armchair: Martha Harris buys an antique chair for her husband's birthday. He loves the chair but when she or her friend try to sit in it they are jabbed. She tries to take the chair back but is told that it is cursed and that she must keep it forever. It was used by a man named Jean Maraque to kill a young lady who spurned him. Martha does not believe the story and is killed when she tries to throw the chair out.

Find the Traitor: General Luis Amendez is driven through a quiet city to his presidential palace. He rules with an iron fist where people are afraid to even speak around him. When he finds a letter saying that he must die and that the people will be free he tells the police to find the individuals behind the letters and to kill them, but if the police can't find them, they will be killed themselves. The police find that the one writing the letters is General Amendez himself (he suffers from schizophrenia). They kill the General to keep from being killed themselves.

The Black Pit: Mort Fallon wants to write an article on the 10th anniversary of a mine collapse. Jamie Walsh agrees to take Mort on a tour of the mine and only agrees to take him to the site of the collapse when Mort offers him $100. While on their way there they hear "tommyknockers" (the souls of miners who lost their lives there) warning them to leave.

A Very Strange Burial: Sydney Clybourne walks in front of a car and is killed. When the police investigate the accident they find a book on him with a story from Sydney's time in Tanganyika. Sydney was on a safari there with Malcolm Billings when they heard a story about a strange ritual that a local tribe goes through whenever their chief dies.

The Amazing Peter Hurkos: Peter Hurkos, the man with the x-ray brain, helps the Dutch authorities in the city of Nijmegen identify the arsonist terrorizing the area.

</Summary>
</ComicInfo>