<ComicInfo>
  <Title>Hollywood and Vines; The Lost Temple of Tuaarkha</Title>
  <Series>Dagger of Blood</Series>
  <Number>2</Number>
  <Volume>1997</Volume>
  <Summary>Hollywood and Vines: As filming continues, Coley has picked up a new friend-- a squirrel monkey-- and thinks he'd like to take him back to California with him. Danny discusses Coley with Harry, and wonders what makes someone gay; while, within earshot of Kit, Harry gives his opinion of women. Coley &amp; Lon go off into the jungle to "play around". Agitated, Harry tells Danny to find them, while he makes plans to find the temple. Danny finds Coley &amp; Lon, and true to form, quickly joins in. Kit feels it's not a good idea for Harry to go off on his own, and winds up following him. Suddenly, they're surrounded by members of the cult, who say they've captured Danny &amp; Lon. Meanwhile, Coley is approached by Esmerelda, who says she's the "only one" who can help him.

The Lost Temple of Tuaarkha: Esmerelda leads Coley to the temple and says she'll tell him all she knows once he gives her what she wants. But Coley wants to have sex with her in front of the temple. Inside, Harry is tied up and whipped. Joquatoth feels confident Coley will come to free his friends. In another chamber, a depraved ex-Nazi scientist performs an unspeakable operation on Lon, hoping it’ll serve as a trial-run for helping to restore Joquatoth to full humanity. Outside, Coley roughly takes Esmerelda again and again while Joquatoth watches, his men finally assaulting Coley as he reaches the height of excitement.

</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-03-31 13:08:57.  [CVDB138804]
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-15 23:43:47. [Issue ID 351868]</Notes>
  <Year>1997</Year>
  <Month>3</Month>
  <Writer>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Writer>
  <Penciller>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Penciller>
  <Inker>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Inker>
  <CoverArtist>John Blackburn</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Fantagraphics</Publisher>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/dagger-of-blood-2-hollywood-and-vines/4000-138804/</Web>
  <PageCount>28</PageCount>
  <Characters>Curt (film crew),Harry "Lance" Larue,Esmerelda,Kit Cameron,Lon Ireland,cult members,Danny Navarro (bodyguard)</Characters>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="368407" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="332735" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="275067" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="282921" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="299858" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="281798" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="317450" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="298356" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="276383" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="289073" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="282167" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="273848" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="294125" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="285851" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="271323" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="264140" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="303620" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="290393" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="301436" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="317032" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="286279" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="296064" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="312932" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="295286" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="345659" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="281491" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="333793" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="305495" />
  </Pages>
  <Count>3</Count>
  <Genre>Adult</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Format>Limited Series</Format>
  <AgeRating>Adults Only</AgeRating>
  <Letterer>John Blackburn,John Blackburn</Letterer>
  <Editor>Ezra Mark</Editor>
</ComicInfo>