<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
  <Characters>Jenny Sparks,Swift],Engineer,The Authority [Apollo,Midnighter,Jack Hawksmoor,Regis,Yngvi,Doctor</Characters>
  <Colorist>Laura Martin,Wildstorm FX,Laura DePuy,Laura DePuy</Colorist>
  <Editor>Rachelle Brissenden</Editor>
  <GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-53625</GTIN>
  <Inker>Bryan Hitch,Paul Neary,Paul Neary</Inker>
  <Letterer>Ali Fuchs,Ali Fuchs</Letterer>
  <Locations>Sliding Albion,Rendelsham,Europe,The Bleed</Locations>
  <Month>11</Month>
  <Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-13T21:04:38 [Issue ID 4000-53625] urn:comicvine:4000-53625
Tagged with ComicTagger 1.6.0a13.dev122 using info from Grand Comics Database on 2024-06-16 22:28:58. [Issue ID 72159]</Notes>
  <Number>7</Number>
  <PageCount>25</PageCount>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" ImageSize="651262" Type="FrontCover" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="789926" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="790186" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="805110" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="712780" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="765854" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="807741" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="778704" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="716527" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="571238" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="827462" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="707701" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="747125" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="851372" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="723026" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="809897" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="733758" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="796566" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="826252" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="844787" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="733304" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="756279" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="676846" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="642538" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="548191" />
  </Pages>
  <Penciller>Bryan Hitch,Bryan Hitch</Penciller>
  <Publisher>DC Comics</Publisher>
  <Series>The Authority</Series>
  <Summary>In Sliding Albion, Regis and his second in command, Yngvi, discuss the rise and fall of their empire. He says that they need to find another Earth because their Earth has been affected greatly by all the warring they've caused. Yngvi updates Regis on the assault their forces led on the Wildstorm Earth Los Angeles. He tells Regis that Jenny Sparks appeared with some companions and drove their forces back. He also tells Regis that Sparks had Door technology even though her world is not supposed to have that technology. The good news for Sliding Albion though, is that they can track Sparks and her companions by following the frequency of the Doors she and The Authority are using.Meanwhile at Rendelsham, Jenny, Angie , and Swift confront Jenny's ex-husband Lorenzo who is imprisoned there. Jenny tells Lorenzo that they just fended off a Sliding Albion attack and wants to know how the Sliding Albion still live. Lorenzo explains that after Jenny castrated Regis, he didn't die. Doctors saved him and he went on to conquer the parallel Earth he occupied. He even went as far as turning China into a giant rape camp in order to ensure the survival of the blue skin species. Suddenly, Lorenzo tries to assault Jenny but she easily puts him down with her electric powers. The three woman then leave Rendelsham.On The Carrier, Apollo and Jack Hawksmoor detect a second wave of Sliding Albion ships over Northern Europe. But before they can react, Doors suddenly appear inside The Carrier and Albion troops invade the ship. Midnighter and The Doctor join the fight and fend off wave after wave of Albion troops. Apollo finally uses his power to emit an energy blast that clears the room of the Albion. But he collapses after expending too much energy.Jenny, Angie, and Swift return to the aftermath of the battle on The Carrier. Jenny gets updated on the situation and in turn updates the others about what they learned from Lorenzo. She decides to send Apollo over Europe, claiming a short time in sunlight will recharge him. Then she orders the others to prepare to move The Carrier.

Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2023-10-19 07:44:35.  [CVDB53625]

https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-authority-7-shiftships-part-3/4000-53625/</Summary>
  <Tags>Swift,Jenny Sparks,The Bleed,Apollo,Shiftships,Sliding Albion,Midnighter,Engineer,The Authority,The Carrier,Jeroen Thornedike,Lorenzo Antonio Slzfi,Europe,Regis,Jack Hawksmoor,Rendelsham,Yngvi</Tags>
  <Teams>The Authority,Sliding Albion</Teams>
  <Title>Shiftships - Three of Four</Title>
  <Volume>1999</Volume>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/the-authority-7-shiftships-part-3/4000-53625/</Web>
  <Writer>Warren Ellis,Warren Ellis</Writer>
  <Year>1999</Year>
  <Count>29</Count>
  <Genre>Superhero</Genre>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
</ComicInfo>