<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Title>The Final Battle</Title>
  <Series>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</Series>
  <Number>13</Number>
  <Count>13</Count>
  <Volume>1993</Volume>
  <Summary>The soldiers open fire and Leonardo falls from his perch near the            opening - fortunately, Raph catches him. As the guys try to figure what            to do, they hear a loud explosion from the surface, and when they peek            out they see that the Triceratons have begun their attack on the base.            A true maelstrom of violence ensues as the agents of D.A.R.P.A. battles            the invading Triceraton forces.          

  The fight doesn't go well for the Triceratons, but the commander aboard            the mothership won't recall his troops. Instead, he plans to crash the            crippled craft into the surface of the Earth at Warp 8, to inflict as            much damage upon the planet as possible and die with what his people            consider honor.          

  As the Turtles and their remaining allies prepare to flee, Braunze            warns the others that their Triceraton companion is a traitor. The beast            fires a blast from its gun that leaves a huge gaping hole in the man's            chest. As Braunze lays dying, he informs Leonardo of the Triceraton            commander's suicide plan. This news enrages their former Triceraton            ally, who refuses to believe that his commander would resort to such            a tactic, and declares that the reptilian aliens will soon rule the            Earth. As the Triceraton warrior makes his speech, a jet engine falls            from the sky and explodes onto him.          

  Braunze's alien friend has the Turtles help him right a Jeep that            had been turned over. The fellow plans to go back inside the D.A.R.P.A.            base to attempt to thwart the Triceratons from crashing their ship into            the Earth. Leonardo attempts to go with his alien compatriot, but a            blast of air from the visitor's shoulder apparatus sends Leo flying.            The alien tells Leonardo to get his friends to safety as he drives off.          

  The TMNT and Casey retreat to the desert.          

  As the alien drives the jeep, we see that Braunze is seated beside            him - the man used his mental powers on the Turtles to fake his death.            Braunze and his friend plan to use an "inter-phase cannon" located on            the base to move the Triceraton mothership out of phase, causing it            to pass through the Earth's crust and resolidify once it reaches the            core - vaporizing the threat.          

  As the TMNT and Casey flee, we see a huge explosion erupt behind them.            The guys can't outrun the blast and are vaporized themselves...          

  Leonardo wakes up from a dream with a start on the couch in Casey and April's apartment.            Casey is cleaning up the place and Shadow is playing a Godzilla video            game. Casey asks Leo if he's okay, and the Turtle asks Jones how they            survived the blast and when they got back home.          

  "From where?" inquires Casey.          

  "Nevada, you idiot!" retorts the bemused Turtle.          

  "Hmmt." Casey shrugs, "Leo, we've never been to Nevada."          

  Leo sits puzzled on the couch for a time, watching Shadow play her            game. The girl notices Leo's distress and comes over to him, and he            picks her up.          

  A thought enters Leonardo's mind: "REMEMBER"          

  Leo goes to the window and looks out. On the street below stands Mr.            Braunze.          

  "GOODBYE, LEO" bids the telepath, and then he walks off into the crowded New York City sidewalk.</Summary>
  <Notes>Tagged with the ninjas.walk.alone fork of ComicTagger 1.3.5 using info from Comic Vine on 2024-05-27 12:21:19.  [CVDB174855]</Notes>
  <Year>1995</Year>
  <Month>10</Month>
  <Day>01</Day>
  <Writer>Jim Lawson</Writer>
  <Penciller>Jim Lawson, Jim Lawson</Penciller>
  <Inker>Jim Lawson</Inker>
  <Colorist>Eric Vincent</Colorist>
  <Letterer>Mary Kelleher</Letterer>
  <CoverArtist>Kevin Eastman, Peter Laird</CoverArtist>
  <Publisher>Mirage</Publisher>
  <Genre>Martial arts,Anthropomorphic-funny animals</Genre>
  <Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-13-the-final-battle/4000-174855/</Web>
  <PageCount>37</PageCount>
  <LanguageISO>en</LanguageISO>
  <Characters>Casey Jones, Donatello, Leonardo, Michelangelo, Mr. Braunze, Raphael</Characters>
  <Teams>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Triceratons</Teams>
  <ScanInformation>(c2c)(demon-alukard)  Eric Vincent (colorist), Jim Lawson (inker, penciler,  Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles,  930d8aa0ba8f55db79e73f5ae0be  Anna&#8217;s Archiveunclosed left paren</ScanInformation>
  <Pages>
    <Page Image="0" Type="FrontCover" ImageSize="687160" />
    <Page Image="1" ImageSize="1742026" />
    <Page Image="2" ImageSize="1086106" />
    <Page Image="3" ImageSize="572398" />
    <Page Image="4" ImageSize="929590" />
    <Page Image="5" ImageSize="941072" />
    <Page Image="6" ImageSize="970164" />
    <Page Image="7" ImageSize="1001896" />
    <Page Image="8" ImageSize="1050822" />
    <Page Image="9" ImageSize="938458" />
    <Page Image="10" ImageSize="886376" />
    <Page Image="11" ImageSize="963810" />
    <Page Image="12" ImageSize="965214" />
    <Page Image="13" ImageSize="988318" />
    <Page Image="14" ImageSize="939508" />
    <Page Image="15" ImageSize="909550" />
    <Page Image="16" ImageSize="945826" />
    <Page Image="17" ImageSize="877354" />
    <Page Image="18" ImageSize="843528" />
    <Page Image="19" ImageSize="793450" />
    <Page Image="20" ImageSize="986096" />
    <Page Image="21" ImageSize="955816" />
    <Page Image="22" ImageSize="907174" />
    <Page Image="23" ImageSize="874984" />
    <Page Image="24" ImageSize="806622" />
    <Page Image="25" ImageSize="782206" />
    <Page Image="26" ImageSize="894258" />
    <Page Image="27" ImageSize="830754" />
    <Page Image="28" ImageSize="780114" />
    <Page Image="29" ImageSize="775852" />
    <Page Image="30" ImageSize="743870" />
    <Page Image="31" ImageSize="820980" />
    <Page Image="32" ImageSize="497854" />
    <Page Image="33" ImageSize="987186" />
    <Page Image="34" ImageSize="1906554" />
    <Page Image="35" ImageSize="619130" />
    <Page Image="36" ImageSize="376274" />
  </Pages>
</ComicInfo>
