<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ComicInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://anansi-project.github.io/docs/comicinfo/schemas/v2.1">
	<Characters>Cherry Poptart,Patty Melt</Characters>
	<Count>23</Count>
	<Day>10</Day>
	<GTIN>urn:comicvine:4000-123776</GTIN>
	<Month>1</Month>
	<Notes>Tagged with comicbox 1.1.1 on 2024-03-14T04:44:53 [Issue ID 4000-123776] urn:comicvine:4000-123776</Notes>
	<Number>18</Number>
	<PageCount>37</PageCount>
	<Pages>
		<Page Image="0" ImageSize="155575" Type="FrontCover"/>
		<Page Image="1" ImageSize="543695"/>
		<Page Image="2" ImageSize="258316"/>
		<Page Image="3" ImageSize="359670"/>
		<Page Image="4" ImageSize="354608"/>
		<Page Image="5" ImageSize="337776"/>
		<Page Image="6" ImageSize="319857"/>
		<Page Image="7" ImageSize="343748"/>
		<Page Image="8" ImageSize="341244"/>
		<Page Image="9" ImageSize="352207"/>
		<Page Image="10" ImageSize="374919"/>
		<Page Image="11" ImageSize="332345"/>
		<Page Image="12" ImageSize="333637"/>
		<Page Image="13" ImageSize="333566"/>
		<Page Image="14" ImageSize="348748"/>
		<Page Image="15" ImageSize="315191"/>
		<Page Image="16" ImageSize="303583"/>
		<Page Image="17" ImageSize="283563"/>
		<Page Image="18" ImageSize="363476"/>
		<Page Image="19" ImageSize="404664"/>
		<Page Image="20" ImageSize="230573"/>
		<Page Image="21" ImageSize="354383"/>
		<Page Image="22" ImageSize="364402"/>
		<Page Image="23" ImageSize="356736"/>
		<Page Image="24" ImageSize="361286"/>
		<Page Image="25" ImageSize="354628"/>
		<Page Image="26" ImageSize="338911"/>
		<Page Image="27" ImageSize="333855"/>
		<Page Image="28" ImageSize="357809"/>
		<Page Image="29" ImageSize="306041"/>
		<Page Image="30" ImageSize="329530"/>
		<Page Image="31" ImageSize="264217"/>
		<Page Image="32" ImageSize="308356"/>
		<Page Image="33" ImageSize="332508"/>
		<Page Image="34" ImageSize="273630"/>
		<Page Image="35" ImageSize="291347"/>
		<Page Image="36" ImageSize="381014"/>
	</Pages>
	<Publisher>Cherry Comics</Publisher>
	<Series>Cherry Poptart</Series>
	<Summary>*Story: "Cherry has an Anxiety Attack"*
Penciler: Larry Welz

Author: Larry Welz

Inker: Larry Welz

Cherry Poptart is hopeful that her friend Ellie Dee will be able to score a couple of tickets to the coming weekend's Aerosmith concert, but if not, she is confident that she will be able to get in one way or another. As she's walking to school, a guy working on his car, a group of boys fighting, and a guy trying to get into his stuck locker, all get distracted by Cherry. Her appearance even stops another teen from using a gun to commit suicide. As Cherry enters the World Lit classroom, she begins to slip into fantasy upon sight of the teacher, Mr. Le Mort. She pictures herself topless, giving the man fellatio as he, book in hand, reads 18th century literature. Cherry then gets fully naked and guides his penis into her vagina from the rear as he moves on to a chapter by Sir Walter Raleigh. Back in reality, Cherry is overcome with embarrassment as she realizes that she had been masturbating unknowingly, much to the laughter of her friend, Patty Melt and the rest of the class. Flustered, Cherry rushes out of the classroom and heads to Ms. Renfrew, the self-image counselor. Cherry begins by stating that she feels she is lacking self-esteem, causing an outburst of rage from the counselor. Ms. Renfrew shouts that she is sick of spoiled brats like Cherry who constantly complain about how tough they think they have it. The counselor apologizes immediately afterward, confessing that she has been under a lot of stress lately. Cherry lends a sympathetic ear, feeling sorry that the woman has to listen to the troubles of so many, without anyone there to listen to her own. She then gives Ms. Renfrew a shoulder massage, followed by a hug. When the counselor concedes that the gestures may not be enough, Cherry French kisses the woman and begins to undress her. The girl then compliments Ms. Renfrew's breasts and vagina before forcing herself on top of her and performing cunnilingus. After finishing making love, Cherry immediately feels a heightened sense of self esteem, and Ms. Renfrew states that she can not wait to share these new feelings with her husband, Roy. It's at that point that Cherry realizes that Mr. Le Mort is her husband and that she had kept her last name.

*Short: "The Codex of Weird Head For Men &amp; Women"*
Penciler: Mark V. Bode

Author: Mark V. Bode

Inker: Mark V. Bode

A short showcasing bizarre ways for males and females to perform fellatio and cunnilingus.

*Short: "Cross Training"*
Penciler: Larry Welz

Author: Larry Welz

Inker: Larry Welz

Cherry misconstrues what her instructor, Monique, means by "cross training" when she carries a giant crucifix on a single wheel while wearing her running shoes.

*Story: "Dances with Dolphins"*
Penciler: Larry Welz

Author: Larry Welz

Inker: Larry Welz

Cherry has taken a summer job at the Mertek Research Institute where she is feeding fresh fish to a couple of dolphins. She then requests the dolphins do some tricks for her, such as dancing backwards on their tails. Working the graveyard shift, Cherry is glad that she gets to be there all by herself with the dolphins. She decided that she's waited long enough to do "a little hands on research", so she strips off all of her clothing and jumps naked into the water. Cherry splashes around with the dolphins for a few moments until one of them, Newton, rolls over, exposing it's erect penis. The aquatic mammal then gets very protective; not allowing the other dolphins to get near the girl. Newton communicates with Cherry, which she understands perfectly, and requests fellatio. Cherry is happy to oblige, but is taken by surprise when she is thrust underwater. She then decides to try climbing on to the dolphin's penis in the missionary position and begins fornicating until the two climax underwater. After the intense session, Cherry climbs out of the tank and feeds the dolphins some more fish. She then meets up with her boss later on who asks if Cherry had any thrilling breakthroughs or unusual behaviors. The girl replies "not really" but then says that another dolphin, Daphne, wants to take another swim with him, like the two had done the previous summer.

*Illustrations*
Illustrations include "Robo Cherry" - a spoof on the character RoboCop, Cherry's Mom, Pepper Poptart, relaxing at home by lifting her dress up to masturbate, and a naked Cherry slyly asking her canine companion what he's like to do next.</Summary>
	<Volume>1982</Volume>
	<Web>https://comicvine.gamespot.com/cherry-poptart-18/4000-123776/</Web>
	<Year>1995</Year>
</ComicInfo>